<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10262" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-10</startdate>
<enddate>2014-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gochuumon wa Usagi Desuka?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gochuumon wa Usagi Desu ka?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gochiusa</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ご注文はうさぎですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Is the Order a Rabbit?</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">주문은 토끼입니까?</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">请问您今天要来点兔子吗?</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11049" type="Sequel">Gochuumon wa Usagi Desuka??</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9579" approval="44" total="47">Kin`iro Mosaic</anime>
<anime id="13966" approval="9" total="11">Tonari no Kyuuketsuki-san</anime>
<anime id="2659" approval="7" total="13">Aria the Animation</anime>
<anime id="14156" approval="1" total="5">Watashi ni Tenshi ga Maiorita!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="463724">It started off so clichéd, but already 2 episodes in it started gaving me that heartwarming feeling, that definitely works for some, while yes, some might find it boring because there is no actual BIG story here. Just a set of 5 different girls doing cute and silly stuff, hanging out, while running cafes. So it`s definitely recommended to fans of iyashi-kei and cute stuff. There`s plenty of that here.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="600311">heart warming atmosphere. nice casual female characters. some comedy and relaxed mood :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="730868">A pale imitation of the Aria series, but still reasonably well done.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="477606">Here is the cutest anime I ever seen , 
I never get tired even though I lost counts of how many times I rewatch this,
Truly a masterpiece, Highly recommended it !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="306510">One of the most heartwarming cutest shows I`ve ever seen.
An absolute must.

I liked it even better than the all time classic "Aishiteru ze Baby", though you cannot truly compare those two.

(If you liked this, have a go at "Hibike! Euphonium", or if you liked that show, try this ^^)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gochiusa.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="13442" type="Chief Animation Direction">Okuda Yousuke</name>
<name id="13442" type="Character Design">Okuda Yousuke</name>
<name id="3724" type="Series Composition">Fudeyasu Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="7872" type="Direction">Hashimoto Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="5818" type="Music">Kawada Ruka</name>
<name id="38929" type="Original Work">Koi</name>
<name id="1555" type="Animation Work">White Fox</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch62374 [Cocoa] arrives at the cafe Rabbit House one day, excited about rabbits. She actually all but lives in that cafe, where she meets many different girls, including a tiny and cool girl named http://anidb.net/ch62375 [Chino]; a tough and soldier-esque girl named http://anidb.net/ch62376 [Rize]; a spacey and quintessentially Japanese girl named http://anidb.net/ch62377 [Chiya]; and the ordinary but dignified http://anidb.net/ch62378 [Sharo].
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1415">6.08</permanent>
<temporary count="1425">7.05</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>150574.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15718</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21273</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://gochiusa.com/01/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Is_the_Order_a_Rabbit%3F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ご注文はうさぎですか%3F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3324</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347914</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17068</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=fNfjpejc5Ks</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=PgoPlPdcVRo</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=aWyPbj1CItQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=6b76qW65E3U</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=ULMVjlHzSBc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2757" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-30">
<name>badminton</name>
<description>Badminton is a racquet sport played using racquets to hit a shuttlecock across a net. Although it may be played with larger teams, the most common forms of the game are "singles" (with one player per side) and "doubles" (with two players per side). Badminton is often played as a casual outdoor activity in a yard or on a beach; formal games are played on a rectangular indoor court. Points are scored by striking the shuttlecock with the racquet and landing it within the opposing side`s half of the court.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192043.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2758" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-05">
<name>volleyball</name>
<description>Volleyball is a team sport in which two teams of six players are separated by a net. Each team tries to score points by grounding a ball on the other team`s court under organized rules.
Use the http://anidb.net/t7147 [competitive beach volleyball] tag for competition or professional beach volleyball play. Use the http://anidb.net/t6478 [beach volleyball episode] tag when the beach volleyball game is a one-off event, such as during a beach or pool visit.</description>
<picurl>221599.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2795" parentid="1973" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>baking</name>
<description>The art of making bread, cakes, pastries, pies, tarts, quiches, cookies and similar food in the oven.
Mmmm.... smells nice.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3119" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>restaurant</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3175" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-22">
<name>hand signs</name>
<description>Characters form attacks through a succession of special hand signs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3694" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>dear mother in heaven</name>
<description>A form of veneration of ancestors, where people call upon their ancestors for help, advice and similar in their everyday life like in other cultures upon God, Jesus, the Virgin Mary or various saints. The veneration of the spirit`s of one`s ancestors is an integral part of Japanese culture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4907" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>small town</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="62374" type="main character in" update="2014-06-01">
<rating votes="60">7.68</rating>
<name>Hoto Cocoa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62375" type="main character in" update="2014-06-01">
<rating votes="83">8.45</rating>
<name>Kafuu Chino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62376" type="main character in" update="2014-06-01">
<rating votes="57">7.91</rating>
<name>Tedeza Rize</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62377" type="main character in" update="2014-06-01">
<rating votes="55">7.55</rating>
<name>Ujimatsu Chiya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62378" type="main character in" update="2014-06-01">
<rating votes="60">8.21</rating>
<name>Kirima Sharo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63189" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-01">
<rating votes="24">6.13</rating>
<name>Aoyama Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63190" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-01">
<rating votes="36">6.49</rating>
<name>Jouga Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="64371" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-01">
<rating votes="26">6.67</rating>
<name>Natsu Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32020" picture="127735.jpg">Murakawa Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65554" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-02">
<rating votes="11">6.67</rating>
<name>Chino no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65555" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-30">
<rating votes="17">5.85</rating>
<name>Tippy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68305" type="appears in" update="2014-06-30">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Anko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157421.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68309" type="appears in" update="2014-06-30">
<name>Chino no Sofu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="158397" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひと目で, 尋常でないもふもふだと見抜いたよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Knew at First Glance That It Was No Ordinary Fluffball</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au premier regard, j’ai deviné qu’il était incroyablement moelleux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitome de, Jinjou de Nai Mofumofu Da to Minuita yo</title>
<summary>Cocoa has moved into the new town where she`ll start attending high school in spring. She gets lost and enters a café called Rabbit House to ask for directions...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653243</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159178" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラッキーアイテムは野菜と罪と罰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Lucky Items Are Vegetables, Crime, and Punishment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les porte-bonheur sont les légumes, le crime et la punition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lucky Item wa Yasai to Tsumi to Batsu</title>
<summary>When Cocoa sees Chino using caffè-de-mancy to tell fortunes with coffee, she has Chino teach her how to do it, then tries telling fortunes for Chino, Lize, and Tippy. After that, for some reason, all sorts of bad luck befalls Cocoa...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653249</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159179" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めて酔った日の事憶えてる? 自分の家でキャンプファイヤーしようとしたわよね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Remember the Day You First Got Drunk? You Tried to Light a Campfire in Your Own Home, Didn`t You?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Te souviens-tu de la dernière fois où tu étais soûl ? Tu essayais d’allumer un feu de camp chez toi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete Yotta Hi no Koto Oboeteru? Jibun no Ie de Campfire Shiyou to Shita wa yo ne</title>
<summary>Cocoa and friends are shopping for mugs when they meet Sharo, an underclassman at Lize`s school who`s also a childhood friend of Chiya`s. Later, Chiya is worried that Sharo is working in some shady establishment, so she and the other girls decide to infiltrate Sharo`s workplace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653247</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159180" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小麦を愛した少女と小豆に愛された少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl Who Loved Wheat and the Girl Loved by Azuki Beans</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille qui aimait la farine et une fille aimée par les haricots sucrés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komugi o Aishita Shoujo to Azuki ni Aisareta Shoujo</title>
<summary>On the way to her new school, Cocoa meets a girl in traditional Japanese clothes named Chiya. It turns out Chiya will be attending the same high school as Cocoa, and her hobby is giving original names to the Japanese sweets she makes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653245</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159289" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159290" update="2014-04-16">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159364" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">AJ2014 PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">AJ2014 PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653201</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159659" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プールに濡れて 雨に濡れて涙に濡れて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wet with Pool Water, Wet with Rain, Wet with Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mouillée par la piscine, la pluie et les larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pool ni Nurete Ame ni Nurete Namida ni Nurete</title>
<summary>Cocoa and the other girls visit a hot spring pool, where they have underwater breathing contests and teach Rize how to swim. Meanwhile, Chino and Chiya begin a game of chess with something big on the line...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653257</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159660" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Call Me Sister.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call Me Sister.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Call Me Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Call Me Sister.</title>
<summary>Lize notices that Chino doesn`t seem like her usual self. She asks Cocoa, who admits that she finished a jigsaw puzzle that Chino had enjoyed working on for a long time. Cocoa is so shocked by her failure as a big sister that she runs out of the café...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653255</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159661" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お話をするお話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Story About Telling a Story</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une histoire racontant une histoire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ohanashi o Suru Ohanashi</title>
<summary>Cocoa comes home to find Chino`s classmates, Maya and Megu, wearing uniforms and helping out at Rabbit House. Maya and Megu immediately become friends with Cocoa and Lize, but for some reason, watching them makes Chino feel bad.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653253</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159662" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ココアと悪意なき殺意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cocoa and Murderous Intent Without Malice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cocoa, crimes et mauvaises intentions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cocoa to Akuinaki Satsui</title>
<summary>Cocoa says she needs to practice with Chiya for their school`s ball sports tournament, but for some reason, she doesn`t look happy as she leaves work early. Later, Chino and Lize head to the park to practice badminton, and they`re greeted by the sight of Cocoa and Chiya lying on the ground.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653251</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159873" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君のためなら寝坊する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For You, I Can Sleep Late</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pour toi, je ferai la grasse matinée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Tame Nara Nebousuru</title>
<summary>On the way to school, Chino notices something strange about Cocoa and learns that she has a high fever. Rize and Chiya come to visit, but her fever won`t go down. When night falls, Chino realizes they`re out of cold medicine and sets out alone to find some...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653265</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159874" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女は赤い外套を纏いウサギを駆りて聖夜の空を行く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl Dons a Red Coat and Drives a Team of Rabbits Across the Christmas Eve Night Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vêtue d’un manteau rouge, elle chevauche un lapin dans le ciel de la sainte nuit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo wa Akai Gaitou o Matoi Usagi o Karite Seiya no Sora o Iku</title>
<summary>While shopping at a Christmas market, Cocoa and the other girls plan a Christmas party. Then on Christmas Day, Maya, Megu, and Aoyama-san join the gang, and their lively Christmas party begins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653263</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159875" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対お姉ちゃん用決戦部隊, 通称チマメ隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Anti-Sister Battle Corps, Also Known as the Chimame Corps</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Guerre fratricide, nom de code capitaine ampoules</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tai Onee-chan You Kessen Butai, Tsuushou Chimame-Tai</title>
<summary>While Cocoa is absent from Rabbit House for an overnight study session at Chiya`s house, Maya and Megu come to spend the night with Chino. Rize watches Chino, Maya, and Megu as they work in the café and gives them the collective nickname "Chimame."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653261</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159876" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青山スランプマウンテン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aoyama Slump Mountain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aoyama Slump Mountain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoyama Slump Mountain</title>
<summary>As Chino is walking home, a paper airplane made from manuscript paper flies toward her head. It was thrown by Aoyama Blue Mountain, who says she has quit her job as a novelist, so Chino brings her to Rabbit House.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653259</identifier>
<identifier>is-the-order-a-rabbit</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160646" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161565" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161566" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162428" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162429" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162986" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162987" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176115" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176116" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176117" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176118" update="2016-03-20">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186419" update="2017-03-25">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">BD&amp;DVD第1巻CM ~青山さん~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD CM 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BD &amp; DVD Dai 1 Kan CM: Aoyama-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186420" update="2017-03-25">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BD&amp;DVD第1巻CM ~シャロ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD CM 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BD &amp; DVD Dai 1 Kan CM: Charo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186421" update="2017-03-25">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">BD&amp;DVD第1巻CM ~チノ父~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD CM 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BD &amp; DVD Dai 1 Kan CM: Chi no Chichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186422" update="2018-10-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">BD&amp;DVD第1巻CM ~千夜~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD CM 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">BD &amp; DVD Dai 1 Kan CM: Chiya</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
