<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10803" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-05-30</startdate>
<enddate>2015-05-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Haiyore! Nyaruko-san F</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">這いよれ! ニャル子さんF</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">潜行吧！奈亚子F</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9459" type="Prequel">Haiyore! Nyaruko-san W</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://nyaruko.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="14529" type="Direction">Nagasawa Tsuyoshi</name>
<name id="16490" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takiyama Masaaki</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="16490" type="Character Design">Takiyama Masaaki</name>
<name id="12417" type="Original Work">Aisora Manta</name>
</creators>
<description>Mahiro awakes from a disturbing dream: having stood at the wedding altar with Nyaruko. He is convinced that this could not have been his free will, and suspects some form of meddling by Nyaruko. But apparently not... still Nyaruko misunderstands the nature of Mahiro dream, and this gets http://anidb.net/ch41187 [Kuuko] and http://anidb.net/ch40331 [Hasuta] involved as well. A quite usual morning at the Yasaka household...
When http://anidb.net/ch41197 [Tamao] and http://anidb.net/ch41194 [Takehiko] visit, they bring along eight tickets to the most popular amusement spot these days: a realistic escape game. And so http://anidb.net/ch41196 [Yoriko] and http://anidb.net/ch43754 [Shantak-kun] come along for the game, located in what appears to be a sinister-looking house. The players then need to group into pairs and decide on what door to enter to clear the mission. It all just seems to be fun and games...
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="477">5.52</permanent>
<temporary count="481">6.76</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>159768.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16604</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>26023</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://nyaruko.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3840</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>351284</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18422</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5930" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shounen ai</name>
<description>At least one male character has a romantic or sexual interest in another male character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="40331" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="84">2.75</rating>
<name>Hasuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41187" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="171">7.60</rating>
<name>Kuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41190" type="main character in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="212">8.04</rating>
<name>Nyaruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41191" type="appears in" update="2012-04-22">
<rating votes="7">3.07</rating>
<name>Nodens</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41194" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="15">2.98</rating>
<name>Yoichi Takehiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41195" type="main character in" update="2012-05-06">
<rating votes="95">1.79</rating>
<name>Yasaka Mahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41196" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="39">7.52</rating>
<name>Yasaka Yoriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41197" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-09">
<rating votes="44">4.67</rating>
<name>Kurei Tamao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43754" type="appears in" update="2015-10-14">
<rating votes="26">4.80</rating>
<name>Shantak-kun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76036" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-24">
<rating votes="4">5.32</rating>
<name>Shirogane Atoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="166895" update="2015-05-31">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2015-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168874" update="2015-06-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168875" update="2015-06-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
