<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11725" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-01-07</startdate>
<enddate>2016-03-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shoujo-tachi wa Kouya o Mezasu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">少女たちは荒野を目指す</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">しょこめざ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">shokomeza</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">少女たちは荒野を目指す ~Girls beyond the youth KOYA~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Girls Beyond the Wasteland</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Shôjotachi wa kôya wo mezasu</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Le ragazze anelano alla landa selvaggia</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">少女们向荒野进发</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11726" type="Side Story">Shoujo-tachi wa Kouya o Mezasu: Anime Edition</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10538" approval="22" total="24">Saenai Heroine no Sodatekata</anime>
<anime id="10779" approval="4" total="13">Shirobako</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="306510">You`ll love this anime if you liked Bakuman and such.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="24572">Another anime about making games, otaku culture, club activity and friendship. Compared to the other animes, for me this adds little to the experience. It starts off with seriousness like a seinen anime but falls back into light-hearted shounen rather quickly.  

The characters are not portrayed in debt so they appear rather shallow. You find the usual stereotypes (nerd, dark, moe, tsundere, sporty and the creepy dude..). They are rather static, it is not the coming-of-age you could expect from such a show. 

I would say this is mostly for fans of the genre. If you haven`t seen Genshiken, Saenai Heroine no Sodatekata, Ore no Imouto, NHK and Bakuman etc., do so first.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="94967">This is geared towards creative people, and due to that so to speak normal people without experience of working in a creative role or simply who have a rational personality type will probably have trouble relating to or understanding characters in this anime. And it`s not like there`s much else going for it, other than character interaction as they strive towards a common goal. In other words, for those, who could appreciate this anime, spending 6 hours of their deadlined lives on it is probably not worth it. So, really, I don`t even know to whom it could be recommended but alas a recommendation needs a type and "for fans" is the lowest one.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://shokomeza.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3066" type="Character Design">Noguchi Takayuki</name>
<name id="21486" type="Series Composition">Ayana Yuniko</name>
<name id="3557" type="Direction">Satou Takuya</name>
<name id="20490" type="Original Work">Takahiro</name>
<name id="2971" type="Music">Watanabe Takeshi</name>
<name id="35813" type="Animation Work">Project No.9</name>
<name id="3066" type="Chief Animation Direction">Noguchi Takayuki</name>
<name id="14856" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tani Keiji</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch77936 [Houjou Buntarou] is a student who wants to be something, but doesn`t know what. One day, his classmate http://anidb.net/ch77941 [Kuroda Sayuki] announces she is working on a bishoujo game and requests his help. Sayuki scouted him because he wrote a good script for drama club, but Buntarou doesn`t know anything about bishoujo games.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="736">3.36</permanent>
<temporary count="740">5.78</temporary>
<review count="1">4.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>239896.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17751</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31914</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://shokomeza.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shōjotachi_wa_Kōya_o_Mezasu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>少女たちは荒野を目指す</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4006</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355054</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18741</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14303</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5640" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-16">
<name>video game development</name>
<description>Part of the anime`s story relates to creating video games.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="77936" type="main character in" update="2015-12-19">
<rating votes="7">4.88</rating>
<name>Houjou Buntarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37882" picture="173035.jpg">Yamashita Seiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77937" type="main character in" update="2015-12-19">
<rating votes="13">4.26</rating>
<name>Andou Teruha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77938" type="main character in" update="2015-12-19">
<rating votes="11">4.87</rating>
<name>Kobayakawa Yuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77939" type="main character in" update="2015-12-19">
<rating votes="4">4.23</rating>
<name>Kai Atomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="303" picture="166016.jpg">Toyonaga Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77940" type="main character in" update="2015-12-19">
<rating votes="8">6.21</rating>
<name>Yuuki Uguisu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77941" type="main character in" update="2015-12-19">
<rating votes="15">6.59</rating>
<name>Kuroda Sayuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35415" picture="146334.jpg">Chisuga Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83801" type="appears in" update="2016-08-13">
<name>Hosokawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83802" type="appears in" update="2016-08-13">
<name>Kuroda Iwao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="173932" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わがままと引き算のメロディー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Melody of Selfishness and Subtraction</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mélodie de caprices et de soustractions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wagamama to Hikizan no Melody</title>
<summary>Buntarou comes down with a case of writer`s block, and the stress begins to take its toll on Yuki. With both writer and artist in a creative slump, what can Kuroda do to help?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779819</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173933" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめてなんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s the First Time</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est la première fois</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete Nanda</title>
<summary>The group gets together for a “camp” to brainstorm ideas for their first project. However, an argument between Sayuki and Teruha may leave the team lacking a programmer!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779817</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173934" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これもひとつの青い春</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is Another Spring of Youth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un autre printemps de jeunesse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore mo Hitotsu no Aoi Haru</title>
<summary>Buntarou is still reeling from the previous day’s events when Saiyuki reveals her plan, which is already underway and only missing the key component: a team.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779815</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173935" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢を追う少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls Who Chase After Their Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La jeune fille qui court après ses rêves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume o Ou Shoujo</title>
<summary>After viewing a skit Buntarou wrote for their school’s drama club, Sayuki asks him out on what might be considered a date. However, she has an odd ulterior motive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779814</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174327" update="2016-01-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174503" update="2016-01-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174625" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">閉じ込められて, 夏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shut Away in Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un été passé à l`ombre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tojikomerarete, Natsu</title>
<summary>Bunta is under house arrest! Kuroda has enlisted the entire team to "help" Bunta get past his writing block the old fashioned way: he can`t leave until he finishes the script.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779827</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174626" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつもと同じ, 違うキミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">As Always, It`s a Different You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Toi, toujours la même et si différente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsumo to Onaji, Chigau Kimi</title>
<summary>Bunta’s having a seriously bad case of writer’s block. The group attempts to stimulate his imagination by acting out one odd scenario after another!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779824</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174627" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これがいわゆるサービス回というものね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is the So-Called Fanservice Episode</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`exemple parfait du fan service</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore ga Iwayuru Service Kai to Iu Mono ne</title>
<summary>The group heads to the beach to replicate beloved fanservice tropes, but will incurable fissures begin to form as Kuroda and Buntarou come to an understanding?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779823</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174628" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の中で見えるのは</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What You Can See in the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce que l`on voit dans la tempête</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Naka de Mieru no wa</title>
<summary>After another heated argument, Ando fires herself. In an attempt to coax her back, Buntarou signs on to help Ando`s family fishing business with dangerous results.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779821</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175243" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女たちは荒野を目指す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls Beyond the Wasteland</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les filles recherchent l`aventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo-tachi wa Kouya o Mezasu</title>
<summary>The members of Rokuhara await the news of their win or loss against the game company Typhoon. When the results come in, why does Kuroda want to break up the team?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779835</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175244" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これが始まりかもしれない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Might Be the Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est certainement ici que tout commence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore ga Hajimari Kamo Shirenai</title>
<summary>The group discovers the truth behind Kuroda`s intentions for creating the bishoujo game. Betrayed, Buntarou and the others abandon her just before the game`s completion.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779834</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175245" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タイフーン襲来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Typhoon Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un typhon en approche</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Typhoon Shuurai</title>
<summary>Rokuhara releases the demo of their first game! As they read reviews, they get word that veteran development team, Typhoon, wants to meet them, but it might be risky.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779833</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175246" update="2018-12-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">好きだから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Because I Love You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Parce que je t`aime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suki Dakara</title>
<summary>The team heads to the recording studio to put Yuka’s voice to their main character, Kirika. However, with the studio on a schedule, can Yuka do the quality job she wants?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779828</identifier>
<identifier>girls-beyond-the-wasteland</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
