<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11864" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-12</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nora to Oujo to Noraneko Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">noratoto</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ノラと皇女と野良猫ハート</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Nora, Princess, and Stray Cat</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">노라와 황녀와 도둑고양이 하트</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">野良和皇女和流浪猫之心</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14509" type="Other">Nora to Oujo to Noraneko Heart (Shin Anime)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://nora-anime.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="29349" type="Direction">Morii Kenshirou</name>
<name id="50259" type="Original Work">Harukaze</name>
<name id="47740" type="Animation Work">W-Toon Studio</name>
<name id="49748" type="Animation Work">DMM.futureworks</name>
<name id="40633" type="Character Design">Miyajima Seiya</name>
<name id="40634" type="Character Design">Kinutani Soushi</name>
<name id="50258" type="Series Composition">Hato</name>
<name id="34836" type="Music">Mori Shintarou</name>
</creators>
<description>The story centers around http://anidb.net/ch90273 [Handa Nora], a high school boy whose mother adopts a girl named http://anidb.net/ch89378 [Yuuri Shachi] who is younger than him. Shachi lost her mother and no longer lives with her father, but both Nora and Shachi were raised well.
Nora`s childhood friend and honors student http://anidb.net/ch89382 [Kuroki Michi] is the head of the school`s public morals committee, and is also friends with http://anidb.net/ch89379 [Asuhara Yuuki], who acts like a kogal but is a reliable confidante.
One day, on the way to school, Nora meets a girl named http://anidb.net/ch89374 [Patricia] in a park. Patricia says that she is a princess of the underworld, and she has come to the surface world to destroy all life. But the first time she touches someone in the surface, she faints, and Nora finds himself nursing her. Patricia asks Nora to tell him the secrets of life, and Nora starts by explaining the adult magazine that they found in the park.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="343">1.82</permanent>
<temporary count="347">4.41</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>207765.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19749</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32447</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://nora-anime.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nora,_Princess,_and_Stray_Cat</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ノラと皇女と野良猫ハート</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4650</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360748</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20275</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18148</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>noratoto_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3315" parentid="2623" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-28">
<name>superhero</name>
<description>In modern popular fiction, a superhero is a type of costumed heroic character who possesses supernatural or superhuman powers and who is dedicated to fighting crime, protecting the public, and usually battling supervillains. A female superhero is sometimes called a superheroine. Fiction centered on such characters, especially in American comic books since the 1930s, is known as superhero fiction.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89374" type="main character in" update="2017-07-12">
<rating votes="2">8.75</rating>
<name>Patricia of End</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89375" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-12">
<name>Eurasia of End</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3622" picture="214935.jpg">Oohashi Ayuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89376" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-12">
<rating votes="2">7.68</rating>
<name>Lucia of End</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89377" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-12">
<name>Ida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32951" picture="223802.jpg">Masuyama Takeaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89378" type="main character in" update="2017-07-12">
<rating votes="2">9.52</rating>
<name>Yuuri Shachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89379" type="main character in" update="2017-07-12">
<rating votes="2">8.75</rating>
<name>Asuhara Yuuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89380" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-12">
<name>Tanaka-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38677" picture="145133.jpg">Kimura Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89381" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-12">
<name>Takada Nobuchina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9405" picture="228517.jpg">Yamaoka Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89382" type="main character in" update="2017-07-12">
<rating votes="4">8.21</rating>
<name>Kuroki Michi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1932" picture="65403.jpg">Sendai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90273" type="main character in" update="2017-07-12">
<name>Handa Nora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38232" picture="140073.jpg">Asai Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188700" update="2017-08-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">革命児</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revolutionaries</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les révolutionnaires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakumeiji</title>
<summary>I love the beach! But I love rhythm games, too!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188701" update="2017-07-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私たちの思い出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nos souvenirs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashitachi no Omoide</title>
<summary>The eldest of the nether world sisters, Lucia, has come to kill Nora.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188702" update="2017-07-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリント配るとき振り向かないやつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Guy Who Never Turns Around When Handouts Are Distributed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ceux qui ne se retournent pas lors de la distribution des polys</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Print Kubaru Toki Furimukanai Yatsu</title>
<summary>Patricia is very interested in learning what it`s like to be a student. As she`s getting to know some friend she`s meeting for the first time, she ends up summoning a skeleton.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188703" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法でネコになっちゃった!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ve Been Turned Into a Cat with Magic?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Métamorphosé en chat ?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou de Neko ni Natchatta!?</title>
<summary>Nora has been turned into a cat by a princess from the nether world. The only way to break is the spell is to be kissed by a girl...?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189026" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189497" update="2017-09-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の花火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Fireworks</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Feux d’artifice estivaux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Hanabi</title>
<summary>Fireworks can be fascinating. That languid feeling you get when cleaning up is fascinating as well.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189498" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">我が名は客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am a Customer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je suis le client</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waga Na wa Kyaku</title>
<summary>Looking back, it was a long journey. Nora and his companions rise up to defend the city.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189499" update="2017-12-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界平和</title>
<title xml:lang="en">World Peace</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La paix dans le monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai Heiwa</title>
<summary>Patricia heads out into nature to eat spinach.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189500" update="2017-08-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リヴァイアサン推し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pushing for Leviathan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fan de Léviathan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Leviathan Oshi</title>
<summary>I won`t let you guys beat me! Feel my strength!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190343" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衣服が足りない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Don`t Have Enough Clothes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pas assez de vêtements</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ifuku ga Tarinai</title>
<summary>We`re so far away now. We can`t drop by for a visit anymore.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190344" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">断捨離</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decluttering</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Renoncer aux biens matériels</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Danshari</title>
<summary>While using a magic circle to dispose of magic grimoires no longer being used, the magic circle becomes clogged.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190345" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先生は, 犯人捜しをするつもりはありません</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Teacher Won`t Look for the Murderer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le professeur n’a pas l’intention de chercher le coupable</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensei wa, Hannin Sagashi o Suru Tsumori wa Arimasen</title>
<summary>A red stain spreads in the mansion. A murder has finally occurred.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190346" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドーナツ屋さんに行きたくなってきた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Feel Like Visiting a Donut Shop</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Envie de donuts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doughnut-ya-san ni Ikitakunatte Kita</title>
<summary>I`d like to visit the donut shop that just opened up in the neighborhood. It`s full of fun stuff.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
