<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11874" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-03-04</startdate>
<enddate>2016-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kanojo to Kanojo no Neko: Everything Flows</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">هي وقطها: كل شيء يطفو</title>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="synonym">그녀와 그녀의 고양이: Everything Flows</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">彼女と彼女の猫 -Everything Flows-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">She and Her Cat: Everything Flows</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Elle et son chat</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">她和她的猫 -Everything Flows-</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="461" type="Sequel">Kanojo to Kanojo no Neko</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="14253" approval="8" total="8">Doukyonin wa Hiza, Tokidoki, Atama no Ue.</anime>
<anime id="5801" approval="2" total="3">Chii`s Sweet Home</anime>
<anime id="6452" approval="2" total="3">Chii`s Sweet Home: Atarashii O`uchi</anime>
<anime id="10956" approval="2" total="2">Kimi to Boku</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="540164">Very short episodes.  Worth every second.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="403522">A surprisingly good story for such short episodes. A definite recommendation if you wanna watch something short. It also contains a nice soundtrack.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="363469">Four 8 minute episodes (32 minutes), and 28 minutes crying and coming down from that emotional rollercoaster. An hour well spent. Well played off of Makoto Shinkai`s work. Must see.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kanoneko.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="445" type="Original Work">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="531" type="Direction">Sakamoto Kazuya</name>
<name id="39770" type="Character Design">Umishima Senbon</name>
<name id="39770" type="Chief Animation Direction">Umishima Senbon</name>
<name id="35233" type="Animation Work">Liden Films</name>
<name id="46372" type="Animation Work">Liden Films Kyoto Studio</name>
<name id="46864" type="Music">To-Mas Soundsight Fluorescent Forest</name>
</creators>
<description>For the longest time, it`s just been the two of them. http://anidb.net/ch79403 [Kanojo] and her cat http://anidb.net/ch79404 [Daru] are inseparable, having grown up together. Now a junior in college, http://anidb.net/ch79402 [Tomoka] — her roommate of a year and a half — moves out of their shared apartment, and in order to keep her living space, Kanojo must find a job. Day by day, Daru watches her continued efforts from a cat`s-eye view, eagerly awaiting his owner`s return. When she gets back, once again, it`s just she and her cat.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="993">6.74</permanent>
<temporary count="997">7.10</temporary>
<review count="2">6.91</review>
</ratings>
<picture>181320.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17980</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kanoneko.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>She_and_Her_Cat#Legacy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>彼女と彼女の猫#テレビアニメ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4080</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355368</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18973</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>그녀와_그녀의_고양이#텔레비전_애니메이션</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>她與她的貓#電視動畫</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>she-and-her-cat-everything-flows-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6555" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-31">
<name>Ultra Super Anime Time</name>
<description>Ultra Super Anime Time was a half-hour anime block produced by http://anidb.net/cr30397 [Ultra Super Pictures] that aired on Tokyo MX and BS11 between July 2015 and June 2016. The block typically featured three http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] anime of about eight minutes each.</description>
<picurl>180340.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7781" type="appears in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="10">7.19</rating>
<name>Chobi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The cat that belongs to the woman in the story. Also takes the role of the narrator. Has a girlfriend (cat) called Mimi. Seems to have feelings for the female (human) though.</description>
<picture>26790.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="79402" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-25">
<rating votes="3">4.73</rating>
<name>Tomoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79403" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-25">
<rating votes="4">8.63</rating>
<name>Miyuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79404" type="main character in" update="2016-03-26">
<rating votes="4">6.59</rating>
<name>Boku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81189" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-25">
<rating votes="3">6.46</rating>
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="175920" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女と彼女の物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She and Her Story</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle et son histoire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo to Kanojo no Monogatari</title>
<summary>She has kept herself locked in her apartment and ignored phonecalls for so long that her friends and family - and Daru - are growing worried. Then, mysteriously, her mother receives a phone call from her home number, but only hears silence on the other end...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>693125</identifier>
<identifier>she-and-her-cat-everything-flows-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175921" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女と彼女のまなざし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She and the Look in Her Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle et son regard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo to Kanojo no Manazashi</title>
<summary>When she hits the lowest point in her despair, Daru wishes for nothing more than to be of help to her, but his aging body just won`t obey his mind the way it used to...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>693123</identifier>
<identifier>she-and-her-cat-everything-flows-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175922" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女と彼女の空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She and Her Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle et son ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo to Kanojo no Sora</title>
<summary>A beautiful sunset reminds her and Daru of the time they first met.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>693121</identifier>
<identifier>she-and-her-cat-everything-flows-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175923" update="2017-07-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女と彼女の部屋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She and Her Apartment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle et son appartement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo to Kanojo no Heya</title>
<summary>After her roommate moves out,
 It is just her and Daru.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>693119</identifier>
<identifier>she-and-her-cat-everything-flows-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176278" update="2016-08-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176857" update="2016-08-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188416" recap="true" update="2017-07-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">完全版</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanzenban</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
