<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12058" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-09-03</startdate>
<enddate>2016-09-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Planetarian: Hoshi no Hito</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Planetarian: Storyteller of The Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Планетарий: грёзы маленькой звезды</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">planetarian ~星の人~</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">Planetarian ~별의 사람~</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12085" type="Prequel">Planetarian: Chiisana Hoshi no Yume</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10854" approval="14" total="14">Plastic Memories</anime>
<anime id="5132" approval="1" total="3">Eve no Jikan</anime>
<anime id="7249" approval="1" total="2">Eve no Jikan Gekijouban</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://planetarian-project.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2887" type="Work">David Production</name>
<name id="16061" type="Direction">Tsuda Naokatsu</name>
<name id="15972" type="Character Design">Takechi Hitomi</name>
<name id="27570" type="Direction">Machitani Shunsuke</name>
<name id="1481" type="Direction">Nakayama Katsuichi</name>
<name id="10770" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sobu Yuuko</name>
<name id="9769" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kiyomaru Satoru</name>
<name id="15972" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takechi Hitomi</name>
<name id="2887" type="Animation Work">David Production</name>
<name id="1046" type="Original Work">Visual Art`s/Key</name>
</creators>
<description>An adaptation of the visual-novel by Key, Planetarian: Hoshi no Hito combines the story of the original work with an expansion that extends the narrative with content from the Hoshi no Hito light-novel sequel.
In the future after much of the world has been devastated by nuclear and biological warfare, a young scavenger or "Junker" exploring a quarantined and abandoned city comes across a service robot still faithfully awaiting customers in the rooftop planetarium of a department store. Against his pragmatic instincts he helps the robot repair the planetarium`s projector: a decision which will change both their fates.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="260">7.62</permanent>
<temporary count="263">7.60</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>189625.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18282</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33190</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://planetarian-project.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Planetarian:_The_Reverie_of_a_Little_Planet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Planetarian_〜ちいさなほしのゆめ〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4569</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356421</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19202</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11921</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>planetarian_pj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07FYS9LHW</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5793" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Asimov`s Three Laws of Robotics</name>
<description>The SF author Isaac Asimov developed (1942) a set of laws he used to govern the behaviour of robots:
1. A robot may not injure a human being or, through inaction, allow a human being to come to harm.
2. A robot must obey any orders given to it by human beings, except where such orders would conflict with the First Law.
3. A robot must protect its own existence as long as such protection does not conflict with the First or Second Law.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="81693" type="main character in" update="2016-04-16">
<rating votes="57">9.04</rating>
<name>Hoshino Yumemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4898" picture="28248.jpg">Suzuki Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81694" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-03">
<rating votes="14">8.15</rating>
<name>Kuzuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83539" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-03">
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<name>Yobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83540" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-03">
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<name>Ruth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21823" picture="131326.jpg">Tsuda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83541" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-03">
<rating votes="4">5.75</rating>
<name>Levi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34880" picture="130561.jpg">Fuku Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83542" type="main character in" update="2016-08-03">
<rating votes="3">7.94</rating>
<name>Hoshi no Hito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84428" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Kanchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5021" picture="188516.jpg">Taki Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84429" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Kurahashi Satomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84430" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Makashima Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6081" picture="228633.jpg">Kushida Yasumichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="176887" update="2016-09-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>120</length>
<airdate>2016-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
