<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12290" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-01-09</startdate>
<enddate>2017-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gabriel Dropout</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ガヴリール ドロップアウト</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Пропащая Габриэль</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Отступница Габриэль</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ガヴリールドロップアウト</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gabriel Dropout</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Gabriel Dropout</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">가브릴 드롭아웃</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">珈百璃的堕落</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10972" approval="20" total="28">Himouto! Umaru-chan</anime>
<anime id="13637" approval="16" total="22">Jashin-chan Dropkick</anime>
<anime id="14630" approval="11" total="18">Machikado Mazoku</anime>
<anime id="323" approval="10" total="12">Pita Ten</anime>
<anime id="4144" approval="5" total="11">Renkin San-kyuu Magical? Pokaan</anime>
<anime id="4777" approval="0" total="5">Lucky Star</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="615767">Definitely not a revolutionary anime, but still quite good. Gabriel dropout has both hysterical and endearing moments - and I’d be hard-pressed to think of a time where there wasn’t at least something going on on-screen. If you like light-hearted comedy series, this will surely find a spot in your heart.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="744772">A cute, funny and relaxing show about four teenage angels and demons who attend a human high-school. You should definitely watch if you`re looking for moe and comedy. If you`re not looking for that you might loose interest very quickly because the characters are very predictable.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://gabdro.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1067" type="Animation Work">Doga Kobo</name>
<name id="12511" type="Character Design">Kumagai Katsuhiro</name>
<name id="7852" type="Direction">Oota Masahiko</name>
<name id="46466" type="Original Work">Ukami</name>
<name id="6742" type="Series Composition">Aoshima Takashi</name>
<name id="12511" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kumagai Katsuhiro</name>
<name id="7802" type="Music">Misawa Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="25520" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kuwabara Naoko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr46466 [Ukami]`s Gabriel Dropout manga.
After the angel http://anidb.net/ch83745 [Tenma Gabriel White] graduated at the top of her class at angel school. She begins to attend a human school on Earth in pursuit of knowledge, but then gets engrossed in a web game and decides that going anywhere was just too much trouble.
Source: ANN
Note: The first episode received a pre-screening in Shinjuku Picadilly theatre (Tokyo) on 18.12.2016.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1665">5.99</permanent>
<temporary count="1673">7.05</temporary>
<review count="1">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>232018.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18671</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34855</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>33731</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://gabdro.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gabriel_DropOut</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ガヴリールドロップアウト</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4393</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>357447</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19765</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gabdroanime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2756" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>board games</name>
<description>People here play a board game. It can vary from chess and Go, to Monopoly, to Dungeons and Dragons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2916" parentid="2756" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-12">
<name>shougi</name>
<description>Japanese chess.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4302" parentid="2876" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>Christianity</name>
<description>Christianity is a monotheistic religion based on the life and teachings of Jesus of Nazareth as presented in the New Testament. http://anidb.net/t524 [Christians] believe Jesus is the son of God, God having become man and the saviour of humanity. Christians, therefore, commonly refer to Jesus as Christ or Messiah.
Source: EN Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4413" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-16">
<name>heaven</name>
<description>Heaven, the Heavens or Seven Heavens, is a common religious, cosmological or transcendent place from which heavenly beings (such as a God, angels, the jinn, and sky deities like King or Queen of Heaven, Heavenly Father, Heavenly Mother, Son of Heaven, heavenly saints or venerated ancestors) originate, are enthroned or inhabit.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="83745" type="main character in" update="2018-05-08">
<rating votes="40">6.49</rating>
<name>Tenma Gabriel White</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tenma Gabriel White, known as Gabriel or Gab for short, is an angel who was the top of her class but turned into a good-for-nothing slacker after becoming addicted to anime and video games. She is often lazy and unmotivated and has a rather bossy attitude.
Gabriel came to Earth to attend a human high school and learn about humans after graduating for her Angel School in the upper world.</description>
<picture>195751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43492" picture="232251.jpg">Tomita Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83746" type="main character in" update="2016-12-09">
<rating votes="55">8.09</rating>
<name>Kurumizawa Satanichia McDowell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurumizawa Satanichia McDowell, known as Satanichia, she puts on airs and aims at being a great devil however she is a naïve and dimwitted devil and her little mischief usually ends in failure. Since Satanichia is so naïve and innocent she becomes the main target of Raphiel sadist jokes.
Like the other girls Satanicha came to earth to attend a human high school and learn about humans after graduating for her Devil School in the lower world</description>
<picture>195753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37280" picture="136935.jpg">Oozora Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83747" type="main character in" update="2016-12-09">
<rating votes="37">6.78</rating>
<name>Shiraha Raphiel Ainsworth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiraha Raphiel Ainsworth, known as Raphiel, was the second-ranked angel in http://anidb.net/ch83745 [Gabriel]`s class. Thou she appears to be a paragon of virtue at first glance, she inside is a sadistic stalker who often enjoys teasing http://anidb.net/ch83746 [Satanichia].
Raphiel came to earth to attend a human high school and learn about humans after graduating for her Angel School in the upper world.</description>
<picture>195750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83748" type="main character in" update="2016-12-09">
<rating votes="51">8.23</rating>
<name>Tsukinose Vignette April</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukinose Vignette April, known as Vignette, is a very responsible devil. Just as http://anidb.net/ch83745 [Gabriel]`s personality doesn`t agree with her role as an angel, Vignette`s is similarly unfit to a devil. She is always looking after Gabriel, who lives in the same building as her and is incapable of ignoring people that are in trouble.</description>
<picture>195752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86985" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-25">
<rating votes="11">4.07</rating>
<name>Master</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86986" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-25">
<rating votes="22">5.55</rating>
<name>Chisaki Taplis Sugarbelle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86987" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-25">
<rating votes="17">4.80</rating>
<name>Machiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10333" picture="170916.jpg">Fuchigami Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86988" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-25">
<rating votes="11">4.79</rating>
<name>Inu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39921" picture="225566.jpg">Izawa Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87234" type="appears in" update="2019-04-05">
<rating votes="3">3.14</rating>
<name>Kouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88062" type="appears in" update="2019-04-05">
<rating votes="6">5.69</rating>
<name>Ueno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42138" picture="184598.jpg">Kino Hina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88063" type="appears in" update="2019-04-05">
<rating votes="7">5.75</rating>
<name>Tanaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39921" picture="225566.jpg">Izawa Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88064" type="appears in" update="2019-04-05">
<rating votes="3">4.83</rating>
<name>Tannin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88186" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="3">3.69</rating>
<name>Alexander</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42138" picture="184598.jpg">Kino Hina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88187" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="3">4.24</rating>
<name>Satanya Otouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="25450.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88188" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<name>Satanya Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88189" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<name>Satanya Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2248" picture="170362.jpg">Kawashima Tokuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88190" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="3">3.14</rating>
<name>Chappy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39921" picture="225566.jpg">Izawa Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88191" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="4">3.20</rating>
<name>Haniel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88192" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="5">5.06</rating>
<name>Martiel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12783" picture="225340.jpg">Fujii Yukiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88193" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<name>Vigne Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1528" picture="223648.jpg">Kawaragi Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88194" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="3">3.66</rating>
<name>Vigne Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2339" picture="151715.jpg">Taketora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88538" type="appears in" update="2019-04-05">
<rating votes="7">6.46</rating>
<name>Zeruel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90078" type="appears in" update="2019-04-05">
<rating votes="4">3.99</rating>
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33369" picture="187996.jpg">Haruna Fuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="183235" update="2017-02-07">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いざ夏休み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Vacation, Ho!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est les vacances d`été !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iza Natsuyasumi</title>
<summary>When Vigne proposes a trip to the beach over summer vacation to Gab and Raphi, Satania makes it known that she must be included. Needless to say, Gab and Raphi are all too happy to pass the message onto Satania... with their own twists on it. Will Satania get to join the other three on their beach trip? And if she does, will she end up regretting it?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727491</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183236" update="2017-01-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友と勤労と虫刺されの夏の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friends, Work, and the Summer of Bugs</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Amies, travail et piqûres de moustiques d`un jour d`été</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo to Kinrou to Mushisasare no Natsu no Hi</title>
<summary>Gabriel gets a job at the local coffee shop to pay for MMO microtransactions, but with zero job experience and even less motivation, things take a weird turn fast. Good thing the boss thinks she`s a foreign student...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727489</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183237" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使と悪魔と委員長</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Angel, the Demon, and the Class President</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ange, le démon et la déléguée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi to Akuma to Iinchou</title>
<summary>Vignette wants to invite Gabriel and Satania to try out the school cafeteria with her, but Satania sneaks out of the classroom with her lunch, and Vigne and Gab realize they don`t know where she`s been eating all this time. When the demon and angel tail her, what they see will shock them...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727487</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183238" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう戻れないと知ったあの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day I Knew I Could Never Go Back</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour où j`ai su que je ne reviendrais jamais en arrière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Modorenai to Shitta Ano Hi</title>
<summary>Gabriel is a model angel at the top of her class in angel school. After her graduation, she descends to the human world in order to learn about humans firsthand and become a full-fledged angel. Each day, she cleans the park of litter and weeds, plays with children, and does good deeds, all while attending a human high school... until one day, she hears a cry for help coming from her laptop. Thus began her first encounter with the human entertainment known as "MMOs"--and her life would never be the same again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727485</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183610" update="2017-01-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183753" update="2017-01-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183981" update="2017-02-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秋の学校生活</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fall School Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Automne lycéen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aki no Gakkouseikatsu</title>
<summary>Raphiel finds herself with a big problem one morning while getting ready for school: her new bra`s already getting a little, uh, tight. Still, as long as she`s careful, she should be able to get through the school day without the clasps breaking. Or at least that`s what she tells herself until she finds out that it`s physical fitness day...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727499</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183982" update="2017-02-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴィーネの悪魔的な日々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vigne`s Demonic Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien démoniaque de Vigne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vigne no Akumateki na Hibi</title>
<summary>Vignette: a demon who gets up the first time her alarm clock goes off, puts out her trash early in the morning, keeps her apartment squeaky clean, and goes to bed on time. Gabriel: an angel who won`t wake up until past noon if she can help it, plays MMO holiday quests while dining on instant cup noodles, and games until she passes out at her laptop. These two friends seem to have little in common... until you take a peek inside their bankbooks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727497</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183983" update="2017-02-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サターニャの逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Satania`s Counterattack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Satanya contre-attaque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Satania no Gyakushuu</title>
<summary>Ever since meeting Gabriel in the human world, Satania just can`t seem to catch a break. But today her luck might finally turn around, thanks to a certain TV shopping channel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727495</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183984" update="2017-02-07">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その幻想を壊されまくった天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Angel Whose Illusions Were Shattered Like Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un ange aux illusions brisées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Gensou o Kowasare Makutta Tenshi</title>
<summary>One blisteringly hot day, a mysterious character dressed in full-body protective equipment descends upon the city of Maiten. It`s none other than the angel Tapris, here in the human world to chase after Gabriel, her beloved role model. Her first day in the mortal world will be filled with shock and horror—especially when she unknowingly runs into Gabriel herself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727493</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184842" update="2017-02-20">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184874" update="2017-03-31">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガヴリールドロップアウト!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gabriel Dropout!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gabriel DropOut !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gabriel Dropout!</title>
<summary>Gabriel hears that her older sister is heading to Earth and seems troubled. Which really comes as no surprise, as her older sister, Zelel, is known to be very efficient in Heaven. She’s a very powerful angel, who is known to be serious and strict, and is referred to as the Hand of God. Gabriel starts panicking, thinking that she might get such a harsh punishment if she finds out that she’s fallen that the world might be destroyed. Will Gabriel be able to get through in one piece?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727507</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184875" update="2017-03-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽しい日々はいつまでも......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fun Forever After...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ces jours heureux s`enchaînent sans fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanoshii Hibi wa Itsumademo......</title>
<summary>Gabriel and the girls are back to business as usual in the human world. Satania realizes a certain dog is missing when it doesn`t appear to steal her melon bread. Also, Tapris comes to visit Gabriel, and take notes on the human world while she`s at it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727505</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184876" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使と悪魔故郷に帰る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Angels and Demons Return Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Anges et démons rentrent au bercail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi to Akuma Furusato ni Kaeru</title>
<summary>Gabriel`s back home in Heaven for summer vacation, and stuck without her computer or video games. At least she can still laze around... if she can get away from her lovable little sister Haniel, anyways. What`s a faillen angel to do?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727503</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184877" update="2017-03-07">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖夜と晦日になんか来た</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas and New Year`s Eve Surprise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Noël et le Nouvel An sont arrivés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiya to Misoka ni Nanka Kita</title>
<summary>Raphiel and Vigne get together to throw a human-style Christmas party. There`s just one little problem: how can they keep Satania from ruining Christmas?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727501</identifier>
<identifier>gabriel-dropout</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186461" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">湯煙旅情編 ~天使の清らかな肌に迫る悪魔の罠~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukemuri Ryojou-hen: Tenshi no Kiyoraka na Hada ni Semaru Akuma no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188017" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2017-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使の贈り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi no Okurimono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221503" update="2019-09-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221504" update="2019-09-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
