<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12300" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2017-03-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fuuka</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">風夏</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Fuuka</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">风夏</title>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="official">후우카</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3203" type="Prequel">Suzuka</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="759964">For Suzuka and Kimi no Iru Machi Fans, a short and wonderful series to watch. The anime continues on in the manga so for those wanting to know more of what happens, highly recommended that you follow the manga afterwards</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://fuuka.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10802" type="Original Work">Seo Kouji</name>
<name id="1789" type="Animation Work">Diomedea</name>
<name id="21506" type="Character Design">Honda Yoshino</name>
<name id="44223" type="Series Composition">Akashiro Aoi</name>
<name id="3422" type="Direction">Kusakawa Keizou</name>
<name id="43888" type="Music">Iga Takurou</name>
<name id="44549" type="Music">West Ground</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch86111 [Haruna Yuu] has transferred to a school in Tokyo so he can live with his sisters after their parents moved to America. Introverted and unskilled at socializing with others, Yuu`s main mode of communication is Twitter. As he`s scoping out his new surroundings with his eyes on his smartphone, he crashes into http://anidb.net/ch67200 [Akitsuki Fuuka], a girl who appeared in front of him out of nowhere.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="817">3.70</permanent>
<temporary count="823">5.98</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221949.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18879</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33743</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://fuuka.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fūka_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>風夏</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4427</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>357874</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19877</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>fuuka_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6840" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-07">
<name>social media</name>
<description>Social media are computer-mediated technologies that allow the creating and sharing of information, ideas, career interests and other forms of expression via virtual communities and networks.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12797" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="9">5.05</rating>
<name>Fujikawa Miho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayano`s daughter and Yamato`s younger cousin by two years. She is very attached and protective of Yamato to the point of being jealous of Suzuka. Occasionally, she reminds Yamato of his childhood promise to marry her to cheer him up or as a joke. During the time skip, she became a high school student, moved into Suzuka`s old room, and became the track manager. When Suzuka moved back to the apartments, she was forced to give up her room and move back in with her mother.</description>
<picture>38414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12801" type="appears in" update="2011-02-26">
<rating votes="4">6.99</rating>
<name>Miyamoto Souichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the members of the track team and captain after Kinugasa graduates. A classmate of Suzuka`s from junior high school. After hearing about Yamato`s performance in physical tests, he actively persuades Yamato to join the track team. When Yamato came to him to help with making better times, he analyzed that data, found that Yamato was reaching his top speed too early, and made a training regimen for him. He believes Yamato has the potential to surpass Kazuki`s skill. Before graduating, he chose Yamato to become the next track captain. He is currently is part of Touto University`s track team and was influential in Yamato getting his recommendation. Even though Yamato eventually chose to attend Seijou, he still wanted him to perform his best.</description>
<picture>66440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="76" picture="16684.jpg">Maeda Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38263" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-11-12">
<rating votes="32">5.11</rating>
<name>Eba Yuzuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The female protagonist of the series. She moved from Tokyo to her father`s hometown. She is staying with the Kirishimas, who are her father`s acquaintances. She has a sociable personality and gets along with others easily. She confesses that she likes Haruto, but it does not prevent her from helping Haruto get closer to Nanami. It is later on revealed in the manga that she had met Haruto once when they were children at the summer festival, and he found her when she was lost and in tears. She consoled Haruto when he was dumped by Nanami. Yuzuki ends up moving back to Tokyo in order to work things out with her troubled family. Prior to her departure, she accepted Haruto`s confession and agreed to have a long distance relationship with him.
A short time later, Yuzuki cuts off all contact with Haruto and avoids Haruto`s request to meet up. Nanami hears from Rin that Eba apparently has a new boyfriend. Yuzuki apparently "explains" this to Haruto in a letter that came with the shirt she bought for him (that Haruto was ignorant of for around a month before it accidentally fell out of the bag). She explains how she must date a boy from her old middle school and therefore must break up with Haruto. However, after reading the letter Haruto decides that the letter`s content was not something Yuzuki would write, and that something has happened to her once again.
It turns out that she really does have a boyfriend, who turns out to be Haruto`s new friend, Kazama. She coldly rejected Haruto and any attempt to see her until one day Kazama collapsed because of his illness, and they meet again at the hospital, in the room where Kazama was staying. After learning the truth, Haruto questions her motives and why she dumped him back then, and she tells him that she knew Kazama since middle school, but after Kazama confessed his love to her, she rejected him multiple times and moved to Hiroshima. After she moved back to Tokyo, Kazama confessed his love to Yuzuki to her again, only this time he revealed that he doesn`t have much left to live, and wants to spend the little time he has with Eba. After Kazama`s funeral, Eba, perhaps feeling guilty about inadvertently contributing to his death, tells Haruto that it is best that they never see each other. Two years later she once again crosses path with Haruto. With every chance encounter, it becomes more apparent that Eba still has lingering feelings for him. Recently Yuzuki confessed to Haruto again, and now they are forging ahead with a new relationship despite everyone`s objections. Later on when Haruto moves to a place near Yuzuki`s house to live they start meeting often but after hearing that Yuzuki`s parents are Shifting to Nagoya Haruto visits her house and Yuzuki`s father`s sudden visits reveals their relationship despite Yuzuki`s father trying to break their relationship Yuzuki leaves the house and starts living with Haruto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>76161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="423" picture="37799.jpg">Nakajima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67200" type="main character in" update="2016-12-22">
<rating votes="16">4.68</rating>
<name>Akitsuki Fuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akitsuki Fuuka is the protagonist of Fuuka, the latest work of the mangaka of Kimi Iru no Machi, http://anidb.net/cr10802 [Seo Kouji].</description>
<picture>196070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86109" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-22">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Mikasa Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86110" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-13">
<rating votes="4">7.69</rating>
<name>Tomomi-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86111" type="main character in" update="2016-12-22">
<rating votes="6">2.11</rating>
<name>Haruna Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32035" picture="151695.jpg">Muranaka Tomo</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86112" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-24">
<rating votes="3">6.03</rating>
<name>Haruna Chitose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86113" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-24">
<rating votes="6">6.76</rating>
<name>Haruna Hibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86114" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-24">
<rating votes="4">7.65</rating>
<name>Haruna Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86115" type="main character in" update="2016-12-22">
<rating votes="13">8.25</rating>
<name>Hinashi Koyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86116" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-22">
<rating votes="8">7.98</rating>
<name>Iwami Sara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86117" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-22">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Nachi Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87120" type="appears in" update="2017-01-16">
<name>Akitsuki Yamato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuuka`s father.</description>
<picture>197008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10413" picture="38405.jpg">Nakamura Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87121" type="appears in" update="2017-03-24">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Akitsuki Suzuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuuka`s mother.</description>
<picture>200075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3921" picture="206017.jpg">Mitsuhashi Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87122" type="appears in" update="2017-01-16">
<name>Akitsuki Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuuka`s younger sister.</description>
<picture>197010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37977" picture="226053.jpg">Oowada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87123" type="appears in" update="2017-01-16">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Yamada Manager</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87473" type="appears in" update="2017-02-04">
<name>Yahagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87474" type="appears in" update="2017-02-04">
<name>Hisashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87475" type="appears in" update="2017-02-04">
<name>Nachi no Sobo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34588" picture="243219.jpg">Yaoya Kyou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87908" type="appears in" update="2017-02-25">
<name>Mogami Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10130" picture="151714.jpg">Takumi Yasuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88197" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<rating votes="2">6.51</rating>
<name>Mikasa Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88198" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<name>Mikasa no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88199" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<name>Nico</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88200" type="appears in" update="2017-03-13">
<name>Tama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="183179" update="2017-01-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライブ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Live!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Live!</title>
<summary>The sight of Yuu on the beach at night with Koyuki is such a shock to Fuuka that she runs away. Yuu tries to make up for it by explaining that he and Koyuki were friends as kids, but that angers Fuuka even more as she asks why he never told her this before. Yuu`s attempt to make up fails, and the mood remains awkward between them at work as well. Then their teacher, Tomomi, shows up at the beach house with the track team captain, Nachi, and Fuuka learns something even more shocking...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728447</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183180" update="2017-01-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トライアングル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Triangle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Triangle!</title>
<summary>"We`re starting a band!" Yuu`s casually spoken words gave Fuuka the idea to start a band. Yuu and Mikasa are dragged into the plan, and the three of them start a light music association. For starters, they need money for instruments, so they decide to stay at a beach house over the summer and work part-time there at Tomomi-sensei`s suggestion. But the owner, Yahagi, is Yuu`s least favorite type of person, causing to struggle with the job that requires serving customers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728445</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183181" update="2017-01-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はばたけ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take Flight!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Habatake!</title>
<summary>Yuu spots Fuuka in the hall and is about to talk to her, but then he notices she`s crying. He follows her eyes and sees that she seems to be looking at their good-looking classmate, Mikasa. After school, Yuu ends up on pool-cleaning duty with Fuuka and Mikasa, but he can`t stop wondering about their relationship. Meanwhile, Koyuki Hinashi, a childhood friend that Yuu lost contact with after she became a popular singer, finally calls Yuu for the first time in years.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728443</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183182" update="2017-01-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風夏!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fuuka!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuuka!</title>
<summary>The introverted Yuu Haruna has moved to Tokyo to live with this three sisters after their parents left to work abroad. While passing through the local shopping district, Yuu`s eyes are riveted on a TV screen in a store window when a girl comes running up the street and crashes into him. That is how he met the girl who seemed to be wrapped in a summer breeze: Fuuka Akitsuki. Their first meeting goes downhill when Fuuka mistakes Yuu`s intentions with the smartphone in his hand, and on top of that, he then finds out that they`ll be in the same class at his new school...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728441</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183473" update="2017-02-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183474" update="2017-01-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183696" update="2017-02-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トップ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Top!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Top!</title>
<summary>The day of the school fair has arrived. Fans enraged by Yuu and Koyuki`s scandal crowd around and shout abuse as their band takes the stage. Yuu is certain that the power of Fuuka`s singing can silence them, but then someone throws a glass bottle at him, and performing becomes the least of his worries. Chaos breaks loose, and Koyuki, who had come to see Yuu`s concert in secret, can`t stand silently by any longer...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728455</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183697" update="2017-02-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大炎上!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blown Up!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Enjou!</title>
<summary>A photo of Yuu and Koyuki together spreads like wildfire on Twitter, creating a huge scandal for the popular singer Koyuki. Even Yuu`s account is found and targeted, and wild rumors are even going around at school. The band`s practices in preparation for the school fair had been coming along smoothly, but the rumors spoil Fuuka`s mood. Meanwhile, Koyuki appears on TV and makes a declaration to the whole world...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728453</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183698" update="2017-02-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷無小雪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koyuki Hinashi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hinashi Koyuki</title>
<summary>Memories of childhood, parting, and regret... Recalling her own past, Koyuki makes up her mind to face Yuu. She visits his home to give him concert tickets, but the two of them had no idea that this meeting would have immense consequences... Then Koyuki runs into Fuuka on her way home, and somehow the two of them end up in a public bathhouse together, where Fuuka, a fan of Koyuki`s, is in high spirits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728451</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183699" update="2017-01-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仲間!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One of Us!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakama!</title>
<summary>The new school term has begun, and Yuu`s band has begun to practice in earnest. They have one of their idols, Hisashi of HEDGEHOGS, teaching them how to play their instruments, but bassist Yuu and vocalist/guitarist Fuuka are complete beginners. Nachi isn`t much better as a drummer, so their practices are going nowhere. Then they meet a senpai from their school, Sara Iwami. She`s cold to them at first, but then something changes her tune...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728449</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184324" update="2017-03-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184331" update="2017-02-04">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184462" update="2017-03-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">1.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Fair wind</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fair Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fair Wind</title>
<summary>Yuu wrote an original song in an attempt to bring Fuuka back to the band, but she persistently refused to meet with him. Now, as their growing popularity online has earned the attention of the HEDGEHOGS members, they`ve been invited to play at a live club again. The members have no choice but to practice their new song with no vocalist, but Yuu still isn`t willing to give up. Can he get his feelings through to Fuuka?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732069</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184463" update="2017-03-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Band</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Band</title>
<summary>"I was scouted, so I`m thinking of making my solo debut." Fuuka`s sudden declaration shook the members of The Fallen Moon. They had successfully completed their first gig and were determined to make their own legend, but they can`t be a band without a vocalist. Despite their lingering regrets, Sara, Mikasa, and Nachi set off to walk their own path. And after agonizing over this change, the answer Yuu arrived at was...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732067</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184464" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei</title>
<summary>Fuuka instantly declined the offer to make her solo debut, but she continues to struggle with the lyrics for the band`s original song. A concerned Mikasa tries to reach out, but Fuuka is unable to verbalize her true feelings. Yuu also becomes worried and calls her, but his kindness only makes her feel worse. With their first gig only days away, what feelings will Fuuka express in her lyrics?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732065</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184465" update="2017-03-07">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デート!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Date!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Date!</title>
<summary>Yuu waits by the ticket gates at a train station, and it`s Koyuki who arrives to meet him. They`ve decided, at her suggestion, to check out this town that she once visited when filming for a variety show. Meanwhile Yuu`s band, The Fallen Moon, has been selected as an opening act for a gig at a live music club. Fuuka suggests they write an original song to play there, but a strange sense of confusion in her heart makes the process difficult.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728457</identifier>
<identifier>fuuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
