<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12349" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-03-27</startdate>
<enddate>2017-06-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hinako Note</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ひなこのーと</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hinako Note</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">히나코 노트</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">雏子的笔记</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13238" approval="11" total="12">Comic Girls</anime>
<anime id="13160" approval="7" total="8">Slow Start</anime>
<anime id="11985" approval="2" total="3">Urara Meirochou</anime>
<anime id="14156" approval="1" total="5">Watashi ni Tenshi ga Maiorita!</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://hinakonote.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="46836" type="Original Work">Mitsuki</name>
<name id="35245" type="Animation Work">Passione</name>
<name id="7474" type="Character Design">Ueta Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="1645" type="Direction">Kitahata Tooru</name>
<name id="3211" type="Chief Direction">Takahashi Takeo</name>
<name id="3073" type="Music">Hashimoto Yukari</name>
<name id="7474" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ueta Kazuyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the comedy yonkoma manga by Mitsuki.
http://anidb.net/ch86801 [Sakuragi Hinako] has a hard time talking with others. In order to get over her paralyzing shyness, Hinako leaves her home in the country because she ends up starting school at the high school that has the drama club that she admires and ends up staying at Hitotose-sou. There, she meets http://anidb.net/ch86799 [Kuina], who loves books and to eat, http://anidb.net/ch86800 [Mayuki], who`s a bit older but smaller who`s good at cooking, and the quiet landlady with the hot body, http://anidb.net/ch86802 [Chiaki-san]. A cute and fun drama comedy about the former girl who was paralyzed from shyness.
Source: crunchyroll
Note: Episode 1 received an early broadcast on Abema TV on March 27, 2017. Regular broadcast started on April 7, 2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="556">4.15</permanent>
<temporary count="557">6.19</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>199971.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18894</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33948</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hinakonote.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hinako_Note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ひなこのーと</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4498</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358040</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20048</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hinakonote</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4042" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-17">
<name>odd jobs</name>
<description>A character (or several of them) in the anime takes on various jobs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="86798" type="main character in" update="2017-03-27">
<rating votes="10">6.33</rating>
<name>Nakajima Yua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39199" picture="242466.jpg">Kouno Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86799" type="main character in" update="2017-03-27">
<rating votes="9">6.77</rating>
<name>Natsukawa Kuina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43492" picture="232251.jpg">Tomita Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86800" type="main character in" update="2017-03-27">
<rating votes="13">7.59</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Mayuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86801" type="main character in" update="2017-03-27">
<rating votes="11">7.37</rating>
<name>Sakuragi Hinako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86802" type="main character in" update="2017-03-27">
<rating votes="9">7.83</rating>
<name>Hagino Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32612" picture="223330.jpg">Toujou Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86803" type="main character in" update="2017-03-27">
<rating votes="8">6.44</rating>
<name>Kuroyanagi Ruriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197027.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38546" picture="228695.jpg">Yoshida Yuuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88876" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<name>Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46395" picture="188869.jpg">Amano Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88877" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<name>Taiyakiya-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42617" picture="170041.jpg">Nakamura Kazumasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88878" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<rating votes="1">7.45</rating>
<name>Hinako (Youshou)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40538" picture="236250.jpg">Kurimoto Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88879" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<name>Toritarou`s</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88880" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<rating votes="2">4.64</rating>
<name>Hinako no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24015" picture="67329.jpg">Satou Kanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88881" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<name>Chiaki no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32216" picture="223331.jpg">Sasa Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88882" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<rating votes="1">7.45</rating>
<name>Chiaki (Youshou)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201156.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40106" picture="218774.jpg">Endou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97875" type="appears in" update="2018-09-08">
<name>Chiaki no Tomodachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41736" picture="185858.jpg">Ueda Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97876" type="appears in" update="2018-09-08">
<name>Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46536" picture="189673.jpg">Naitou Honoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97877" type="appears in" update="2018-09-08">
<name>Onannoko no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29850" picture="203454.jpg">Nakamura Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97878" type="appears in" update="2018-09-08">
<name>Obaasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5026" picture="151676.jpg">Sawada Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97879" type="appears in" update="2018-09-08">
<name>Toritarou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="186350" update="2017-05-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かかしひろいん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scarecrow Heroine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’héroïne épouvantail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakashi Heroine</title>
<summary>It`s been about a month since the start of the school year, and the theater society is practicing as always when Hinako notices child in the room. Kuina comments that the child has been showing up for a few days. None of the other members seem to mind that there`s a child among them; in fact, they all seem to be practicing harder than usual. Since the child is next to Chiaki, Hinako and Kuina wonder if she`s a theater troupe relation, or perhaps even Chiaki`s daughter. Finally, Yua can`t stand to listen anymore and straightens them out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733707</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186351" update="2017-04-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ともだちかんちがい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mistaken Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fausse amie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi Kanchigai</title>
<summary>The Hitotose Troupe was finally formed, with the goal of someday performing in the famous theater Suzuran. Then the school term begins, and Hinako tries to introduce herself to her class, but as usual her nerves take over and she freezes up like a scarecrow again. As Hinako is feeling down, Chiaki shows up and hands her a flyer that the school`s new theater society is handing out to recruit new members. Hinako is excited that theater has returned to the school, but then a classmate, Nakajima Yua, appears and demands to know Hinako`s connection to Chiaki...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733705</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186352" update="2017-04-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ここからはじまる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Begins Here</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tout commence maintenant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koko kara Hajimaru</title>
<summary>Chiaki, the landlady of Hitotose Manor, gave Hinako the suggestion to start up a new theater troupe. While Hinako is busy worrying about whether she`s actually capable of starting her own troupe, Chiaki asks her why she wants to go into theater, so she explains why she wanted to join the theater club. After hearing her reason, Chiaki tells her there`s no plan yet for the Fujimiya High theater club to return, so maybe it would be best to start a new troupe. As they`re discussing what sorts of productions they could put on, Kuina suggests making use of Hinako`s popularity with animals by using real animals in their act...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733703</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186353" update="2017-04-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とくぎは, かかしです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Talent Is Being a Scarecrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon talent, jouer les épouvantails</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokugi wa, Kakashi Desu</title>
<summary>Sakuragi Hinako is a girl who freezes up like a scarecrow when in front of people. Because animals love her, she often worked as an actual scarecrow at her old home in the country, but now she`s she decided to attend Fujimiya High School, which has a theater club she wants to join, in hopes of getting better at talking to people. So she left the countryside to move into Hitotose Manor in Tokyo, where she met its unusual but lovable residents, Kuina and Mayuki.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733701</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186823" update="2017-04-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186824" update="2017-04-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187269" update="2017-06-07">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">がんばりすぎて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trying Too Hard</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À trop en faire...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ganbari Sugite</title>
<summary>Hinako`s first summer break as a high school student has begun. She`s helping out at the used bookstore for that very reason, but when a customer comes in, her nervousness peaks and she freezes up like a scarecrow. When Chiaki and Mayuki return from an outing, Hinako takes a break to have tea with them, and then Yua pops in to lend Hinako some DVDs with her favorite small troupe performances as well as acting lessons. Hinako can`t help but smile at Yua`s kindness. The next day, as she`s helping out at the coffee shop, Hinako collapses while serving a customer...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733715</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187270" update="2017-06-07">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まよえるみずぎ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lost Swimsuit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Maillot de bain en perdition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mayoeru Mizugi</title>
<summary>It`s midsummer, and as the sun`s rays grow stronger, the days grow so hot that they seem to burn the girls` skin. Hinako starts to worry when she sees Kuina plastered to her desk in deference to the heat. When Kuina asks why it`s so hot, Hinako`s answer is a profoundly simple "Because it`s summer." Kuina has to accept that answer... but then she rises from her seat as if some great idea has struck her. She says that hot summer days like these make her want to visit the ocean, and suggests that all the Hitotose girls and Yua-chan make a trip to the ocean together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733713</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187271" update="2017-05-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めいどとおばけとゆめのぶたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maids, Ghosts, and the Stage of Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La pièce de la soubrette, du fantôme et du rêve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maid to Obake to Yume no Butai</title>
<summary>Hinako`s intense training under the exasperated Yua comes to an end, and the theater society is busy with wardrobe fittings for the culture festival that starts the next day. Mayuki helps with the costume fitting, and Hinako, Yua, Kuina, and all the other members begin to look more and more glamorous. While in their costumes, they end up doing an impromptu dress rehearsal, and Hinako is thrilled when she makes it through without messing up any lines for the first time. Yua reminds her that the actual performance is yet to come, and soon enough, the day of the culture festival arrives.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733711</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187272" update="2017-05-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やさしくないやさしいこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Kind Girl Who Isn`t Kind</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une gentille fille pas gentille</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasashikunai Yasashii Ko</title>
<summary>Ruriko, the theater club advisor who`s just returned from a theater trip in Europe, tells the club members that the script she wrote to demonstrate everything she learned in her travels will be the play they perform at the upcoming culture festival. She`s chosen Hinako to play the heroine, but Hinako messes up everything she tries to do. Yua, who feels she`s lost the leading role to a complete theater newbie, expresses her displeasure in no uncertain terms, but as she watches Hinako trying her hardest, she finds her opinions changing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733709</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187513" update="2017-05-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2017-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひなこのーと~ひととせちゃれんじ~ 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hinako Note: Hitotose Challenge 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187852" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あこがれのばしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Place We Longed to Reach</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’endroit rêvé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akogare no Basho</title>
<summary>Hinako is too cold to fall asleep, so she heads downstairs for a warm drink and notices a tasty smell coming from the coffee shop. Curiously, she peeks into the dark kitchen... and sees Mayuki stirring something in a large pot, chanting Chiaki`s name like some sort of spell. Hinako timidly speaks up, and Mayuki`s reaction makes it appear that she`s hiding something. Unable to bring herself to question this strange behavior further, Hinako tells Kuina about what she saw.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733723</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187853" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆくとしくるとし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From One Year to the Next</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une année s’achève, une autre commence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuku Toshi Kuru Toshi</title>
<summary>One day in winter, as Christmas approaches, Mayuki wonders if the Hitotose girls can`t put on some kind of event to draw customers to the coffee shop. Chiaki suggests that the troupe put on another play on Christmas Eve, and the girls quickly grow excited for their second public performance. Many ideas are shared, but they decide that since it`ll be taking place on Christmas Eve, their play should be a Christmas story... and with that, the preparations begin.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733721</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187854" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぱぱぱれーど</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pa-Pa-Parade</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Pa-pa-parade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PaPaParade</title>
<summary>Kuina has completed the script for the Hitotose Troupe`s first performance and is handing out copies to the other members. Chiaki`s reaction after reading through it is positive, and everyone is happy to have all the details of the story in place. Mayuki is especially happy to finally have a chance to plan out everyone`s costumes, and she immediately buys costumes for all the members to try. But then she learns that the "dress parade" normally happens after rehearsals have progressed to a certain point. Chiaki explains why it`s too early to think about costumes, but Mayuki insists that they try them on...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733719</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187855" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">がっしゅくします</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`ll Have a Training Camp</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le stage d`entraînement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gasshuku Shimasu</title>
<summary>One day, Hinako returns from school to find a letter from her mother. In it, her mother says she`d be visiting Tokyo to see Hinako acting. But Hinako is worried that she`ll get nervous and freeze up like a scarecrow if she knows her mother is watching, not to mention she hasn`t appeared on a stage since the culture festival. She even gets embarrassed just being seen working at the Hitotose coffee shop. Then she finds out about a stamp rally event planned in the shopping district, and she suggests having their troupe perform at Hitotose for it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733717</identifier>
<identifier>hinako-note</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187981" update="2017-05-26">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2017-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひなこのーと~ひととせちゃれんじ~ 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hinako Note: Hitotose Challenge 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188189" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2017-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひなこのーと~ひととせちゃれんじ~ 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hinako Note: Hitotose Challenge 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
