<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12554" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-12</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hajimete no Gal</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">はじめてのギャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">My First Girlfriend Is a Gal</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">第一次的辣妹</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13248" type="Other">Hajimete no Gal: Hajimete no Bunkasai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7286" approval="9" total="10">B Gata H Kei</anime>
<anime id="8853" approval="4" total="10">Nazo no Kanojo X</anime>
<anime id="11756" approval="1" total="4">Oshiete! Galko-chan</anime>
<anime id="12350" approval="1" total="4">Oshiete! Galko-chan: Natsuyasumitte Hontou Desuka?</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="579554">Well .... a "plain boring otaku boy meats harem of hotties"-anime with Gyaru Babes.

Sounds standard? It is! From the first episode to the last you won`t be surpriced in anything that happens. Which is a good thing in it`s own way. Brains out and enjoy the view. But if you havn`t seen it allready i recommend waiting for the DvD and the uncensored version.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hajimete-no-gal.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="39009" type="Animation Work">Naz</name>
<name id="12155" type="Character Design">Furukawa Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="30857" type="Series Composition">Momose Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="47852" type="Original Work">Ueno Meguru</name>
<name id="12155" type="Direction">Furukawa Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="26108" type="Music">Yashikin</name>
<name id="11766" type="Chief Animation Direction">Terao Kenji</name>
<name id="15243" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ootsuka Yae</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr47852 [Ueno Meguru].
http://anidb.net/ch88291 [Hashiba Jun`ichi] is an uncool high school student who frets about wanting to lose his virginity. Egged on by his friends, Jun goes on his knees and confesses his love to a classmate named http://anidb.net/ch88289 [Yame Yukana]. The confession surprisingly works and the couple goes out. However, Jun finds himself in uncharted waters with Yame, a trendy and fashion-conscious gal.
Source: ANN
Note: The first two episodes get an advance airing on June 25, 2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1123">3.01</permanent>
<temporary count="1131">5.69</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>203739.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19254</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34403</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hajimete-no-gal.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>My_First_Girlfriend_Is_a_Gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>はじめてのギャル</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4611</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358868</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20253</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>haji_GAL</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07GC4ZGPV</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4042" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-17">
<name>odd jobs</name>
<description>A character (or several of them) in the anime takes on various jobs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4352" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-11">
<name>censored uncensored version</name>
<description>Even the DVD and Blu-ray releases do not let you see everything you were expecting to, and you will have to live with censorship in the show. That normally applies to fan service, but may also apply to gore and violence. A very common example is characters without nipples, as in http://anidb.net/a6083 [KissXSis]; in other cases, something such as steam or foam stays in the camera`s way, like in http://anidb.net/a6531 [Kanamemo]. In some shows, the censorship in the disk releases is even stronger than in the TV version, while others may use creative censorship as a replacement for the removed fan service or even as a joke.
This does not apply to censorship of what Japanese pornography laws still require to be censored.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4761" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-11">
<name>love letter</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime receives a love letter, usually stashed away in their school shoe locker. Or in other cases a girl might directly give the love letter to the boy she loves.
Plot device to further the relationship between characters, may also be used as comedic element creating awkward situations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6408" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-17">
<name>bowling</name>
<description>Bowling refers to a series of sports or leisure activities in which a player rolls or throws a bowling ball towards a target.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>173577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="88289" type="main character in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="42">7.76</rating>
<name>Yame Yukana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41761" picture="196454.jpg">Nagaku Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88290" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="24">6.42</rating>
<name>Honjou Ranko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88291" type="main character in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="19">1.78</rating>
<name>Hashiba Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88292" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="31">7.18</rating>
<name>Fujinoki Nene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88293" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-25">
<rating votes="27">7.34</rating>
<name>Kashii Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89668" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="10">2.96</rating>
<name>Sakamoto Shinpei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203264.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="303" picture="166016.jpg">Toyonaga Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89669" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="6">1.87</rating>
<name>Ishida Keigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2487" picture="23183.jpg">Akabane Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89670" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="12">1.26</rating>
<name>Kobayakawa Minoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90068" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-15">
<rating votes="9">6.08</rating>
<name>Uesaka Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10080" picture="235712.jpg">Aranami Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90069" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-15">
<rating votes="6">4.97</rating>
<name>Shiina Kokoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43627" picture="176871.jpg">Hara Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94287" type="appears in" update="2018-03-05">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Ikemen Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94288" type="appears in" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Ero Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94289" type="appears in" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Nega Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="303" picture="166016.jpg">Toyonaga Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94290" type="appears in" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Zen Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94343" type="appears in" update="2018-03-07">
<name>Jun`ichi (Shougakusei)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9512" picture="35180.jpg">Togashi Misuzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94344" type="appears in" update="2018-03-07">
<rating votes="1">6.95</rating>
<name>Yame-san Inochi Jun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94489" type="appears in" update="2018-03-11">
<name>Mitarai Dai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188514" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての清楚ギャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Serious Gal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma première bimbo comme il faut</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Seiso Gal</title>
<summary>Junichi is eating lunch with Yukana in the courtyard, but Ranko is with them ruining the atmosphere. Kashii Yui, a serious, prim and proper type of girl, tries to talk to him. After school, she takes Junichi to a cafe, and is interested whether Junichi and Yukana are truly dating. Junichi tells Yui just how happy he is with Yukana, but…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742289</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188515" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての黒ギャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Spray-On Gal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma première bimbo bronzée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Kuro Gal</title>
<summary>Junichi finds a love letter in his shoe box after school, but feels compelled to properly turn the girl down, as he already has a girlfriend. As it turns out, there’s another gal waiting for him who starts to get hot and heavy with him. Only for Yukana to show up at the worst possible moment…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742287</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188516" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめてのカラオケ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Karaoke</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon premier karaoké</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Karaoke</title>
<summary>Junichi’s kneeling love confession worked and he’s now dating Yukana. He never though he’d be able to get such a cute girlfriend, and his friends are jealous. Yukana invites Junichi to karaoke after school, but according to his friends, that’s where couples go to have sex. Will Junichi lose his virginity already?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742285</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188517" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての土下座</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Time Begging for It</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma première prosternation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Dogeza</title>
<summary>Hashiba Junichi is a high school student that wants to do anything to lose his virginity. His evil friends force him to ask out a gal in his class, Yame Yukana, so he begs her to date him while kneeling on the ground. She calls him a freak, but then something amazing happens…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742283</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189024" update="2018-05-21">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189025" update="2018-05-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189505" update="2017-07-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Trip</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon premier voyage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Ryokou</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742297</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189506" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめてのバイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Job</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon premier job</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Baito</title>
<summary>The gang decides to go to the beach for summer vacation, and in order to save up money, Junichi is working at a cosplay cafe. By coincidence, Yukana, Ranko, Yui, and Nene are all working there too. Junichi is working the kitchen, however. The four girls work with the customers, but the manager at the shop is a little weird…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742295</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189507" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての八女さん家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Time at Yame-san`s House</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma première excursion chez Yame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Yame-san Chi</title>
<summary>Junichi is getting much closer to Yukana. Shinpei suggests playing the King Game in order to get even closer. Junichi has his friends and Yukana’s friends meet up at Yukana’s house, where they all play the game. Yukana’s in a different outfit than usual in her house clothes, which is surprisingly stimulating to Junichi, and just when things seem to be getting good between them…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742293</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189508" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめてのパギャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Half-Assed Gal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma première mi-bimbo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Pagal</title>
<summary>Junichi is dreaming about having sex with Yukana and is in a rather pleasant mood. In his dream, he reaches out to feel Yuaka’s breasts, and unconsciously does the same thing in reality, only to find a soft sensation in front of him. Junichi, surprised, awakens to find a rather large-breasted gal on top of him, but he has no clue who she is, and is confused by her gal-speak.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742291</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190079" update="2017-08-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma première déclaration d’amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Kokuhaku</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742301</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190080" update="2017-08-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめてのケンカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma première dispute</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Kenka</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742299</identifier>
<identifier>my-first-girlfriend-is-a-gal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199911" update="2018-05-21">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="199912" update="2018-05-21">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="199913" update="2018-05-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
