<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12952" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-12-30</startdate>
<enddate>2018-04-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Overlord II</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">オーバーロード II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">overlord 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">overlord2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">OVERLORD II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Overlord II</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">오버로드 II</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">OVERLORD II</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14008" type="Sequel">Overlord III</anime>
<anime id="10816" type="Prequel">Overlord</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="272004">While I personally liked the episodes centered around Sebas, I felt the show was overshadowed by season one and hence, couldn`t live up to my expectations. 
It is by no means a bad watch, I highly recommend you to give it a shot. If you have access to all (as of now) three seasons, I suggest you watch them all in a timely manner. Season two won`t feel as weak this way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="415669">This season was good even if the main character didn`t appear much because of the side story. It was still enjoyable and I recommend watching it if you liked the first season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="384109">It`s a great watch had lots of fun. The first half was the best one, great change of perspective, funny moments, satisfying battles... 

The second half fell a bit short in comparison. It wasn`t bad but lacked big moments similar to the battles at the end of season 1. It`s "only" a build up for things to come. But since the next season isn`t far away it`s nothing major.

If you liked the first season watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="274570">If you like the first season you must this season

animation and cgi is almost the same with the first season but the way of delivering the plot is quite good some people might be annoyed by the first half of the season but the second half is amazing I can`t wait for the 3rd installment of this anime.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://overlord-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="33733" type="Music">Katayama Shuji</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="7839" type="Character Design">Tasaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="33391" type="Series Composition">Sugawara Yukie</name>
<name id="6476" type="Direction">Itou Naoyuki</name>
<name id="42661" type="Original Work">Maruyama Kugane</name>
<name id="8251" type="Chief Animation Direction">Imamura Taiki</name>
<name id="7839" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tasaki Satoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the light novel series by the same name written by http://anidb.net/cr42661 [Maruyama Kugane] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr42662 [So-Bin].
Note: The first episode received an early screening at a special event held at United Cinema Aqua City Odaiba on 17.12.2017 and later received an early airing on Abema TV on 30.12.2017. The regular airing started on 09.01.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2247">6.30</permanent>
<temporary count="2265">7.26</temporary>
<review count="1">5.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224710.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20397</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35073</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>37087</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://overlord-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Over_Lord_(novel_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>オーバーロード_(小説)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4798</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363245</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>360029</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20784</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>over_lord_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="72777" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-13">
<rating votes="94">3.98</rating>
<name>Aura Bella Fiora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72778" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-10">
<rating votes="344">6.05</rating>
<name>Albedo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Albedo is the Overseer of the Floor Guardians of the Great Tomb of Nazarick. She is in charge of the general management and supervises the activities of the seven Floor Guardians, meaning that she ranks above all the other NPCs in Nazarick. She is the sister of Nigredo and Spinel. She was created by Tabula Smaragdina.
She was originally programmed to be a nymphomaniac, but Momonga altered her personality and changed her setting to be in love with him.
Source: Overlord Wikia</description>
<picture>174511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72779" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-09">
<rating votes="57">7.09</rating>
<name>Cocytus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cocytus is the Guardian of the 5th Floor of Nazarick.
Cocytus is the personal creation of Warrior Takemikazuchi, one of the 41 members of Ainz Ooal Gown. Cocytus was created to personify the perfect warrior both in body and spirit. Cocytus is loyal to a fault to the Supreme Beings but he`s not just a dumb muscle and is willing to learn in to better serve his lord. Amongst the denizen of Nazarick, he`s more accepting of outsiders provided they share the same strength, honor, and warrior spirit that he epitomizes.
Cocytus design is based on the Gelugon, a type of ice-devil from D&amp;D. He has the highest offensive capabilities of melee fighters in Nazarick backed up by ice-elemental skills. Cocytus have no need for armor as his exoskeleton serves as a living armor. His creator, Warrior Takemikazuchi, has equipped Cocytus with many of his own personally crafted weapons and has programmed Cocytus with the knowledge of all of the Divine Weapons own by the Supreme Beings.
Cocytus seems to prefer the company of other insectoids like him from Nazarick. He also hold good relations with Demiurge and often asks the demon for advice too difficult for himself to understand.</description>
<picture>174516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72780" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="227">4.40</rating>
<name>Shalltear Bloodfallen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shalltear Bloodfallen is the first, second and third floor guardian. She is a true vampire and the Floor Guardian of the first to third floors in the Great Tomb of Nazarick. She was created by Peroroncino.
Shalltear is the strongest of the floor guardians and is completely loyal to Ainz and is also a love rival to Albedo for his affections. She takes great joy in being able to prove her worth and fantasizes about the praise she expects to receive. When a situation doesn`t go in her favor, she panics about the scolding she believes that she will get.
Source: Overlord Wikia</description>
<picture>174512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72781" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-10">
<rating votes="90">7.42</rating>
<name>Sebas Tian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72782" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-09">
<rating votes="144">4.06</rating>
<name>Demiurge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Demiurge is the Guardian of the 7th Floor of the Great Tomb of Nazarick.
Demiurge is the personal creation of Ulbert Alain Odle, one of the 41 members of Ainz Ooal Gown. Ulbert created Demiurge as the personification of evil. As such, Demiurge relish in acts that embodies this twisted morality scripted onto him. He is cruel and uniformly incompassionate to all beings who do not belong to the Tomb of Nazarick and thinks little more of them than tools and toys to amuse himself with. However, to all of his comrades, Demiurge demonstrate true care and loyalty. Demiurge suffers an existential crisis, more than other denizens of Nazarick, due to his fear of losing Ainz Ooal Gown as the last remaining Supreme Being.
Demiurge is amongst the weakest of the Floor Guardian in pure destructive power. However, he has an extremely high intellect and excel at long term strategic planning. Often, he can predict the actions of people with high standing on a national level and equally high hubris down to the exact detail. Though his own personal power is low, Demiurge commands the Demon Lords, a group of high level subordinate whom themselves command legions of inferno demons.
Though he`ll get along with anyone who`s a comrade in Nazarick, Demiurge have an unexplained dislike of Sebas Tian. Unbeknownst to both NPCs, they`ve inherited the conflict from the personal dispute of their own creators.</description>
<picture>174515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72783" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="255">6.35</rating>
<name>Narberal Gamma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Narberal Gamma is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades], combat maids under http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas Tian]. She`s a doppelganger and http://anidb.net/ch76797 [Momon]`s companion in their adventurers` guild, Darkness. She was chosen as one due to her most human-looking appearance out of all other maids. As an adventurer, she refers to herself as Nabe.
Like most of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick] residents, she holds great disdain towards humans. This often proves troublesome, as she becomes incredibly violent when human males make advances on her.</description>
<picture>176197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72784" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-10">
<rating votes="69">5.53</rating>
<name>Mare Bello Fiore</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72785" type="main character in" update="2017-05-10">
<rating votes="513">5.24</rating>
<name>Ainz Ooal Gown</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momonga is the guildmaster and only remaining active player of the guild Ainz Ooal Gown from the DMMORPG game Yggdrasil, once one of the top guilds in the game. When the guild`s base, the Underground Tomb of Nazarick, was transported to an alternate reality and a new world, Momonga soon assumed for himself the name of Ainz Ooal Gown and began a campaign to make his guild legendary, subsequently turning to world domination.
When he was still human and an Yggdrasil player, Ainz was an adult man already jaded by life, making him prone to analyse things from his perspective as a company worker. In the new world, his game avatar, an undead lich, became his real body, along with all the physical characteristics such a body would have; as a result, he is nigh immune to strong emotions and worldly temptations and desires, because his status as an undead physically shuts them down.
Ainz is calculating, subversive, and cowardly when approaching or in the imminence of a battle, placing his continued survival, as well as that of the guild and its NPCs, who gained life with the transfer, above all else, and planning many moves ahead; once his plans are set in motion, he is ruthlessly efficient in their execution, and will not bat an eyelid at slaying his opponents when pressed. His actions are vicious and ruthless towards any and all that oppose him, and he is motivated by his own gains and survival and the glory of his guild`s name. His greatest weakness is his great fear of not being recognized as a proper leader by the guild`s NPCs, causing him to play along with their plans when he does not understand them simply to not be forced to admit to them that he is not following what they have in mind.</description>
<picture>174510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75834" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-11">
<rating votes="58">7.83</rating>
<name>Gazef Stronoff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2573" picture="240892.jpg">Shirokuma Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76483" type="appears in" update="2015-08-11">
<rating votes="7">6.28</rating>
<name>Touch Me</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176217.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76773" type="appears in" update="2018-03-23">
<rating votes="43">5.79</rating>
<name>Hamusuke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hamusuke, also known as the Virtuous King of the Forest, is a monster capable of using magic, possessing incredible power. It lives deep in the forest, so there are few eyewitness reports, but its existence has been known for quite a long while. Some even say it is a several hundred years old, four-legged, silverish white beast with a snake-like tail. It is a giant hamster and http://anidb.net/ch76797 [Momon]`s pet.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>178716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76788" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="48">6.31</rating>
<name>Yuri Alpha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri Alpha is the vice captain of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s a http://anidb.net/t804 [dullahan], and like http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas], she doesn`t like killing humans without reason. The other Pleiades look up to her and her behavior is strict like a teacher.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76792" type="appears in" update="2018-09-26">
<rating votes="6">4.40</rating>
<name>Fukuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40343" picture="223254.jpg">Kameyama Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76797" type="main character in" update="2018-01-30">
<rating votes="123">6.35</rating>
<name>Momon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momon is http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz Ooal Gown]`s alter ego as an Adamantite-ranked Adventurer.
Ainz created this persona for the purpose of gaining fame in the Kingdom of Re-Estize and intelligence about possible high level adversaries in the area. He stylized himself as the quiet and enigmatic dark warrior. The iconic raven black armor and red cape has earned his adventurer team the unofficial name of Darkness.</description>
<picture>176222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76799" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="109">3.87</rating>
<name>Solution Epsilon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Solution Epsilon is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s a slime and one of the most dangerous Pleiades to humans, since she enjoys devouring humans alive. An assassin and poisoner who can decide to protect or dissolve things she absorbs, she can also control the speed of her digestion. Solution gets along with http://anidb.net/ch72780 [Shalltear] because of their similar tastes.</description>
<picture>217386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76801" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-16">
<rating votes="106">3.59</rating>
<name>Entoma Vasilissa Zeta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Entoma Vasilissa Zeta is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades] and an insect-summoner who likes preying on humans.
Her face is actually a bug shell that hides her true face, while she disguises her voice with that of a cute girl by using a leech that can mimic a human`s voice. Her original voice, which she dislikes using is harsh and grating, similar to that of http://anidb.net/ch72779 [Cocytus]. She harbors a big grudge against an adventurer named http://anidb.net/ch93725 [Evileye] who used anti-bug magic to destroy her cute voice in battle.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76802" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="53">6.30</rating>
<name>CZ2128 Delta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>CZ2128 Delta is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s an automaton whose weapons look rather futuristic compared to the setting. Her personality is silent and emotionless, but she dislikes cannibalism and likes cute things. Her neutral personality also makes her safer to humans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76803" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="125">5.04</rating>
<name>Lupusregina Beta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lupusregina Beta is one of the http://anidb.net/ch89828 [Pleiades]. She`s a werewolf with a very bright and outgoing personality and a druid capable of using healing magic, and often carries a massive staff to fight. While she appears to be sociable and friendly toward humans, it is only a mask to conceal her brutal and cunning personality.
Lupusregina is later assigned by http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz] to protect the inhabitants of Carne Village after he tames http://anidb.net/ch76773 [Hamsuke] (as her presence was the only thing keeping monsters away from there). However, when she fails to notify him about a threat to the village, believing it to be an unnecessary action, Ainz flies into a rage, terrifying all those around.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77873" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-12">
<rating votes="74">7.88</rating>
<name>Brain Unglaus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77877" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="14">6.73</rating>
<name>Pandora`s Actor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pandora`s Actor is the area Guardian in charge of the Treasury and finances of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick], who was created by http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Momonga] himself. He`s a high level Doppelgänger whose face is a simple egghead with three holes dressed in a Neo-Nazi-esque uniform but can transform himself into others, even copying their abilities and powers.
In Momonga`s original design, he`s the combination of everything that he thought was cool, with exaggerated gestures and body language but now that he is actually alive, he embarrasses Momonga. Despite his appearance and personality, he is on the same level as the Floor Guardians and is considered as intelligent as http://anidb.net/ch72778 [Albedo] and http://anidb.net/ch72782 [Demiurge]. He is granted permission to secretly call Ainz his father—secretly he does not want rumors of favoritism to spread.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217387.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77906" type="appears in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<name>Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77907" type="appears in" update="2018-03-13">
<rating votes="4">4.04</rating>
<name>Bukubukuchagama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89828" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="7">8.19</rating>
<name>Pleiades</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Pleiades are a team of special maids led by http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas Tian], who were originally designed to protect and serve in the Throne room of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick]. Despite each member, with the exception of Sebas, being weak by Nazarick`s standards, their strength is equivalent to a legendary monster in the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>203682.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92890" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-12">
<rating votes="39">6.25</rating>
<name>Climb</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Climb is the personal bodyguard of princess http://anidb.net/ch92895 [Renner]. She saved him when he was just a street urchin about to die from sickness. As such, he views his services to her as a fulfilling of that debt he owes and is even willing to give up his life for her. However, he remains unaware of Renner`s true nature.
He is rather disliked due to him having such a position despite not even being a commoner, but an urchin. Despite this position, he holds no talent in fighting, making up for it with sheer effort. He eventually meets http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas] and, after convincing him to teach him some of his skills, they become friends, though he remains unaware of his loyalty towards http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>222179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92891" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-09">
<rating votes="20">4.47</rating>
<name>Crusch Lulu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cursch Lulu is the wife of http://anidb.net/ch92892 [Zaryusu Shasha] and acting Chieftain of the Red Eyes tribe. She is an albino, which normally would entail abandonment at birth, but she was kept and raised by her parents. She is powerful magic user.
During a famine, her father, the chief, committed fratricide to prevent the death of his people. Unable to bear the shame, Cursch, arranged an uprising, which was successful, passing the mantle of chief to her. She and Zaryusu met when he came to ask for an alliance between lizardmen, and they fell in love, when he, while infatuated by her beauty, let out a mating cry for her. They eventually became closer and marry and even had a son, who was also an albino.
She became a representative for the lizard people, after the fight against http://anidb.net/ch72779 [Cocytus]. She met http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz], talked to him with fear and respect, and he offered to bring back Zaryusu in return for her acting as an informant to him, for any sign of rebellion. She is the most powerful magic caster among the lizardmen, but due to her skin, she is extremely vulnerable to the sun, making her wear a ridiculous bush outfit whenever she goes out in the day. She is still fearful of Ainz, as when he inquires about the child she fears he might take him away.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92892" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-09">
<rating votes="18">6.94</rating>
<name>Zaryusu Shasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zaryusu Shasha is a lizardman of the Green Claw tribe and younger brother of http://anidb.net/ch92893 [Shasuryu Shasha], the Chief of the Green Claw tribe. He is the one, who managed to unify all lizardman tribes to fight against http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz], who declared a slaughter upon them.
Zaryusu is a Traveler, a member of the tribe who leaves the social hierarchy and is untethered from its traditions and obligations. It is an uncoveted position that is both shunned and respected at the same time.
Zaryusu is a renaissance man due to his circumstances. He single handledly bring his tribe`s level of technology from purely hunting/gathering to near sustainable agriculture. He`s a powerful warrior and his fame is widespread for defeating and succeeding the previous owner of Frost Pain (a legendary sword made of pure ice.) He`s a experienced adventurer and knows of many monsters and mystic arts from his time as a traveler. He`s keenly aware of politics, economy, and population geography. As the crisis of war with the Tomb of Nazarick is inevitable, he is the first one to act and come up with a solution for continuing the survival of his race.
Source: Wikipedia, Novel</description>
<picture>211796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92893" type="appears in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="2">6.86</rating>
<name>Shasuryu Shasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shasuryu Shasha is the elder brother and Chieftain of the Green Claw tribe. He is among the few lizardmen to fight against http://anidb.net/ch92893 [Cocytus] and be revived. He and http://anidb.net/ch92892 [his brother] are very caring of each other.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92894" type="appears in" update="2018-01-16">
<rating votes="4">6.67</rating>
<name>Zenberu Gugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zenberu Gugu is the Chieftain of the Dragon Tusk tribe.</description>
<picture>212009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92895" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-12">
<rating votes="30">5.57</rating>
<name>Renner Theiere Chardelon Ryle Vaiself</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Renner Theiere Chardelon Ryle Vaiself is the Third Princess of the Kingdom. She is publicly known as the Golden Princess due to her great beauty, benevolence and kindness as well as being a reformer who brought positive changes to the Kingdom. However, in reality she has a psychopathic personality and does not care about the feelings of others. The only exception to this is http://anidb.net/ch92890 [Climb] towards who she harbours a demanded love, viewing him as her "puppy". She merely maintains this facade in order to maintain her good reputation.
Her love towards Climb emerged from that fact that her mental capacities were overdeveloped, causing no one to truly understood her until she saved him and he began to hold onto her every word. Initially, she merely influenced events behind the scenes to increase Climb`s reputation.</description>
<picture>222178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27357" picture="75009.jpg">Yasuno Kiyono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93153" type="appears in" update="2018-07-10">
<rating votes="4">3.71</rating>
<name>Eclair Ecleir Eicler</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eclair Ecleir Eicler is the assistant butler.</description>
<picture>217371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93154" type="appears in" update="2018-01-10">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Zindlux Vaision</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3161" picture="69050.jpg">Yamanoi Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93155" type="appears in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="2">5.87</rating>
<name>Picky</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2328" picture="171565.jpg">Satou Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93156" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="4">5.00</rating>
<name>Pestonya Shortcake Wanko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pestonya Shortcake Wanko is the Head maid of the Homunculus Maids of the http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Great Tomb of Nazarick]. She is one of the few NPCs who does not look down on normal humans and would prefer to be kind to them, alongside http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas] and http://anidb.net/ch76788 [Yuri Alpha].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93157" type="appears in" update="2018-09-26">
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<name>Boullope-kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marquis Boullope was the leader of the Nobility Faction and one of the six leaders of the Six Great Nobles of http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>224511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44893" picture="223787.jpg">Ihara Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93158" type="appears in" update="2018-01-10">
<rating votes="2">4.90</rating>
<name>Ramposa III</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3102" picture="24178.jpg">Chou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93159" type="appears in" update="2018-01-10">
<rating votes="3">6.62</rating>
<name>Bangai Sekiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93160" type="appears in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Rigrit Bers Caurau</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rigrit Bers Caurau is a former member of Blue Rose and one of the 13 Heroes, from 200 years ago. She is described as an elderly woman, with a cheerful, and mischievous personality. Also, she is stated to be a Necromancer and, like all magic casters, is able to extend her life beyond natural limits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93288" type="appears in" update="2018-01-17">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Messenger Monster</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44893" picture="223787.jpg">Ihara Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93289" type="appears in" update="2018-01-17">
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<name>Senshi Atama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93290" type="appears in" update="2018-01-17">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Shuryou Atama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43270" picture="173943.jpg">Maki Shun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93291" type="appears in" update="2018-01-17">
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<name>Saishi Atama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41981" picture="170979.jpg">Izawa Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93292" type="appears in" update="2018-01-17">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Rororo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212027.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93367" type="appears in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="3">4.39</rating>
<name>Iguva 41</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93368" type="appears in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="2">5.87</rating>
<name>Suukyu Juju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28881" picture="66208.jpg">Sakurai Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93369" type="appears in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="2">5.87</rating>
<name>Kyukuu Zuuzuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29852">Asashina Junpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93516" type="appears in" update="2018-01-30">
<rating votes="3">7.48</rating>
<name>Victim</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93725" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-12">
<rating votes="27">8.32</rating>
<name>Evileye</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93726" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-10">
<rating votes="8">6.81</rating>
<name>Gagaran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93727" type="appears in" update="2018-02-13">
<rating votes="2">1.05</rating>
<name>Cocco Doll</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93728" type="appears in" update="2018-02-13">
<rating votes="2">1.70</rating>
<name>Zero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93729" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="55">8.03</rating>
<name>Tuare</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tuare is a former sex slave from a brothel in the capital of Re-Estize. In the course of her job, she was thoroughly broken physically and mentally, to the point she was slated for "disposal". At the time she was being disposed of, http://anidb.net/ch72781 [Sebas] chose to rescue her and take her in.</description>
<picture>217367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3198" picture="160468.jpg">Shimamura Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93730" type="appears in" update="2018-03-27">
<rating votes="4">7.46</rating>
<name>Tia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93731" type="appears in" update="2018-02-20">
<rating votes="5">8.53</rating>
<name>Tina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43492" picture="232251.jpg">Tomita Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93732" type="appears in" update="2018-02-13">
<rating votes="2">2.12</rating>
<name>Hilma Cygnaeus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20501" picture="186150.jpg">Yukinari Toa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93733" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-12">
<rating votes="26">8.17</rating>
<name>Lakyus Alvein Dale Aindra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93892" type="appears in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="5">3.55</rating>
<name>Elias Brandt Dale Raeven</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elias Brandt Dale Raeven is the leader of the Royalty Faction and the most powerful noble among the Six Great Nobles of the http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom].
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>223689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45579" picture="211758.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93893" type="appears in" update="2018-02-20">
<rating votes="3">2.05</rating>
<name>Succulent</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93894" type="appears in" update="2018-02-20">
<rating votes="7">4.32</rating>
<name>Zanac Valleon Igana Ryle Vaiself</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17167" picture="170235.jpg">Fujiyoshi Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93895" type="appears in" update="2018-02-20">
<rating votes="3">1.17</rating>
<name>Staffan Heivish</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213311.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94317" type="appears in" update="2018-03-27">
<rating votes="2">2.50</rating>
<name>Edstrom</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94318" type="appears in" update="2018-03-27">
<rating votes="2">1.42</rating>
<name>Malmvist</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94319" type="appears in" update="2018-03-06">
<rating votes="2">1.83</rating>
<name>Peshurian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21337" picture="207958.jpg">Yamamoto Shouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94320" type="appears in" update="2018-03-06">
<rating votes="2">1.99</rating>
<name>Davernoch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43270" picture="173943.jpg">Maki Shun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94321" type="appears in" update="2018-03-06">
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<name>Maid</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51372" picture="206421.jpg">Suzuki Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94322" type="appears in" update="2018-03-06">
<rating votes="3">5.13</rating>
<name>Maid</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51371" picture="206419.jpg">Tanaka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94526" type="appears in" update="2018-03-13">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Ulbert Alain Odle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94845" type="appears in" update="2018-03-27">
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<name>Jaldabaoth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94846" type="appears in" update="2019-01-16">
<rating votes="3">6.34</rating>
<name>Entoma Vasilissa Zeta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94887" type="appears in" update="2018-05-10">
<rating votes="4">6.85</rating>
<name>Lockmeier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33637" picture="92099.jpg">Yano Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95427" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="2">5.87</rating>
<name>Gargantua</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gargantua is the guardian of the Fourth Floor. It is a stone golem with a height of over 30m. Its arms and legs are chunky and a red glow permeates from its chest, like a heart. But unlike the other floor guardians, it has no personality or will. It is not a custom NPC like the others, but in fact, a bonus from a game administrator, given to http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz Ooal Gown] for capturing Nazarick under specific conditions.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217376.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95428" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="4">6.85</rating>
<name>Nazarick Chika Dai Funbo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Great Tomb of Nazarick is the guild headquarters of http://anidb.net/ch72785 [Ainz Ooal Gown], widely renowned for being an unconquerable dungeon throughout DMMO-RPG named Yggdrasil.
Prior to Ainz Ooal Gown conquering this dungeon, the Great Tomb of Nazarick was originally set to have only six floors. After he conquered it, the dungeon was completely reconstructed and was stretched to over ten floors. For travel between floors, there are specific points on each floor, where gates open to allow magical transit. Each floor has its own guardians as well as numerous monsters under their command.
At the start of the series, the Great Tomb of Nazarick was transported to another world along with Ainz and its custom NPCs, who also came to life as a result of this. After finding himself in an unknown world, Ainz began to strengthen the tomb and collect information to protect it from any threats.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
<picture>217377.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95429" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="3">6.11</rating>
<name>Shalltear Bloodfallen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch72780 [Shalltear]`s disguise during Operation Gehenna.
http://anidb.net/ch72782 [Demiurge] assigned her as a reserve in order to avoid causing trouble with their operation against Eight Fingers. While she was observing from afar, she encountered http://anidb.net/ch77873 [Brain Unglaus], whom she defeated in the past but forgot due to memory loss.</description>
<picture>217381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95430" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Ao no Bara</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Blue Rose is one of the only three adamantite adventurer groups in Re-Estize Kingdom, alongside Darkness and Red Drop. It is an all-female group, consisting of five members. They appear very close to one another, although, some of them occasionally end up bickering over mundane things. They were regarded as the strongest adventurers in Re-Estize, until Darkness arrived. Blue Rose is one of the few adventurer groups who were willing to take jobs that involve politics.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217388.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95431" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="3">5.08</rating>
<name>Re-Estize Oukoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Re-Estize Kingdom, commonly referred to as The Kingdom, is a human nation located to the north-west of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick]. Throughout the nation`s history, it has been plagued by corrupt and inept nobles who view commoners as mere pawns in their power plays. In recent years, they have even started to attempt to usurp the king`s authority and take control of the Kingdom. To make matters worse, the Baharuth Empire annually declares war on the Kingdom and criminal organizations are undermining the nation from within.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</character>
<character id="95432" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="3">2.31</rating>
<name>Baharuth Teikoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Baharuth Empire, commonly referred to as The Empire, is a human nation located to the east of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick]. It was once a feudal state, like the http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom], until the current Emperor established an absolute monarchy by purging many of the nobles. Under his rule, the Empire continues to gain more and more prosperity. The Empire also annually wares war with the Re-Estize Kingdom. However, these invasions are merely meant to slowly weaken the Kingdom while the Empire waits for the opportunity to conquer it with minimal losses.
The Empire became the first nation to make official contact with Nazarick. Fearing the power of its inhabitants, the Emperor chose to accept it as an independent nation while attempting to rally other human nations against it. However, this never came to be, as everyone became terrified of Nazarick`s military might. Afterwards, the Emperor submitted to Nazarick, causing the Empire to become its first vassal state.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</character>
<character id="95433" type="appears in" update="2018-09-04">
<rating votes="12">4.66</rating>
<name>Jircniv Rune Farlord El Nix</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jircniv Rune Farlord El Nix is the current Emperor of the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Empire]. He holds the nickname Bloody Emperor, for the numerous nobles he killed after his ascension to the throne. He is a calm and pragmatic person who is willing to purge anyone who gets in his way and replace them with whomever he sees as more fitting, be it a noble or a commoner.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>223200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95434" type="appears in" update="2018-09-04">
<rating votes="8">5.39</rating>
<name>Fluder Paradyne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fluder Paradyne is the imperial court wizard of the http://anidb.net/ch95432 [Empire]. He is the strongest magic caster in existence, being able to use up to tier 6 magic, the highest rank attainable by humans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>223201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95436" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Shikkoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Darkness is one of three most powerful and strongest adventurer parties in the http://anidb.net/ch95431 [Re-Estize Kingdom], with http://anidb.net/ch76797 [Momon] being its leader. They didn`t chose their name, but were rather called that way because of the color of Momon`s armor.</description>
<picture>217396.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95438" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="2">3.10</rating>
<name>Slane Houkoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Slane Theocracy, usually referred to as The Theocracy, is a human nation located to the south of http://anidb.net/ch95428 [Nazarick]. It was founded over 600 years ago by the Six Great Gods, who were heavily implied to have been players from Yggdrasil, after they led the humans in a rebellion against the dragons who had enslaved them. It is the strongest human nation around and promotes a doctrine of human supremacy and the persecution of other "lesser" races. With its goal of allowing humanity to survive in the face of the more powerful demi-human nations, the Theocracy often manipulates the affairs of other human nations for what they see as the greater good.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>217401.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95441" type="appears in" update="2018-05-11">
<rating votes="2">6.51</rating>
<name>Shikkoku Seiten</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Black Scripture is the strongest of the Six Scriptures of the http://anidb.net/ch95438 [Slane Theocracy]. It`s their trump card, a special forces unit comprising of individuals with heroic-level abilities that are utilizing the equipment originating from the arsenal of items belonging to the Six Great Gods.
Source: Overlord Wiki</description>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194281" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の軍勢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Army of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`armée de la mort</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">죽음의 군세</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Gunzei</title>
<summary>As the Lizard Men celebrate, Ains holds a conference to address the floor guardians. A proposal is presented to keep the Lizard Man tribes from being wiped out. Nazarick provides a show of force to the Lizard Men.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759349</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194282" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">集う, 蜥蜴人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lizard Men, Gathering</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`union des hommes-lézards</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">집결하는 리저드맨</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsudou, Sekiekijin</title>
<summary>Zenberu tests Zaryusu`s strength in combat, while the latter defends Crusch`s honor. The Lizardmen chiefs conduct a war council, and formulate a strategy to defend themselves against their common enemy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759347</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194283" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="15">3.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Départ</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">여행</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi</title>
<summary>The leaders of the Green Claw tribe gather to discuss their response to the threat that faces them. Zaryusu proposes an alliance with the other Lizardman tribes, and is sent to meet with the Red Eye tribe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759345</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194284" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="16">4.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望の幕開け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dawn of Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Prélude au désespoir</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">절망의 개막</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou no Makuake</title>
<summary>Officers of the Slane Theocracy gather to discuss recent losses. The noblemen of Estize plot to push back the Empire. Ains surveys a world map as his plans are set in motion. Shalltear recovers from her ordeal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759343</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195014" update="2018-01-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195202" update="2018-01-16">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の2「異世界の社員たち」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 2 "The Staff in Another World"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 이세계의 사원들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 2 Isekai no Shain-tachi""</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195203" update="2018-01-16">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の1「混乱の幕開け」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 1 "The Dawn of Confusion"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 혼란의 개막</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 1 "Konran no Makuake"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195205" update="2018-03-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195367" update="2018-03-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年の思い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Boy`s Feeling</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La détermination du jeune homme</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">소년의 마음</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen no Omoi</title>
<summary>Climb delivers Lakyus`s message to Evileye and Gagaran, who offer guidance to the young man. Climb happens upon some men beating up a boy in the street, who is then rescued by Sebas, from whom he seeks training.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759357</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195368" update="2018-03-07">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼の薔薇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Roses</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rose bleue</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">청장미</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ao no Bara</title>
<summary>Gazef finds Climb practicing with his sword outside the castle, and asks to spar with him. Renner and Lakyus examine the coded document recovered by Evileye. Sebas finds himself beset upon from all sides over Tuare.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759355</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195369" update="2018-03-07">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">拾う者, 拾われる者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Pick Up, Those Who Are Picked Up</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sauveur et sauvé</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">거둔 자, 거두어진 자</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hirou Mono, Hirowareru Mono</title>
<summary>Sebas happens upon a near-lifeless woman, and takes her under his protection. Brain, left defeated by his encounter with Shalltear, meets up with Gazef. Members of the Blue Rose take measures against a drug plantation.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759353</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195370" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷結の武神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Freezing God</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Divinité glaciaire</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">빙결 무신</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyouketsu no Bushin</title>
<summary>At the outpost in the Tob Forest, Ains strategizes with his guardians, and imposes Shalltear`s penance upon her. The Lizard Man chiefs assemble and receive Cocytus on the battlefield for their final showdown.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759351</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195396" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の5「評決の部長」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 5 "The Manager of Verdict"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 평결의 부장</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 5 "Hyouketsu no Buchou"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195397" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の4「凄い忠誠」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 4 "Great Loyalty"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 굉장한 충성</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 4 "Sugoi Chuusei"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195398" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の3「集う, 幹部」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 3 "Executives, Gathering"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 집결하는 간부들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 3 "Tsudou, Kanbu"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196098" update="2018-03-07">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の9「舞い上がる人ら」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 9 "Soaring Spirits of People"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 피어오르는 사람</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 9 "Maiagaru Hitora"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196099" update="2018-03-07">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の8「顧客の思い」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 8 "Customers` Feeling"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 고객의 마음</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 8 "Kokyaku no Omoi"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196100" update="2018-03-07">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の7「ばらばら」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 7 "Out of Order"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 따로따로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 7 "Barabara"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196101" update="2018-03-07">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の6「拾う者たち」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 6 "Those Who Pick Up"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 거두는 자들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 6 "Hirou Mono-tachi"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196449" update="2018-04-03">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強最高の切り札</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Trump Card</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le plus puissant des atouts</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">최강 최고의 비장의 수</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou Saikou no Kirifuda</title>
<summary>The guardsmen and adventurers face a daunting array of demons until Momon arrives and takes charge. Brain once again comes face to face with Shalltear. While Evileye is occupied, Demiurge reveals his plan to Ains.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>767443</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196450" update="2018-03-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">動乱最終決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Battle of the Disturbance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataille décisive à la capitale</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">동란 최종결전</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Douran Saishuu Kessen</title>
<summary>Evileye petitions Momon to help her, and he begins fighting the disguised Demiurge. As Climb and the others try to get Tuare out of the compound, they face resistance. Renner convenes an emergency strategy meeting.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>765657</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196451" update="2018-03-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤルダバオト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jaldabaoth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jaldabaoth</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">얄다바오트</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jaldabaoth</title>
<summary>Demiurge takes charge of Nazarick`s forces, laying out the mission to strike at Eight Fingers. Meanwhile, Lakyus details a similar mission to her squad captains. Sebas, Climb, and Brain raid Six Arms` compound together.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>765655</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196452" update="2018-03-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">王都動乱序章</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disturbance Begins in the Royal Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Prélude à la révolte de la capitale</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">왕도 동란 서장</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Outo Douran Joshou</title>
<summary>Ains calls on Sebas to answer for his actions, and to discuss what is to become of Tuare. Renner meets with the Blue Rose, then Marquis Raeven, to consult with them about her planned attacks against Eight Fingers.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>765653</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196453" update="2018-03-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞い上がる火の粉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soaring Sparks of Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ces étincelles qui virevoltent</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">흩날리는 불똥</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maiagaru Hinoko</title>
<summary>Sebas begins his raid of the brothel from one side, while Climb and Brain enter from the other. While Climb covers the exit alone, he is confronted by Succulent and Cocco Doll trying to flee, and a desperate fight begins.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759359</identifier>
<identifier>overlord</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197024" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の10「おっとどうなんでしょう」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 10 "Oh Dear, I Wonder"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 이런 어떨까요</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 10 "Otto Dou Nan Deshou"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197198" update="2018-03-20">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の11「ヤバイヤツダ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 11 "Jackass"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 위험한 녀석이다</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 11 "Yabai Yatsu Da"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197517" update="2018-03-27">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の12「業界動乱序章」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 12 "Introduction of Industry Disturbance"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 업계 동란 서장</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 12 "Gyoukai Douran Joshou"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197728" update="2018-04-03">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ぷれぷれぷれあです2】ぷれ2の13「絶望の幕開けへ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 Ch 13 "To the Dawn of Despair"</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플레플레 플레이아데스 2: 절망의 개막으로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ple-Ple-Pleiades 2: Ple 2 no 13 "Zetsubou no Makuake e"</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
