<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13038" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-11-25</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Itsudatte Bokura no Koi wa 10 Centi Datta.</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">告白実行委員会シリーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">We Have Always Been 10 cm Apart.</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">いつだって僕らの恋は10センチだった.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Our Love Has Always Been 10 Centimeters Apart.</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">언제나 우리의 사랑은 10cm였다.</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我们的爱总是只有10厘米。</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11376" type="Prequel">Zutto Mae kara Suki Deshita. Kokuhaku Jikkouiinkai</anime>
<anime id="12041" type="Other">Suki ni Naru Sono Shunkan o. Kokuhaku Jikkouiinkai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4568" approval="1" total="7">Byousoku 5 Centimeter</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.honeyworks-movie.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="42709" type="Animation Work">Lay-duce</name>
<name id="6242" type="Character Design">Fujii Maki</name>
<name id="17298" type="Character Design">Tokiwa Kentarou</name>
<name id="2169" type="Series Composition">Narita Yoshimi</name>
<name id="38009" type="Original Work">HoneyWorks</name>
<name id="27375" type="Direction">Tsukada Takurou</name>
<name id="5732" type="Chief Direction">Nanba Hitoshi</name>
<name id="38009" type="Music">HoneyWorks</name>
</creators>
<description>Under the cherry blossom tree at Sakuragaoka High School`s Entrance Ceremony, Miou Aida meets Haruki Serizawa for the first time. Ever since that day, their eyes chased after each other. Miou is reserved, while Haruki is very social. While many mistook them as a couple, their relationship remained a little more than friends. As they stop to sit on the steps of a deck on their walk home, Miou cannot help but ask, "Haruki...do you like anyone?" Haruki replies, "I do like someone ...what about you?" Just 10 centimeters between their hands. It`s just 10 centimeters, but the distance remains...
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="388">5.69</permanent>
<temporary count="388">6.64</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>211374.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20055</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36220</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.honeyworks-movie.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kokuhaku_Jikkō_Iinkai_~Ren'ai_Series~</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>告白実行委員会〜恋愛シリーズ〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4757</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361700</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20551</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>HoneyWorksMovie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>our-love-has-always-been-10-centimeters-apart</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="165" parentid="2883" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>painting</name>
<description>Painting is the practice of applying paint, pigment, color or other medium[1] to a surface (support base). The medium is commonly applied to the base with a brush but other implements, such as knives, sponges, and airbrushes, can be used.
In art, the term painting describes both the act and the result of the action. Paintings may have for their support such surfaces as walls, paper, canvas, wood, glass, lacquer, clay, leaf, copper or concrete, and may incorporate multiple other materials including sand, clay, paper, gold leaf as well as objects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2978" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-28">
<name>aim for the top</name>
<description>This can be a positive or negative plot device. A character may strive to become the best in an altruistic way (e.g. best healer, most widely learned master), or it can be quite banal and primitive (e.g. challenged delinquents wanting to be the strongest fighters).
Alas in fighting anime the latter usually prevails.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3946" parentid="2883" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-15">
<name>filmmaking</name>
<description>Filmmaking is the process of making a film. This may be tied to studios with very large budgets or to inexpensive independent products alike, and even to amateur films; modern technology allows people to film events of significance in their lives, such as their marriages. Anime in school settings may have a film club, which sometimes produce their own films for e.g. the school culture festival.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="76332" type="main character in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="8">6.29</rating>
<name>Aida Miou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76333" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="10">5.44</rating>
<name>Hayasaka Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76334" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="4">3.99</rating>
<name>Mochizuki Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76335" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="15">7.03</rating>
<name>Enomoto Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76336" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="5">3.89</rating>
<name>Setoguchi Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76337" type="main character in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="5">4.97</rating>
<name>Serizawa Haruki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78248" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="2">7.24</rating>
<name>Akechi Saki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="192762" update="2017-12-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">卒業, 旅立ち, 未来の色.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Graduation, Adventures, Color of the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Diplôme, départ et la couleur du futur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sotsugyou, Tabidachi, Mirai no Iro.</title>
<summary>Graduation is finally here, and everyone is ready to move on as Miou decides her future career, and Haruki is ready to embark on a new adventure. But before that, will Haruki and Miou`s ten centimeter gap finally close?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>755167</identifier>
<identifier>our-love-has-always-been-10-centimeters-apart</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192763" update="2017-12-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初雪, 夢, 涙の色.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Snow, Dreams, Color of Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Première neige, rêves et la couleur des larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsuyuki, Yume, Namida no Iro.</title>
<summary>Haruki has not come to school for a few days and everyone is starting to get worried. Miou is determined to finish her “painting of love” and talk to Haruki about an unfortunate event that happened in the past. “I’ll wait as long as it takes” she says, as the first snow of the season begins to fall.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>755165</identifier>
<identifier>our-love-has-always-been-10-centimeters-apart</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192764" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">留学, 未来図, 心の色.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Study Abroad, Map of the Future, Color of the Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Études à l`étranger, avenir et la couleur du cœur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuugaku, Mirai Zu, Kokoro no Iro.</title>
<summary>Miou shuts herself off from Haruki and her friends, due to the guilt she is feeling. It’s up to Natsuki and Akari to find out why their friend is so sad. Some memories from the past start to resurface for Haruki and causes him to question his dream of becoming a film director.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>755163</identifier>
<identifier>our-love-has-always-been-10-centimeters-apart</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192765" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密, 孤独, 夕暮れ色.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret, Solitude, Color of Twilight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Secret, solitude et la couleur du crépuscule</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu, Kodoku, Yuugure-iro.</title>
<summary>The deadline for the “painting of love” is here and Haruki will need to make a choice. Meanwhile, Miou struggles with her feelings towards Haruki, further complicated by discovering the identity of the man who saved her her life when she was young.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>755161</identifier>
<identifier>our-love-has-always-been-10-centimeters-apart</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192766" update="2017-12-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏, 花火, 恋の色.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer, Fireworks, Color of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Été, feu d`artifice et la couleur de l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu, Hanabi, Koi no Iro.</title>
<summary>The Movie Club members ask the Art Club to help them out with their last film before graduation. They need to create a piece that depicts the theme of “love.” But what exactly is the color of love?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>755159</identifier>
<identifier>our-love-has-always-been-10-centimeters-apart</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192767" update="2017-11-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">春, 初恋, 桜色.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring, First Love, Color of Cherry Blossoms</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Printemps, premier amour et cerisiers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru, Hatsukoi, Sakurairo.</title>
<summary>In the Spring of their first year of high school, Haruki and Miou meet for the first time under the cherry blossoms. Afterwards, they grow close as they spend time and walk home together. Their relationship is so close that everyone thinks they’re dating, but will they be able to put their feelings into words?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>755157</identifier>
<identifier>our-love-has-always-been-10-centimeters-apart</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194768" update="2018-01-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194769" update="2018-01-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198761" update="2018-05-06">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンディング主題歌「東京ウインターセッション」ミュージックビデオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Theme Song "Tokyo Winter Session" MV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ending Shudaika "Tokyo Winter Session" Music Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198762" update="2018-05-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">オープニング主題歌「ノンファンタジー」ミュージックビデオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Theme Song "Non Fantasy" MV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Opening Shudaika "Non Fantasy" Music Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
