<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13030" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Konohana Kitan</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">此花亭奇譚</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">此花亭奇谭</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">このはな綺譚</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Konohana Kitan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Konohana Kitan</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">코노하나 기담</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">此花綺譚</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">此花绮谭</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7874" approval="27" total="29">Hanasaku Iroha</anime>
<anime id="11985" approval="22" total="26">Urara Meirochou</anime>
<anime id="13362" approval="13" total="19">Hakumei to Mikochi</anime>
<anime id="13564" approval="8" total="8">Kakuriyo no Yadomeshi</anime>
<anime id="13875" approval="3" total="4">Wakaokami wa Shougakusei!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="317942">A cute and heartwarming story. Highly recommended for days when you are feeling down.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="279344">This tugged at my heartstrings. Warm, cute, funny, emotional, every episode rich with all these feelings.

If I have to compare this to other older and known anime, I`d take Hanasaku Iroha`s environment and add the awesomeness and mysteriousness of Aria (the Animation). Perfect fit.

Enjoyed this anime A LOT and I am sure I will come back to it again. Can`t wait.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://konohanatei.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="27220" type="Animation Work">Lerche</name>
<name id="20777" type="Character Design">Kurosawa Keiko</name>
<name id="3730" type="Series Composition">Yoshioka Takao</name>
<name id="7569" type="Direction">Okamoto Hideki</name>
<name id="49355" type="Original Work">Amano Sakuya</name>
<name id="2240" type="Music">Kikuchi Hajime</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a fantasy slice of life manga written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr49355 [Amano Sakuya].
In a village inhabited by Youkai, the lives of several fox mononoke working in a hot spring inn. The stories revolve around a new employee, http://anidb.net/ch90639 [Yuzu]. Yuzu had always been living in the mountains, but now has to adjust to a new life working in a high class inn. She is oblivious and clumsy at first, but with her simple cuteness, she is able to get along with all the other foxes.
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="748">6.75</permanent>
<temporary count="754">7.18</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221608.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19812</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35241</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://konohanatei.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Konohana_Kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>此花亭奇譚</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4680</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360260</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20529</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>konohana_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07KTBG3DF</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="362" parentid="2793" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-24">
<name>dancing</name>
<description>Dance is when people move their body to music. There are many kinds of dance, like ballet or waltz. Dancing can be done for fun but can be also an art.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1298" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>drawing</name>
<description>The art or technique of representing an object or outlining a figure, plan, or sketch by means of lines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1543" parentid="1482" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-25">
<name>sumo wrestling</name>
<description>Sumo wrestling is a competitive full-contact wrestling sport where a rikishi (wrestler) attempts to force another wrestler out of a circular ring (dohyou) or into touching the ground with anything other than the soles of his feet.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206585.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2391" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>bishoujo</name>
<description>In Japanese, a bishoujo is any pretty female from toddlerhood to late adolescence. In the West, the word specifically refers to attractive girls generally from late childhood or early adolescence, especially those that appeal to males, and particularly to fictional characters designed in a way traditionally associated to shoujo manga. Fictional bishoujo tend to be cute, pastel-coloured teenagers; they lack the sophistication of older women, instead having detailed eye and hair design, fluttery costumes often including ribbons, and all sorts of generally sparkly fluff.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3363" parentid="2876" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-04">
<name>Buddhism</name>
<description>Buddhism is a nontheistic religion or dharma, "right way of living", that encompasses a variety of traditions, beliefs and practices largely based on teachings attributed to Siddhartha Gautama, commonly known as the Buddha ("the awakened one").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169453.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3504" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>sake</name>
<description>Sake, generally referred to as a Japanese rice wine, is an alcoholic beverage made by fermenting rice.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215208.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4413" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-16">
<name>heaven</name>
<description>Heaven, the Heavens or Seven Heavens, is a common religious, cosmological or transcendent place from which heavenly beings (such as a God, angels, the jinn, and sky deities like King or Queen of Heaven, Heavenly Father, Heavenly Mother, Son of Heaven, heavenly saints or venerated ancestors) originate, are enthroned or inhabit.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5779" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-18">
<name>anachronisms</name>
<description>Customs, events, or objects are shown in a period to which they do not belong, e.g. jet planes in medieval Japan.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5914" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-05">
<name>afterlife</name>
<description>The afterlife is the continued existence of an essential part of an individual`s identity or consciousness after the death of the body. When people continue existing beyond the death of their physical bodies, they may or may not keep interacting with the realm of the living and/or retain their memories. It is possible for them to start a new life without a physical body in a spirit realm, and they may or may not be able to understand that they`re already dead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5970" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-17">
<name>Urashima Tarou</name>
<description>A Japanese legend about a fisherman, Urashima Tarou, who rescues a turtle, the daughter of the emperor of the sea, Ryuujin, from being bullied by children. Upon this, the princess Otohime - previously the turtle - rewards him with a visit to the Dragon God`s palace. He stays there for three days but, upon his return to his village, he finds himself in a strange world that is actually 300 years in the future, as time passed differently in the palace.
The anime or episode is either completely devoted to depicting the tale of Urashima Tarou or contains important references to this tale.</description>
<picurl>169472.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6028" parentid="2876" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-10-12">
<name>Shintoism</name>
<description>Shintoism presents a blessed being or creature that governs over areas of terrain, general space of existence, or an individual object (be it alive or inanimate). Everything has its own "spiritual essence".
Defined as the earliest Japanese thoughts of an unified religion, the word Shinto comes from the Chinese hanzi "神道", combining two kanji: "shin" (神), meaning gods or spirits; and "tō" (道), meaning a philosophical path or study.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6184" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>autumn</name>
<description>Autumn, interchangeably known as fall in the US and Canada, is one of the four temperate seasons. Autumn marks the transition from summer into winter, in September (Northern Hemisphere) or March (Southern Hemisphere), when the arrival of night becomes noticeably earlier and the temperature cools considerably. One of its main features is the shedding of leaves from deciduous trees.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161967.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7089" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-28">
<name>Kamakura</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="90639" type="main character in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="24">9.08</rating>
<name>Yuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuzu is an innocent and loving foxgirl who has grown up with a http://anidb.net/ch91585 [nun], and just arrived at Konohanatei to expand her horizons. She has great respect for everyone around her, but takes a particular liking to http://anidb.net/ch90643 [Satsuki]. A healing character, she brightens up the visitors` days.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>205574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46495" picture="225573.jpg">Oono Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90640" type="main character in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="12">6.50</rating>
<name>Kiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiri is a relaxed, older foxgirl who is the head of all the others. She appears to be laid back but has an emotionally-intelligent side, seeming to have lots of experience in dealing with others. Is secretly fond of http://anidb.net/ch90642 [Sakura] and acts as her caretaker.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>205579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90641" type="main character in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="13">5.78</rating>
<name>Natsume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsume is a tomboyish foxgirl that would easily pass as male. She has an exuberant and playful personality, but can be quite dedicated and courageous at times. She is quite protective of http://anidb.net/ch90644 [Ren], but gets along with everyone else.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>205576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34407" picture="202909.jpg">Suwa Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90642" type="main character in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="14">5.32</rating>
<name>Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura is a tiny foxgirl who is mysterious and idiosyncratic. Her thoughts are seldom known and she always seems to be doing weird, genius-like things. She spends some time with http://anidb.net/ch90639 [Yuzu] since they`re both the smallest, but secretly seems to trust http://anidb.net/ch90640 [Kiri] the most.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>205578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90643" type="main character in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="21">7.21</rating>
<name>Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satsuki is a serious-minded foxgirl and a bit of a workaholic. Deep down, she is quite sensitive, hoping to become a http://anidb.net/t1663 [miko] someday. Nevertheless, this only makes her work harder at Konohanatei to make up for her feelings of incompetence. She is quite fond of http://anidb.net/ch90639 [Yuzu], but not very good at showing it.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>205575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32471" picture="173756.jpg">Hata Sawako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90644" type="main character in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="14">4.88</rating>
<name>Ren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ren is a feminine and perfectionistic foxgirl who seeks solace in being beautiful and performing well in her work. She is afraid of men due to childhood traumas of being bullied by them, but seems to see http://anidb.net/ch90641 [Natsume] as her `boyfriend` figure.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>205577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46602" picture="224736.jpg">Kubota Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91585" type="appears in" update="2017-10-09">
<rating votes="6">6.29</rating>
<name>Yao Bikuni</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yao Bikuni is a nun that took care of http://anidb.net/ch90639 [Yuzu] when she was young and brought her up. She`s an old acquaintance of the Konohanatei`s owner, to whom she entrusted Yuzu.</description>
<picture>208112.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91586" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-15">
<rating votes="4">8.22</rating>
<name>Tsubaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsubaki, often referred to as Okami by http://anidb.net/ch90640 [Kiri], is the owner of Konohanatei. She was the one that http://anidb.net/ch90639 [Yuzu] got entrusted to by http://anidb.net/ch91585 [Yao Bikuni]. Even though she might appear that way, she`s kind and caring towards her employees, especially noticeable when she threatened one guest to leave the Konohanatai because he was molesting http://anidb.net/ch90644 [Ren].</description>
<picture>209700.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92139" type="appears in" update="2017-11-04">
<rating votes="4">6.40</rating>
<name>Okiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Okiku is a cursed doll that was brought into Konohanatei by some priest. Compared to regular Japanese dolls, she talks, moves and her hair grows. Before that, she was given to a certain girl by her grandma as a present for being firstborn. Her family found her creepy at times and, due to that, they put her away in the shed for several seasons.
Once she arrived at the Konohanatei, girls made her new clothes and http://anidb.net/ch90644 [Ren] fixed her hair and makeup. She became attendant and was often bullied by http://anidb.net/ch90642 [Sakura] for fun.</description>
<picture>209243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92140" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-04">
<rating votes="10">6.78</rating>
<name>Hiiragi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiiragi is http://anidb.net/ch90643 [Satsuki]`s older sister and a priestess.</description>
<picture>209244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5036" picture="153265.jpg">Ikebe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92141" type="appears in" update="2017-11-05">
<rating votes="2">6.17</rating>
<name>Urinosuke</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Urinosuke is a creature that looks like wild boar piglet, that hatched from an egg which got attached to http://anidb.net/ch90644 [Ren] and http://anidb.net/ch90643 [Satsuki]. It occasionally feeds on nightmares of the residents of Konohanatai.
According to http://anidb.net/ch90639 [Yuzu], Urinosuke could be baku - supernatural being that devours dreams and nightmares in Japanese folklore.</description>
<picture>209245.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92142" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="4">4.60</rating>
<name>Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23608" picture="65179.jpg">Mochizuki Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92461" type="appears in" update="2017-11-25">
<rating votes="4">5.42</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34984" picture="222849.jpg">Ueda Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92462" type="appears in" update="2017-11-25">
<rating votes="4">4.76</rating>
<name>Tanabe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92463" type="appears in" update="2017-11-25">
<rating votes="3">4.72</rating>
<name>Kaito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92464" type="appears in" update="2017-11-25">
<rating votes="2">2.74</rating>
<name>Kaito no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41289" picture="186235.jpg">Kanemasa Ikuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92465" type="appears in" update="2017-11-25">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Takahashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10413" picture="38405.jpg">Nakamura Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92468" type="appears in" update="2017-11-25">
<rating votes="2">4.32</rating>
<name>Rei no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92469" type="appears in" update="2017-11-25">
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<name>Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92470" type="appears in" update="2017-11-25">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Kaito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209902.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92553" type="appears in" update="2017-11-29">
<rating votes="4">4.74</rating>
<name>Awanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92554" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="2">2.17</rating>
<name>Kame</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3823" picture="223449.jpg">Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92800" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="2">5.22</rating>
<name>Kusuriya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2067" picture="186243.jpg">Hoshino Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92801" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<name>Nezumi Oyabun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210723.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92802" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="4">3.99</rating>
<name>Hanamaki Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is one of two sisters that http://anidb.net/ch90639 [Yuzu] stumbled into, who serves the gods of Takamagahara, ensuring the well-being of Nakatsukuni.</description>
<picture>210724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92804" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="4">3.18</rating>
<name>Hanamaki Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is one of two sisters that http://anidb.net/ch90643 [Satsuki] stumbled into, who serves the gods of Takamagahara, ensuring the well-being of Nakatsukuni.</description>
<picture>210726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92805" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="2">2.17</rating>
<name>Neko Tenshu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30040" picture="195187.jpg">Kanda Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92806" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="2">2.74</rating>
<name>Kappa no Kyaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10413" picture="38405.jpg">Nakamura Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92807" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="3">4.03</rating>
<name>Aoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32911" picture="230127.jpg">Furuki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92808" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Rou Gitsune Otto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92809" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Rou Gitsune Tsuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3770" picture="228624.jpg">Hatori Yasuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92810" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="2">2.74</rating>
<name>Kyaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10413" picture="38405.jpg">Nakamura Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92811" type="appears in" update="2018-03-25">
<rating votes="4">4.76</rating>
<name>Hataori no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is one the weaver sisters who resided in the weaving shed near Konohanatei as well as one of the guests. http://anidb.net/ch92139 [Okiku] and http://anidb.net/ch90639 [Yuzu] were supposed to bring her lunch only to find out that she didn`t finish her breakfast yet.
Her attitude towards the two was cold at first, but after several tries, girl finally told them what was wrong. She mentioned that her older sister is the fastest among them, while her younger sister makes the finest fabric. Unfortunately for her, she is somewhere in the middle and her wish is that one day she`ll be best among them.</description>
<picture>210733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1445" picture="33610.jpg">Takamoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92812" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Oshou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92813" type="appears in" update="2017-12-15">
<rating votes="2">3.46</rating>
<name>Yohei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5887" picture="203017.jpg">Nagano Yoshikazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93109" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Ikusa no Kami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93110" type="appears in" update="2019-04-01">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Geinou no Kami A</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93111" type="appears in" update="2019-04-01">
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<name>Geinou no Kami B</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93112" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="3">5.61</rating>
<name>Tsubaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch91586 [Tsubaki], after applying her makeup.</description>
<picture>211489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93113" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Kareshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10413" picture="38405.jpg">Nakamura Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93114" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46284" picture="188357.jpg">Shiraki Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93115" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="2">4.42</rating>
<name>Lily</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29667" picture="223460.jpg">Maeda Rena</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93116" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Tsubaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch91586 [Tsubaki], as she appeared before http://anidb.net/ch90639 [Yuzu] when she got caught in a different time line where Konohanatei doesn`t exist yet.</description>
<picture>211493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93117" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29850" picture="203454.jpg">Nakamura Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93118" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29850" picture="203454.jpg">Nakamura Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93119" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Tsukushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39007" picture="148258.jpg">Ozawa Ari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93120" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="2">2.81</rating>
<name>Uka no Mitama no Kami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93121" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Kaeru</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93122" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Tome-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41289" picture="186235.jpg">Kanemasa Ikuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93123" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Rouba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211507.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5352" picture="134103.jpg">Tani Ikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93126" type="appears in" update="2018-01-01">
<rating votes="3">6.86</rating>
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46284" picture="188357.jpg">Shiraki Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93129" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30040" picture="195187.jpg">Kanda Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93130" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Kyaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41289" picture="186235.jpg">Kanemasa Ikuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93131" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Satsuki no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93132" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Satsuki no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30040" picture="195187.jpg">Kanda Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93133" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Usagi A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211534.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30040" picture="195187.jpg">Kanda Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93134" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Usagi B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211535.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46284" picture="188357.jpg">Shiraki Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93135" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<name>Kaguya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211536.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93136" type="appears in" update="2018-01-02">
<rating votes="2">4.42</rating>
<name>Yanagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211537.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37280" picture="136935.jpg">Oozora Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="190912" update="2017-10-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の浮き橋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raft Bridge of Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pont où flottent les rêves</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">꿈의 부교</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Ukihashi</title>
<summary>Konohanatei is visited by two strange beings: a mystery egg, to which Ren wakes up found fixed to her belly, and a fast-growing child, and an elderly lady who appears to be her grandmother.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749201</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190913" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋待ち焦がれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Waiting Lovesick</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`attends l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">사랑 애타게 기다리며</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Machikogare</title>
<summary>One of the guests, Aoi, seems to have developed a crush on Natsume. Ren isn`t amused.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749199</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190914" update="2017-10-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">春の旅路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le voyage du printemps</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">봄의 여행길</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru no Tabiji</title>
<summary>Satsuki gets a well-deserved day off, but she doesn`t appreciate it as much as she should. As it turns out, there`s a reason.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749197</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190915" update="2017-10-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくやこのはな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakuya Konohana</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pavillon où s`épanouissent les fleurs</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">이 꽃이 피었다</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakuya Konohana</title>
<summary>Yuzu is the new live-in employee at Konohanatei, a hot spring hotel run by fox girls. It`s tough work, but she makes new friends, and gets plenty of help adjusting.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749195</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191443" update="2018-06-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191444" update="2018-06-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191909" update="2017-12-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かりそめの訪客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Transient Guest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un client de passage</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">잠깐 동안의 손님</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karisome no Houkyaku</title>
<summary>It’s a castaway! It’s a mermaid! Actually, it’s a troubled human girl, one of several people who have wandered into the inn’s presence recently.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749209</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191910" update="2017-12-05">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏祭りの夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night of the Summer Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">여름 축제의 밤</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Matsuri no Yoru</title>
<summary>The bon festival is here, and the attendants take turns off work to check it out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749207</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191911" update="2017-11-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">此花亭怪談</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Konohanatei Horror Stories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les histoires de fantômes du Pavillon des Fleurs</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">코노하나정 괴담</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konohana Tei Kaidan</title>
<summary>The girls spend a night sharing horror stories. Just as the boss yells at them for being up past bedtime, they count an extra member in the group.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749205</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191912" update="2017-11-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">梅雨送りし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spring Rains Bring with It</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Accompagner la saison des pluies</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">장마 보내기</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baiu Okurishi</title>
<summary>A priest brings an odd Japanese doll to Konohanatei. Not only is the doll cursed, she seems to have an attitude.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749203</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192946" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大晦日の奇跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Miracle on New Year`s Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le miracle du jour de l`An</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">섣달그믐의 기적</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oomisoka no Kiseki</title>
<summary>The Konohanatei gang visit the shrine for New Year’s Eve. Yuzu gets lost again, but she makes some new friends as she tries to find her way home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749217</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192947" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神様の休日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A God`s Day Off</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour de vacances des dieux</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">신님의 휴일</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamisama no Kyuujitsu</title>
<summary>One of Sakura’s regulars visits Konohanatei, followed by two gods of entertainment. Things get really busy at Konohanatei.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749215</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192948" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">姉上襲来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sister Strikes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`attaque de la grande sœur</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">언니 습격</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aneue Shuurai</title>
<summary>Satsuki accidentally gets herself shrunken down. Her sister makes a visit, mostly to tease her, but also to bring what could be sad news for the rest of Konohanatei.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749213</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192949" update="2017-12-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">泡沫[うたかた]の...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evanescent...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`éphémère...</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">물거품의...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utakata no...</title>
<summary>The goddess of water bubbles pays a visit to Konohanatei. The reason for her stay doesn’t become clear until it’s a little too late.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749211</identifier>
<identifier>konohana-kitan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193835" update="2018-06-03">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193836" update="2018-06-03">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193837" update="2018-06-03">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200721" update="2018-06-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
