<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13199" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Just Because!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ジャストビコーズ!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Just Because!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Just Because!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Just Because!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12761" approval="12" total="15">Tsuki ga Kirei</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://justbecause.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="32834" type="Series Composition">Kamoshida Hajime</name>
<name id="15726" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takada Akira</name>
<name id="44448" type="Animation Work">Pine Jam</name>
<name id="9905" type="Character Design">Yoshii Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="25571" type="Direction">Kobayashi Atsushi</name>
<name id="52181" type="Music">Fukasawa Erika</name>
<name id="29595" type="Music">Yanagi Nagi</name>
</creators>
<description>It is winter of their third year of high school, near the end of second semester, when students have very little time in high school left. Everyone was just waiting for graduation.
Until http://anidb.net/ch89589 [he] suddenly came home.
He was their classmate in middle school that had moved far away. His transferred in at a peculiar time, which reunited them. It was as if it were a go signal rang out to the feelings of the students who had just thought to end their high school life without fanfare.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="843">5.51</permanent>
<temporary count="845">6.76</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>206720.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19945</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35639</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://justbecause.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Just_Because!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Just_Because!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4679</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360812</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20528</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>JustBecause_JP</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0765NVW1L</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3947" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-04">
<name>cram school</name>
<description>Cram schools ("juku" in Japan) are specialized schools that train their students to meet particular goals, most commonly to pass the entrance examinations of high schools or universities. The English name is derived from the slang term "cramming", meaning to study hard or to study a large amount of material in a short period of time.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6840" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-07">
<name>social media</name>
<description>Social media are computer-mediated technologies that allow the creating and sharing of information, ideas, career interests and other forms of expression via virtual communities and networks.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89589" type="main character in" update="2017-08-19">
<rating votes="8">4.56</rating>
<name>Izumi Eita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52057" picture="225903.jpg">Ichikawa Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89590" type="main character in" update="2017-08-19">
<rating votes="6">4.16</rating>
<name>Souma Haruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89591" type="main character in" update="2017-08-19">
<rating votes="26">6.52</rating>
<name>Natsume Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42353" picture="243221.jpg">Isobe Karin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89592" type="main character in" update="2017-08-19">
<rating votes="13">6.56</rating>
<name>Morikawa Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42648" picture="207956.jpg">Yoshino Yuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89593" type="main character in" update="2017-08-19">
<rating votes="37">6.60</rating>
<name>Komiya Ena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91672" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-06">
<rating votes="6">5.61</rating>
<name>Inui Yoriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46412" picture="207957.jpg">Sakuraba Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91673" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-06">
<rating votes="1">3.01</rating>
<name>Takahashi Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47010" picture="223717.jpg">Nukui Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91674" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-06">
<rating votes="2">6.38</rating>
<name>Suzuki Momoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43914" picture="225361.jpg">Kondou Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91675" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-06">
<rating votes="1">1.89</rating>
<name>Satou Mayuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91676" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-06">
<rating votes="3">2.17</rating>
<name>Saruwatari Junpei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40642" picture="62085.png">Amasaki Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91677" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-06">
<rating votes="1">3.01</rating>
<name>Ishigaki Rikuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21337" picture="207958.jpg">Yamamoto Shouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91678" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-06">
<rating votes="1">3.01</rating>
<name>Shimizu Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10906" picture="200861.jpg">Yanagita Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91679" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-06">
<rating votes="1">3.01</rating>
<name>Yamaguchi Kaoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41754" picture="181639.jpg">Kobayashi Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91680" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-06">
<rating votes="1">3.01</rating>
<name>Watanabe-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188099" update="2017-06-30">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190920" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Full swing</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Full Swing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Full Swing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Full Swing</title>
<summary>Emotions run high as Haruto feels emboldened enough to finally confess his feelings, but will his words be able to reach the one he cares about?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190921" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Andante</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Andante</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Andante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Andante</title>
<summary>The group reconnects after their trip to the aquarium but things take an unexpected turn when Ena takes an interest in Eita.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190922" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Question</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Question</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Question</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Question</title>
<summary>Haruto works up the courage to ask out Morikawa but does his confession go as well as he had envisioned it?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190923" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">On your marks!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On Your Marks!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À vos marques!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">On Your Marks!</title>
<summary>The end of high school is near for a group of students but their yearning for reconnection might change the course of their lives.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191644" update="2018-08-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191645" update="2017-10-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191950" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">High Dynamic Range</title>
<title xml:lang="en">High Dynamic Range</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">High Dynamic Range</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">High Dynamic Range</title>
<summary>Ena finally decides to ask Eita on a date despite Mio`s objection. Everything seems to be going well until Mio bumps into them.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191951" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Snow day</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Snow Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Snow Day</title>
<summary>Mio remembers Eita`s kindness in middle school and starts to question her relationship with him. What will happen as Ena begins to spend more time with Eita?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191952" update="2017-11-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Restart</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Restart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Restart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Restart</title>
<summary>Tension is on the rise, as Haruto seeks guidance from Eita, on how to respond to Hazuki`s message.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191953" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Rolling stones</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rolling Stones</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rolling Stones</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rolling Stones</title>
<summary>Things change between Haruto and Hazuki, and both of them try to deal with it in their own way. Mio, on the other hand, is trying to come to terms with her feelings.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="192286" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ「Just Because!」ヒミツの課外授業SP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Just Because!" Himitsu no Kagaijugyou SP</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192725" update="2017-11-09">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふらり, Just Because! の旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furaki, Just Because! no Tabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193022" update="2017-11-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Get set, go!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Set, Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Get set, Go! – Prêts, partez !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Get Set, Go!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193023" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Roundabout</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roundabout</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Roundabout – Rond-point</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roundabout</title>
<summary>As entrance exams rear their head, Eita can`t help but remember Mio`s expression when she noticed his phone. What will happen as their paths start to diverge?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193024" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Childhood`s end</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Childhood`s End</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Childhood`s End – La fin de l`enfance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Childhood`s End</title>
<summary>Eita seems to be coming to terms with his feelings. In the meantime, Mio is starting to learn what is truly important to her.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193025" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Answer</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Answer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Answer – Réponse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Answer</title>
<summary>Mio finally chooses to confront her demons. In the meantime, Eita is working through his own dilemma with Ena.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203771" update="2018-08-05">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203772" update="2018-08-05">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203773" update="2018-08-05">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203774" update="2018-08-05">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
