<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13619" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-07-04</startdate>
<enddate>2018-09-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Back Street Girls: Gokudols</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">バックストリートガールズ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gokudolls</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Back Street Girls -ゴクドルズ-</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">백 스트리트 걸스: 조폭 아이돌</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">后街女孩</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://backstreetgirls-anime.toeiad.co.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1482" type="Direction">Kon Chiaki</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="52820" type="Original Work">Jasmine Gyuh</name>
<name id="50649" type="Music">Gesshoku Kaigi</name>
<name id="55587" type="Series Composition">Yamakawa Susumu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a gender bender comedy seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr52820 [Jasmine Gyuh].
A group of three yakuza failed their boss for the last time. After messing up an important job, the boss gives them two choices: honorably committing suicide, or going to Thailand to get a sex reassignment surgery in order to become female idols. After a gruesome year-long training to become idols, they successfully debut with overwhelming popularity, much to their dismay. This is where their tragedy truly begins.
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="335">4.44</permanent>
<temporary count="339">6.12</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221819.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20851</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36873</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://backstreetgirls-anime.toeiad.co.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Back_Street_Girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Back_Street_Girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4957</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363605</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21193</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>inuganekikaku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3550" parentid="6021" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-05">
<name>sex change</name>
<description>Someone in this anime has his/her body changed to the opposite gender.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4606" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>slide show animation</name>
<description>The entire anime or parts of it show sequences of still images. Sometimes used in low budged animations for action scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5936" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>uniform fetish</name>
<description>Focuses on many different kinds of, often sexy, uniforms.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="96097" type="main character in" update="2018-07-15">
<rating votes="2">6.94</rating>
<name>Yamamoto Airi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47010" picture="223717.jpg">Nukui Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96098" type="main character in" update="2018-07-15">
<rating votes="2">6.94</rating>
<name>Sugihara Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46676" picture="215636.jpg">Akao Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96099" type="main character in" update="2018-07-15">
<rating votes="2">6.94</rating>
<name>Tachibana Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53513" picture="229081.jpg">Maeda Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96100" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-15">
<name>Yamamoto Kentarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96101" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-15">
<name>Sugihara Kazuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96102" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-15">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Inugane-kumichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="211227.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96103" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-15">
<name>Tachibana Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96723" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-15">
<name>Mandarin Kinoshita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96880" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-25">
<name>George</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96881" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-25">
<name>Rina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33633" picture="151771.jpg">Takahashi Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="201999" update="2018-06-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴクドルズの秘密 / 伝説のライブ / 超愛 / ソウルフード / キズ / 恨みます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goku Dolls no Himitsu / Densetsu no Live / Chou Ai / Soul Food / Kizu / Uramimasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202000" update="2018-06-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女マスター / 銀幕の星 / やり直したい / 第四の男 / 極道でアイドル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Master / Ginmaku no Hoshi / Yarinaoshitai / Gokudou de Idol</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202001" update="2018-06-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">だって.... / ありえない / トークの秘訣 / 女子コミとは? / 愛し合ってるかい?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Datte.... / Arienai / Talk no Hiketsu / Joshi Komi to wa? / Aishiatterukai?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202002" update="2018-06-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わしらアイドル始めました. / 親分! 先生? プロデューサー!? / 甘酸っぱい思い出 / わかってくれてる / 打倒!! ヤクザ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Washira Idol Hajimemashita. / Oyabun! Sensei? Producer!? / Amazuppai Omoide / Wakate Kureteru / Datou!! Yakuza!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202545" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202890" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドッキリ / 勇気をあげる / Shall we dance or revenge? / 面接 / 下半身の出来事 / ヒゲとボイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokkiri / Yuuki o Ageru / Shall We Dance or Revenge? / Mensetsu / Kahanshin no Dekigoto / Hige to Boin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202891" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニルヴァーナ / 大切なもの / 親の教え / 大物ルーキー / 女子高生 / 先輩後輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nirvana / Taisetsu na Mono / Oya no Oshie / Oomono Rookie / Joshikousei / Senpai Kouhai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202892" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">労働者よ, 団結せよ! / 対決ババア / ピジョン / Honesty / 夫婦善哉 / 5人の悪魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roudousha yo, Danketsu Seyo! / Taiketsu Babaa / Pidgeon / Honesty / Fuufu Zenzai / 5 Nin no Akuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202893" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">栄光なき勝者 / 男惚れ / ジャパニーズ・ドリーム / ドンと親分 / 家族の絆 / ゴクドルズ被害者の会にて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eikou Naki Shousha / Otoko Hore / Japanese Dream / Don to Oyabun / Kazoku no Kizuna / Goku Dolls Higaisha no Kai nite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204287" update="2018-08-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">極道魂 / 水の泡 / Hellプ ミー / 卒業 / ステップアップ / 最終回･･</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokudoudama / Mizu no Awa / Hellp Me / Sotsugyou / Step Up / Saishuukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204288" update="2018-08-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">路線変更 / My Angel / さすがです!! / 愛惨々と.. / 愛燦爛と / やさしさに包まれて / 取材</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rosenhenkou / My Angel / Sasuga Desu!! / Ai Sansan to.. / Ai Sanran to / Yasashisa ni Kurumarete / Shuzai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218092" update="2019-06-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">キャストコメント映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Comment Video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cast Comment Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218093" update="2019-06-14">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイリ, マリ, チカのアイドルへの道 完全版</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Airi, Mari, and Chika`s Road to Idol Full Version</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Airi, Mari, Chika no Idol e no Michi Kanzenban</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
