<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13649" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-07-13</startdate>
<enddate>2018-07-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Minna no Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 21</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon the Movie: Everyone`s Story</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokémon the Movie 21: Everyone`s Story</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokémon the Movie: The Power of Us</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokémon the Movie 21: Our Story</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 ポケットモンスター みんなの物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pokemon the Movie: The Power of Us</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Pokémon - Der Film: Die Macht in uns</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Film Pokémon: Siła jest w nas</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14993" type="Sequel">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Koko</anime>
<anime id="12646" type="Prequel">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Kimi ni Kimeta!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.pokemon-movie.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="34645" type="Animation Work">Wit Studio</name>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="5875" type="Character Design">Kaneko Shizue</name>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="31099" type="Direction">Yajima Tetsuo</name>
<name id="8688" type="Chief Animation Direction">Marufuji Hirotaka</name>
<name id="14846" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishitani Yasushi</name>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
<name id="17243" type="Series Composition">Umehara Eiji</name>
<name id="31099" type="Series Composition">Yajima Tetsuo</name>
<name id="27525" type="Character Design">Matsumiya Toshinobu</name>
<name id="27526" type="Character Design">Matsushima Kenji</name>
<name id="27643" type="Character Design">Nishino Kouji</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="68">6.13</permanent>
<temporary count="68">6.78</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221119.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36927</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pokemon-movie.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Pokémon_the_Movie:_The_Power_of_Us</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版ポケットモンスター_みんなの物語</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5394</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>362714</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21309</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>pokemon_movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="69" type="main character in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="15">7.39</rating>
<name>Pikachu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pikachu is an Electric-type Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves from Pichu when leveled up with high friendship and evolves into Raichu when exposed to a Thunder Stone. However, the starter Pikachu in Pokémon Yellow will refuse to evolve into Raichu unless it is traded and evolved on another save file.
In Alola, Pikachu will evolve into Alolan Raichu when exposed to a Thunder Stone.
It also has a Gigantamax form.
Pikachu is popularly known as the mascot of the Pokémon franchise and a major representative of Nintendo`s collective mascots.
It is also the game mascot and starter Pokémon of Pokémon Yellow and Pokémon: Let`s Go, Pikachu!. It has made numerous appearances on the boxes of spin-off titles.
Pikachu is also the starter Pokémon in Pokémon Rumble Blast and Pokémon Rumble World.
Pikachu is a short, chubby rodent Pokémon. It is covered in yellow fur with two horizontal brown stripes on its back. It has a small mouth, long, pointed ears with black tips, and brown eyes. Each cheek is a red circle that contains a pouch for electricity storage. It has short forearms with five fingers on each paw, and its feet each have three toes. At the base of its lightning bolt-shaped tail is a patch of brown fur. A female will have a V-shaped notch at the end of its tail, which looks like the top of a heart. It is classified as a quadruped, but it has been known to stand and walk on its hind legs.
The anime has shown that wild Pikachu live in groups in forested areas. Pikachu communicate amongst themselves using squeaks and tail-shaking as friendly gestures. In the anime, Alolan Pikachu are known to greet each other by sniffing one another and rubbing their tails together. Electricity can be used to receive and send messages with each other, as well as other Electric Pokémon species. It raises its tail to check its surroundings and is occasionally struck by lightning in this position. When groups grow, they can inadvertently cause lightning storms. Pikachu forages for Berries, which it roasts with electricity to make them tender enough to eat. A sure sign that Pikachu inhabits a location is patches of burnt grass. It has been observed eating and sometimes destroying telephone poles, wires, and other electronic equipment.
Pikachu charges itself while sleeping overnight, though stress and a lack of sleep can affect this. It is able to release electric discharges of varying intensity. Pikachu has been known to build up energy in its glands, which it will need to discharge to avoid complications. It is also able to release energy through its tail, which acts as a grounding rod, as well as recharging fellow Pikachu with electric shocks. Pikachu can also electrify itself to use its signature move Volt Tackle.
Pikachu has three alternate forms: one, the Cosplay Pikachu appeared exclusively in Pokémon Omega Ruby and Alpha Sapphire. It is always female, has a black heart-shaped spot at the end of its tail, and can be dressed in any of five outfits corresponding to the five Contest conditions. The second form is Pikachu in a cap, which debuted as an event-exclusive Pokémon in Generation VII. It is always male and has seven variants, each wearing one of Ash`s hats from the anime. In addition to these two forms, many other Pikachu variants have appeared in various media. The last, Partner Pikachu is the Pokémon the player starts with in Pokémon: Let`s Go, Pikachu!. This Pikachu can be either gender, has higher base stats, and has access to moves that normal Pikachu do not.
As Gigantamax Pikachu, it becomes larger and chubbier. Its tail becomes longer and stores all of the electricity it generates, causing it to glow a bright yellow and enabling it to become as powerful as a lightning strike. Its power is equal to that a power plant; however, it is difficult to use it in peoples` homes since Pikachu can only remain in its Gigantamax form for a short time.
Pikachu is the only known Pokémon capable of using the Z-Move Catastropika, while Pikachu in a cap has its own exclusive Z-Move, 10,000,000 Volt Thunderbolt. Partner Pikachu is the only Pokémon capable of using Zippy Zap, Floaty Fall, Splishy Splash, and the Partner Power, Pika Papow. Pikachu is the only Pokémon capable of using the Light Ball item. Gigantamax Pikachu is the only known Pokémon capable of using the G-Max Move G-Max Volt Crash.</description>
<picture>68371.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1937" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-03">
<rating votes="479">5.96</rating>
<name>Musashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jessie is one half of of the Team Rocket duo that follows around Ash Ketchum and friends in the Pokemon anime, usually trying to steal Ash`s Pikachu, but always failing.
Jessie`s mother, Miyamoto, was a high-ranking Team Rocket agent. When Jessie was around the age of three, Miyamoto left on a mission to the Andes Mountains to record the voice of the elusive Pokemon Mew. However, Miyamoto disappeared, and Jessie was put into a foster home which had very little money. There were times when she had no choice but to eat snow because of a lack of more nourishing food.
When she was old enough, she left home to become a Pokemon nurse in Jouto. However, the school she was enrolled in was literally for Pokemon nurses (i.e. Chansey), so she failed to graduate and left, leaving behind a Chansey she had befriended there. It is assumed that she then traveled back to Kanto, where she enrolled in Pokemon Tech, a trainer`s school, met James, and subsequently failed and dropped out. After this, Jessie and James joined a bicycle gang in Sunny Town, where Jessie was known for swinging a chain above her head as she rode her bike (nicknamed "Chainer Jess").
Due to conflicts in canon between Kanto and Johto episodes and the special episode "Training Daze", what happened between Jessie and James after the bike gang is unknown. What is known, as shown in the special episode, is that they joined Team Rocket separately and were on initially unfriendly terms after being grouped with Meowth. However, they quickly made up and the rest is history.
Sometime before joining Team Rocket, and it is not known when, Jessie obtained a Contest Pass in the Hoenn region. Also during the years before Team Rocket, she had several boyfriends, all of whom left her and/or treated her badly. In "Xatu the Future", she revealed that she had once worked at a T.V. station as the Weathergirl. In "From Cradle to Save" is also revealed that she once was a ninja.
She has a long-standing bitter rivalry with Cassidy, another member of Team Rocket. Another member, Wendy, held a grudge against Jessie for failing to pay for a drink (making Wendy pay), but got her revenge when she added the charge to Jessie`s overall Team Rocket bill.
In the episode "Ignorance is Blissey", Jessie was reunited with her friend Chansey from the Pokemon nurse school; Chansey had since evolved into a Blissey.
Starting in Hoenn, Jessie has become a Pokemon Coordinator, entering every contest that she could. She frequently makes it to the battle round, but usually loses there. However, in "Borrowing on Bad Faith", she finally succeeded in winning an (unofficial) contest by using Ash`s Aipom, which she had saved earlier in the episode. And, in "Team Shocker!", she finally wins an official contest with her Dustox in at Solaceon City. Later she also won a ribbon with help of her Yanmega. She has Contest Passes to compete in the Hoenn, Kanto, and Sinnoh regions.
While Jessie`s role in the Pokemon anime has not yet ended, in Toshihiro Ono`s manga, "The Electric Tale of Pikachu", she ended up married to James and with child.
Jessie seems to have a special preference for snake-like Pokemon, owning both an Arbok and a Seviper. In "The Ninja Poke Showdown", she expressed a preference for Poison-type Pokemon in general.
For unknown reasons, she, James and Meowth mostly use hot air balloons instead of faster ways of transportation.
In the Kanto contests, Jessie disguises herself as Jessebella (which is similar to James former fiancee Jessiebelle) wearing a red dress and glasses. Eventually, Ash, Brock, Max and May finds out her true identity at the last contest.
During the Kanto Grand Festival, Jessie dresses up as Jessadia (Japanese: キャンディ・ムサリーナ Candy Musalina). and wears glasses, long white socks, a yellow and orange dress, and has her hair in pigtails. She works there as an announcer and Lilian Meridian`s assistant; Lilian herself says she may not really like "Jessadia"`s style, but recognizes her talent. In the Latin American dub, she enters Super Contests under the name Jessiebella (referencing Jessiebelle again). Jessie currently still continues to use the Jessalina disguise while participating in Super Contests.
In "Pruning a Passel of Pals!" and "Strategy With a Smile!" she once again used her Jessadia disguise to report on the Wallace Cup.
Although Jessie had entered mostly every contest in Hoenn &amp; Kanto, she lost in every single one, whether it was the first match of the Battle Rounds or the finals. But in the Sinnoh Region, she has so far won 2 ribbons using her Dustox and Yanmega.</description>
<picture>2338.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="420">5.46</rating>
<name>Nyarth (Rocket-dan)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meowth is a very unique Pokémon as it has many of the characteristics of a human. It walks on two feet, talks and is as smart as any human. Meowth is currently a member of Team Rocket and he travels around with Jessie and James trying to capture Pikachu and other rare Pokémon for Giovanni.
Meowth generally finishes his sentences with "Nyaa (ニャー)" which is the equivalent of "meow" in English. This helps people remember that despite his ability to talk like a human, he still has cat character traits.
Meowth is also known for coming up with his many schemes to try to capture Pikachu. While Jessie and James always agree with Meowth and think his plans are brilliant, they are generally foiled by Ash and his friends.
Long Con to Access Raimon City Pokémon Center
Meowth schemed with Jessie, James and Doctor Zager to figure out a way for them to infiltrate the Raimon City Pokémon Center where high-leveled Pokémon are stored in a vault that is protected by a security machine scan system that would only open if Nurse Joy (Isshu) or Nurse Joy`s Audino were scanned. Meowth pretended to be no longer part of Team Rocket making up a story that his made an error while executing a certain operation and when headquarters hear of his mistake, they told him he was fired.
Ash, Iris and Cilan believed him and allowed Meowth to travel with him. Pikachu though didn`t trust Meowth even though Meowth proved on numerous occasion that it should be trusted. Meowth`s plan was put into action when they arrived at the Raimon City Pokémon Center and as soon as Nurse Joy`s Audino was scanned to open the door, Meowth turned on Pikachu and the other and captured all the Pokémon in the vault. The long con had been a success and Meowth met up with Jessie and James below the Pokémon Center. Unfortunately, they weren`t able to get away as Ash and his friends realized that Meowth had just been conning them and they were able to stop Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>56344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3832" picture="170554.jpg">Inuyama Inuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2611" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="370">7.66</rating>
<name>Kojirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>James is one part of of the Team Rocket trio that follows around Ash Ketchum and friends in the Pokémon anime, usually trying to steal Ash`s Pikachu, but always failing.
James is mostly a comedic parody of bishounen characters; the English dub in particular tends to give him a melodramatic and even campy tone. He is somewhat famous for carrying a rose, though in more recent episodes he does not display it often. Mostly, his rose is displayed in the Team Rocket motto.
The only child of millionaires, James was forced to endure formal society. At a young age, he was forcefully engaged to a girl of whom he was terrified, Jessiebelle, all because his parents wanted to have a wealthy daughter-in-law. Thus, he ran away from home, leaving behind his beloved pet Growlie. He attempted to enroll in Pokémon Tech, a trainer`s school, but, along with his new friend Jessie, flunked out. Then, with Jessie, he joined the Sunny Town bicycle gang, where he was popular for being the only gang member to have to use training wheels (nicknamed "Trainer Jim"). Eventually James, Jessie, and the bike gang went their separate ways.
Due to conflicts in canon between Kanto and Johto episodes and the special episode "Training Daze", what happened between James and Jessie after the bike gang is unknown. What is known, as shown in the special episode, is that they joined Team Rocket separately and were on initially unfriendly terms after being grouped with Meowth. However, they quickly made up and the rest is history.
Since he is proficient in several activities, including Pokémon haiku and PokéRinger, it is possible that he developed his skills during his temporary separation from Jessie, but this is not known for sure.
In the episode "Holy Matrimony!", James returned to his home as a result of a trap by his parents, who pretended to be dead. He was reunited with his old pet Growlie and managed to avoid marrying Jessiebelle. Growlie stayed behind when James returned to Jessie and Meowth.
James has a tendency to be swindled by a Magikarp Salesman, who has on many occasions tricked him into buying a Magikarp or other useless Pokémon and items for large sums of money.
James also has a tendency to cross-dress, but has not done it since "Pros and Con Artists". He does, however, dress up like famous celebrities as well, such as Professor Oak, Juan, and Norman.
James loves rare bottle caps and has an impressive collection of them. In the episode "All That Glitters!" it is revealed that he has "drunk enough soda pop to float an aircraft carrier".
For unknown reasons, he, Jessie and Meowth mostly use hot air balloons instead of faster ways of transportation. However in newer episodes the balloon is shown with `jets` attached to explain how they get from one place to another faster than walking.</description>
<picture>2423.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6693" type="main character in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="911">2.49</rating>
<name>Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
Ash is the main character of the Pokémon anime. Raised in Pallet Town, he started his journey to become a Pokémon Master at the age of 10. On the day that he started his journey, Ash carelessly woke up late despite being told by his mother, Delia Ketchum to get to bed. He rushed to Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory only to find out that the beginner Pokémon - Bulbasaur, Squirtle, and Charmander - had already been given out to trainers who arrived on time. However, Professor Samual Oak mentioned that there was one more Pokémon available - Pikachu. Despite constantly hitting Ash with Electric-type attacks and refusing to return to its PokéBall, Ash decided to take Pikachu along with him on his journey to become a Pokémon Master. Pikachu is cold towards Ash at first and laughs at his failures; however, when Ash saves Pikachu from a flock of wild Spearow, he begins to warm up to his new trainer and the two finally become friends. After the battle with the flock of Spearow, a Ho-Oh is seen flying towards a rainbow in the sky. The PokéDex reveals that the Ho-Oh is an unidentified Pokémon. Thus, the journey of Ash and Pikachu begins.
Captures in Viridian Forest
While making his way towards Pewter City and his first Kanto League Gym Battle, Ash came upon a wild Caterpie deep within Viridian Forest. Instead of using Pikachu to battle against the wild Pokémon, Ash took his chances and threw a PokéBall without weakining the Caterpie first. Luckily, he was able to catch the Pokémon without any trouble. The capture of Ash`s Caterpie marked Ash`s first capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Caterpie the second Pokémon to join his team.
The next day, while continuing the trek through the Viridian Forest, Ash came up on a wild Pidgeotto. He tried to just throw a PokéBall like he did with Ash`s Caterpie, but Pidgeotto swatted the PokéBall away. Misty informed that he must weaken the Pokémon first before attempting to capture it. He called out Ash`s Caterpie to battle against, but Misty quickly informed him that Bug-type Pokémon are weak against Flying-type Pokémon like Pidgeotto. After Pidgeotto dealt significant damage to Ash`s Caterpie, Ash recalled it and sent out Pikachu. Pikachu was able to use its Thundershock to weaken Pidgeotto and allow Ash to capture it with a PokéBall. Thus, this capture marked Ash`s second capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Pidgeotto the third Pokémon to join his team.
Later on, while still in the Viridian Forest, Ash was approached by Team Rocket, who attempted to steal his Pokémon. After defeating Meowth, James`s Koffing, and Jessie`s Ekans, Ash`s Caterpie evolved into Ash`s Metapod.
Some of Ash`s greatest accomplishments have been at the various Pokémon Leagues. He was the victor at the Orange League and the Battle Frontier. He also competed in the Indigo League and the Johto Silver Conference where he placed admirably in both those competitions as well.
Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup
Ash participated in the Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup at the Kagome Town stadium. In the first round he was in the fifth match and faced off against Marris. The match was quickly showcased and Ash won the battle and advanced to the second round while Marris was eliminated from the tournament.
The Isshu League
Ash participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where he was matched up against Trip. Trip`s Serperior was sent out to battle Pikachu and Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior`s speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter Trip`s Serperior speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round. The two met in the Pokémon Center after the battle, and Trip vowed that the next time they met that he would win. The two shook hands and parted ways.
In the first main round, Ash`s opponent was shown on the match up electronic board but not much else is known about the battle. Ash`s Scraggy participated in the second main round of the Isshu League tournament where it faced off against a Darumakka. It was able to defeat it so that moved on to the next round.
In the third round, Stephan was matched up against Ash. Cilan noted that the two of them have a very direct taste and that it would be a good battle. It was only a 3 on 3 battle but the both of them gave it their all. The first two battles of the third round setup the final match up of Stephan`s Sawk vs Ash`s Krookodile, both of which were very injured from the previous battles. Both of them did their best to muster up their reserve strength but in the end a surprise move of Aerial Ace by Ash`s Krookodile was super effective against Stephan`s Sawk and it knocked it out to give Ash the victory while eliminating Stephan from the tournament. Stephan realized after the battle that the reason that Ash withdrew Waruvial after the first battle was because Ash knew that Stephan would definitely send out Dageki, so he didn`t reveal that it knew Aerial Ace and saved until the end.</description>
<picture>6210.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98169" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-08">
<name>Zeraora</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zeraora is a bipedal feline Pokémon that has black underfur and yellow fur on its head, forearms, chest, hips, and upper legs. Blue fur can also be seen on its forehead, chest, and whiskers. Its eyes and paw-pads are similarly blue. Black zigzagging stripes can be seen on its thighs and forearms. It has four-fingered paws, while its feet have three toes each. A long, yellow, thunderbolt-shaped ponytail extends from the back of its head, giving the appearance of an actual tail.
Zeraora can create a very powerful magnetic field through the strong electric currents generated from its paw-pads. This magnetic field can allow Zeraora to levitate and fly through the air at high speeds. It can travel as fast as a lightning strike. Unlike most Electric-type Pokémon, Zeraora does not have organs to create electricity; instead, it gathers and stores it from outside sources, then uses it as its own electric energy. Its fur is known to stand on its ends all across the body whenever it is using massive amounts of electricity.
Zeraora is the only known Pokémon capable of learning the move Plasma Fists.</description>
<picture>224448.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="100347" type="main character in" update="2019-01-17">
<name>Lisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67068.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="58453" picture="237414.jpg">Kawaei Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="193780" update="2018-07-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2018-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
