<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13831" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2018-12-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Goblin Slayer</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Goblin Katili (Goblin Slayer)</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Убиец на гоблини</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">ゴブスレ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gobusure</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゴブリンスレイヤー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Goblin Slayer</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Убийца гоблинов</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">고블린 슬레이어</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">قاتل الغوبلن</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">哥布林杀手</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14782" type="Other">Goblin Slayer: Goblin`s Crown</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4892" approval="27" total="40">Claymore</anime>
<anime id="98" approval="23" total="38">Kenpuu Denki Berserk</anime>
<anime id="11712" approval="16" total="30">Hai to Gensou no Grimgar</anime>
<anime id="169" approval="4" total="11">Lodoss-tou Senki</anime>
<anime id="10894" approval="3" total="21">Dungeon ni Deai o Motomeru no wa Machigatte Iru Darouka: Familia Myth</anime>
<anime id="12138" approval="2" total="16">Violet Evergarden</anime>
<anime id="5503" approval="1" total="8">Druaga no Tou: the Aegis of Uruk</anime>
<anime id="10" approval="1" total="7">Bastard!! Ankoku no Hakai Shin</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="18">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="540059">this has got rave reviews, all these calls of masterpiece... but srsly, everything is wonderful aesthetically just beautiful, but the story telling is SubPar alot, plot holes about, progression disjointed. The powers of the people just make no sense, it is as if a child designed the magic system,  an untalented child. I watched to ep8 because its so nice to look at. Yeah the spells are all so silly, the like level 2 healer can cast a sheild forever if its convenient, or just a second. And i like a stoic and slightly twisted MC, but this guy, is just kinda so out of it, gets half killed all the time, and then does a supersaiyayin tranfo for no apparent reason. i dunno. just my take.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="81544">In the dark time of anime of the god forsaken year 2018 came this gem to the light for the lesser be....watchers of anime which are starved for the touch of a grim and living fantasy story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="94891">I was positively surprised by this series. The story and the animation of the series is in my opinion very well done. Finally a series where you can see some blood and violence and not always the standard series 1 man and 7 women. I can`t understand why this series only got a 6 as a vote, from me this series gets a 8/10 stars. What I liked about this series is that you don`t see a typical super hero, but an ordinary adventure who just wants to kill goblins for revenge and the rest of the world doesn`t interest him. It`s just something different. From me a clear recommendation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="272780">Just started watching but it already gives me goosebumps . Reminds me of Hai to Gensou no Grimgar but I enjoy graphic style more in this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="272004">I consider Goblin Slayer as quite decent. What sets it apart from a lot of other fantasy shows is that every decision has an immediate consequence, which may even be death. You can`t just run around swinging your sword and everything will be alright. 
Animation and sound are great, but it`s somewhat lacking in terms of character depth and storytelling. Going for 24 episodes may have been a better choice. 
The show is not bad by any means though. It`s good. If you`re into fantasy, this is for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="543137">one off few anime that will watch it over and over story and characters are very great</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="541081">this anime is a dark and a bloody story  the fighting is more in reality style not fantasy style

the hero is not some super strong main character this hero is just a very smart human that uses his skill and intelligence to overcome the enemy

if you dont like dark bloody graphic anime this is not for you but if you like bloody  or dark anime like berserk or claymore then you are going to like this anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="166014">WARNING: The first episode might be disturbing for some but if you liked the anime ``berserk`` I would recommend watching this.

This is a very good anime, the main character isn`t an overpowered fella if you were expecting him to be. I mean he is a "goblin slayer".

You could say his power come from knowledge and experience. You will mostly not find those typical super power like sword that 1 shots everything it touches blablabla.

definitely a must watch for action and fantasy fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="831936">It`s a Dark JRPG style anime.
The MC is traumatized and seemingly enjoys killing the green things.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="625307">dark, brutal and psychological. the graphic violence is only overshadowed by the emotional brutality. adventuring and overcoming your enemies with ingenuity is the basis of this show, while with each character another aspect of psychological traumata is explored. audio visual composition is sligthly above average. while character development is exceptional, the plot is sometimes lacking the element of surprise.

if you just want mindless violence then this is not for you, brutality is a key factor in understanding these characters.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="243082">Vastly under rated anime (at least on anidb ratings). Extremely dark but despite people thinking it is excessively so I can assure you it is absolutely necessary. Some people have suggested there is not much character development, though I can see their point it is simply not true. 

90% of the development is subtle and to the main character himself, who is essentially emotionally damaged due to a horrific experience and his years of training as a Goblin Slayer. The rest are again even more subtle changes to the supporting characters (priestess, elf, farm owner, newbie adventurers etc.) and development to the whole adventurers guild in how they see the outcast Slayer. Make no mistake it is there to be seen.

Emotional stories, hardships, harrowing and often near death experiences all give this anime a quality not often seen. Fantasy animes tend to trivialize combat with lesser foes. This anime focuses on it and emphasizes the dangerous and brutal nature of the world.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="342700">Serious &amp; Solid watch. The focus on characters is really weak, you don`t really get to know them too much, the emphasis stays on plot. Dark fantasy with rather brutal background (not too brutal, just the right dose, 1st episode is the `darkest`). Addictive from the very beginning. It shows rather different light on RPG/fantasy/medieval world, where all adventurers want to focus on serious monsters, while none pays attention to little goblins, oh, almost none, because main hero is crazy about them. I would like to watch more... someday (rather sooner, than later ;p)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="123101">Let`s keep it short - If you enjoy action do yourself a favour and watch this.

Yes, it has a "weird" begin but you will love it since the first episode.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="260637">It was truly a masterpiece ..., unpredictable for all fights, don`t know if he will survive(yeah yeah MC), not op like other "huh" goblin genres.I am truly waiting for a season 2 gg for another DnD experience. :) must watch!!!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.goblinslayer.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="53807" type="Original Work">Kagyuu Kumo</name>
<name id="1555" type="Animation Work">White Fox</name>
<name id="18895" type="Character Design">Nagayoshi Takashi</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="15075" type="Direction">Ozaki Takaharu</name>
<name id="2435" type="Music">Suehiro Ken`ichirou</name>
<name id="18895" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nagayoshi Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a dark fantasy light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr53807 [Kagyuu Kumo] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr53808 [Kannatsuki Noboru].
"I`m not saving the world. I`m just killing goblins."
At the guild on the frontier, someone has accomplished a rare feat, rising to become a Silver-ranked adventurer solely by hunting goblins...
http://anidb.net/ch93847 [Priestess], a newly minted adventurer, joined her first party only to meet with disaster. The man who saved her is called http://anidb.net/ch93845 [Goblin Slayer].
He uses whatever means necessary, sparing no expense or effort to exterminate all goblins. Around him, he gathered a priestess he vexed, an ever-affable http://anidb.net/ch93846 [lady guild worker], and his http://anidb.net/ch98612 [childhood friend], http://anidb.net/ch93850 [farm girl]. In the midst of everything, an http://anidb.net/ch93848 [elven girl] who`s heard rumors about him appears with a request...
Source: Official page</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2041">6.52</permanent>
<temporary count="2066">7.28</temporary>
<review count="3">5.38</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221146.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20672</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38807</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>37349</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.goblinslayer.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Goblin_Slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゴブリンスレイヤー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5052</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363389</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>GoblinSlayer_GA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07K36TVLL</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3269" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-11">
<name>genocide</name>
<description>The systematic killing of substantial numbers of people on the basis of ethnicity, religion, political opinion, social status, or other particularity.
Acts committed with intent to destroy, in whole or in part, a national, ethnic, racial or religious group.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3481" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-04-19">
<name>recruiting teammates</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3581" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>tactics</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3635" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-01">
<name>sea battles</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4084" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-20">
<name>dark atmosphere</name>
<description>Usually metaphorical. Sometimes literal. At times both!
Typically this refers to the fact that the story is set in a grim, dog eat dog milieu — for example a decaying city.
Often the characters are just doing what they need to do to survive, with little or no expectation that their lives can be better. And often characters may feel they do not have any real choice in what they do.
And yes, occasionally the setting is actually dark — be it night or perpetually heavy cloudy sky and rain. It all adds to the oppressive, hopeless feeling of the show.
You probably will not feel uplifted or happy after watching this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4387" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>good vs evil</name>
<description>A theme often used to relay lessons of morality. The fight between two entities, with one side representing all that is good and right and the other one all that is evil and wrong.
It’s one of the most conventional themes in literature, and sometimes considered to be a universal part of the human condition.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6730" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>torture</name>
<description>Torture involves the deliberate act of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or apply coercion to compel action from the victim. Torture, by definition, is a knowing and intentional act; deeds which unknowingly or negligently inflict pain without a specific intent to do so are not typically considered torture.
This is distinct from http://anidb.net/t2905 [erotic torture], which is generally for the purpose of using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6901" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-23">
<name>underground</name>
<description>Some or all of the action occurs underground, in caves, mines, sewers, subways or underground cities.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7141" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-16">
<name>goblin</name>
<description>A goblin is a monstrous creature from European folklore, first attested in stories from the Middle Ages. They are ascribed various and conflicting abilities, temperaments and appearances depending on the story and country of origin. They are almost always small and grotesque, mischievous or outright malicious, and greedy, especially for gold and jewelry. They often have magical abilities similar to a http://anidb.net/t780 [fairy] or http://anidb.net/t2646 [demon].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>220782.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="93845" type="main character in" update="2018-09-19">
<rating votes="37">8.33</rating>
<name>Goblin Slayer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93846" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-19">
<rating votes="37">7.52</rating>
<name>Uketsukejou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93847" type="main character in" update="2018-09-19">
<rating votes="50">5.72</rating>
<name>Onna Shinkan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93848" type="main character in" update="2018-10-20">
<rating votes="44">7.28</rating>
<name>Yousei Yunde</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93849" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="9">4.58</rating>
<name>Yari Tsukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93850" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-19">
<rating votes="86">7.78</rating>
<name>Ushikai Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224112.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93851" type="main character in" update="2018-09-19">
<rating votes="16">5.89</rating>
<name>Tokage Souryo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93852" type="main character in" update="2018-09-19">
<rating votes="18">6.24</rating>
<name>Kouhito Doushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93853" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="29">7.34</rating>
<name>Majo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98485" type="appears in" update="2018-10-08">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Kenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10130" picture="151714.jpg">Takumi Yasuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98486" type="appears in" update="2018-10-08">
<rating votes="2">4.75</rating>
<name>Butouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98487" type="appears in" update="2018-10-08">
<rating votes="2">2.24</rating>
<name>Majutsushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32588" picture="87531.jpg">Koiwai Kotori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98528" type="appears in" update="2018-10-08">
<rating votes="2">1.13</rating>
<name>Goblin Shaman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32567" picture="170552.jpg">Nakanishi Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98529" type="appears in" update="2018-10-08">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Hobgoblin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55776" picture="220705.jpg">Yamane Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98599" type="appears in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="2">7.96</rating>
<name>Goblin Slayer no Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34984" picture="222849.jpg">Ueda Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98600" type="appears in" update="2018-11-24">
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<name>Goblin Slayer no Youshouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38908" picture="225568.jpg">Matsuda Satsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98601" type="appears in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Gin`yuushijin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98602" type="appears in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="7">6.54</rating>
<name>Onna Kishi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225461.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12783" picture="225340.jpg">Fujii Yukiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98605" type="appears in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="2">5.32</rating>
<name>Shinmai Senshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55877" picture="222023.jpg">Maeda Seiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98606" type="appears in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Sonchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98607" type="appears in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Ushikai Musume no Oji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40456" picture="181638.jpg">Hayashi Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98608" type="appears in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Ushikai Musume no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225470.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98609" type="appears in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="3">4.50</rating>
<name>Kantokukan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38978" picture="183949.jpg">Hioka Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98610" type="appears in" update="2018-10-21">
<rating votes="3">3.99</rating>
<name>Minarai Seijo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37300" picture="167153.jpg">Itou Ayasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98611" type="appears in" update="2018-12-31">
<rating votes="2">8.20</rating>
<name>Juu Senshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39583" picture="186257.jpg">Hamano Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98612" type="appears in" update="2018-10-13">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Ushikai Musume no Youshouki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98809" type="appears in" update="2018-10-21">
<rating votes="2">5.32</rating>
<name>Shounen Sekkou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45621" picture="205087.jpg">Wakayama Akihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98810" type="appears in" update="2018-10-21">
<rating votes="3">3.99</rating>
<name>Shoujo Fujutsushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47245" picture="224994.jpg">Harada Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98922" type="appears in" update="2018-10-27">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Ogre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32937" picture="89644.jpg">Kagami Riki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98923" type="appears in" update="2018-10-27">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Onna Elf</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53526" picture="242924.jpg">Hasegawa Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99025" type="appears in" update="2018-11-03">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Hojin Sekkou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46388" picture="200800.jpg">Iwanaka Mutsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99026" type="appears in" update="2018-11-03">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Tan`ya Shokunin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99027" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-11-12">
<rating votes="20">6.14</rating>
<name>Tsurugi no Otome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99181" type="appears in" update="2018-11-17">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Goblin Champion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55776" picture="220705.jpg">Yamane Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99182" type="appears in" update="2018-12-30">
<rating votes="2">5.06</rating>
<name>Kensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99183" type="appears in" update="2018-12-30">
<rating votes="2">2.81</rating>
<name>Yuusha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53024" picture="232385.jpg">Shimabukuro Miyuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99184" type="appears in" update="2018-12-30">
<rating votes="2">2.81</rating>
<name>Kenja</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46819" picture="224887.jpg">Inoue Honoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99185" type="appears in" update="2018-11-10">
<rating votes="2">1.03</rating>
<name>Jashinkan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36770" picture="151722.jpg">Nose Ikuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99442" type="appears in" update="2018-11-24">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Oomedama</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99443" type="appears in" update="2018-11-24">
<rating votes="1">2.40</rating>
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47035" picture="191960.jpg">Ogura Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99444" type="appears in" update="2018-11-24">
<rating votes="2">3.03</rating>
<name>Rhea</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99878" type="appears in" update="2018-12-30">
<rating votes="2">1.36</rating>
<name>Goblin Lord</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99879" type="appears in" update="2018-12-22">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Shibuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50466" picture="236024.jpg">Volcano Oota</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99880" type="appears in" update="2018-12-22">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Keikenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56095" picture="223106.jpg">Takeda Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99881" type="appears in" update="2018-12-22">
<rating votes="3">7.65</rating>
<name>Onna Senshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57248" picture="229103.jpg">Kikuchi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="207961" update="2018-10-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="24">5.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ある冒険者たちの結末</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fate of Particular Adventurers</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Schicksal der Abenteurer</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Falanca Maceracıların Akıbeti</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aru Boukensha-tachi no Ketsumatsu</title>
<summary>On the first day that the Priestess became an adventurer, she joins three other rookie adventurers on a quest to save some girls who were kidnapped by some goblins. Despite being one of the weakest monsters around, the rookie adventurers fall for some traps that were set for them in the goblin cave, which leads to dire results. A goblin was about to attack the Priestess when a mysterious armored figure appears before her. The armored figure then mercilessly starts slaughtering the goblins and tells the Priestess that his name is Goblin Slayer...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777760</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="207962" update="2018-10-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小鬼を殺す者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goblin Slayer</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Dämonentöter</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Goblin Slayer (Goblin Katili)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kooni o Korosu Mono</title>
<summary>The Goblin Slayer is a silver-ranked adventurer covered in armor from head to toe. The Goblin Slayer never accepted any quests from the Adventurers` Guild other than quests to slay goblins so he was perceived as strange by the other guild members. Ever since she was saved by the Goblin Slayer the Priestess had been joining him on quests and slowly began to understand how he functions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777761</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="207963" update="2018-10-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="16">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">思いがけない来客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unexpected Visitors</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Unerwarteter Besuch</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Beklenmedik Ziyaretçiler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoigakenai Raikyaku</title>
<summary>The High Elf Archer, Dwarf Shaman, and Lizardman Priest come to see Goblin Slayer. They tell him of a demon lord that`s revived with the intent to destroy the world, and they ask for Goblin Slayer`s help. However, he tells them they have no interest until they mention goblins...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777762</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="207964" update="2018-11-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強き者ども</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strong</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Starken</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Güçlü Olan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyoki Monodomo</title>
<summary>Goblin Slayer and his companions enter some ancient ruins that had been taken over by the demon lords` minions. Goblin Slayer works together with the High Elf Archer and the others to slay the army of goblins, but suddenly, an ogre appears. The tables turn on the battle as the ogre beats Goblin Slayer down...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777763</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209172" update="2018-10-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209173" update="2018-10-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209411" update="2019-01-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冒険と日常と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adventures and Daily Life</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abenteuer und Alltag</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Maceralar ve Gündelik Yaşam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bouken to Nichijou to</title>
<summary>Goblin Slayer and the others return successful from their quest in the ruins. Goblin Slayer spends a few days sleeping at Cow Girl`s home to recover and then heads to the guild. There, he gives advice to a couple of adventurers on how to deal with some giant rats and also accepts a request from Guild Girl.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778471</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209412" update="2018-11-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水の街の小鬼殺し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goblin Slayer in the Water Town</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Goblintöten in Wasserstadt</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Goblin Slayer (Goblin Katili) Su Şehrinde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizu no Machi no Koonigoroshi</title>
<summary>Goblin Slayer and his party recieve a request to slay some goblins. The one who sent the request was the Sword Maiden, one of the heroes that defeated the Demon Lord. Goblin Slayer, Priestess, High Elf Archer, Dwarf Shaman, and Lizardman Priest head to Water Town. It`s a peaceful, beautiful city, but apparently, there are some scary incidents happening. The party believes that there might be some goblins hiding in the sewers so they head down there as soon as possible.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778472</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209413" update="2018-12-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死へ進め</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Onward Unto Death</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf in den Tod</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ölüme Doğru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi e Susume</title>
<summary>Goblin Slayer and his party go into the sewers of Water Town to investigate some brutal incidents they think were caused by goblins. When they go down to the sewers, they are immediately attacked by a horde of goblins. Because of the sheer number of goblins, the party has a hard time dealing with them all and then a goblin champion also appears before them...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778473</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209414" update="2018-12-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">囁きと祈りと詠唱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whispers and Prayers and Chants</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Flüstern, Gebete und Gesänge</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Fısıltılar, Dualar ve İlahiler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasayaki to Inori to Eishou</title>
<summary>Goblin Slayer was gravely injured after the battle with the goblin champion. The Priestess and Sword Maiden work together to heal Goblin Slayer with a special ritual. Meanwhile, High Elf Archer and the others investigate the sewers a bit further and encounter a mysterious creature. Due to the creature`s abilities, the party heads back up to the surface to regroup with Goblin Slayer and Priestess before they go any further.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778474</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210171" update="2018-12-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">往きて, 還りし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There and Back Again</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Hin und zurück</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yine Gidiş Geliş</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukite, Kaerishi</title>
<summary>The party encounters a giant mirror in the sewers. The mirror, the mysterious creature they encountered, the horde of goblins, and the goblin champion that appeared... Goblin Slayer and the others try to get to the bottom of what`s going on. They once again encounter the horde of goblins as well as the goblin champion, which gravely injured Goblin Slayer previously. But Goblin Slayer had a plan to take care of them once and for all...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778475</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210172" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まどろみの中で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dozing</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schlummer</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Pinekleme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Madoromi no Naka de</title>
<summary>Goblin Slayer and his party head back to town. The news that the Hero had defeated the Demon Lord is spreading, putting everyone in a celebratory mood. However, Goblin Slayer doesn`t seem to care much about the news and continues on with his daily life. On the other hand, it seems that Goblin Slayer is changing ever so slightly through his interactions with his companions...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778476</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210173" update="2019-01-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冒険者の饗宴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Gathering of Adventurers</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Festmahl für Abenteurer</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Maceracıları Toplama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boukensha no Kyouen</title>
<summary>Goblin Slayer does his usual rounds around the farm and finds a bunch of goblin footprints, and realizes that they`re planning to attack the farm that night. Goblin Slayer tries to convince Cow Girl and her uncle to leave, but she refuses to leave, wanting to protect the one place that Goblin Slayer has to come home to. In order to protect the farm Goblin Slayer heads to the guild to make a request...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778477</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210174" update="2019-01-14">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ある冒険者の結末</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fate of an Adventurer</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vom Ende eines Abenteurers</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Maceracının Kaderi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aru Boukensha no Ketsumatsu</title>
<summary>The battle against the Goblin Lord and his horde of goblins had begun, and High Elf Archer, Dwarf Shaman, Lizardman Priest, and the other members from the guild face them head-on. Meanwhile, Goblin Slayer goes to face the Goblin Lord alone...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778478</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210970" recap="true" update="2019-01-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冒険記録用紙[アドベンチャーシート]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adventure Sheet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Adventure Sheet</title>
<summary>The Cow Girl waits for Goblin Slayer to come back home and reflects on his childhood and his interactions with his new companions. We get to see why the Silver-ranked Goblin Slayer slays goblins through the Cow Girl`s eyes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780461</identifier>
<identifier>goblin-slayer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
