<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13894" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-01-25</startdate>
<enddate>2019-03-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Psycho-Pass: Sinners of the System</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">PSYCHO-PASS SS</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">サイコパス SS</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">PSYCHO-PASS Sinners of the System</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14735" type="Sequel">Psycho-Pass 3</anime>
<anime id="10066" type="Prequel">Gekijouban Psycho-Pass</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="724513">Writing is bland. 
Animation is great with some exceptional use of 3D elements. 
All in all, decent popcorn flicks.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="498162">I enjoyed the Psycho-Pass series, although this one is about 3 different side stories, it is really high production and real awesome!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://psycho-pass.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="8630" type="Character Design">Aoki Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="2992" type="Direction">Shiotani Naoyoshi</name>
<name id="3729" type="Chief Animation Direction">Abe Hisashi</name>
<name id="2163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="6331" type="Character Design">Asano Kyouji</name>
<name id="3729" type="Character Design">Abe Hisashi</name>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="3033" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakamura Satoru</name>
<name id="6306" type="Music">Kanno Yuugo</name>
</creators>
<description>Set in the near future in a world where a person`s mental state can be viewed as a set of numbers, PSYCHO-PASS is the story of detectives wielding guns called "Dominators" that can see your "crime coefficient", a number that shows how likely you are to commit a crime, and tracking down "latent criminals" before they can break the law.
The three stories are set in Asia and Japan 100 years in the future – depicting the world`s present, past, and future. Facing these crimes will be Enforcers, whose crime coefficient has gone beyond the legal limits, and Inspectors, elite detectives who were hand-picked by the Sybil System. What do you need to stop a crime before it happens? A hunter`s wisdom, or a hunting dog`s instincts? The cases reveal unexpected truths, and show the world as it really is. The untold missing links of the PSYCHO-PASS story are about to be revealed.
Source: Fuji TV</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="270">7.48</permanent>
<temporary count="274">7.79</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>231725.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37440</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>37441</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>37442</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://psycho-pass.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Psycho-Pass:_Sinners_of_the_System</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>PSYCHO-PASS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363620</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>363621</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>363622</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21752</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>psychopass_tv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=ONsIal0E5sI</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4050" parentid="2674" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Tibet</name>
<description>Tibet is a historical region covering much of the Tibetan Plateau in Central Asia. It is the traditional homeland of the Tibetan people as well as some other ethnic groups such as Monpa, Qiang, and Lhoba peoples and is now also inhabited by considerable numbers of Han Chinese and Hui people. Tibet is the highest region on Earth, with an average elevation of 4,900 metres (16,000 ft).
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214282.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5842" parentid="2925" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-23">
<name>guerilla warfare</name>
<description>Guerrilla warfare is a form of irregular warfare and refers to conflicts in which a small group of combatants including, but not limited to, armed civilians use military tactics, such as ambushes, sabotage, raids, the element of surprise, and extraordinary mobility to harass a larger and less-mobile traditional army, or strike a vulnerable target, and withdraw almost immediately.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7431" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Himalayas</name>
<description>The Himalayas is a mountain range in Asia, separating the plains of the Indian subcontinent from the Tibetan Plateau. The range has many of the Earth`s highest peaks, including the highest, Mount Everest, Nepal. The Himalayas include over fifty mountains exceeding 7,200 m (23,600 ft) in elevation, including ten of the fourteen 8,000-metre peaks. By contrast, the highest peak outside Asia (Aconcagua, in the Andes) is 6,961 m (22,838 ft) tall.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="48064" type="main character in" update="2014-11-27">
<rating votes="270">7.99</rating>
<name>Kougami Shin`ya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48307" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-24">
<rating votes="298">6.20</rating>
<name>Tsunemori Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48540" type="main character in" update="2018-03-20">
<rating votes="48">4.10</rating>
<name>Ginoza Nobuchika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginoza Nobuchika is an Inspector and the leader of http://anidb.net/ch76608 [Public Safety Division 1] at the http://anidb.net/ch76607 [Public Safety Bureau].
After his father http://anidb.net/ch48543 [Masaoka Tomomi] was killed during the final showdown with http://anidb.net/ch48756 [Makishima Shougo], Ginoza`s Crime Coefficient rises above regulation levels to 140, and he is demoted to an Enforcer at Division 1.</description>
<picture>165040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48541" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-27">
<rating votes="41">5.01</rating>
<name>Kagari Shuusei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48542" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-08">
<rating votes="87">5.43</rating>
<name>Kunizuka Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67980.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48543" type="main character in" update="2014-11-27">
<rating votes="52">7.94</rating>
<name>Masaoka Tomomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48544" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-08">
<rating votes="87">7.35</rating>
<name>Karanomori Shion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67975.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48756" type="appears in" update="2014-11-27">
<rating votes="128">5.66</rating>
<name>Makishima Shougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54383" type="appears in" update="2015-02-07">
<rating votes="38">1.92</rating>
<name>Kasei Joushuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56084" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="9">5.27</rating>
<name>Aoyanagi Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70086" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-18">
<rating votes="23">4.81</rating>
<name>Hinakawa Shou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70419" type="main character in" update="2019-11-16">
<rating votes="160">4.91</rating>
<name>Shimotsuki Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68095.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71380" type="main character in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="8">3.10</rating>
<name>Sugou Teppei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164216.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94647" type="main character in" update="2018-09-14">
<rating votes="18">7.37</rating>
<name>Ginoza Nobuchika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginoza Nobuchika is an Enforcer with http://anidb.net/ch76608 [Public Safety Division 1] at the http://anidb.net/ch76607 [Public Safety Bureau].
He was demoted to Enforcer after his Crime Coefficient rose above regulation levels to 140, after the death of his father http://anidb.net/ch48543 [Masaoka Tomomi] at the hands of http://anidb.net/ch48756 [Makishima Shougo]. As part of the incident, Ginoza lost his left arm and gained a prosthetic, much like his father. Ginoza`s personality and outlook on life also drastically changed. Further, he no longer wears glasses; when http://anidb.net/ch48307 [Tsunemori Akane] asks if he actually needed prescription glasses, Ginoza replied that he wore glasses as he did not like the shape of his face, but he no longer cares about this aspect of his appearance.</description>
<picture>177477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98906" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-27">
<name>Kukuri Takeya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="40581" picture="223587.jpg">Hirai Sachie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98907" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-10">
<name>Yasaka Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2189" picture="21746.jpg">Yumiba Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98908" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-27">
<name>Matsurai Rodion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98909" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-27">
<name>Ukan Akashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4270" picture="197671.jpg">Nakagawa Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98910" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-27">
<name>Gentaku Aiko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98911" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-27">
<name>Noto Kouji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="622" picture="214429.jpg">Tadano Youhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98912" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-27">
<name>Tsujishi Kyoukou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="317" picture="17155.jpg">Oka Hiroe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98913" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-24">
<name>Ootomo Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98914" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-24">
<name>Ootomo Itsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98915" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-10">
<rating votes="11">7.12</rating>
<name>Hanashiro Frederica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98916" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Kinlay Dorothy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98917" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Guillermo Garcia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="560" picture="41051.jpg">Isobe Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98918" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Jean-Marcel Belmondo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98919" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Tshering Gurung</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98920" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-10">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Tenzing Wangchuk</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Japanese-Tibetan mixed girl, who father died during the war.</description>
<picture>240984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="196968" update="2019-03-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>70</length>
<airdate>2019-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恩讐の彼方に__</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vengeance`s Horizon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onshuu no Kanata ni__</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196969" update="2019-02-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2019-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">First Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">First Guardian</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196970" update="2019-01-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2019-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪と罰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crime and Punishment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumi to Batsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197188" update="2018-03-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Next Project 告知映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1 Next Project Kokuchi Eizou (1:12)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Next Project Kokuchi Eizou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
