<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13989" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2019-06-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hitoribocchi no Marumaru Seikatsu</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">هيتوري بوتشي نو مارو مارو سيكاتسو</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hitoribocchi no OO Seikatsu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ひとりぼっちの○○生活</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hitoribocchi no Marumaruseikatsu</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">一个人的○○小日子</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="778494">The "lonely" girl (=hitoribocchi) meet a girl namens "to be" (=aru) and one from a foreign country (=soto kara kita) and so on. This type of humor is very funny, while bocchi is on her way to befriend her whole class. 
Not very sophisticated, but nice to watch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hitoribocchi.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="49235" type="Original Work">Katsuwo</name>
<name id="13150" type="Animation Work">C2C</name>
<name id="36182" type="Character Design">Tanaka Kie</name>
<name id="1775" type="Series Composition">Hanada Jukki</name>
<name id="36182" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Kie</name>
<name id="56369" type="Direction">Anzai Takefumi</name>
<name id="22480" type="Music">Tanaka Hidekazu</name>
<name id="13539" type="Music">Takada Ryuuichi</name>
<name id="11759" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oda Takeshi</name>
<name id="28195" type="Chief Animation Direction">Saitou Atsuko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a comedy shounen 4-koma manga by http://anidb.net/cr49235 [Katsuwo].
http://anidb.net/ch94833 [Hitori Bocchi], a girl with extreme social anxiety, has had only one http://anidb.net/ch100611 [friend] throughout elementary school. When Bocchi learns they`ll be split up after graduation, she makes a promise to her: "By the time of my middle school graduation, I`ll make friends with everyone in my class." And if she can`t do it... they won`t be friends anymore?! But Bocchi has a hard time talking to people. When she gets nervous, her legs cramp. She can`t look other people in the eye. She doesn`t even know how to make friends! Every way she thinks of to make friends ends up failing. Will Bocchi`s friend-making plan pay off?! It`s a story of the persistence of the lonely girl, Bocchi!
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="485">6.23</permanent>
<temporary count="485">7.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>230685.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20806</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37614</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hitoribocchi.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hitori_Bocchi_no_Marumaru_Seikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ひとりぼっちの○○生活</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5245</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363816</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21809</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>bocchi_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2752" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tennis</name>
<description>Tennis is yet another sport involving hitting a ball. Were it not for the copious amounts of grass involved in certain varieties, it seems hard to imagine that people would pay it any attention at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4030" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-13">
<name>mental cinema</name>
<description>The ability to imagine all kinds of things, as if they were real.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4085" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-17">
<name>unlikely duo</name>
<description>Comedy element: There is usually not only a difference in gender but also in appearance, character, and background concerning the main characters of this anime. Making it very unlikely for them to appear in the same context. Non-the-less they share the same adventure, as in "opposites attract".
These differences are exploited to come up with all sorts of wacky situations.
Examples: A demon-killer or Hero and the daughter of the Demon King. A girl from a normal family and a very intelligent and attractive boy from a very rich background (Shoujo). A very energetic outgoing girl and her very calm almost introverted best friend.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6184" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>autumn</name>
<description>Autumn, interchangeably known as fall in the US and Canada, is one of the four temperate seasons. Autumn marks the transition from summer into winter, in September (Northern Hemisphere) or March (Southern Hemisphere), when the arrival of night becomes noticeably earlier and the temperature cools considerably. One of its main features is the shedding of leaves from deciduous trees.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161967.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="94833" type="main character in" update="2019-01-20">
<rating votes="14">5.95</rating>
<name>Hitori Bocchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54316" picture="232312.jpg">Morishita Chisaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100404" type="main character in" update="2019-01-20">
<rating votes="7">2.98</rating>
<name>Sotoka Rakita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38231" picture="140074.jpg">Kurose Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100405" type="main character in" update="2019-01-20">
<rating votes="12">5.89</rating>
<name>Honshou Aru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41766" picture="242448.jpg">Kitou Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100406" type="main character in" update="2019-01-20">
<rating votes="13">6.46</rating>
<name>Sunao Nako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38297" picture="150939.jpg">Tanaka Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100610" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-27">
<rating votes="5">3.77</rating>
<name>Kurai Kako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52537" picture="225050.jpg">Ichinose Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100611" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-27">
<rating votes="7">4.50</rating>
<name>Yawara Kai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48852" picture="225071.jpg">Kohara Konomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102011" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-23">
<rating votes="4">2.53</rating>
<name>Oshie Teruyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33633" picture="151771.jpg">Takahashi Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="213452" update="2019-04-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Première déclaration</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">اعترافي الأول</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Kokuhaku</title>
<summary>April. A young girl stands alone, acting suspiciously in front of the entrance to a middle school... That girl is Hitori Bocchi, a new first year student at the school. And starting today, she`s going to become friends with everyone in her class... hopefully!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782898</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213453" update="2019-04-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当はありがとう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Actually, Thank You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Merci infiniment</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">شكرًا لك، في الحقيقة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hontou wa Arigatou</title>
<summary>I made my very first friend, Nako-chan, mad!! But I don`t know why she`s mad or how to even apologize! What do I do?! What should I do...?! That`s when--!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782899</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213454" update="2019-05-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つたわる空回り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Getting It Across by Spinning Your Wheels</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La roue tourne</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">العبور عن طريق تدوير عجلاتك</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsutawaru Karamawari</title>
<summary>"I want to go home with Honshou-san. I want to go home with Honshou-san..."
As Bocchi keeps muttering her desire, Nako offers her some advice: "First you need to go invite her."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782900</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213455" update="2019-05-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弟子になります</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Be Your Apprentice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je serai ta disciple</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">سأكون تلميذتك</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deshi ni Narimasu</title>
<summary>"I`ve been searching for you this whole time. You can`t fool my eyes."
The road to school is full of danger! As Bocchi tries to hide her presence and make it to school she runs into a bright foreigner?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782901</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215731" update="2019-05-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルアルあるある</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happens All the Time</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ça arrive tout le temps à Aru-Aru</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يحدث هذا طوال الوقت</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aruaru Aruaru</title>
<summary>Aru is an unfortunate girl. Today she unfortunately came to school wearing an elementary school backpack. She`s already come up with the perfect excuse to turn this unfortunate event into a perfect day, but...?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782902</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215732" update="2019-05-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">五七五で夏が来る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Comes in 5-7-5</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’été arrive en haïkus</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يحلّ الصّيف في 5-7-5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Go Shichi Go de Natsu ga Kuru</title>
<summary>"Fever, come to me!" Bocchi shouts, desperately wanting to skip school. She tries clenching her fist, taking a cold shower, and so on... but it all just makes her feel even better?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782903</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215733" update="2019-06-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やわらかい涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gentle Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De douces larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">دموع مرهفة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yawarakai Namida</title>
<summary>"The world is cruel."
It`s July 19th, and summer break starts tomorrow. Bocchi has... not become friends with her entire class. So she needs to make one more friend today, even if it`s only one...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782904</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215734" update="2019-06-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">外からおかえり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome Back from Elsewhere</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bienvenue à la maison</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">مرحبًا بعودتك من مكان ما</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soto kara Okaeri</title>
<summary>The new semester begins and the dazzling foreigner Sotoka is still shining bright this second semester, gaining incredible popularity with her handmade shuriken. In contrast, Bocchi really wants to talk to Kako, but it`s not going very well for her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782905</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="216330" update="2019-10-31">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216331" update="2019-09-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217154" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶好のカレーパンケーキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Perfect Curry Pancakes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les meilleurs pancakes au curry</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">فطائر كاري مقلية مثالية</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zekkou no Curry Pancake</title>
<summary>When everyone groups off cooking class, Bocchi ends up in a different group than Nako and Sotoka. But today Bocchi is Strong Bocchi. She tries talking to everyone in her group... and fails. Her imaginations keep running round and round in her head, but...?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782906</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217155" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめて言われたこと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No One Said That Before</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On ne m’avait encore jamais dit ça</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لم يقل أحد ذلك من قبل</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete Iwareta Koto</title>
<summary>Strong Bocchi powers up! Today she`s Super Strong Bocchi! And Sotoka becomes Super Strong Sotoka too! What`s making her stronger than usual? ...Her shoe?? Natto?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782907</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217156" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たぷたぷからプリプリまで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Tap-Tap to Print-Print</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Du code PIN à la cabine</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">من نقر-نقر إلى طبع-طبع</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabutabu kara Puripuri made</title>
<summary>If she doesn`t talk to all of her friends every day, they`ll forget her! While Bocchi has more friends now, she has more worries too. What should she do to ensure she remains friends with everyone? Make her CD Debut?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782908</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217157" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もしかしたらきっと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maybe I Just Might</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Si ça se trouve</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ربما قد أستطيع</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moshikashitara Kitto</title>
<summary>Finally... Finally... Bocchi has a smartphone! Now Bocchi can join the smartphone tap-tap group too. Yet first she takes her friend`s advice and greets her phone. So when it responds and she asks it to be her friend...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782909</identifier>
<identifier>hitoribocchi-no-marumaruseikatsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221844" update="2019-10-31">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221845" update="2019-09-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221846" update="2019-09-30">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221847" update="2019-09-30">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
