<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14173" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>39</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2019-07-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Ougon no Kaze</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Невероятните приключения на Джо-Джо: Вятър от злато</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">jojo5</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">JJBAGW</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">JJBA 2018</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">JoJo 2018</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ジョジョの奇妙な冒険 黄金の風</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Golden Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">JOJO 的奇妙冒險 黃金之風</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">JOJO的奇妙冒险 黄金之风</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11734" type="Prequel">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Diamond wa Kudakenai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="123101">It`s JoJo and just that already tells you that the story will be full of "I wasn`t expecting this" twists. This is exactly like that since the first episode but many may hate the last episode due to a certain lack of connections and rushed conclusion. Still good nonetheless, it`s really good up to that point.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://jojo-animation.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9371" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Haruka</name>
<name id="29284" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishimoto Shun`ichi</name>
<name id="19257" type="Direction">Takahashi Hideya</name>
<name id="2887" type="Animation Work">David Production</name>
<name id="4147" type="Character Design">Kishida Takahiro</name>
<name id="2702" type="Series Composition">Kobayashi Yasuko</name>
<name id="981" type="Original Work">Araki Hirohiko</name>
<name id="17701" type="Direction">Kimura Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="16061" type="Chief Direction">Tsuda Naokatsu</name>
<name id="6306" type="Music">Kanno Yuugo</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on Part 5, called Vento Aureo, of the JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure manga series by http://anidb.net/cr981 [Araki Hirohiko]. The arc spanned 17 volumes total and was serialized in Weekly Shonen Jump from November 1995 to April 1999.
Teenager http://anidb.net/ch96495 [Giorno] is a small-time thief, but that doesn`t mean he doesn`t have hopes and dreams! In fact, his aspirations are grand: to overthrow the head of a powerful mafia called Passione so he can finally help the people of Naples.
Before he can set his sights on the boss, though, he has to worry about his petty minions - like Leaky-eye Luca, who appears before Giorno to demand protection money for operating in the territory of Passione. A decisive battle between the two ends with Leaky-eye Luca in a coma, but also with Giorno fated for assassination.
Luckily for him, the assassin is a mafia member named http://anidb.net/ch96498 [Bruno] who also has a desire to change how they do business in the city. In the end, Bruno agrees to help Giorno infiltrate the gang by inviting him as a member of Passione. Now, Giorno, Bruno, and the other members of their group must rise through the ranks so they can get in with the boss, take him out for good, and help the city in a way only gangsters can.
Source: Tokyo Otaku Mode
Note: The first episode received a screening at a special event held at Italian Cultural Center`s Anyerri Hall in Tokyo and Japan Expo in Paris on 05.07.2018, and it was later screened at Anime Expo in LA on 07.07.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="510">8.22</permanent>
<temporary count="516">7.84</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>226420.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21131</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37991</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>38972</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://jojo-animation.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>JoJo's_Bizarre_Adventure:_Golden_Wind</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ジョジョの奇妙な冒険_(テレビアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5030</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>364692</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21519</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_jojo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2810" parentid="2831" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Italy</name>
<description>Italy, officially the Italian Republic, is a unitary parliamentary republic in Europe. Located in the heart of the Mediterranean Sea, Italy shares open land borders with France, Switzerland, Austria, Slovenia, San Marino and Vatican City.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3317" parentid="2810" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Venice</name>
<description>Venice is a city in northeastern Italy and the capital of the Veneto region. It is situated across a group of 118 small islands that are separated by canals and linked by bridges, of which there are 400. The islands are located in the shallow Venetian Lagoon, an enclosed bay that lies between the mouths of the Po and the Piave Rivers. Parts of Venice are renowned for the beauty of their settings, their architecture, and artwork. The lagoon and a part of the city are listed as a World Heritage Site.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4353" parentid="2810" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Rome</name>
<description>Rome is the capital of Italy and a special comune (named Comune di Roma Capitale). Rome also serves as the capital of the Lazio region. It is also the country`s most populated comune. It is the fourth-most populous city in the European Union by population within city limits. It is the centre of the Metropolitan City of Rome. Rome is located in the central-western portion of the Italian Peninsula, within Lazio (Latium), along the shores of the Tiber.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214356.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7131" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-05">
<name>Crunchyroll Anime Awards</name>
<description>Crunchyroll Anime Awards are annual awards given to recognize anime from the previous year. The awards were first held in January 2017. The judges create a short list in different categories and public votes for the winners are held online.</description>
<picurl>219996.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="894" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="170">8.36</rating>
<name>Kuujou Joutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuujou Joutarou has a very tough exterior, and is even rather rough and delinquent, but he also is very dedicated, intense, and loyal. He is intelligent, but usually lets his (or Star Platinum`s) fists do the talking with the enemy, even though he often has to rely on his wits to deal with stand users` attacks. Joutarou has a perpetual cooler-than-thou, slightly disinterested attitude, although he loves his mother and respects his grandfather. It is not that he is unaware of his own love and/or respect; rather, he thinks anyone can tell his emotions just by looking at him, and probably thinks further effort in portraying how he feels to be a waste of time. In the manga, he`s constantly chased by adoring girls, whom he ignores or tries to drive away. He is the main target of http://anidb.net/ch895 [Dio], who realises that Joutarou is his greatest threat.</description>
<picture>147627.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1720" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="18">7.38</rating>
<name>Star Platinum</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the strongest stands in the JoJo universe; Star Platinum possesses super human senses, strength, stamina, accuracy and speed. It can see for great distances and at great magnifications. As an added bonus, it has a "Star Finger" attack in which it extends its finger to attack.
It is similar to Dio`s The World stand, and, it turns out, can likewise be used to stop time, but that ability is only revealed in Jotaro`s epic battle with Dio Brando when Dio was about to drop a lorry on him.
The Star card symbolises, above all, hope. This is very appropriate, since Jotaro is very much the young new hope of the series. Like other physically powerful stands, Star Platinum suffers from a narrow range of activity. It can only be active within a 2-3 metre radius from Jotaro.</description>
<picture>153555.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1722" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-08-14">
<rating votes="41">8.11</rating>
<name>Mohammed Avdol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Avdol is a fortune teller, born in Cairo, Egypt. He was also one of the first to meet Dio after the vampire`s resurrection, barely escaping with his life and sanity. Before the events in the anime, he had met and barely tamed the Stand-wielding dog Iggy.</description>
<picture>147623.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1724" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="10">4.45</rating>
<name>Magician`s Red</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magician`s Red appears as a red humanoid figure with the head of a great eagle and fur-covered legs. Its abilities all involve the manipulation of fire. Abdul was born with this Stand and learned to control its power.
This fiery stand can also be remotely controlled and generates intense flames capable of melting steel within moments. The fire is hot enough to have evaporated including but not limited to metal projectiles in mid-air and sliced through railroad tracks. It also has more nuanced uses, such as suffocating foes by placing flame in front of their mouth (Red Bind), or using floating balls of psychic flame which flicker in response to enemy presence. Magician`s Red can also produce a "heat radar", a cruciform mass of flame that indicates the location of heat sources.</description>
<picture>152747.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1725" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="72">8.48</rating>
<name>Jean Pierre Polnareff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Polnareff is the stereotypical "good natured klutz": he is heroic and protective of those he loves, but is not very bright (although he has shown lots of cunning and strategy throughout the series). He is very impulsive and loud, and is quick to jump into action without considering the risk, character traits that have landed him in lots of trouble. However, he is sincerely dedicated to doing good, and is a good man to watch your back. He also fancies himself as a ladies man, but this is probably him overestimating his actual prowess (he probably has horrible luck with the ladies).
Out of all the characters in the series, Polnareff is the one that has the least problems showing his feelings, and he adds a lot of humour and warmth to what would otherwise be a pretty cold team (Kakyoin and Jotaro in particular are very cold characters). Indeed, while he may sometimes be seen as the comic relief of the series, Polnareff`s companions appreciate his good nature and trust him to help them win when a tough battle arrives.</description>
<picture>147625.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1727" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-05-02">
<rating votes="9">6.95</rating>
<name>Silver Chariot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very powerful, battle-dedicated Stand: all its powers are destructive in nature or assist him in battle. In appearance, it looks like a thin, robotic humanoid clad in medieval armour, armed with a rapier. Silver Chariot is an incredibly agile Stand, able to attack enemies with barrages of sword slashes and thrusts before the opponent can react. It can also use this agility, along with its sword, to defend and deflect attacks aimed at it (he has been able to slash fire attacks from Abdul away from him without any harm). If necessary, Polnareff can also shed Silver Chariot`s armour away, exposing its robotic form. In this form, Silver Chariot is even faster, to the point it can actually move fast enough to create doubles of itself. These doubles are not illusory: the Stand is moving at faster-than-the-eye-can-see speed between different positions. As such, were all the doubles to attack at once, it`d mean that the Stand is attacking from all those positions simultaneously, giving it incredible destructive power. Similarly, because of this same speed, attacking the doubles would be futile, as the Stand can easily move away before being harmed. Polnareff`s `secret attack` is called `shooting the sword`, in which the blade of his sword detaches at high speed. He uses this only when it is certain it will it strike, because the blade has to be reattached before Silver Chariot can be fight effectively again.</description>
<picture>155121.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1732" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="50">7.78</rating>
<name>Kakyouin Noriaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially a student who has travelled to Egypt, Dio Brando sensed his Stand powers and asked him for a demonstration, which turned out to be a fight.
Afterwards, Kakyoin is brainwashed by Dio using buds from his own cells into following his will, which is to kill Jotaro Kujo.
In the anime, he attacks Jotaro by possessing the body of a female student with his Stand. He is defeated by Jotaro either way. Jotaro soon discovers that Kakyoin was under the influence of Dio. Jotaro then used his own Stand, Star Platinum, to remove Dio`s implant buds from Kakyoin`s head in spite of the risk that it may openly attack both of them. Kakyoin is freed from Dio`s slavery afterwards to which he joins the heroes as thanks for helping them.</description>
<picture>147624.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1737" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-04-12">
<rating votes="11">5.40</rating>
<name>Hierophant Green</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hierophant Green is an elastic and remote Stand, capable of `scouting` and performing actions from far distances. Kakyoin has wielded this Stand since birth. His Stand looks humanoid but robotic with yellow eyes, no distinguishable mouth, and green-coloured appendages that resembles a watermelon in texture. The exterior features of the Stand sports a cream-white or beige colour. The composition of this Stand isn`t solid; instead, it is a compact winding coils of itself that can unravel at a moment`s notice. The Stand is approximately as tall as Kakyoin himself. Whenever the green appendages glow, the Stand is priming for an attack, such as Emerald Splash.</description>
<picture>153549.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1742" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-12-18">
<rating votes="114">8.53</rating>
<name>Joseph Joestar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joseph comes to the aid of his daughter Holly, and his grandson Joutarou. He teaches his grandson about the Stand, and for the most, has done his share of directing the group towards their goal, through fatherly advices and tactics and analysis. He deciphered Kakyouin Noriaki`s message despite cryptic depictions in regards to Dio`s power.</description>
<picture>147622.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92155" type="appears in" update="2017-11-05">
<rating votes="3">7.81</rating>
<name>Echoes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Echoes is the stand of http://anidb.net/ch81464 [Koichi Hirose].</description>
<picture>209310.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96494" type="main character in" update="2019-01-18">
<rating votes="7">8.30</rating>
<name>Guido Mista</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96495" type="main character in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="13">6.71</rating>
<name>Giorno Giovanna</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96496" type="main character in" update="2018-12-21">
<rating votes="5">5.82</rating>
<name>Narancia Ghirga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96497" type="main character in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="5">4.48</rating>
<name>Pannacotta Fugo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33512" picture="225800.jpg">Enoki Jun`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96498" type="main character in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="11">8.33</rating>
<name>Bruno Bucciarati</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96499" type="main character in" update="2019-04-29">
<rating votes="6">7.48</rating>
<name>Leone Abbacchio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98426" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="4">6.83</rating>
<name>Gold Experience</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225027.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98429" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="2">9.08</rating>
<name>Sticky Fingers</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225031.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98430" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="3">9.46</rating>
<name>Moody Blues</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225033.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98432" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="8">8.27</rating>
<name>Sex Pistols</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225036.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98433" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="4">7.85</rating>
<name>Aerosmith</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225038.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98435" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-05">
<rating votes="3">7.08</rating>
<name>Purple Haze</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225041.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98452" type="appears in" update="2018-10-06">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Namidame no Luca</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Luca is a member of Passione who extorts money from taxi drivers picking up tourists from Naples airport. He is commonly called “Leaky-eye Luca” because of injury due to which his right eye tears up.
When smashing a frog created by http://anidb.net/ch96495 [Giorno`s] http://anidb.net/ch98426 [Gold Experience] stand, Luca gets his attack reflected and falls into coma. After that the Passione boss gives an order to dispose of him.</description>
<picture>66682.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="98453" type="appears in" update="2018-10-06">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Kuujou Joutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the year 2001, Joutarou sends Kouichi to Italy in search of http://anidb.net/ch96495 [Haruno Shiobana] who reveals to be a son of http://anidb.net/ch75409 [Dio Brando].</description>
<picture>66683.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98458" type="appears in" update="2019-03-05">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Hirose Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66684.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98751" type="appears in" update="2018-10-20">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Polpo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Passione capo responsible for recruiting new members who gives http://anidb.net/ch96495 [Giorno] a lighter to be kept lit for 24 hours as a test.</description>
<picture>66736.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98752" type="appears in" update="2018-10-20">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Black Sabbath</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66737.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="99021" type="appears in" update="2018-11-17">
<rating votes="2">4.66</rating>
<name>Mario Zucchero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66766.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99022" type="appears in" update="2018-11-03">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Sale</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66767.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99023" type="appears in" update="2018-11-03">
<rating votes="2">8.39</rating>
<name>Passione</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>66768.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="99024" type="appears in" update="2018-11-09">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Soft Machine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66785.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="99439" type="appears in" update="2018-11-24">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Kraft Work</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66855.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="99528" type="main character in" update="2019-01-22">
<rating votes="6">3.57</rating>
<name>Trish Una</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99533" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-01">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Spice Girl</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67529.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="99540" type="appears in" update="2018-12-01">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Pericolo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66873.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99541" type="appears in" update="2018-12-01">
<rating votes="2">3.12</rating>
<name>Formaggio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66874.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4821" picture="186259.jpg">Fukushima Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99560" type="appears in" update="2018-12-01">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Little Feet</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66875.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="99561" type="appears in" update="2018-12-01">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Squadra Esecuzioni</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>66878.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="99562" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<rating votes="2">6.45</rating>
<name>Risotto Nero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66908.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="17634" picture="237832.jpg">Fuji Shinshuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99563" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Illuso</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66905.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99564" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Prosciutto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66903.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99565" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Pesci</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66907.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="25023" picture="70106.jpg">Kimura Subaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99566" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Melone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66906.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99567" type="appears in" update="2018-12-08">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Ghiaccio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66904.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99854" type="appears in" update="2018-12-21">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Man in the Mirror</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66945.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100271" type="appears in" update="2019-01-12">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Coco Jumbo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67044.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100272" type="appears in" update="2019-01-12">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Mr. President</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67045.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100273" type="appears in" update="2019-01-25">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Beach Boy</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67102.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100274" type="appears in" update="2019-01-12">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>The Grateful Dead</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67047.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100671" type="appears in" update="2019-02-02">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Baby Face</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67128.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100672" type="appears in" update="2019-02-02">
<rating votes="2">3.12</rating>
<name>Anita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54091" picture="225341.jpg">Sugiyama Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100725" type="main character in" update="2019-07-08">
<rating votes="4">5.36</rating>
<name>Diavolo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100726" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-08">
<rating votes="2">6.70</rating>
<name>King Crimson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235982.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="100727" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-08">
<rating votes="2">3.88</rating>
<name>Vinegar Doppio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235983.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="100728" type="appears in" update="2019-04-23">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Metallica</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67409.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100879" type="appears in" update="2019-02-16">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>White Album</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67184.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="101405" type="appears in" update="2019-03-16">
<rating votes="2">6.45</rating>
<name>Squalo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101406" type="appears in" update="2019-03-16">
<rating votes="2">5.53</rating>
<name>Clash</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231330.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101407" type="appears in" update="2019-03-16">
<rating votes="2">6.45</rating>
<name>Tiziano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101408" type="appears in" update="2019-03-16">
<rating votes="2">8.27</rating>
<name>Talking Head</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231332.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101687" type="appears in" update="2019-03-30">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Carne</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67326.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101688" type="appears in" update="2019-03-30">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Notorious B.I.G</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67327.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="102837" type="appears in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Cioccolata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="623" picture="18148.jpg">Miyauchi Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102838" type="appears in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Secco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102839" type="appears in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Green Day</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67488.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="102840" type="appears in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Oasis</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="103083" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="3">9.07</rating>
<name>Jean Pierre Polnareff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6976" picture="158591.jpg">Komatsu Fuminori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="202562" update="2018-10-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄金体験(ゴールド・エクスペリエンス)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Golden Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ougon Taiken (Gold Experience)</title>
<summary>Naples, Italy. It`s an absolutely beautiful city but it`s overrun with gangs. Koichi Hirose travels to Naples in order to find the possible son of DIO, Haruno Shiobana. Once he arrives, he meets a young man named Giorno Giovanna who ends up stealing his luggage. Koichi discovers that not only is Giorno Haruno Shiobana, but he`s also a Stand user. Meanwhile, Giorno runs into some trouble with a gang member named Leaky Eye Luca, which later gets him into trouble with another gang member named Bruno Bucciarati...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777705</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208199" update="2018-10-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブチャラティが来る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bucciarati Is Coming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bucciarati ga Kuru</title>
<summary>Bucciarati is looking for the person responsible for critically injuring Leaky Eye Luca and attacks Giorno with his Stand Zipperman. Giorno uses his own Stand named Golden Wind to retaliate. During this fight, Giorno learns that Golden Wind not only has the ability to give objects life but he also learns that it can also make his opponent`s sense go berserk.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777706</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208200" update="2019-11-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">塀の中のギャングに会え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meet the Gangster Behind the Wall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hei no Naka no Gang ni Ae</title>
<summary>Bucciarati accepts Giorno`s resolve to join Passione and has him take the test to get into the gang. The one giving the test is one of Passione`s capos, Polpo, and he`s currently in prison. Polpo gives Giorno a lit lighter and tells him to make sure that flame doesn`t go out for 24 hours. However while he`s taking the test, Koichi appears before him, looking for his passport.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777707</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208201" update="2018-11-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギャング入門</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Joining the Gang</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gang Nyuumon</title>
<summary>When the lighter was relit, Polpo`s Stand, Shadow Sabbath, appeared and attacked. Giorno is able to see through Shadow Sabbath`s weakness and faces it alongside Koichi. Koichi realizes that the arrow is involved in this situation and they realize that the point of Polpo`s exam is to try to create more Stand users.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777708</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209144" update="2018-10-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209145" update="2019-08-09">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209455" update="2019-11-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポルポの遺産を狙え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Find Polpo`s Fortune!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Porpo no Isan o Nerae!</title>
<summary>Giorno passes the test to join Passione and meets Bucciarati`s subordinates, Leone Abbacchio, Guido Mista, Narancia Ghirga, and Pannacotta Fugo. After welcoming Giorno into the team, they all head to Capri to retreive Polpo`s hidden fortune. Meanwhile, other members of Passione hear about the fortune and also go to look for it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778394</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209456" update="2018-11-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムーディー・ブルースの逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moody Jazz`s Counterattack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moody Blues no Gyakushuu</title>
<summary>Bucciarati and his gang are attacked by someone`s Stand on their way to Capri. The members start disappearing one after another and then Giorno purposely gets attacked to help find out who exactly is attacking them. Abbacchio still doesn`t trust the newbie, but accepts his resolve and uses his Moody Jazz. He replays what happened to Narancia and then tries to figure out the enemy`s abilities along with Bucciarati.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779043</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209457" update="2018-12-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">セックス・ピストルズ登場 その①</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Six Bullets Appears, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sex Pistols Toujou: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Bucciarati is able to defeat Zucchero, a member of Passione who was after Polpo`s fortune and also save his friends. But they find out that Zucchero was in contact with someone else on Capri and was planning to meet up with them, thanks to Moody Jazz`s ability. Mista and Giorno decide to head over to Capri first to try to find Zucchero`s partner and get rid of him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779044</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209458" update="2018-12-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">セックス・ピストルズ登場 その②</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Six Bullets Appears, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sex Pistols Toujou: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Giorno and Mista arrive at Capri and find Zucchero`s partner, Sale. Mista uses his Stand Six Bullets to fight Sale, but Sale`s Arts &amp; Crafts proves to be a formidable enemy. Mista manages to fight back but then realizes he`s left with only four bullets...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779045</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210293" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボスからの第一指令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Mission from the Boss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boss kara no Daiichi Shirei</title>
<summary>Bucciarati and his team managed to safely retrieve Polpo`s hidden treasure of 10 billion lire and they are visited by another capo from Passione, Pericolo. Pericolo accepts the 10 billion lire from Bucciarati and immediately gives them an order from the boss. Their mission is to protect the boss`s daughter, Trish Una, from a group of traitors within the organization.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779046</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210294" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗殺者チーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hitman Team</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ansatsusha Team</title>
<summary>Narancia was attacked by Formaggio`s Stand, Tiny Feet, and slowly grows smaller and smaller. But Narancia fights back with his own Stand, Li`l Bomber. While being pursued by Narancia Formaggio looks back on something that the boss had done to the hitman team to send them a message...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779047</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210295" update="2018-12-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナランチャのエアロスミス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Narancia`s Li`l Bomber</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Narancia no Aerosmith</title>
<summary>Formaggio uses his Stand, Tiny Feet, to shrink Narancia so he`s only a few centimeters tall and captures him so that he can force him to tell him where the boss`s daughter Trish is. He puts Narancia into a bottle along with a spider and questions him on Trish`s whereabouts. Narancia is determined not to tell Formaggio anything and uses Li`l Bomber to fight back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779048</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210296" update="2019-01-14">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボスからの第二指令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Second Mission from the Boss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boss kara no Daini Shirei</title>
<summary>In order to protect Trish from the Hitman Team, Bucciarati and crew`s second mission from the boss was to go find a key in Pompei for some kind of vehicle that should aid them later on. Following orders, Giorno, Abbacchio, and Fugo head to Pompei to retrieve the key. When they get there, Fugo notices a suspicious shadow reflecting in a mirror that happened to be placed on one of the pillars there...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779049</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211279" update="2019-01-14">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マン・イン・ザ・ミラーとパープル・ヘイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mirror Man and Purple Smoke</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Man in the Mirror to Purple Haze</title>
<summary>The person hiding in the mirror was Illuso from the Hitman Team. Fugo ends up being dragged into the mirror by Illuso`s Stand, Mirrorman. Fugo then summons his own Stand, Purple Smoke. Despite Giorno wanting to find Fugo, Abbacchio decides to go look for the key, since that was their mission. However, once Abbacchio finds the key, he also gets dragged into the mirror world...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779050</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211518" recap="true" update="2019-01-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジョジョの奇妙な冒険 黄金の風 Inizio del vento aureo</title>
<title xml:lang="en">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Golden Wind - Inizio del Vento Aureo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Ougon no Kaze - Inizio del Vento Aureo</title>
<summary>We take a look back at Giorno`s adventures so far.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780774</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211519" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フィレンツェ行き超特急</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Express Train to Florence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Firenze Yuki Choutokkyuu</title>
<summary>"Take Trish to Venice." With their next order from the boss, Bucciarati and his crew head to Naples Station. "Use the key at the water fountain with the turtle on the 6th platform." They find the water fountain, but can`t find the place to use the key. Meanwhile, Proscuitto and Pesci from the Hitman Team follow Bucciarati and the others to Naples Station. Bucciarati figures out the mystery behind the key and gets on the express train to Florence, and Proscuitto and Pesci follow.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780976</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211520" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">偉大なる死(ザ・グレイトフル・デッド) その①</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Thankful Death Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idai Naru Shi (The Grateful Dead): Sono 1</title>
<summary>In order to draw out Bucciarati and his crew, who are hiding somewhere on the train, Proscuitto uses his Stand The Thankful Dead`s powers and turns everyone on the train old. Bucciarati and the others were hiding inside the turtle, but they also start to age. Mista goes out to try to fight back, but he`s caught by Pesci`s Stand, Fisher Man.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780977</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211521" update="2019-02-04">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">偉大なる死(ザ・グレイトフル・デッド) その②</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Thankful Death Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idai Naru Shi (The Grateful Dead): Sono 2</title>
<summary>Number Six from Six Bullets manages to warn Bucciarati about the enemies and fights back, but The Thankful Death`s powers are taking a toll on him. Bucciarati steels his resolve and throws himself out with Proscuitto out of the train that`s going 150kph. Barely hanging onto life, Proscuitto uses The Thankful Dead again. Pesci decides to take Proscuitto`s resolve to heart and attacks Bucciarati.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780978</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211986" update="2019-08-09">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211987" update="2019-02-11">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベイビィ・フェイス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Babyhead</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baby Face</title>
<summary>After defeating Proscuitto and Pesci, Bucciarati and the others head to Venice in a car. Melone from the Hitman Team finds some of Bucciarati`s blood at the scene where the train had stopped and then activates Babyhead. The powerful remote-control Stand created by assaulting a woman on the train then goes after Bucciarati.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780979</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211988" update="2019-02-19">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴェネツィアへ向かえ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Head to Venice!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Venezia e Mukae!</title>
<summary>Using Babyhead`s Stand`s ability to turn human parts into other things, Giorno uses his Golden Wind to make parts for the human body. He rebuilds his own body and fights back. Meanwhile, another member of the Hitman Team who`s also after Trish, Ghiaccio, was trying to regroup with Melone and was driving to Giorno`s location.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780980</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211989" update="2019-02-19">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホワイト・アルバム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">White Album</title>
<summary>Ghiaccio`s Stand, White Ice is able to envelop him like a bodysuit and able to freeze everything around him to extremely low temperatures. Giorno and Mista somewhat make it to Venice, despite being partially frozen by Ghiaccio. But in order to try to get away from Ghiaccio, Giorno drives their car into the canal and they get stuck. Mista tries to sacrifice himself, but Giorno tells him that what`s important right now isn`t for him to sacrifice himself but for him to have resolve.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780981</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211990" update="2019-03-06">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボスからの最終指令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Mission from the Boss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boss kara no Saishuu Shirei</title>
<summary>Mista and Giorno were able to defeat Ghiaccio. They then confirm the mission on the disc and head to the location they`re supposed to take Trish. Bucciarati goes up the tower with Trish, but while they`re in the elevator, Trish suddenly disappears. Bucciarati then realizes what the boss`s true motives are.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780982</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212614" update="2019-03-06">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キング・クリムゾンの謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of Emperor Crimson</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">King Crimson no Nazo</title>
<summary>Bucciarati finds out that the boss`s true motive is to eliminate Trish because of her relationship with him, causing him to betray the boss and save Trish. Meanwhile, Giorno feels something bizarre is going on as they waited for Bucciarati`s return. The boss`s Stand, Emperor Crimson rises.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780983</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212615" update="2019-04-08">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガッツの「G」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The "G" in Guts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guts no `G`</title>
<summary>Because of their own wills and their sense of justice, Bucciarati and the others end up betraying the organization. Trish also wants to find out who her father truly is, so she tells the others that her mother met her father in Sardinia. They all decide to have a meal in Venice before they leave and Narancia is suddenly attacked by a Stand. The boss`s own personal elite guard was now on the move.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782558</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212616" update="2019-04-08">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クラッシュとトーキング・ヘッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crush and Talking Mouth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Crash to Talking Head</title>
<summary>The Stand that attacked Narancia was named Crush and belonged to Squallo, a member of the boss`s elite guard. On top of that, Narancia suddenly can only say the exact opposite of what he`s thinking, thanks to the ability of Talking Mouth, the Stand of Squallo`s partner, Tiziano. Using Narancia, Squallo and Tiziano throw the team into chaos. The two elite guard members put Narancia in danger, but he boldly faces them so they can get out of Venice safely.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782559</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212617" update="2019-04-08">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノトーリアスB・I・G[ビッグ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Notorious Chase</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Notorious Big</title>
<summary>After defeating Squallo and Tiziano, Bucciarati and the others head off to Sardinia to find out about the boss`s past. They head to Marco Polo International Airport in order to get a jet, but a strange man was following them. Mista manages to kill the strange Stand user before they`re able to call upon their Stand. Even though they`re a bit put off at how simple that was, they get onto the jet and fly off. But once they`re on the jet, Giorno hears a weird noise...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782560</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212618" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スパイス・ガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spice Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Spice Girl</title>
<summary>The man who was killed by Mista at the airport, Carne, was first able to activate his stand, Notorious Chase, after he died. Notorious Chase reacts to movement and it attacks Giorno, resulting in him losing both arms. This makes him unable to use Golden Wind’s abilities, but he gives life to his brooch and recreates his left hand. Trish decides that she’s going to protect that left hand and goes after the brooch, but she’s detected. When all seemed lost, Trish’s Stand, Spicy Lady, was activated.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782561</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213146" recap="true" update="2019-04-08">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジョジョの奇妙な冒険 黄金の風 determinazione</title>
<title xml:lang="en">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Golden Wind - Determinazione</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Ougon no Kaze - Determinazione</title>
<summary>We take another look back at the path that led Giorno and the others to where they are now.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780984</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213794" update="2019-11-26">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213795" update="2019-07-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214707" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほんの少し昔の物語 ~ぼくの名はドッピオ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Little Story from the Past: My Name Is Doppio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honno Sukoshi Mukashi no Monogatari: Boku no Na wa Doppio</title>
<summary>The summer of 1965... A woman gave birth to a baby boy inside a women’s prison that sat in the middle of the Adriatic Sea. Bizarrely, she hadn’t been near any man in two years, but somehow got pregnant now. Time passed, and a young man arrived at Sardinia. His name was Doppio. Meanwhile, the leader of the Hitman Team, Risotto, as well as Trish, Bucciarati and the rest of his team all arrive at Sardinia. Doppio encounters Risotto at Costa Smeralda.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782562</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="214708" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キング・クリムゾン vs. メタリカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emperor Crimson vs. Metallic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">King Crimson vs. Metallica</title>
<summary>Risotto figures out that Doppio must be a Stand user that the boss trusts in deeply because he’s able to hear the noise from a certain Stand. Risotto then uses his Stand Metallic against him. Metallic is able to control magnetic force and attacks Doppio. Doppio uses the part of the boss’s power he received from him. While they’re fighting, Risotto realizes that Doppio’s personality and actions seem to be changing and he realizes exactly who Doppio is.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782563</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="214709" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今にも落ちて来そうな空の下で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beneath a Sky on the Verge of Falling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima ni mo Ochite Kitasou na Sora no Shita de</title>
<summary>Doppio is on the brink of death after his fight with Risotto, but he manages to finish him off by having Narancia’s Li’l Bomber attack him. Bucciarati and Narancia go up onto the cliff to find the enemy that Li’l Bomber found and Abbacchio stays on the shore so he can use Moody Jazz to replay who exactly took the photo of Trish’s mother 15 years ago.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782564</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215735" update="2019-05-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目的地はローマ! コロッセオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get to the Roman Colosseum!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mokutekichi wa Roma! Colosseo</title>
<summary>fter his death, Abbacchio was able to leave the others a copy of the boss’s face and fingerprints with Moody Jazz’s replay. The others try to find out who the boss is with the fingerprint and suddenly get contacted by someone. The mysterious man tells them that the boss’s name is Diavolo and tells them that the secret behind defeating him lies in the arrow. Bucciarati and the others head to Rome to meet him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783786</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215736" update="2019-05-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グリーン・ディとオアシス その①</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Green Tea and Sanctuary, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Green Day to Oasis: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Bucciarati and the others end up facing off with 2 assassins sent by the boss, Cioccolata and Secco. Cioccolata uses his Stand Green Tea against them. His Stand creates a mold that makes living creatures rot away and he unleashed it upon the fishing village that Bucciarati and his crew arrived at. Bucciarati and the others manage to evade the attack for the most part and try to keep heading towards the Colosseum, but then Secco also uses his Stand, Sanctuary.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783787</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215737" update="2019-06-06">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グリーン・ディとオアシス その②</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Green Tea and Sanctuary, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Green Day to Oasis: Sono 2</title>
<summary>As soon as Ciccolata went up in a helicopter, Green Tea’s ability’s murderous range grew even more. He then flies to Rome and tries to spread his murderous mold. Bucciarati and the others go to stop Ciccolata, but Secco gets in their way. Giorno and Mista go after Ciccolata while Bucciarati faces off with Secco.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783788</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215738" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グリーン・ディとオアシス その③</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Green Tea and Sanctuary, Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Green Day to Oasis: Sono 3</title>
<summary>After a fierce battle, Giorno and Mista were able to strike down Cioccolata. However, Secco happens to receive one last voicemail from Cioccolata and finds out there’s a secret to defeating the boss at the Colosseum. Secco realizes that Cioccolata probably lost and heads to the Colosseum to find out what this secret is. Bucciarati attacks Secco in order to stop him from getting to the Colosseum, but Secco’s Sanctuary gives him trouble. An intense battle then takes place right in front of the Colosseum.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783789</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="216113" recap="true" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジョジョの奇妙な冒険 黄金の風 destino</title>
<title xml:lang="en">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Golden Wind - Destino</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Ougon no Kaze - Destino</title>
<summary>Another look back at the adventures that Giorno and the rest of the crew have had to this point.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>782565</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217717" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そいつの名はディアボロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">His Name Is Diavolo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soitsu no Na wa Diavolo</title>
<summary>Bucciarati managed to win in his battle against Secco, but his body was reaching its limit. The boss had already arrived in Rome and used Doppio to get closer to Bucciarati. Bucciarati’s condition worsens and he mistakes Doppio as Trish and Doppio plays along. The man with the secret to defeating the boss was waiting for them inside the Colosseum. Time then skips and the boss’s true identity is revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783790</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217718" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鎮魂歌[レクイエム]は静かに奏でられる その①</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Requiem Quietly Plays, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Requiem wa Shizuka ni Kanaderareru: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Jean Pierre Polnareff holds the key to defeating the boss. The one who appeared before him wasn’t Bucciarati or his squad, but the leader of Passione, Diavolo himself. Diavolo tries to eliminate Polnareff once and for all and summons Emperor Crimson, but then Polnareff summons Silver Chariot and it is pierced with the arrow. That’s when something happens to everyone in or nearby the Colosseum. They find themselves losing strength and all fall asleep. After waking from their deep sleep, they all realize something has changed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783791</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217719" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鎮魂歌[レクイエム]は静かに奏でられる その②</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Requiem Quietly Plays, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Requiem wa Shizuka ni Kanaderareru: Sono 2</title>
<summary>After being pierced with the arrow, Silver Chariot becomes Chariot Requiem and goes berserk. As a result, everyone’s minds are switched. Among all the confusion, Polnareff reveals himself to Giorno and the others. If someone with power uses the arrow, they would be able to obtain the power to rule over the minds of all living creatures. Polnareff lets them know that there is more to their Stand’s usual Stand ability if they have access to the arrow. Giorno and crew reunite with Bucciarati and they all go to try to steal the arrow back from Chariot Requiem.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783792</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217720" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディアボロ浮上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diavolo Surfaces</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Diavolo Fujou</title>
<summary>Because of Chariot Requiem’s true power, something starts happening to Polnareff’s body. This just makes Bucciarati and the others try to get the arrow back even quicker. But then Giorno states that Diavolo’s mind is possessing one of their bodies. Who will get to the arrow first, Giorno and the rest of the crew or Diavolo? Finally, Diavolo shows himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783793</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217721" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">王の中の王[キング・オブ・キングス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King of Kings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">King of Kings</title>
<summary>Diavolo had been possessing Trish’s mind and is able to solve the mystery behind Chariot Requiem, making it possible for him to take the arrow. Giorno and the others attack in order to get the arrow back, but their attacks are futile against Eulogy. The moment that Diavolo tries to pierce his Stand with the arrow, Bucciarati completely destroys Chariot Requiem. Giorno and the others begin their final showdown with the almighty Diavolo.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783794</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218366" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴールド・E[エクスペリエンス]・レクイエム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Golden Wind Requiem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gold Experience Requiem</title>
<summary>Giorno takes the arrow that Bucciarati and the others had acquired and stabs Golden Wind with it during the final battle with Diavolo. Golden Wind evolves into Golden Wind Requiem and doesn’t even allow Diavolo to reach the truth of “dying” and he is forced to meet an end that never truly has an end.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783795</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218367" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眠れる奴隷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sleeping Slave</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemureru Dorei</title>
<summary>Before Giorno had met Bucciarati and the others, a certain florist appeared before Bucciarati. The florist tells him that his daughter had jumped off the roof of an apartment holding a strange looking rock and he wanted to find out the truth behind that bizarre incident. Mista is put in charge of this mission and he goes to track down Scolippi, a sculptor who was the daughter’s boyfriend. Scolippi tells Mista that they are all slaves to destiny, and then a bizarre rock appears in front of them, which tells them Bucciarati’s fate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783796</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218574" update="2019-07-08">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218575" update="2019-08-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219227" update="2019-08-09">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219228" update="2019-08-09">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224628" update="2019-11-26">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224629" update="2019-11-26">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224630" update="2019-11-26">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224631" update="2019-11-26">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224632" update="2019-11-26">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2f</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
