<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14514" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-04-10</startdate>
<enddate>2019-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sewayaki Kitsune no Senko-san</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">世話やきキツネの仙狐さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Helpful Fox Senko-san</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">도우미 여우 센코 씨</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">贤惠幼妻仙狐小姐</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11469" approval="3" total="14">Flying Witch</anime>
<anime id="12091" approval="3" total="8">Kobayashi-san Chi no Maidragon</anime>
<anime id="14570" approval="1" total="7">Nekopara (2020)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="614578">The theme is caring for others. A very loving anime. See one ep and see if this is what you want. Definitely better than its poor rating.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="166014">Personal stress management with Senko 

Pretty much a relaxing comedy series.
Senko a Fox priestess who is being the ``wife`` taking care of our stressed out and tired
main character which I`m pretty sure many of us can relate to.

definitely worth a look.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://senkosan.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1067" type="Animation Work">Doga Kobo</name>
<name id="3779" type="Character Design">Ooshima Miwa</name>
<name id="22911" type="Series Composition">Nakamura Yoshiko</name>
<name id="56774" type="Original Work">Rimukoro</name>
<name id="28622" type="Direction">Koshida Tomoaki</name>
<name id="3779" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ooshima Miwa</name>
<name id="10771" type="Chief Animation Direction">Soga Atsushi</name>
<name id="12511" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kumagai Katsuhiro</name>
<name id="31562" type="Music">Fujisawa Yoshiaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a comedy manga by http://anidb.net/cr56774 [Rimukoro].
Sometimes the cure to a hard day`s work is the tender love and care of...a fox girl?! Salaryman http://anidb.net/ch100846 [Nakano]`s stressful life is suddenly intruded upon by the fox, http://anidb.net/ch100847 [Senko-san], who is eager to help him heal his exhaustion. Whether she`s cooking, cleaning, or finding other ways to care for Nakano, she`s there to take away his stress!
Source: funimation</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="625">5.48</permanent>
<temporary count="630">6.74</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>231094.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21908</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38759</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://senkosan.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Helpful_Fox_Senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>世話やきキツネの仙狐さん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5249</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366350</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21895</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sewayakisenko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07RC7GR6G</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3017" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-04-21">
<name>human - god relationship</name>
<description>The anime explores the relationship between a mere human and a god. This usually comes with a "sense of foreboding".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3018" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>first person view</name>
<description>The events in this anime are shown from the perspective of one or several characters, as if you watch the scenes through their eyes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3504" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>sake</name>
<description>Sake, generally referred to as a Japanese rice wine, is an alcoholic beverage made by fermenting rice.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215208.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4352" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-11">
<name>censored uncensored version</name>
<description>Even the DVD and Blu-ray releases do not let you see everything you were expecting to, and you will have to live with censorship in the show. That normally applies to fan service, but may also apply to gore and violence. A very common example is characters without nipples, as in http://anidb.net/a6083 [KissXSis]; in other cases, something such as steam or foam stays in the camera`s way, like in http://anidb.net/a6531 [Kanamemo]. In some shows, the censorship in the disk releases is even stronger than in the TV version, while others may use creative censorship as a replacement for the removed fan service or even as a joke.
This does not apply to censorship of what Japanese pornography laws still require to be censored.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5409" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-22">
<name>longing</name>
<description>One or more characters yearn for some person or some place.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6184" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>autumn</name>
<description>Autumn, interchangeably known as fall in the US and Canada, is one of the four temperate seasons. Autumn marks the transition from summer into winter, in September (Northern Hemisphere) or March (Southern Hemisphere), when the arrival of night becomes noticeably earlier and the temperature cools considerably. One of its main features is the shedding of leaves from deciduous trees.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161967.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7222" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-30">
<name>groping</name>
<description>Groping is the act of subjecting another person to unwanted sexual touching.</description>
<picurl>68310.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="100845" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-31">
<rating votes="14">7.39</rating>
<name>Shiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100846" type="main character in" update="2019-03-31">
<rating votes="5">6.29</rating>
<name>Nakano Kuroto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100847" type="main character in" update="2019-05-29">
<rating votes="21">9.65</rating>
<name>Senko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42471" picture="242433.jpg">Waki Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100848" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-31">
<rating votes="10">7.80</rating>
<name>Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100849" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-31">
<rating votes="9">7.01</rating>
<name>Kouenji Yasuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102065" type="appears in" update="2019-06-26">
<rating votes="3">1.39</rating>
<name>Mitaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4821" picture="186259.jpg">Fukushima Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102066" type="appears in" update="2019-04-10">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Nakano no Sobo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20320" picture="151663.jpg">Katsura Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102067" type="appears in" update="2019-04-10">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Nakano (Shounen)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44509" picture="237813.jpg">Matsumoto Sara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102521" type="appears in" update="2019-06-25">
<rating votes="2">1.99</rating>
<name>Yoko-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102522" type="appears in" update="2019-06-25">
<rating votes="2">2.50</rating>
<name>Don Tanuki-otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103738" type="appears in" update="2019-06-20">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Nakano no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103739" type="appears in" update="2019-06-20">
<rating votes="2">1.99</rating>
<name>Joushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103881" type="appears in" update="2019-06-25">
<rating votes="2">3.97</rating>
<name>Daikitsune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="213576" update="2019-04-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">存分に甘やかしてくれよう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Going to Pamper Him to His Heart`s Content!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zonbun ni Amayakashite Kureyou</title>
<summary>It was another long, hard day at work for Kuroto Nakano... until he came home to find a demigod fox cooking dinner for him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783549</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213577" update="2019-03-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恥ずかしがらずともよいよい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Be Shy, Now!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hazukashigarazu to mo Yoiyoi</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783550</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213578" update="2019-04-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おぬしが幸せならそれでよい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">As Long as You`re Happy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onushi ga Shiawase nara Sore de Yoi</title>
<summary>Nakano and Senko`s neighbor finally confronts them! Fortunately she`s a fan of Little Yoko, Inari Girl. Later, Senko and Nakano visit the supermarket.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783538</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213579" update="2019-05-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なぜ休日に仕事をせねばならんのじゃ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Why Must You Work on a Day Off!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naze Kyuujitsu ni Shigoto o Seneba Naran no ja!?</title>
<summary>Senko tries to help Nakano get up for work on a Sunday, then gets into a bit of a mess with the household appliances.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783539</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215645" update="2019-05-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しっぽなら, わらわのがあるじゃろ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ve Got a Tail, Too, You Know?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shippo nara, Warawa no ga Aru Jaro?</title>
<summary>Shiro does her best to please Nakano, but gets a little more than she bargained for. Later, Senko scrubs Nakano`s back for him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783540</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215646" update="2019-05-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もふりたいだけじゃろ, おぬし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Just Want to Fluff More</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mo Furitai dake Jaro, Onushi</title>
<summary>Shiro drops by to play video games with Nakano. Later, Senko receives a gift from Koenji.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783541</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215647" update="2019-06-28">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おぬし, 別のキツネの匂いがするのう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Smell Like Another Fox</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onushi, Betsu no Kitsune no Nioi ga Suru nou</title>
<summary>Senko shows Nakano her amazing massage skills. Later, Nakano misses the last train home, but gets some help from Shiro.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783542</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="215648" update="2019-05-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わらわが忘れさせてやろう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Make You Forget All About It</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warawa ga Wasuresasete Yarou!</title>
<summary>Shiro takes everyone to the beach for a day of summer fun. While there, Kuroto encounters a mysterious stranger.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783543</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217287" update="2019-06-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こうすれば恥ずかしくないじゃろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is This Less Embarrassing for You?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kou Sureba Hazukashikunai Jaro</title>
<summary>Senko notices Nakano drooling over gratin on TV, and enlists Koenji and Shiro to help her make some. Later, Nakano gets a haircut!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783544</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217288" update="2019-06-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たまには童心に返るのもよいじゃろ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Nice to Let Your Inner Child Out Now and Then, Isn`t It?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tama ni wa Doushin ni Kaeru no mo Yoi Jaro?</title>
<summary>A thick layer of fresh snow provides loads of fun for Senko and Nakano. However, the mood changes when the mysterious stranger returns!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783545</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217289" update="2019-06-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今夜は少し荒れそうじゃの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Going to Be a Rough Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kon`ya wa Sukoshi Aresou ja no</title>
<summary>Senko`s Izakaya welcomes Nakano after a rough day at work. Later, Nakano decides to visit his mother and father.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783546</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217290" update="2019-06-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それでも, あやつを......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Still...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soredemo, Ayatsu o......</title>
<summary>Nakano returns home to find that Senko is not there. What will be the outcome of Senko`s meeting with Sora?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783547</identifier>
<identifier>the-helpful-fox-senko-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218269" update="2019-06-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218270" update="2019-06-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226654" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 1</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ①</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226655" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ②</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226656" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ③</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226657" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 4</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ④</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226658" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 5</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ⑤</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226659" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 6</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ⑥</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226660" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 7</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 7</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ⑦</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226661" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 8</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 8</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ⑧</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226662" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 9</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 9</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ⑨</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226663" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 10</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ⑩</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226664" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 11</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 11</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ⑪</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226665" update="2020-02-04">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーパー仙狐さんタイム 12</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Senko-san Time 12</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슈퍼 센코씨 타임 ⑫</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
