<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5975" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Toaru Majutsu no Index</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Индекс Волшебства</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Некий магический индекс</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">어떤 마술의 금서목록</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Historia pewnego magicznego Indexu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">To Aru Majutsu no Index</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Toaru Majutsu no Kinsho Mokuroku</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">То ару маджіцу но Індекс</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Index</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Index1</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">とある魔術の禁書目録[インデックス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">A Certain Magical Index</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">คัมภีร์คาถาต้องห้าม อินเด็กซ์</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">魔法禁書目錄</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">魔法禁书目录</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7599" type="Sequel">Toaru Majutsu no Index II</anime>
<anime id="6460" type="Side Story">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun</anime>
<anime id="14440" type="Side Story">Toaru Kagaku no Accelerator</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9772" approval="95" total="106">Strike the Blood</anime>
<anime id="3348" approval="11" total="22">Fate/Stay Night</anime>
<anime id="3408" approval="9" total="20">Shakugan no Shana</anime>
<anime id="10182" approval="4" total="14">Mahouka Koukou no Rettousei</anime>
<anime id="458" approval="4" total="10">Mahou Tsukai ni Taisetsu na Koto</anime>
<anime id="11739" approval="2" total="18">Boku no Hero Academia</anime>
<anime id="7568" approval="2" total="15">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai</anime>
<anime id="157" approval="2" total="7">Psychic Academy Aura Banshou</anime>
<anime id="2435" approval="1" total="4">Gakuen Alice</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="28">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="269894">Fun watch, but there is absolutely no plot build-up. Accelerator makes the series a little bit better.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="219674">One of the best visuals I have seen in anime. The story is pretty engaging too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="313812">Magic, Science, and Alchemy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="241743">What made this anime worthwhile was last order :3</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="306731">I`m recommending it for sci-fi and shounen fans :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="148500">I really enjoyed this series.  The characters were not cookie-cutterish, and grew throughout the series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="372341">I really like the show.  But I wish it were longer though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="460841">Expect some few disappointments for the first several episodes, after getting a jumpstart, prepare to meet the unexpectedly great plots and twists revealed on the mid-part up to the next seasons.
Appreciating this anime will be greater if one went through the process of reading the good amount of light novel of the same title.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="65380">Yeah, I can recommend it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="780947">that man kamijo even with that right hand of his has a big pair on him lol and that punch. Definitely expected more from this but it was okay. find myself like most it seems drawn to misaka wish she were in it more but thats why theres a whole series with her. Loved the first ending song too</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="188268">it would be nice to see a second one ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="478043">A very cool and interesting story with fun characters. Science vs Magic stuff can get pretty boring, but the way it is portrayed in this anime is pretty awesome.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="459124">It is shiny, it has a good plot, it has great sequels. Biri biri makes it even better</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="405748">Nice easy anime to watch. High rewatchable value. Typical shonen anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="122200">Very good animation, sound, and visuals</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="244867">It`s made of awesomness!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="293766">Index was THE BREAKING POINT in anime. It combines so many aspects of genre into one action packed, thriller series! It has just about anything anyone could ever ask for in any story. Even for those in the minority groups! It has the thrill and suspense of a detective story, the action and heart of a sports film, perfect display of your typical herione, a sci-fi/fantasy setting, and even some echii comedy is thrown in the mix * nudge, nudge, wink, wink*. Index is unique, mind blowing, and will keep you on your toes. Truly a work of art.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="313575">Simply great. And the protagonist isn`t a wimp. Great slowly developing plot. Great music and characters, and a nice amount of sci fi.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="242116">Actually I wasnt sure about this anime. But it has all, putting ecchi aside, what I need to approve that this one is pretty good. And its one 24 episodes series with a sequel, so definitely longer than most of the 12-13 ep animes.
Comedy 3/3
Story 2/3
Characters 3/3</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://toaru-project.com/index_1_2/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="4112" type="Music">Iuchi Maiko</name>
<name id="1603" type="Direction">Nishikiori Hiroshi</name>
<name id="1795" type="Character Design">Tanaka Yuuichi</name>
<name id="8138" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawakami Tetsuya</name>
<name id="9564" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamashita Yuu</name>
<name id="1795" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Yuuichi</name>
<name id="7260" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iwataki Satoshi</name>
<name id="9564" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamashita Yuu</name>
<name id="3391" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hasegawa Shin`ya</name>
<name id="3389" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kimoto Shigeki</name>
<name id="8138" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawakami Tetsuya</name>
<name id="14053" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamura Shunsuke</name>
<name id="9748" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sano Keiichi</name>
<name id="3896" type="Music">I`ve Sound</name>
<name id="6311" type="Series Composition">Akahoshi Masanao</name>
<name id="6886" type="Original Work">Kamachi Kazuma</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr6886 [Kamachi Kazuma], illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr6874 [Haimura Kiyotaka].
Set in Academy City, a city of scientifically advanced superhuman students, located to the west of Tokyo, in a world where magic is also real. http://anidb.net/ch2342 [Kamijou Touma]`s right hand, the Imagine Breaker, can negate all magic, psychic, or divine powers, but not his own bad luck. One day he finds a young girl, http://anidb.net/ch870 [Index], hanging on his balcony railing. She turns out to be a nun from the Church of England, and her mind has been implanted with the Index Librorum Prohibitorum — all the magical texts the Church has removed from circulation. His encounter leads him to meet others from the secret world of science and magic and right into an adventure where science and magic collide.
Touma`s unusual power then places him at the centre of conflicts relating magicians and science-based espers in Academy City. As Touma tries to help and protect his friends, he learns the people he knows are not quite what they appear to be. To make thinks worse he begins to attract the unwanted attention of powerful magicians and espers alike, as they try to unravel the secrets of Academy City and Index.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7167">6.09</permanent>
<temporary count="7230">7.43</temporary>
<review count="3">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>233291.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10044</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4654</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5955</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4337</identifier>
<identifier>tuwdue</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://toaru-project.com/index_1_2/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>A_Certain_Magical_Index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>とある魔術の禁書目録</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1487</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331523</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10306</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2222</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2638</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2008/toarumajyutsu_no_index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10702</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1403" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-10">
<name>nun</name>
<description>A nun is a member of a religious community of women, typically one living under vows of poverty, chastity, and obedience. She may have decided to dedicate her life to serving all other living beings, or she might be an ascetic who voluntarily chose to leave mainstream society and live her life in prayer and contemplation in a monastery or convent. The term "nun" is applicable to Catholics (eastern and western traditions), Orthodox Christians, Anglicans, Lutherans, Jains, Buddhists, Taoists, Hindus and some other religious traditions.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>165755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4136" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-03-05">
<name>sudden loli companion appearance</name>
<description>The main character meets a preadolescent girl in an unexpected way becoming a friend / partner of the main character.
(The term loli is short for Lolita meaning a girl in preadolescent age. Typical attributes are moe, cute, and innocent.)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4302" parentid="2876" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>Christianity</name>
<description>Christianity is a monotheistic religion based on the life and teachings of Jesus of Nazareth as presented in the New Testament. http://anidb.net/t524 [Christians] believe Jesus is the son of God, God having become man and the saviour of humanity. Christians, therefore, commonly refer to Jesus as Christ or Messiah.
Source: EN Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5788" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-03">
<name>experiments</name>
<description>Involves (para-)scientific experiments.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="870" type="main character in" update="2019-04-07">
<rating votes="457">3.25</rating>
<name>Index</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Index, also known by her full name, Index Librorum Prohibitorum, is the series` co-heroine, a young nun from Necessarius ("Church of Necessary Evil"), a branch of the Church of England. Her mind has been implanted with the 103,000 magical texts of the Index-Librorum-Prohibitorum as she possess Photographic memory at the cost of her own memories, or so the church authorities say. Her sorcery name is Dedicatus545. She is said to have 15% of memory space left to use in daily activities, which allows her to live normally for less than a year. However, all of this is a lie and are the church`s plan to make her unable to betray, by "maintenance" her once the memory has come to its limit.</description>
<picture>232175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2342" type="main character in" update="2019-04-07">
<rating votes="698">6.35</rating>
<name>Kamijou Touma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamijou Touma is the main protagonist of Toaru Majutsu no Index and a recurring character in its spin-off Railgun.
He has the lowest psychic rank possible at Level 0— largely because the people testing psychic abilities cannot detect or classify his abilities. Due to this, the founder of Academy City considers him neither a Psychic nor a Magician but rather a normal person with a unique ability.
Actually his power is Imagine Breaker (幻想殺し, Gensou Goroshi, "Imagine Killer"), a power which negates all magic, psychic, or divine powers but also his own good luck. He tends to stay away from trouble but possesses a strong sense of justice, albeit somewhat shallow and dogmatic. In order to save Index from the need of a memory reset, he had activated her self-protection system and destroyed the spell responsible for her mind strain but ended up losing all of his past memories, including everything about Index, when he came in contact with Feather of Light (光の羽, Hikari no Hane); this remains a secret to everyone except himself, the doctor that takes care of him (who is, unknown to Touma, the Heaven Canceler) and later Mikoto in the sixteenth novel. Though he no longer remembers the past, he has not completely forgotten the people he cares about.
Throughout the series, he tries to live his life normally while still facing against the many adversaries from the worlds of science and most of the magic and the conflicts that follow. Despite his very bad luck, he has managed to get the interests and hearts of many ladies who are infatuated with him, which Aisa jokes about, that his life is like a dating sim where he is bound to unlock more paths to more girls.</description>
<picture>232176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2469" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="2278">8.66</rating>
<name>Misaka Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaka Mikoto is one of the series` main heroines, as well as the main protagonist of the side story, A Certain Scientific Railgun. Her parents are Tabigake and Misuzu Misaka, which her father is a prominent businessman and millionaire. Despite her rich background, she grew up in a normal typical childhood.
At a young age, she was discovered to be a Level 1 Electromaster, espers who have the ability to generate and control electricity. She enrolled into Academy City to train her powers and worked very hard until her powers were ranked Level 5, the highest esper ranking, with her being the third strongest of the seven espers with this rank. As an electromaster, she can generate and manipulate electricity which she can use to shock opponents, hack into electronics like computer networks and security systems, and use electromagnetism to cling to surfaces or manipulate iron particles into a chain-sword whip. Mikoto`s signature move is her ability to shoot metal projectiles such as coins at high destructive speeds, hence her nickname, The Railgun. If she is in a bad mood, she will sometimes let out bursts of electricity describing her emotional stress, usually resulting in power failures or even citywide blackouts.
Mikoto attends Tokiwadai Middle School, a famous girls` school for the rich and elite psychics and one of the five elite schools of Academy City. To most people, she is considered a proper lady, but in reality, she has a short-tempered, prideful, and improper attitude with some tomboyish tendencies and insecurities, a fact few other characters know. She is fond of cute, childish things, such as flowery pajamas and Gekota, the popular frog mascot franchise. Contrary to what she claims, she has a strong sense of morals and hates injustice. Mikoto has a one-sided rivalry with Touma, who nicknamed her Biri Biri (ビリビリ, relating to the sound of an electric shock), ever since their first meeting before the events of the first novel when he first dissipated her electricity after he unsuccessfully tried to rescue her. Since that incident, she is always trying to have a proper match with Touma and defeat him despite his many attempts to avoid conflict with her.
When Mikoto was young, she was tricked into giving the city`s scientist her DNA under the pretense of finding the cure for Duchenne muscular dystrophy; their actual goal to create military-grade combat clones of her. When it was discovered that the clones did not have the same power level as Mikoto, they were instead used in an Project called Level 6 Shift, intended to make Accelerator the first level 6 esper by having him kill 20,000 clones. The events of how Mikoto tried to stop the project are briefly mentioned in the third novel and expanded upon in the Railgun manga. When all of her attempts failed, she contemplates letting herself be killed by Accelerator, as an unexpected variable to destroy Tree Diagram`s calculations. However, it is not until Touma intervenes and beats Accelerator, proving him to be really weak, that the project is canceled and the remaining 9969 surviving Sisters are spared.
After those events, she eventually develops strong romantic feelings towards Touma but is unable to express them due to her insecurities and the fact other girls are also interested in him. Even though she and Touma tend to bicker and argue with each other, they share a somewhat friendly relationship.</description>
<picture>232410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2470" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="972">6.22</rating>
<name>Shirai Kuroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirai Kuroko is a level 4 psychic, and member of Judgement, a special public committee group, whose duty it is to maintain peace and order in Academy City. She is in love with Misaka, who she calls "Onee-sama" (sister) and tends to get jealous if someone else gets her attention. This unfortunately happens to be Touma, since he has caught the attention of Misaka for various reasons. Her special power is instant teleportation, which allows her to teleport herself and anything in her possession - as long as it weighs around 130-137 kilograms - to anywhere in a radius of around 81-85 metres.</description>
<picture>232414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2471" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="162">6.15</rating>
<name>Himegami Aisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A quiet, young girl with a rather blunt personality who wears Miko attire. While she may seem normal, she is also known as "Deep Blood" and has the ability to kill vampires, as her blood`s smell attracts vampires who die when they approach her. However, it made her miserable because with the exception of sucking blood, vampires were just like humans. This prompts her to go to Academy City, hoping to find a way to get rid of her powers, until she meets the alchemist http://anidb.net/ch2730 [Aureolus Izzard].</description>
<picture>232405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2472" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="219">7.30</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanzaki Kaori is an eighteen-year-old Japanese sorceress from Necessarius. Unlike her partner Stiyl, she uses magic to magically strengthen her body. Her sorcery name is Salvare000, "Be the salvation of those who cannot be saved" (救われぬ者に救いの手を, Sukuwarenu Mono ni Sukui no Te o). She uses a two-meter-long nodachi called "Seven Heavens Seven Swords" as her weapon. She has a special attack called Nanasen (七閃, "Seven Flash") that uses her sword and some wires. She used to be a kind woman who treated Index like a sister, but when Index`s memories were deleted by Necessarius, Kaori changed into a cold and silent woman as Index no longer remembered her and consequentially did not trust her. After Touma saves Index`s life and her current memories, she decides to let Index stay at Academy City as she feels Touma can protect her.
Later in the novels, more of her past is revealed. Not only is Kaori a skilled swordswoman, but she is a Catholic Saint possessing the "Stigma" — the ability to call upon God`s power — and the former leader of the Amakusa Catholics; however, Kaori left the group as she resented that she had been fated since birth to become its leader, which led her to despise the concept of luck and fortune. Though she is Catholic, she joined Necessarius in hopes of changing her fate and befriended Index, developing a sisterly relationship with her. The repeated failed attempts to make Index remember her after each memory erasure resulted in her cold personality as Kaori began to accept that no matter how much a person tries, no one can change their destiny. She begins to show a kinder side to herself after Touma saves Index (thus giving her hope that anyone can defy their destiny) and gradually falls in love with him after he helps her face her past with the Amakusa Catholics, becoming more prone to showing emotion and sometimes showing a little embarrassment if she is with him. She is the protagonist of her own spin-off mini light novel bundled with the Toaru Kagaku no Railgun DVDs.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>232404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2473" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="194">5.78</rating>
<name>Tsukuyomi Komoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite her childish and very short (135 cm) appearance, she is actually an adult and one of Touma`s teachers. This is proven by her apartment being littered with beer cans and cigarettes. She also contradicts her age by acting childish to her students, having a child-like crush on Touma, and ending her sentences with desu, something a child usually does. This irony means that she is often regarded as one of the seven great mysteries of Academy City.</description>
<picture>232411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="546" picture="17760.jpg">Koyama Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2474" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="96">5.01</rating>
<name>Stiyl Magnus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sorcerer from Necessarius. His sorcery name is Fortis931. He is an extremely heavy smoker; he claims a world without nicotine would be hell. He specializes in using flames and is able to use a flame sword or summon a 3000 degree Celsius fire called Innocentius to battle his enemies. Despite his looks, he is actually fourteen years old and is physically weak. He has a short temper but is actually kind, as he cares about Index very much and his failure to save her life without losing her memories was his greatest regret.</description>
<picture>232467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2730" type="appears in" update="2010-12-28">
<rating votes="11">3.84</rating>
<name>Aureolus Izzard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aureolus Izzard is an 18 year old alchemist and former Catholic Church magician who turned traitor. His sorcery name is Honos628, "My honor is for the world" (我が名誉は世界のために, Waga Meiyo wa Sekai no Tame ni). He possesses an ability called "Ars Magna", a skill produced by alchemy that turns his thoughts into reality through his words. This ability is heavily reliant on his belief and state of mind; the more he doubts, the weaker his spell becomes until it does not activate at all. Three years before the story began, he was Index`s former partner and was devastated when the young nun was forced to have her memories erased in order to save her life. In order to spare Index from repeatably losing her memories, he works with Aisa, using her powers to attract vampires to catch one and use them to turn Index into a vampire to overcome her life expectancy. When he learns that Index has already been saved, he angrily turns on everyone including Aisa, though Touma stops Aureolus by using his own powers against him and driving him mad. Out of pity, Stiyl changes Aureolus` appearance so that the Catholic Church is unable to capture and punish him.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>22616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2731" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="43">2.51</rating>
<name>Aleister Crowley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Once the greatest magician in modern magic history, more than half of all modern magicians are affected by this man`s established theories, and two-fifths of them are direct followers of his ways. Having stretched the boundaries of sorcery farther than the advances made in the last few millenia alone and written many top-class spellbooks like The Book of the Law, it is no surprise that many mages were outraged when this eccentric genius literally "dumped" all his magic abilities and decided to "ace it" in the field of science, thus establishing the Academy City and becoming its hidden monarch.
When he chose to stop using magic and was running for his life from a hoard of enraged stalker magicians, he met the Heaven Canceler, who eventually helped him found Academy City in a far-eastern island of Japan and also provides help in this ex-magician`s new goal; to extend his lifespan for as long as possible by having all but his consciousness rely on the power of machines.</description>
<picture>232427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10527" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-07">
<rating votes="340">7.61</rating>
<name>Accelerator</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Accelerator is the most powerful Psychic in Academy City. His real name is unknown, though Accelerator recalls his surname was composed of two characters and his given name consisted of three characters. First appearing as an antagonist, he later becomes a main character and the lead of the science side in the Toaru Majutsu no Index series. Because Accelerator has been this reflexively powerful since childhood, he was unstoppable even when the military was sent to kill him. However, these past influences resulted in his inability to trust others and he was left alone. After meeting Touma, he develops a sense of admiration and jealousy towards Touma`s heroism and ability to help others, contrasting with how Accelerator feels he is only able to destroy.
A sadistic boy about the same age as Touma, he has an ability called Vector Change, a form of telekinesis allowing him to change the vector values of anything he touches. This ability allows Accelerator perform feats such as reversing the blood flow inside a person`s body, increasing the wind velocity around him to create a massive plasma storm, and blocking sound. His ability is automatic, which means that he must consciously allow gravity to affect him and that his body blocks all ultraviolet radiation, resulting his albino appearance (white hair and pale skin) because his body is unable to make melanin. The automatic nature of Redirection also prevents the use of projectiles (like bullets) and explosives (like bombs) against him. After being shot by http://anidb.net/ch14551 [Amai Ao], Accelerator`s ability to use his power is hindered, but slowly recovers with the help of http://anidb.net/ch14534 [Heaven Canceller] and the http://anidb.net/ch14538 [Misaka Network]. However, he is forced to use a cane and is restricted to using his ability for only 15 minutes at a time, as well as losing more than half of his computation ability even with 10,000 sisters doing calculations for him.
Accelerator`s unique ability make him the subject of an experiment attempting to create the first Level 6 psychic; according to the city`s best supercomputer, Tree Diagram (which was unprecedentedly destroyed by Index`s Dragon Breath), this feat could only be achieved by killing 128 skilled Level 5 psychics without a single failure. Since there are only six other known Level 5s in Academy City, an alternative plan was formed to level up Accelerator by having him kill 20,000 skilled Level 2 psychics: the Misaka clones. He willingly joins the experiment to gain a reputation as the most powerful and feared psychic that no one would be foolish enough to challenge and even killed many who got in his way. The Sisters` memories of his behavior during the experiment may suggest that he is, in a way, a pacifist; since his power won`t disappear, the only way he sees to stop fighting is to be so strong and sadistic that no one would raise a finger against him. He even seems to attempt to frighten the Sisters or otherwise encourage them to refuse the battle. Mikoto tries to stop the experiment to save her sisters, but it is Touma who finally does so and defeats Accelerator after discovering his weakness: Accelerator was physically weak because of his total reliance on his powers. Overconfidence in his psychic abilities resulted in his defeat as Touma beat him with his Imagine Breaker and street-fighting skills.
After his defeat, he reappears later and takes a more heroic role protecting a girl named Last Order, the last Misaka clone. In the aftermath of the incident, Accelerator is shot in the head by Amai Ao, damaging his brain and severely limiting the use of his power.</description>
<picture>232181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12960" type="appears in" update="2009-11-13">
<rating votes="31">5.25</rating>
<name>Ryoukan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="383" picture="24124.jpg">Okohira Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13691" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="165">5.61</rating>
<name>Yomikawa Aiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teacher at Touma`s school and a friend of Komoe. She is beautiful, has glamorous proportions, and is always seen with a green jersey. She is a member of the Anti-Skills and cares deeply for her students, and is apparently an active peacekeeper within the Academic City. A favor to her old friend, Yomikawa is asked by Yoshikawa Kikyou to take care of Accelerator and Last Order after they are released from the hospital.</description>
<picture>232406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14530" type="appears in" update="2010-05-23">
<rating votes="17">4.49</rating>
<name>Sphynx</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sphinx is Index`s pet kitten she cares for due to her caring nature. She first finds Sphinx in volume two inside a box. Toma tries to convince her that she cannot keep it due to the dorm he is at does not allow pets, but they manage to pull it off without anyone suspecting them.</description>
<picture>4464.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="14531" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-07">
<rating votes="81">5.36</rating>
<name>Tsuchimikado Motoharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blonde teenager who is always seen with sunglasses and wearing an Aloha shirt. He is a friend and classmate of Touma who just happens to be his next-door neighbor at the dormitory they`re staying at. While he seem like a normal, average teenager, there`s more to him than meets the eye. Secretly, Tsuchimikado is actually a former agent of Necessarius who became a freelance spy for Necessarius, Academy City, and other unknown organizations; the leaders of both Necessarius and Academy City are both aware of this but have decided to let him be for the time being. His sorcery name is Fallere825, `the back-stabber`.
He was formerly a skilled Onmyouji as his family are descendants of Abe no Seimei but gave up his abilities when he went under the ESP development curriculum. He has a younger step-sister named Maika, whom he is also in love with, and for this he is known as the Shisukon Gunsou (シスコン軍曹, "Sis-com Sergeant"). He is also a member of one of Academy City`s secret organizations, the "GROUP". His ESP ability is the Level 0 Auto Regeneration (肉体再生, Nikutai Saisei, lit. "Body Regeneration"). Due to this power, he can still use magic as he can repair the damage done to his body, making him the only successful psychic/magician hybrid. Despite these advantages, he avoids using magic except in the most desperate situations as he cannot avoid the extreme pain caused by using it.</description>
<picture>232182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2002" picture="21307.jpg">Katsu Anri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14532" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-27">
<rating votes="43">1.89</rating>
<name>Aogami Pierce</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His real name is unknown. Touma`s friend and classmate. A funny individual who tends to see Touma`s bad luck, who he calls "Kami-yan" in a different way. He is a self-confessed pervert, lolicon, and masochist who enjoys being punished by his teacher, Tsukuyomi. He is always seen with Motoharu. He, Motoharu, and Touma are known as the three idiots in their class as not only do they have the lowest test scores, but they are also Level 0s (except the latter two have good reasons for being that way).</description>
<picture>231737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14533" type="appears in" update="2019-04-12">
<rating votes="14">3.48</rating>
<name>Etzali</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An Aztecan sorcerer. He borrows the appearance of Unabara Mitsuki, the Tokiwadai Middle School principal`s grandson. A certain group outside Academy City became aware of the growing "Kamijou Faction", so they sent him as a spy. Borrowing the appearance of Mitsuki, he attempts to become closer to Misaka Mikoto, but he ends up falling in love with her. After he loses the battle with Touma, he makes him promise to protect Mikoto and the world around her. He uses a copy of the obsidian spearhead of the god Tlahuizcalpantecuhtli, which reflects light from Venus destroying anything the light falls upon. It is later revealed that he is member of the GROUP.</description>
<picture>232502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14534" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="75">5.82</rating>
<name>Kaeru Kao no Ishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The "Heaven Canceller". Often mentioned as "the Frog-Faced Doctor" by Touma, he is an exceptionally-gifted and benevolent physician who can cure any illness and heal any injury, even if it is terminal. He is only unable to heal specific brain-related injuries, such as the "Imagine-Breaker Boy`s" damaged memories and Accelerator`s computation ability; however, in the latter case, he was able to configure Accelerator to control his powers with support from the Misaka Network. This medical genius also manages the life extension devices for the ruler of Academy City, Aleister Crowley, while also supporting the foundation of the city itself.</description>
<picture>232416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="415" picture="241624.jpg">Nakano Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14535" type="appears in" update="2014-01-28">
<rating votes="2">3.62</rating>
<name>Himegami Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14536" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="64">6.17</rating>
<name>Tsuchimikado Maika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Motoharu`s younger step-sister. She wears a maid attire (as she goes to a Maid School) and rides on top of a cleaning `bot. She has a friendly relationship with Touma and knows that he has two girls (Index and Aisa) living with him but keeps the secret between her and Touma and is a good friend of Mikoto as she works at her school. Even though she lives in her school`s dormitory, she sometimes goes to live at her brother`s apartment; for instance, in episode ten, she stays at said residence because her dormitory`s air conditioner breaks down.</description>
<picture>232413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14537" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="206">7.77</rating>
<name>Misaka Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced in both the third volume of the novel and manga, respectively, and episode ten of the anime, Touma meets the younger `twin sister` of Mikoto who he calls Misaka`s sister (御坂妹, Misaka Imouto), who seems rather quiet and emotionless. Her voice is rather monotonous and computer-like. Her speech pattern is unique, for she talks in third person (adding a description of herself after she finishes talking). While both sisters may look alike from a distance, Misaka has paler eyes and wears striped panties under her skirt. Misaka also wears a special set of goggles that enables her to see electron beams and magnetic field lines for the reason that, unlike Mikoto, she does not have that ability. At the beginning of the third volume, Mikoto seems to dislike and worry about Misaka for some reason, and later events reveal why.
In reality, Misaka imouto is a clone of Mikoto; in fact, the first one Touma meets is No. 10032 out of 20,000 other clones (excluding Full-Tuning and Last Order) copied from Mikoto called `The Sisters`. Even though they have a weaker variant of Mikoto`s electric abilities (Level 3), the Sisters` minds are connected by a special psychic ability called Radio Noise (欠陥電気, Kekkan Denki?, "Flawed Electric"), which enables their brainwaves to become electric signals; this allows them to share their thoughts and memories within their communication network, also known as the Misaka Network. Being rapidly-manufactured clones, the Sisters rarely change their facial expression because they did not learn how to. Due to minds having connected to the Misaka Network, most of the Sisters never considered themselves human yet some of them had slight difference in personalities.
20,000 clones were created in total, to be used in an experiment designed to create the first Level 6 psychic ("Level 6 Shift"), Accelerator. By the time of third novel, 10,031 were killed in the experiment. After the Level 6 Shift experiment fails, all 9969 surviving Sisters are ordered back to the research center where they were created to have "readjustments" so that they will have normal life spans. The Sisters later began showing their owned unique personalities to differentiate themselves after learning how to `disconnect` from the Network and keeping their own private memories inaccessible to the others in the Network.
Misaka 10032, also known as Misaka Imouto, is the most prominent clone that is most featured in the series. She is known for having a soft spot for cats which she herself has a pet black kitten. She was the first sister clone that Touma met. Due to the many interactions she had with him, 10032 wonder why she thought about him so much. Misaka 10032 was Accelerator`s latest target in the Level 6 experiment, but Touma managed to stop him before he killed her. Confused, she asks him why he did so since she was a clone, to which he replied that even though she was a clone, she was still an individual with a life. His words (along with Mikoto`s) affect her so much that she and the Sisters decide to help Touma by controlling all of the city`s wind turbines to prevent Accelerator from creating a plasma storm.
After the Level 6 experiment was canceled, she was one of ten Sisters to stay in Academy City while the rest went overseas around the world for treatment. She later falls in love with Touma and receives a necklace from him (he bought it for her during his date with Mikoto and mistook 10032 for Mikoto) which she treasures.</description>
<picture>232463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14538" type="appears in" update="2015-07-28">
<rating votes="12">8.16</rating>
<name>Sisters</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Introduced in both the third volume of the novel and manga, respectively, and episode ten of the anime, http://anidb.net/ch2342 [Touma] meets the younger twin sister of http://anidb.net/ch2469 [Mikoto] who he calls Misaka`s sister (御坂妹, Misaka Imouto), who seems rather quiet and emotionless. Her voice is rather monotonous and computer-like. Her speech pattern is unique, for she talks in third person (adding a description of herself after she finishes talking). While both sisters may look alike from a distance, Misaka has paler eyes and wears striped panties under her skirt. Misaka also wears a special set of goggles that enables her to see electron beams and magnetic field lines for the reason that, unlike Mikoto, she does not have that ability. At the beginning of the third volume, Mikoto seems to dislike and worry about Misaka for some reason, and later events reveal why.
In reality, Misaka Imouto is a clone of Mikoto; in fact, the first one Touma meets is No. 10032 out of 20,000 other clones (excluding Full-Tuning and http://anidb.net/ch14550 [Last Order]) copied from Mikoto called The Sisters. Even though they have a weaker variant of Mikoto`s electric abilities (Level 3), the Sisters` minds are connected by a special psychic ability called Radio Noise (欠陥電気), which enables their brainwaves to become electric signals; this allows them to share their thoughts and memories within their communication network, also known as the Misaka Network. Being rapidly-manufactured clones, the Sisters rarely change their facial expression because they did not learn how to. Due to minds having connected to the Misaka Network, most of the Sisters never considered themselves human yet some of them had slight difference in personalities.
20,000 clones were created in total, to be used in an experiment designed to create the first Level 6 psychic ("Level 6 Shift"), Accelerator. By the time of third novel, 10,031 were killed in the experiment. After the Level 6 Shift experiment fails, all 9969 surviving Sisters are ordered back to the research center where they were created to have "readjustments" so that they will have normal life spans. The Sisters later began showing their owned unique personalities to differentiate themselves after learning how to disconnect from the Network and keeping their own private memories inaccessible to the others in the Network.</description>
<picture>143487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14543" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="38">5.39</rating>
<name>Sasha Croitsef</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sasha Croitsef is a battle nun of Annihilatus, who first appears in the fourth novel and in the anime episode Angel Fall. She carries around a bunch of unique weapons, from hammers to saws.
During the events of the Angel Fall spell, her body was accidentally switched to the Archangel Gabriel, which prompted the archangel to find the caster of the spell using Sasha`s body under the alias Misha Croitsef. Sasha later appears as herself in the following novels and the second anime season.</description>
<picture>232470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="25450.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14544" type="appears in" update="2010-09-07">
<rating votes="13">4.44</rating>
<name>Kamijou Touya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14545" type="appears in" update="2010-09-07">
<rating votes="21">5.51</rating>
<name>Kamijou Shiina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14546" type="appears in" update="2019-04-07">
<rating votes="3">3.78</rating>
<name>Unabara Mitsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Tokiwadai Middle School principal`s grandson, a level 4. Seemingly romantically interested in Misaka. It is later revealed that Mitsuki`s place was in reality taken by Etzali, an Aztecan sorcerer who planned to place mistrust between Touma and his friends and allies. However, the real Mitsuki appeared and his cover was blown.</description>
<picture>232180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14550" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="216">7.69</rating>
<name>Last Order</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Last Order is the name of http://anidb.net/ch2469 [Misaka Mikoto]`s No. 20001 clone. She is the administrator of the http://anidb.net/ch14538 [Misaka Network] and the fail-safe mechanism in case the Sisters got out of control. She is not designed to function independently and survive for long outside a culture container and appears to be only about ten years old. Due to intercepting an emotion program http://anidb.net/ch55166 [Nunotaba Shinobu] intended to install into all of the clones, she is capable of showing emotions unlike the other sisters and has a close relationship with Mikoto, http://anidb.net/ch14537 [Misaka Imouto], http://anidb.net/ch10527 [Accelerator] and her adult guardians, http://anidb.net/ch13691 [Yomikawa Aiho] and http://anidb.net/ch14552 [Yoshikawa Kikyou]. Like her older clone sisters, she speaks in third person with a description, except she says "Misaka" twice. She has all of the memories of the Misaka clones and has observed Accelerator through this method, posing a theory that Accelerator did not actually want to do the Level 6 Shift experiment.
Accelerator meets Last Order when she follows him home one day after he fends off a bunch of street thugs hearing of his defeat against a Level 0. Though Accelerator tries to dissuade her from hanging around him, she persists in following him around because she wants someone to keep her company. She is later kidnapped by http://anidb.net/ch14551 [Amai Ao] so he can infect the Misaka clones to possibly go on a rampage and attack people. Accelerator manages to stop him but gets injured in the process. Last Order and Accelerator are put under the care of Aiho after the incident. Accelerator does all he can to protect her since she is the first person in his life who requested his help. Throughout the story, she remains with Accelerator and has been involved in situations relating to him. After Accelerator`s confrontation with Aiwass, she is left in critical condition. However, Accelerator brings Last Order with him to Russia in hopes of finding http://anidb.net/ch870 [Index], who may have the knowledge to cure her.</description>
<picture>232462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="129542.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14551" type="appears in" update="2010-10-17">
<rating votes="9">1.24</rating>
<name>Amai Ao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Former researcher for the "The Sisters" project. His specialty is creating personality data with self-learning capabilities. During the "Level 6 Shift" project, he was assigned to directing the experiments. After the project is put to a stop, he tries to join an organization outside Academy City by planting a virus upon Last Order and leaking information about the city.</description>
<picture>57049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14552" type="appears in" update="2011-01-15">
<rating votes="23">5.64</rating>
<name>Yoshikawa Kikyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Academy City`s researcher. She was in charge of the "Level 6 Shift" project. Even after the project was put to a stop, she kept herself in the laboratory, creating a vaccine for the virus program that Ao Amai put in Last Order. She is shot by Amai while trying to protect Accelerator and Last Order but recovers and is later released from the hospital along with Accelerator and Last Order.</description>
<picture>63321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14560" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="26">5.76</rating>
<name>Sherry Cromwell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Her sorcery name Intimus115, "Everything I offer to my lost friend". A member of Necessarius and a talented "Decoder", she has tanned skin and wears a black Gothic Lolita dress. Her blonde hair is unkempt and according to Tsuchimikado, she has the silhouette of a lion. She is a master of Kabbalah Statue art and utilizes oil pastel or chalk to draw a spell to summon a golem Sherry refers to as "Ellis".
Sherry appears in Academy City with the intention of attacking a person of importance to either Academy City or Necessarius in order to cause a conflict- and eventually, war- between the two factions. During her assault, she reveals to Toma that she seeks to keep science and magic divided as revenge for her late friend Ellis, an esper from Academy City. Ellis was involved in a secret experiment between Academy City and Necessarius in an attempt to create the first magician-esper hybrid. But it went horribly wrong as not only did the espers participants suffered major injuries from magic but were killed by the Knights of England as the experiment was illegal under the truce between Science and Magic. Blaming both sides for letting Ellis suffered and killed, Sherry swore revenge against them by making them suffered like she did.</description>
<picture>232401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14561" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="56">3.88</rating>
<name>Kazakiri Hyouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is Index`s first "friend" in Academy City. She is gentle but shy. Not much is known about her aside from the fact that she was an overachiever at Kirigaoka Academy for Girls (霧ヶ丘女学院, Kirigaoka Jyogakuin), according to Aisa. Her ability is Counter Stop (正体不明, Shoutai Fumei, "Unknown Identity"). Details about her level are unknown but it could be high, since it was mentioned that she was among the top psychics in the Kirigaoka Academy for Girls. It is later revealed that she is not a human at all but instead an algorithm of the psychic`s AIM with a conscious. The nature of her being leads her to be indestructible, as she can recreate any damage done to her body and lift objects several times her size. When not physically manifested, she exists in a realm she calls `the city of shimmers`, a warped shadow of Gakuen Toshi.</description>
<picture>232464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14562" type="appears in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="56">6.17</rating>
<name>Laura Stuart</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Archbishop of Necessarius. Despite being the Archbishop, she looks like an eighteen-year-old girl with long blonde hair; other than that, any other details about her are unknown. She speaks funny Japanese, courtesy of Tsuchimikado teaching her. She might sound simple and irresponsible, but behind her smile lies a cold and calculating personality. She loves baths and has a collection of the latest bath accessories from Academy City.</description>
<picture>230636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14760" type="appears in" update="2011-07-09">
<rating votes="19">8.79</rating>
<name>Judgment</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The public moral committee. It is made up of students with powers from every grade level whose duty is to maintain peace and order within the school system. As most of the city population are students, it is the duty of Judgment to catch those delinquents misusing their powers along with other offenders and protect the students. Each district in Academy City has at least one Judgment branch office headed by a senior student who serves as a police chief. In the event of a situation that Judgment members cannot handle, their superiors and the city`s security forces, the Anti-Skills will take over. Overall, the role of a Judgment officer is more like a part-time civilian patrol officer as their authority is normally limited to their district area where their local Judgment branch office is located and they can only use their authority at other districts when ordered to by their superiors or in cases of emergency. Most Judgment members can be recognized by the green stripped arm band with a shield symbol they wear.</description>
<picture>6487.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="14761" type="appears in" update="2010-03-23">
<rating votes="14">6.51</rating>
<name>Anti-Skill</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Anti-Skill is the city`s police and security forces. Unlike Judgment, most members of Anti-Skills are adults who are mostly normal people and even school teachers who are trained to deal with the city`s day-to-day activities and security, in addition to dealing with rogue psychics who abuse their powers. Most members of Anti-Skills are seen with special SWAT armor that resist psychic powers along with firearms and riot gear, which shows how serious the situation has to be for them to be called out. They are also responsible in investigating and stopping the experiments that are against the law and inhumane to students but due to the interventions by the city administration, they are stopped from investigating experiments that were approved by the Board of Directors. Their symbol is a three-point spear shaped like a capital "E" turned 90 degrees to the left.</description>
<picture>4219.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="24827" type="appears in" update="2011-07-10">
<rating votes="12">7.99</rating>
<name>Tokiwadai Chuugaku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>One of the elite five schools of Academy City, this elite girls middle school is located within District 7, the School Garden.</description>
<picture>6498.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="25053" type="appears in" update="2010-11-27">
<rating votes="36">4.32</rating>
<name>Musujime Awaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Musujime Awaki is a sophomore attending Kirigaoka Academy for Girls. She is a Level 4 esper with a teleport ability called Move Point (座標移動, Zahyou Idou). Her teleportation powers are more powerful than Kuroko as she can teleport anything weighing up to 4,500kg without even touching it by a distance up to 800 meters. However, due to a past trauma where she miscalculated and teleported her leg inside a wall, accidentally tearing her leg skin and muscles out from the wall and almost dying, she has a fear of using her powers on herself and feels physically ill whenever she is forced to teleport herself. This fear prevents her from becoming a Level 5.
She steals a remnant of the destroyed Tree Diagram and confronts Kuruko and Mikoto. However, she is beaten by Accelerator and the remnant is destroyed. Awaki is one of the guides to the windowless building where Aleister Crowley resides. She is also living with Tsukuyomi Komoe. Later, she is blackmailed to join team Group.</description>
<picture>59860.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25343" type="appears in" update="2014-01-29">
<rating votes="5">5.81</rating>
<name>Necessarius</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Necessarius is the secret magical branch of the Church of England. Officially named the Church of Necessary Evil, the organization was started by Puritans who despise the use of magic in England and sought to destroy it by using magic themselves but now the organization no longer has an anti-magic stance and supports magic. Officially, Necessarius is under the authority of the Archbishop of Canterbury but the current leader and Archbishop of Necessarius secretly controls the Archbishop of Canterbury thus Necessarius is the true power behind the Anglican Church. As one of the three magic powers of Britain, Necessarius represent the religious magic community. Necessarius is currently led by Archbishop Laura Stuart.</description>
<picture>61492.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="26157" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="3">1.47</rating>
<name>Roman Seikyou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>232449.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26189" type="appears in" update="2014-01-29">
<rating votes="5">3.93</rating>
<name>Igirisu Seikyou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>61492.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="34327" type="appears in" update="2011-07-09">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Misawa Juku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Misawa Juku was a school which degenerated into a cult that centered its worship on science. It converted people by saying rare abilities could be copied and given to someone else. Aureolus Izzard eventually took over the school and destroyed the cult, as he needed Himegami to obtain a vampire. Aureolus converted the cram school into his fortress.</description>
<picture>75057.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34366" type="appears in" update="2011-07-11">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Roman Seikyou Juu-San Kishi Dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Roman Seikyou Juu-San Kishi Dan, or Thirteen Knights of the Roman Catholic Church, is a group of warriors created by the Roman Catholic Church. They were once dispatched to hunt and eliminate Aureolus Izzard but were decimated by him.</description>
<picture>75116.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34367" type="appears in" update="2014-01-29">
<rating votes="20">7.50</rating>
<name>Gakuen Toshi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Gakuen Toshi, or Academy City, is a city of several schools and institutions of higher learning from kindergarten to university level that learn side-by-side along with the scientists who research on psychic powers and higher technology, the latter being one of the primary reasons for its establishment. It is the most advanced city in the world and its technology is said to be 30 years ahead of what`s `outside` of it.</description>
<picture>149221.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34517" type="appears in" update="2011-07-13">
<rating votes="3">4.15</rating>
<name>Tatsugami Otohime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsugami Otohime is Kamijou Touma`s cousin and appears during the Angel Fall Incident. Her true appearance is only seen in a picture as her outer appearance was changed to look like Misaka Mikoto for the duration of the Angel Fall Incident.</description>
<picture>6512.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34518" type="appears in" update="2019-04-15">
<rating votes="5">2.97</rating>
<name>Gabriel</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gabriel is an archangel that appears during the Angel Fall Incident. It first appeared under the name Misha Croitsef while inhabiting Sasha Croitsef`s body.</description>
<picture>232664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="25450.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34537" type="appears in" update="2011-07-14">
<rating votes="14">5.25</rating>
<name>Magical Powered Kanamin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magical Powered Kanamin is the titular character of the eponymous Magical Powered Kanamin anime which airs in Academy City. The anime is about the adventures of a young girl with magic powers on the run from Roman Catholic Church witch hunters. Index is a big fan of it.</description>
<picture>75414.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34679" type="appears in" update="2011-07-16">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Toaru Koukou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Toaru Koukou (A Certain High School) is the term usually used to describe the high school Kamijou Touma attends. Its official name is unknown.</description>
<picture>6532.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="55167" type="appears in" update="2013-04-20">
<rating votes="29">7.93</rating>
<name>Misaka Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56897" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<rating votes="7">5.96</rating>
<name>Level 5</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Within Academy City, the Level 5s are the most powerful psychics in the city. The following are the currently known Level 5s; ranked not by strength but by how useful they are to http://anidb.net/ch2731 [Aleister]`s plans.
1.) http://anidb.net/ch10527 [Accelerator]
2.) http://anidb.net/ch98257 [Kakine Teitoku]
3.) http://anidb.net/ch2469 [Misaka Mikoto]
4.) http://anidb.net/ch56199 [Mugino Shizuri]
5.) http://anidb.net/ch54960 [Shokuhou Misaki]
6.) Unknown. A possible impersonator claiming to be Aihana Etsu has appeared.
7.) http://anidb.net/ch107656 [Sogiita Gunha]</description>
<picture>243175.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57768" type="appears in" update="2013-07-07">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Keibi Robo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139704.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91638" type="appears in" update="2017-10-04">
<name>Innocentius</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 3000-degree-Celsius fire monster which can be summoned by Stiyl Magnus.</description>
<picture>207865.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91639" type="appears in" update="2017-10-04">
<rating votes="4">4.52</rating>
<name>Misaka 10031</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaka 10031 is one of the many clones of Misaka Mikoto and the first clone that Kamijou Touma meets.</description>
<picture>207869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91644" type="appears in" update="2017-10-05">
<name>Annihilatus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Annihilatus is a secret branch of the Russian Orthodox Church that deals with magic, specifically the disposal of spirits and such that should not exist. It is the Russian counterpart of the Anglican Church`s Necessarius.</description>
</character>
<character id="91645" type="appears in" update="2017-10-05">
<name>Roshia Seikyou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Russian Orthodox Church is the largest of the Orthodox Churches and one of the three world`s largest Christian organizations.</description>
<picture>65426.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="91646" type="appears in" update="2017-10-05">
<name>Souji Robo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cleaning Robots are automated cylindrical machine designed to clean the grounds of Academy City. They can be described as mobile trashbins.</description>
<picture>207890.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91650" type="appears in" update="2017-10-05">
<name>Golem Ellis</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A golem summoned by Sherry Cromwell.</description>
<picture>207892.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="93300" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="45">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園都市</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Academy City</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Miasto akademickie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen Toshi</title>
<summary>Kamijo meets Index, who is on the run from a magic society that wants the library of forbidden knowledge stored in her memory. Later, Kamijo is shocked to find Index at his house – bleeding and accompanied by a strange man.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719257</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93301" update="2017-08-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="41">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔女狩りの王[イノケンティウス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Innocentius (The Witch Hunter King)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Innocentius</title>
<summary>The magician reveals that his name is Stiyl Magnus and explains that his partner Kaori Kanzaki unintentionally hurt Index as her magical garb was supposed to stop the blow. His mission was actually to protect Index, who possesses photographic memory of the 103,000 grimoires implanted in her mind called the Index Librorum Prohibitorum. Angered by Stiyl`s harsh treatment of Index, Touma attacks him, to which Stiyl responds by using fire magic and is surprised when Tōma nullifies the spell. To stop Touma, Stiyl summons a fire creature known as Innocentius. When Touma finds himself unable to negate the creature, Index activates John`s Pen, her self-protection system personality, to reveal that Innocentius` power comes from runes placed around the building. Touma defeats Stiyl and Innocentius by setting off sprinklers to wash away the runes. However, because of Index`s wounds and Touma`s inability to use magic, he brings Index to the only non-esper he knows, that being his teacher Komoe Tsukuyomi.
Source: wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719259</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93541" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="37">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">必要悪の教会[ネセサリウス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Necessarius (The Church of Necessary Evil)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Necessarius</title>
<summary>Kamijo learns more about Index’s history with Necessarius, the Church of Necessary Evil. Later, after a trip to the bathhouse leads to an argument with Index, Kamijo finds himself in the company of a mysterious stranger.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719261</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93557" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="36">4.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">完全記憶能力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Perfect Memory Ability</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Doskonała pamięć</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanzen Kioku Nouryoku</title>
<summary>Kaori Kanzaki confronts Kamijo, demanding that he hand over Index. Kamijo is wounded in the ensuing scuffle – and when he wakes up a few days later, Index offers to take drastic measures to protect him from further harm.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719263</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93558" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="33">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">十二時[リミット]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limit (12 o`clock)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Limit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Limit</title>
<summary>When Kamijo springs into action to prevent Kanzaki and Stiyl from erasing Index’s memory, he learns there’s a chance that the Church was lying about the threat to Index’s life all along!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719265</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93567" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="34">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻想殺し[イマジンブレイカー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Imagine Breaker</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Łamacz Woli</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imagine Breaker</title>
<summary>Kamijo succeeds in eliminating the magical threat to Index’s life. Unfortunately, his memory is erased in the process! Later, Stiyl’s boss orders him to work with Kamijo. Their assignment: Find “Deep Blood.”
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719267</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95045" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="30">4.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三沢塾[かがくすうはい]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Science Cult (Misawa Cram School)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Kult nauki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagaku Suuhai</title>
<summary>Stiyl tells Kamijo (who has no memory of the sorcerer) about his plan to raid Misawa Prep School in order to rescue a young girl who wields a vampire-summoning power known as Deep Blood.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719269</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95046" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="31">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄金練成[アルス=マグナ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ars Magna (Golden Transmutation)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ars Magna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ars Magna</title>
<summary>Kamijo and Stiyl quickly fall under attack after infiltrating Misawa Prep School! During the raid, Kamijo runs into the girl they hoped to rescue – but there’s a chance she isn’t interested in leaving the campus!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719271</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95047" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吸血殺し[ディープブラッド]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep Blood (Vampire Killer)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Głęboka Krew</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deep Blood</title>
<summary>Aureolus finds his plan to turn Index into a vampire thwarted and learns that Kamijo has already saved Index’s memory. Overwhelmed by anger and jealousy, the alchemist attacks Kamijo in a fit of murderous rage.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719273</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95144" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="30">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お姉様[みさかみこと]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mikoto Misaka (Sissy)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misaka Mikoto</title>
<summary>Kamijo senses something odd about the relationship shared by Mikoto and Misaka, who appears to be Mikoto’s twin. Later, after a friendly meeting with Kamijo, Misaka has a much more intense encounter with Accelerator.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719275</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95145" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="28">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹達[シスターズ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sisters (Sisters)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Siostry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sisters</title>
<summary>Kamijo is surprised – and confused – by the sudden arrival of yet another Misaka doppelganger. When the new look-alike explains why there are so many Mikotos running around, Kamijo decides to investigate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719277</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95306" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="28">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対能力[レベル6]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Level 6 (Absolute Ability)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Poziom 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Level 6</title>
<summary>Kamijo learns that thousands of Mikoto clones were created for one simple, violent reason. Now that her look-alikes are dying off, the real Mikoto vows to save the rest of her doppelgangers by making the ultimate sacrifice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719279</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95424" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="28">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一方通行[アクセラレータ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Accelerator (One Way)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Akcelerator</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Accelerator</title>
<summary>During a trip the bathhouse, Komoe offers insight on the awakening of esper powers to Index and Himegami. Later, Mikoto is skeptical when Kamijo volunteers to take on Accelerator in battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719281</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95955" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="31">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強[さいじゃく]VS最弱[さいきょう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Weakest vs. Strongest (Strongest vs. Weakest)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Najsłabszy kontra najsilniejszy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saijaku vs Saikyou</title>
<summary>Kamijo fights Accelerator to gain a better life for Mikoto and her clones. When the battle ends, Misaka 10032 visits Kamijo in the hospital to discuss the steps that must be taken for the clones to adapt to life in Academy City.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719283</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96263" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="30">5.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">御使堕し[エンゼルフォール]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angel Fall (Angel Fall)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Upadły Anioł</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Fall</title>
<summary>After Kamijo travels to a beach-side resort to meet his family, he winds up tangling with a Russian sorcerer named Misha. Later, Kanzaki and Tsuchimikado explain the ramifications of a recently cast spell called Angel Fall.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719285</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96264" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="28">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">父親[かみじょうとうや]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toya Kamijo (Father)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamijou Touya</title>
<summary>After Kamijo and Tsuchimikado rush to confront Misha about her suspicious behavior, they realize that Toya might have something to do with the Angel Fall spell. Can Kamijo save his dad from the Russian sorcerer’s wrath?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719291</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96298" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="28">4.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大天使[かみのちから]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Power of God (Archangel)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Boska moc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami no Chikara</title>
<summary>After figuring out the truth of Misha’s real identity, Kanzaki sends Kamijo and Toya to destroy the ritual spot. When Tsuchimikado suggests that Toya must die for the spell to end, a violent – and seemingly fatal – encounter ensues.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719293</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96496" update="2010-02-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96497" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96556" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="30">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽者[レプリカ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Replica (Impostor)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Replika</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Replica</title>
<summary>In order to shake off the unwanted attention she’s getting from Unabara, Misaka asks Kamijo to pretend to be her boyfriend. Things get complicated when the faux-couple discovers that Unabara is hiding a magical secret.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719295</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96557" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="23">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">打ち止め[ラストオーダー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Order (The End)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ostatni Rozkaz cz. 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Order</title>
<summary>Accelerator meets the last of Misaka’s clones – Last Order – who explains the special role she played in the Sister experiment. Later, Accelerator learns what steps he’ll have to take to keep Last Order safe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719305</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96558" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="24">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終信号[ウィルスコード]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Virus Code (Final Signal)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ostatni Rozkaz cz. 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Virus Code</title>
<summary>After Accelerator frees Last Order of the virus infecting her brain, he’s attacked by gun-wielding Amai. Just as all appears lost for Accelerator, Yoshikawa arrives to help – but Amai isn’t going down without a fight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719307</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96807" update="2016-01-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2009-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="16">2.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とある魔術の禁書目録[インデックス]たん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Certain Magical Index-tan</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">어떤 마술의 인덱스-땅</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toaru Majutsu no Index-tan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96873" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="21">3.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正体不明[カウンターストップ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Counter Stop (Identity Unknown)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Niwelator</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Counter Stop</title>
<summary>School’s back in session and that means new transfer students – one of which is Index! In class, Komoe offers more insight into the realities of life as an esper – and a powerful new magical presence is detected in Academy City.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719313</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96874" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="21">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">石像[ゴーレム]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Golem (Stone Figure)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Golem</title>
<summary>Panic ensues in Academy City upon the arrival of the sorcerer Sherry Cromwell, who makes no secret of her plans to destroy Kazakiri! Kamijo steps up to ruin Sherry’s plot – but the situation is more complex than he knows.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719315</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96977" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="24">2.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚数学区・五行機関</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Imaginary Number School District - Five-Element Agency</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Sekcja Liczb Urojonych, Stowarzyszenia Pięciu Elementów</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyosuu Gakku, Gogyou Kikan</title>
<summary>Kamijo, Index and Kazakiri join forces to take on Ellis. When the battle ends, and with the support of Index, Kazakiri returns to the place of her origin. Later, Tsuchimikado ponders Aleister’s role in recent events.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719319</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96978" update="2016-11-25">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="21">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風斬氷華[トモダチ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friends (Hyoka Kazakiri)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Przyjaciółka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi</title>
<summary>Kamijo chases Sherry away only to discover the sorcerer now has designs on Index! Meanwhile, with her secret revealed, Kazakiri takes advantage of her new situation and sets out to fight Ellis.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>719317</identifier>
<identifier>a-certain-magical-index</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="97264" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="5">P21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Parody 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103861" update="2016-01-15">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2009-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="14">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とある魔術の禁書目録[インデックス]たん 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Certain Magical Index-tan 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">어떤 마술의 인덱스-땅 II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toaru Majutsu no Index-tan 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106570" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108337" update="2010-02-25">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113019" update="2018-10-12">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128867" update="2011-03-16">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2009-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128868" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128869" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2009-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128870" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2009-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128871" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140205" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
