<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7134" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ookami Kakushi</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gods` harboring</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Hidden God</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Унесённые волками</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Скрывание Богов</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ookamikakushi</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">狼神隐</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Ookami</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">おおかみかくし</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Okamikakushi: Masque of the Wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">神隐之狼</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3574" approval="135" total="175">Higurashi no Naku Koro ni</anime>
<anime id="4894" approval="100" total="133">Higurashi no Naku Koro ni Kai</anime>
<anime id="5634" approval="93" total="124">Higurashi no Naku Koro ni Rei</anime>
<anime id="7268" approval="40" total="47">Shiki</anime>
<anime id="8556" approval="17" total="29">Another</anime>
<anime id="6051" approval="15" total="35">Umineko no Naku Koro ni</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="14283">For fans of Angst-themed Anime like Higurashi worth a shot, but starts extremely slow and confusing, even for this genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="832296">Only for fans of Mr. Ryuukishi07`s creations, and even some of them may be disappointed...
A certain young boy from big city arrives to a certain small town. At first, townspeople seem friendly, but it turns out they hide some dark secrets from him. Eventually, people start to disappear mysteriously. And there`s also a legend concerning the townspeople`s ancestry...
Alas, many points which were strong in "Higurashi", lack in this anime... Unmanly "hero", who has nothing in common with word-magician Keiichi or chess-master Battler. Very sketchy harem, dominated by childish stalker claiming to be a "sudden girlfriend". Simplified plot and mystery, having nothing on "Higurashi" or even "Umineko". The main antagonist is simple and sketchy as well...
But all things above could be bearable, if there was no HORRIBLE episode 13. It should be rather a separate OVA, because it`s... a parody!

It was a warning. Only for "Higurashi" fans, and even not every of them.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="398971">This one is indeed heavily underrated. The plot wasn`t too deep but it still found the series overall enjoyable. I wouldn`t recommend anyone to watch this just because they liked Higurashi and are looking for something similar - I hardly found this similar to Higurashi at all. Recommended for fans of the fantasy genre though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="379712">Actually, this series is infinitely less confusing then Higurashi - there is no time loop and its a mystery series so of course they`re not just going to come right out and tell you every little detail. Then it wouldnt be much of a mystery now would it?

In my opinion Ookami Kakushi is better then Higurashi and if your a fan of mystery, supernatural or thriller series then you should definetely give this a try. Its a very compelling watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="594546">I think I will recommend this one. It`s not a bad show, and it`s not an amazing show. It`s more like, pretty nice/good. This show is waaay too fucking underrated! Either the people are just going with the crowd or they are just looking at the bad sides of this show. I think this was pretty nice, I admit the ending was more on the side of OVA because most of the episode seems like that, but the last few scenes are the ending I was willing to work with. So I give this show a: 7.8/10. This was pretty good, but it`s shown in a way that makes you want to take a about an hour or two break on the show then go back. Overall, this was pretty nice, in the last 2 episodes the main character finally grew some balls. :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="469382">Not that bad of a series if you like dark stuff and you`re bored. Give it a shot and you might like it - it is only 11 episodes after all. 

And it`s been said before, but if you go into this series expecting another Higurashi you`re just setting yourself up for disappointment.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="296235">Ookami Kakushi is really underrated. Even though the last episode is indeed somewhat disappointing, it`s still enjoyable until episode 11, which is the actual ending.
Well, if you like horror/mystery anime like me,  I`d say this one is for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="656573">So great！</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/okami/</url>
<creators>
<name id="732" type="Animation Work">AIC</name>
<name id="5911" type="Original Work">Ryuukishi07</name>
<name id="5911" type="Original Plan">Ryuukishi07</name>
<name id="3012" type="Animation Character Design">Watanabe Atsuko</name>
<name id="677" type="Series Composition">Machida Touko</name>
<name id="1536" type="Direction">Takamoto Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="3012" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Atsuko</name>
<name id="15552" type="Original Work">Konami Digital Entertainment</name>
<name id="12305" type="Music">Ozawa Takumi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a PSP mystery adventure visual novel conceived after a concept by http://anidb.net/cr5911 [Ryuukishi07] and with designs by http://anidb.net/cr1312 [Peach-Pit].
Is it a god (kami)? Or a wolf (ookami)? A secret law in the old part of town ... brings together dread and mystery. It is the summer of Shouwa 58, 1983. Ten stories, intertwined by the idle thoughts of people caught in repeating nightmares ... what could possibly be the truth therein!?
A 16 year old boy, http://anidb.net/ch12586 [Kuzumi Hiroshi], started to live in a new town that is located in the mountains. The town is separated into new and old streets by the river, and many mysterious local cultures still remain. Although confused and enjoying his new life, one person kept her distance from him: class committee member Kushinada Nemuru. In their few encounters she gave him a word of advice: "Stay away from the old streets".</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1908">3.23</permanent>
<temporary count="1932">6.02</temporary>
<review count="1">5.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>37970.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11045</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7079</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4574</identifier>
<identifier>uojmyw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/okami/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ookami_Kakushi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>おおかみかくし</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1819</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335598</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12226</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2377</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2420" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>enigmatic</name>
<description>An enigmatic person is someone with a mysterious personality that is difficult to grasp and/or defies description.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5962" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>rural town</name>
<description>The rural town is one that is either isolated from what is considered "normal" society or it is so far away from the city centre that there are not a lot of buildings. Some rural towns do not have the technology of the city (and some want it that way), while others just seem to be behind the times. Most of these towns have some sort of farming culture or inn culture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12586" type="main character in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="6">2.45</rating>
<name>Kuzumi Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiroshi is a normal boy and the main character of the story. His family moved to Jyougamachi due reasons relating to his father`s line of work. The kanji for his name can also be read as "Professor", so many people call him Hakase as a nickname. Hiroshi isn`t fond of this nickname because it makes people believe that he`s some kind of a genius, which is far from the truth. Despite this, he still allows Kaname to call him by it.</description>
<picture>37927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12587" type="main character in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="14">7.08</rating>
<name>Kushinada Nemuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nemuru is the sole daughter of the Kushinada clan, the family with the most political power and presence in Jyougamachi. She is the class president of Hiroshi`s class. Nemuru is very cold to Hiroshi and considers him to be a bother.</description>
<picture>37928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12588" type="main character in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="8">4.99</rating>
<name>Kuzumi Mana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mana is Hiroshi`s 12-year old little sister. Due to a traffic accident, she is bound to a wheelchair. In spite of this, she strives to be independant, and becomes quite annoyed when her brother rushes to her side to help her with the smallest of tasks.</description>
<picture>37926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12589" type="main character in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="6">5.51</rating>
<name>Asagiri Kaname</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname moved to Jyougamachi with her family a few months before Hiroshi, and is Isuzu`s best friend. Because she`s a year older than the two, she tends to be the voice of the reason of the group. Kaname has somewhat of a dark personality, and doesn`t hesitate to tease or trick her two friends.</description>
<picture>37929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10333" picture="170916.jpg">Fuchigami Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12590" type="main character in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="8">7.00</rating>
<name>Tsumuhana Isuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isuzu is a girl that lives next door to Hiroshi. She has a tomboy personality and is extremely affectionate towards Hiroshi, sometimes to his dismay. Isuzu`s best friend is Kaname, and there seems to be some bad blood between her and Nemura. She also has a brother in university named Issei.</description>
<picture>37925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12592" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="5">5.93</rating>
<name>Mana Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>37930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14196" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-21">
<rating votes="2">1.46</rating>
<name>Kuzumi Masaaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="211227.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14197" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-21">
<rating votes="1">4.87</rating>
<name>Tsumuhana Issei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14198" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-21">
<rating votes="3">5.46</rating>
<name>Sakaki Shun`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14199" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-21">
<name>Washiu Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14200" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-21">
<rating votes="2">1.16</rating>
<name>Kushinada Shigetsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14201" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-21">
<rating votes="2">1.46</rating>
<name>Kushinada Juuzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18481" type="appears in" update="2010-06-04">
<name>Yomoda Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female waitress who works at the Cafè Etranger in the Old Town. She is good with people and has a reputation as a diligent worker.</description>
<seiyuu id="1444" picture="172066.jpg">Masu Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18482" type="appears in" update="2010-06-04">
<name>Tsumuhana Suzuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsumuhana Isuzu`s and Issei`s mother. She works as a part-timer in the New Town`s supermarket during the day.</description>
<seiyuu id="18698" picture="49321.jpg">Nakane Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18483" type="appears in" update="2010-06-04">
<name>Tsumuhana Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsumuhana Isuzu`s and Issei`s father.
They`ve lived in this town forver, but along with the town`s development the whole family moved into the apartment complex in the New Town.
He works as a buisiness man in a trading company in the New Town.</description>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18484" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<name>Ogasabara Shuugi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A classmate of Kuzumi Hiroshi.
A male student who has started to talk to him often lately.
Because people moving in from the outside are rare and he isn`t the only one who was approached by him, Hiroshi thinks nothing of it.
He is basically a good guy, but occasionaly he cracks some pretty strange jokes, which gave Hiroshi the creeps.</description>
<picture>153365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18485" type="appears in" update="2010-06-04">
<name>Machida Yuushio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man in the prime of his life who got assigned by the neighborhood association to be a night watchman (in the vigilant corps).
He works in a small in-town factory.
He has one child with his wife, so he leads a fairly normal family life.
His most favourite part about patroling the lonely streets at night is that he could even fart without any restraints, so he`s not a man with any special mentionable traits.
By the order of the neighborhood association and council, he is now tailing Tsumuhana Issei.</description>
<seiyuu id="42652" picture="170339.jpg">Matsuhisa Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18486" type="appears in" update="2014-04-21">
<name>Kasai Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The assistant chief of the Jougamachi Medical Center, a very capable man.
He graduated as top student from the Private Jouga University and is also a very talented surgeon.
Although he is still young, the expectations as a candidate to follow Kushinada Shigetsugu as the next hospital chief are piling up on him.
Still he is very diligent and shows a very strict attitude towards people who show incapability.
To stand above other people and lead them, he seeks for a way to gain more experience and strengthen his image.
He shows disgust towards the Ochibito.</description>
<picture>154681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18487" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Itsukushima Kanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young woman who snatched the lips of an Ochibito and turned her partner into a Kamibito.
It was the boy who actually started it, but she was still executed by the laws of the Kamibito.
Whatever reason there might have been, to turn an Ochibito into a Kamibito is a serious crime and needs to be punished according to the law.</description>
<seiyuu id="9124" picture="186845.jpg">Hayama Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18488" type="appears in" update="2011-01-16">
<rating votes="3">5.62</rating>
<name>Ichigaki Masami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3190" picture="62583.jpg">Yamaguchi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66450" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<name>Aniki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26" picture="170737.jpg">Chijiwa Ryuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66451" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<name>Sabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="111977" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嫦娥町</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Joga Town</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jouga Machi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112212" update="2009-12-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">4.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112741" update="2010-01-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Siblings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ani Imouto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113055" update="2010-01-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Impulse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113182" update="2010-08-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Runaway</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113183" update="2010-01-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">予感</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Premonition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116178" update="2010-05-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116179" update="2010-05-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116227" update="2010-02-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">錯綜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Complication</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakusou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116228" update="2010-08-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">喪失</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116229" update="2010-08-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116505" update="2010-02-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">密室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Room</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misshitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116773" update="2010-03-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">八朔祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hassaku Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hassaku Matsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116853" update="2010-03-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終焉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Demise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116856" update="2010-03-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嫦娥町奇譚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Tale of Joga Town</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jouga Machi Kitan</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
