<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7939" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-07-16</startdate>
<enddate>2011-10-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dantalian no Shoka</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Таинственная библиотека Данталиан</title>
<title xml:lang="la" type="synonym">Bibliotheca Mystica de Dantalian</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Тайнствената библиотека на Данталиан</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Містична бібліотека Данталіан</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ダンタリアンの書架</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Mystic Archives of Dantalian</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">The Mystic Archives of Dantalian</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">단탈리안의 서가</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">丹特麗安的書架</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">丹特丽安的书架</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8944" type="Side Story">Dantalian no Shoka: Ibarahime</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7719" approval="140" total="165">Gosick</anime>
<anime id="8370" approval="8" total="18">Kamisama no Memo-chou: It`s the Only NEET Thing to Do.</anime>
<anime id="105" approval="1" total="6">R.O.D: Read or Die</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="522619">simply beautiful, that`s how I describe this anime, it has similar character to gosick..., goth lolita main character Dantian reminds me of Victorica from Gosick, but the story was different for me..., for story term Kamisama no memochou is more similar gosick..., they have "similar taste" with different background..., I enjoy this anime..., but the ending wasn`t totally ended here..., should be a second season...recommended for those who enjoy Gosick</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="481909">Actually I thought I`ll get a very simple entertainment with some loli-fanservice. And really this Dalian reminds me a lot of this detestable Victorica from Gosick. But fortunately that is the only real bitterness in this show and I`m really impressed by the solid groundwork of this show. There is actually a knowledge on books that probably only bibliophiles will really know to appreciate, but for the other ones there is still Dalian...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="163989">It has this awesome feeling and atmosphere around it. In general it looks great. It has an excellent array of strong individual plot in each episode but last two episode seemed introduction to solid storyline so it is a beggining not an end, I`m expecting second season. Even if not the show still was a good change from all the traditional anime, it truly was something special.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="94967">This is a tough one to rate. Episode 1 is an animation masterpiece by Gainax with both period feel and certain heaviness to itself, despite the light novel origin. Yet none of the episodes afterwards come even close to it. Nevertheless for that first episode and that episode alone I`m declaring this a must see. For all I care you can skip the rest of the show, just give that episode 1 a try. Thankfully episode 1 is both an introduction as well as the complete story of the meeting of the two lead characters.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://dantalian.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9952" type="Original Work">Mikumo Gakuto</name>
<name id="718" type="Animation Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="10944" type="Character Design">Kinoshita Sumie</name>
<name id="20972" type="Direction">Uemura Yutaka</name>
<name id="6725" type="Music">Tsuji You</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr9952 [Mikumo Gakuto]`s Bibliotheca Mystica de Dantalian (Dantalian no Shoka) light novel series.
http://anidb.net/ch30365 [Lord Hugh Disward (Huey)] has inherited his grandfather`s estate, including his large collection of books collected over a lifetime only if he agrees to also become the custodian of a legendary library called the Bibliotheca Mystica de Dantalian, said to have been created by the Daemon of Knowledge Dantalian, and to look after a mysterious girl named http://anidb.net/ch30364 [Dalian] who holds the secrets to the collection. The responsibilities also include, with the help and guidance of Dalian, continuing to collect and seal away books that prove powerful and dangerous.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2241">5.59</permanent>
<temporary count="2258">7.00</temporary>
<review count="2">5.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>72331.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11860</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8915</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4942</identifier>
<identifier>tvgknu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/dantalian/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dantalian_no_Shoka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ダンタリアンの書架</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2203</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339544</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13551</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="355" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-30">
<name>wings</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2688" parentid="2641" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>World War I</name>
<description>Set in the time of World War 1</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2689" parentid="2641" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-02">
<name>1920s</name>
<description>During the 1920s, we had gangsters, Mafia, alcohol, and gambling prohibition.
The Corleones ruled that time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2777" parentid="2809" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>London</name>
<description>London is the capital and most populous city of both England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south east of the island of Great Britain, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. It was founded by the Romans, who named it Londinium.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214379.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2807" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>France</name>
<description>France, officially the French Republic, is a country whose territory consists of metropolitan France in western Europe, as well as several overseas regions and territories. The metropolitan area of France extends from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean. The overseas territories include French Guiana in South America and several islands in the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian oceans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214343.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2884" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>psychoactive drugs</name>
<description>Psychoactive drugs are chemical substances that affect the function of the central nervous system, altering perception, mood or consciousness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3196" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-19">
<name>photographic backgrounds</name>
<description>Real-life backgrounds, with the possible addition of a few 2D elements are shown / used in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3772" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>library</name>
<description>In a traditional sense, a library is a large collection of books, and can refer to the place in which the collection is housed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4136" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-03-05">
<name>sudden loli companion appearance</name>
<description>The main character meets a preadolescent girl in an unexpected way becoming a friend / partner of the main character.
(The term loli is short for Lolita meaning a girl in preadolescent age. Typical attributes are moe, cute, and innocent.)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4199" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-20">
<name>live-action closing -- TO BE MOVED AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be removed. For each tagged anime, please tag the corresponding ending/credits episodes with the http://anidb.net/t6679 [live-action episode] tag (adding them and their relation to the ending songs if necessary) and then remove this tag from it. Please do not apply this credit to the main episode that has the live-action ending, only to the corresponding credits episode. For example, if episode 22 has a live-action ending, and that ending is also credits episode C7, tag episode C7, not episode 22.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4337" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-03-11">
<name>you`re my hidden weapon!</name>
<description>One or more characters (females usually) turn into weapons or release them from their body to be used by their teammate or partner in times of need.
Examples: Himemiya Anthy from Shoujo Kakumei Utena, Soul from Soul Eater, Kureha from Shining x Tears Wind, and Yuzuriha Inori from Guilty Crown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4715" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-07-01">
<name>dementia</name>
<description>Serious emotional and mental deterioration of organic or functional origin, often age-related.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5030" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>pact</name>
<description>A pact, from Latin pactum ("something agreed upon"), is a formal agreement. Within anime as a medium is usually entails some sort of sacrifice on one`s part in the exchange for power.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5307" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-01-24">
<name>aggressive plants</name>
<description>Plants that can actually attack humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5779" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-18">
<name>anachronisms</name>
<description>Customs, events, or objects are shown in a period to which they do not belong, e.g. jet planes in medieval Japan.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5838" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-26">
<name>fire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6730" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>torture</name>
<description>Torture involves the deliberate act of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or apply coercion to compel action from the victim. Torture, by definition, is a knowing and intentional act; deeds which unknowingly or negligently inflict pain without a specific intent to do so are not typically considered torture.
This is distinct from http://anidb.net/t2905 [erotic torture], which is generally for the purpose of using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="30364" type="main character in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="77">7.55</rating>
<name>Dalian</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30365" type="main character in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="33">8.31</rating>
<name>Hugh Anthony Disward</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74089.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34786" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-07-18">
<rating votes="9">4.41</rating>
<name>Shounen Huey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35302" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="10">6.85</rating>
<name>Camilla Sauer Keynes</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47838.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35828" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="19">6.11</rating>
<name>Shoka no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35829" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">6.11</rating>
<name>Hal Kamhout</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35830" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="13">5.47</rating>
<name>Flamberge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35831" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="3">5.62</rating>
<name>Patricia Nash</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="129542.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35832" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="4">4.19</rating>
<name>Meibel Nash</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35833" type="appears in" update="2011-09-29">
<rating votes="4">7.43</rating>
<name>Rasiel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35834" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="4">4.51</rating>
<name>Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13872" picture="223706.jpg">Yamaguchi Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35835" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11054" picture="39865.jpg">Sakamoto Kunpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35836" type="appears in" update="2011-09-29">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Kyouju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35837" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Sobo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3608" picture="24899.jpg">Maeda Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35838" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Sofu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3125" picture="24097.jpg">Mitsuo Senda</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35839" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="4">3.54</rating>
<name>Armand Jeremiah</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35840" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Granville Ani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35841" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Granville Otouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47715.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35842" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Sir Balboa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35843" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Melgar Hakushaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47731.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35844" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Lord Moskin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35845" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="4">6.51</rating>
<name>Viola</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35846" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="4">6.48</rating>
<name>Danshaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35847" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="3">3.54</rating>
<name>Paula Dickinson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35848" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<name>Lateisha Sakis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35849" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">6.76</rating>
<name>Lenny Lentz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35850" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Kyokuin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30012" picture="130105.jpg">Odagaki Yuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35851" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="3">3.54</rating>
<name>Mildred</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35852" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Shou Futori no Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="478" picture="17453.jpg">Nakamura Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35853" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Akage no Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35854" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="6">5.01</rating>
<name>Estella Lilburn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35855" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Martin Geese</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2248" picture="170362.jpg">Kawashima Tokuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35856" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Footman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>47843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9704" picture="42147.jpg">Yasui Kunihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36042" type="appears in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Noss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2145" picture="82117.jpg">Miyashita Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36043" type="appears in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="9">5.89</rating>
<name>Fiona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36044" type="appears in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Vance</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36045" type="appears in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28228" picture="50074.jpg">Mishima Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36046" type="appears in" update="2011-08-27">
<rating votes="2">2.58</rating>
<name>Shachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="601" picture="165793.jpg">Nakamura Hidetoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36295" type="appears in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="3">2.86</rating>
<name>Fieron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36296" type="appears in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<name>Maid</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28304" picture="51542.jpg">Tanaka Satowa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36297" type="appears in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<name>Lianna Scholes</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36298" type="appears in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<name>Josei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5889" picture="30436.jpg">Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36299" type="appears in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Wakamono</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28303" picture="51533.jpg">Shinohara Takumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36300" type="appears in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="480" picture="232940.jpg">Kawakubo Kiyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36301" type="appears in" update="2011-09-03">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Footman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12665" picture="227715.jpg">Kawakami Takafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36635" type="appears in" update="2011-09-11">
<rating votes="3">5.62</rating>
<name>Ira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36636" type="appears in" update="2011-09-11">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Salut</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3135" picture="24120.jpg">Fujimoto Yuzuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36637" type="appears in" update="2011-09-11">
<rating votes="4">3.49</rating>
<name>Gianni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36638" type="appears in" update="2011-09-11">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Teito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36639" type="appears in" update="2011-09-11">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Heishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36640" type="appears in" update="2011-09-11">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Oobaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36641" type="appears in" update="2011-09-11">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Akachan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4622" picture="26955.jpg">Horiguchi Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37002" type="appears in" update="2011-09-24">
<rating votes="7">6.75</rating>
<name>Christabel Sistine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59534.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37003" type="appears in" update="2011-09-24">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Kendrick</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37004" type="appears in" update="2011-09-24">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Dallaglio Hayward</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37215" type="appears in" update="2011-09-29">
<rating votes="4">5.81</rating>
<name>Ilas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37216" type="appears in" update="2017-09-15">
<rating votes="4">4.22</rating>
<name>Evans</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23246" picture="61476.jpg">Tajiri Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37217" type="appears in" update="2011-09-29">
<rating votes="3">4.21</rating>
<name>Chuutaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23515" picture="64437.jpg">Kuramochi Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37274" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Shounen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20274" picture="52888.jpg">Nakajima Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37275" type="appears in" update="2011-10-02">
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<name>Keikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18360" picture="48491.jpg">Yamazaki Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="126556" update="2011-01-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130760" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仕掛け絵本</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Turn-up Book</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`Arlequinade</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Livro De Dobradura!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikake Ehon</title>
<summary>Hugh Anthony Disward visits the estate of his inheritance after news of his grandfather’s untimely death. A notorious bibliophile, the old man left behind a library that’s out of this world. But who is that mysterious young girl?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131689" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">換魂[かんこん]の書</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of Soul Exchange</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le livre de la transformation</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Livro Da Troca De Almas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kankon no Sho</title>
<summary>After finishing the second book in a trilogy, Dalian is desperate to read the last. Not only did the author die before writing it, he also wrote a letter to Disward pleading for help. They soon learn that Dalian is not the only die-hard fan of the series.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131690" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">叡智の書 / 月下美人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of Wisdom / Queen of the Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le livre de la sagesse / Reine de la nuit</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Livro Da Sabedoria! - Rainha Da Noite!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eichi no Sho / Gekkabijin</title>
<summary>A childhood friend tells Huey of a schoolteacher whose students have become knowledgeable beyond measure. Later, two suspicious men come to the Disward manor in search of a valuable book.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131691" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">胎児の書</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of Fetus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le livre du foetus</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Livro Do Feto!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiji no Sho</title>
<summary>Huey and Dalian are hired to appraise the Lilburn family’s library and soon discover that a string of murders surround the beautiful maiden of the estate, Estella. Could it be the curse of a Phantom Book?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132018" update="2012-04-04">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132226" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黄昏の書</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of Twilight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le livre du crépuscule</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Livro Do Crepúsculo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tasogare no Sho</title>
<summary>A swarm of insects ravages a town, and one girl is on a mission to protect it and her beloved. But Dalian warns that the poison she’s making won’t be enough. What are these bugs anyway?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132227" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">等価の書 / 連理の書</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of Equivalence / Book of Relationship</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le livre de l`équivalence / Le livre de l`union</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Livro Da Equivalência! - Livro Do Relacionamento!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touka no Sho / Renri no Sho</title>
<summary>Huey and Dalian go on a wild goose chase when they realize Camilla has obtained a Phantom Book that can exchange items of equal value. Then, Armand pleads for help with more relationship problems that are growing worse by the minute.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132228" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">調香師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Perfumer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La parfumeuse</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Perfumista!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choko-shi</title>
<summary>A trip to the bakery is interrupted by a woman on the run. Before long, Huey and Dalian find themselves in the midst of a famous perfume company’s ordeals. But something smells fishy—just how is a criminal organization involved?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132229" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">焚書官[ふんしょかん]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Libricide</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le brûleur de livres</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Queimador De Livros!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funshokan</title>
<summary>A man who calls himself a Libricide Officer arrives in a town shrouded in mystery. Along for the ride is his peculiar companion—a woman with a lock just like Dalian’s!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132230" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔術師の娘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magician`s Daughter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille du magicien</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A Filha Do Mago!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majutsushi no Musume</title>
<summary>An old friend asks Huey for a Phantom Book, hoping to win the heart of a beguiling courtesan. But on the next full moon, they find that he’s far from being the only man after the beauty’s hand, or her life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132724" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まだ見ぬ明日の詩[うた]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Song for the Unwritten Future</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Poème d`un futur encore voilé</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Canção Do Amanhã Desconhecido!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mada Minu Ashita no Uta</title>
<summary>The city is plagued by increasing numbers of zombies, and a newspaper leads Huey and Dalian to the culprits. But this time, it may be more than they can handle, and Huey still has to make good on a childhood promise before it’s too late.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132725" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラジエルの書架</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bibliotheca Razielis Archangeli</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bibliothèque de Raziel</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Biblioteca Mística De Rasiel!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rasiel no Shoka</title>
<summary>When Huey was a new recruit during the war, he quickly befriended his captain, Eilas. A lover of poetry, the pilot’s writing took on a sort of power when read aloud. But a Bibliotheca from the past appears before Eilas once more with a curious question.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132726" update="2018-07-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom Score</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les partitions fantômes</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Fantasia!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genkyoku</title>
<summary>Huey and Dalian meet a talented violinist in the park who is rumored to have played a Phantom Score. The piece is said to be impossible to play, and that it will cause extreme emotions in anyone who hears it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133731" update="2011-10-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133732" update="2011-10-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138444" update="2012-04-04">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">15s TV Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138445" update="2012-04-04">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">15s TV Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138446" update="2012-04-04">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">50s Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149696" update="2013-04-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2011-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特典ディスク ダリアンの本棚 その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dalian no Hondana Sono 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
