<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8181" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-04-15</startdate>
<enddate>2011-06-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ano Hi Mita Hana no Namae o Bokutachi wa Mada Shiranai.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">We Still Don`t Know the Name of the Flower We Saw That Day.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ano Hana</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Невиданный цветок</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">А нам всё невдомёк, как звался тот цветок</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Nadal nie znamy nazwy kwiatu, który widzieliśmy tamtego dnia.</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">لازلنا لا نعرف أسماء الزهور التي رأيناها في ذلك اليوم</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">אנחנו עדיין לא יודעים את השם של הפרח שראינו באותו היום</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">O Gün Gördüğümüz Çiçeğin Adını Hala Bilmiyoruz</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Невідома квітка, що ми побачили того дня</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">那日所見花兒之名我們仍未知曉</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">那日所见花儿之名我们仍未知晓</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">هنوز اسم گلی که آن روز دیدیم را نمی دانیم</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="synonym">Тэр Цэцэг</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">anohana</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Ano Hana</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="short">那朵花</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="short">Ано Хана</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あの日見た花の名前を僕達はまだ知らない.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Anohana: The Flower We Saw That Day</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Ano Hana: Ancora non conosciamo il nome del fiore che abbiamo visto quel giorno</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Anohana: The Flower We Saw That Day</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">그날 본 꽃의 이름을 우리는 아직 모른다</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ดอกไม้ มิตรภาพ และ ความทรงจำ</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Все още не знаем името на цветето, което видяхме онзи ден.</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">我們仍未知道那天所看見的花名。</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我们仍未知道那天所看见的花的名字.</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Anohana: The Flower We Saw That Day</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="official">Тэр Нэгэн Өдөр Харсан Цэцгийн Нэрийг Бид Одоо ч Мэдэхгүй</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9356" type="Sequel">Gekijouban Ano Hi Mita Hana no Namae o Bokutachi wa Mada Shiranai.</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2835" approval="59" total="110">Hachimitsu to Clover</anime>
<anime id="9387" approval="24" total="45">Nagi no Asukara</anime>
<anime id="5101" approval="22" total="46">Clannad</anime>
<anime id="8620" approval="22" total="46">Ano Natsu de Matteru</anime>
<anime id="6424" approval="20" total="53">Cross Game</anime>
<anime id="10959" approval="18" total="30">Kokoro ga Sakebitagatterunda.</anime>
<anime id="13439" approval="18" total="24">Shichisei no Subaru</anime>
<anime id="10525" approval="18" total="23">Sora no Method</anime>
<anime id="8852" approval="15" total="36">Tasogare Otome x Amnesia</anime>
<anime id="10771" approval="7" total="7">Sakura Capsule</anime>
<anime id="2002" approval="6" total="19">Air</anime>
<anime id="9132" approval="6" total="16">Little Busters!</anime>
<anime id="896" approval="3" total="19">Kimi ga Nozomu Eien</anime>
<anime id="9126" approval="3" total="11">Natsuyuki Rendezvous</anime>
<anime id="4568" approval="2" total="15">Byousoku 5 Centimeter</anime>
<anime id="3572" approval="2" total="8">Shinigami no Ballad</anime>
<anime id="6374" approval="1" total="23">Asura Cryin`</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="91">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="333468">very good plot sad + comedy, the best sad ending ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="404506">best show</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="494562">I think it was a good watch but not great but if ask me if i could rewatch this anime i would say no of course</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="61503">Highly recommend, entertaining and emotional.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="127743">Great series with a good ending. I Cried, I laughed, I felt sadness. The music was touching too. God, It`s been one hell of a ride!  Must see it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="518341">Even though you know that you are getting conveniently spoon-fed with the melodrama, you still can`t help but to get emotionally engaged (well, most people).
Very few can withstand this without shedding tears. A beautiful story. I didn`t care for it being sometimes over-the-top.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="473733">Ya... the plot was nice a refreshing. This is by far one of the best in this season. But everyone ignores many weakness in this plot. And please don`t compare this with Clannad After Story.... this doesn`t stand a chance in both plot and character.... The process ain`t THAT sad.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="507045">Childhood chums who have drifted apart struggle with guilt and shame over the death of a beloved friend. She returns as a ghost with a request from the group which demands they rekindle their close bond and forge new connections with their families.

The often frustrating attempts to guess the needs and wishes of a spirit that only one person in the group can see add to the viewer`s desire that  these friends settle their differences, sort out their issues and feel the love and comraderie that brought them together as children.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="396857">Plot is good, music is good, drama is fairly good. Characters are all right. Art and animation is nothing special, but it`s decent. Definitely a very good anime overall though, and definitely heartwarming. I`d say it`s not quite as sad or moving as I was expecting based on some of the other comments here, as I like drama anime, and consider myself pretty emotional, but I "only" actually cried twice watching this, which is less than when I watched, say, Clannad, or Tamayura (granted all the seasons combined make it a fairly long series), or the Koe no Katachi movie. But still, it was a nice watch. Recommended. I guess I`ll watch the movie next.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="492628">A story about grief, sadness, loss, friendship, happiness and never ending love.
Because the early to middle episodes are so dragging it becomes hard to get attached at first but when you do... it`s gonna fell like ninjas cutting onions all over the place.
Happy ending.
Recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="265326">Just great anime , the sheer amount of emotion in the last episodes made me jumps off my chair . Such a heartwarming anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="119972">Ano Hi Mita... is very well-made anime, but it lacks new ideas. The plot is predictable.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="277303">highly recommended!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="468466">It has a suprisingly great story with great character development. I find the characters very believable and while a little sad it has a heart warming story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="82129">I found it a wonderful story with a happy but tragic sad ending because I did`nt want it to end. And neither did the charactors. 
This is a story about loss and gain of ones self, it`s about unfinished relationships and unrequited love that becomes something.  It`s a must see for any hopeless romantic and anyone that believes in things unseen and wants to see them.  You will be able to relate to at least one charactor/ Which one will be upto you. This story will tear at you from every direction slowly. And the more compassion you have the more this story effect you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="421392">This anime was better than I expected, the plot is very similar to that of clannad. Characters are likeable and the visuals are excellent.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="507364">im just going to say that i cried ..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="311880">This anime is just amazing! Six childhood friends comes together after a while, well just 5 to be exact... why were separated in the first place, how have they changed and what will happen now ? Each episode reveals more and more, the story is so exiting that you just can`t wait to see the next episode!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="228576">After all these anime I`ve seen I never thought there is an anime that would still make me shed a tear. Both storyline and animation are great.
Definitely MUST SEE!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="149129">If u`re an anime fans, then this is one of the best. masterpiece graphic + impressive storyline.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="164374">This series was great. animation + story combined! This one is a real tearjerker!! The message this series created was well received by me! I hope it sends different wavelengths of emotions to anybody who watches and understands its realness! Although there was a lot happening by the time the series was ending, it did not deteriorate or disappoint at all! To anyone who`s thinking of watching Ano Hana, I plead you to do it a.s.a.p.!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="380155">Wow, just wow, this is one of the best dramas I`ve ever seen! Everything in it is just soo good and it really got to me, so if you`re looking for a good drama out there, watch this! It`s a must see!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="90098">the only problem with it, was the lenght of it :P other then that it was a gr8 watch :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296364">this anime is great i kept going back to watch it after every release and the ending got me</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="412755">Really something special - it tugs at your emotions like no other anime. Highly recommended for anyone.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="474919">Absolutely brilliant. 
Though some might say it`s predictable and unoriginal, the plot is nicely paced and makes for an extremely entertaining and exciting watch. A tear jerker at the end, it`ll surely bring you a few all-too-short hours of enjoyment.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="466955">I had very so much fun enjoying this anime, it was very emotional at the end.
Watch this Feel-Good anime now.
I guarantee you will like this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="43461">I just finished watching the last ep and I have to say, I had to fight back the tears that were welling up. I knew where it was going but there were still a surprise moment with Poppo near the end that put a mental image in me that made it harder to stave off the tears. Such a bittersweet ending. This is a solid must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422859">I cried man tears.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="480721">Words fail to describe just how well this is done.  I found myself thankful I never had to go through something similar.  

Bottom line is see it and you`ll know why it made it on the list of top anime`s of 2011.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="135091">amazing storyline, amazing characters, fell in love with this show, amazing soundtracks as well</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="35401">A two toliet paper roll anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="373896">This was just great. Nothing more to say. Great, amazing, awesome, brilliant. I have no negative comments about this. It made me cry not just at the end. And the overall atmosphere was great.
Everyone who likes the genre should watch this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="148166">Without doubt AnoHana is one of the EXCELLENT shows out there in both the drama category and anime in general .. the music and songs are chosen to fit perfectly with the themes .. the animation is excellent for a Drama show and character designs and color palettes are lively and vibrant .. story is very well paced and has a strong impacting climax .. characters have depth and the show gives every one of them a chance to shine … .. oh .. and no disgusting fan-service, no pointless nudity, no dick jokes or boob groping or panty shots, no dumb cardboard characters … what’s not to like !!!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="468231">A wonderful story. If you are like me, your emotions will take over.
Do not need to say anything more. It`s already covered by other recommendations.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="335602">Ridiculously good drama series that sets such a nice atmosphere throughout the entirety of this anime that never bores you at all. Also the first anime that actually got me in tears during the last episode.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="583710">I completely lost it crying, so touching and sweet. I love this anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="171409">I cried....</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="162486">If you like the drama genre and original plots this one is for you. It`s quite astonishing that the plot is something you never saw before, while still describing daily life (with only one supernatural element in it).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="475247">Anohana and Clannad are best tragedy anime. Masterpieces. Both. Watch it and prepare to cry a lot. 

BTW OP and ED are one of the best i ever seen.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="504638">If you`re looking for low-commitment drama, here it is. Ano Hana is surely one of the best series in this department. With only 11 episodes, you get involved with the characters and the struggles of coming of age almost as if you already knew them beforehand. Take a seat and appreciate this sweet and touching story about friendship and loss.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="212957">Heart wrenching, heartwarming story like none other I`ve seen. Simply a masterpiece!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="509872">Drink plenty of water to stay hydrated from all the tears!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="69105">It`s just good. I don`t know what else to say.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="485620">For me, after Clannad the secound best Drama. The Story and the Charakters are great. Many Sad moments which delights the heart, but there are still funny situation, especially Menma.

must see</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="396739">epic just epic ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="454583">for my 2 years experience on anime, this is one of the best, its a masterpiece!, you`ll regret not watching this, MUST SEEE</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="397320">It`s a short anime that from the first episode you will surely love it. The Op and the Ed are great. The story is not real but you think it could really happen. Just amazing. MUST SEE!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="554983">It is the only anime that ever wrung tears from my eyes. That`s self-explanatory, you must see it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="498732">A masterpiece and maybe the best show in the last years despite the mandatory loli-character that has plagued every anime these days.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="483674">GORGEOUS</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="473021">If you don`t like it, you`re a terrible person.♥</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="448871">One of the best slice of life anime I have ever seen. You will not regret watching this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="460607">Psychology in anime at its very best. Every aspect of every character is thought out. Story is emotional and thought provoking. Gems of such quality do not come often - you should do yourself a favour and watch it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="460841">Well, you see... It`s rare for me to do this but uhm. I`ll spare you the nonsense... but here, know this!
What you see is what you get! See that ratings(9+), see that comments(the best of spring), see how great this is.
You will (NOT) regret this (4.44)!!!
(I`ve been through 8, I heard the last 3 will be the climax spike)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="151437">This is a must see, this is my first time recommending an anime and I tell you THIS IS A MUST SEE!

Each episode is getting more and more interesting!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="456383">This is the best series of this spring 2011... simple has masterpiece written all over it. This has never being my type of anime but after getting ep 1 by mistake I could not stop watching. It`s so different than anything else... A true breath of fresh air.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="472569">tho I don`t like anime, I couldn`t stop watching this one after i downloaded it for my sister. the story is great, the animation has good quality and the dialogues are rich, and I loved it.. worth wasting your time on watching it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="264691">could be big flop in my life `cause i didnt know this series when it comes out. Must see. Emotional and touchy story and music is good especially the ending song. it makes me cry couple times. The ending could be expected but it`s great anime overall.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="383243">inexpressible. last time I felt something like that when I watched сlannad 2.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="54309">Watch it while it`s awesome.

You will either end up watching one of the best ever, or one of the biggest disappointments.

It`s gonna be legen... wait for it...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="335704">Awesome drama which is good to watch if you don`t like the shoujo/josei type drama.

You will expierence a myriad of emotions while watching this anime, which for me is what a good/succesful anime is about.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="167028">Drama worth watching with a brilliant use of the ending song that actually was from 10 years ago. Nice touch indeed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="324464">interesting story must see..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="275831">I tell you, this is one of the best dramas I`ve seen so far. If you liked Clannad, Air or Angel Beats, you must see this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="151942">Fantastic show! a unique story with great character development and an awesome soundtrack to boot.  I will re-watch this series for sure. I believe that this would be something a non-anime fan could appreciate as well!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="366429">Watch it!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="484892">What can I say about Ano Hi Mita Hana no Namae wo Bokutachi wa Mada Shiranai?  Well, it is one of the best slice of life, touchy-feely animes that I have seen.  There is excellent character development within this anime, and the relationships between the characters develop immensely for just a 11 episode anime.  But beware:  This anime will probably make you cry.  Overall, it was very worth watching and one of the best animes of the past year.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.anohana.jp/tv/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="2210" type="Character Design">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="2188" type="Direction">Nagai Tatsuyuki</name>
<name id="1303" type="Animation Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="2210" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="24701" type="Music">Remedios</name>
<name id="51037" type="Original Work">Chou Heiwa Busters</name>
</creators>
<description>When http://anidb.net/ch28416 [Yadomi Jinta] was a child, he was a central piece in a group of close friends. In time, however, these childhood friends drifted apart, and when they became high school students, they had long ceased to think of each other as friends.
One of the friends from that group, http://anidb.net/ch28417 [Honma Meiko], now has a wish she asks Jinta to fulfil. The problem is, she can`t remember what her wish is anymore. As Meiko won`t cease to bother Jinta about it, he gives in and decides to try to grant this wish he knows nothing of; for that, however, the help of his other former friends, now all very estranged from himself and from each other, may turn out to be necessary. He hasn`t spoken to http://anidb.net/ch28415 [Anjou Naruko], http://anidb.net/ch28418 [Matsuyuki Atsumu], http://anidb.net/ch28419 [Tsurumi Chiriko], or http://anidb.net/ch28414 [Hisakawa Tetsudou] in a long time; as he struggles to grant Meiko`s wish and gathers his old friends together in the process, all the old feelings that still exist between them and have long been stashed away are bound to come up again.
— written by Hinoe
Note: The first episode was scheduled to receive a preview screening as part of an event at Animecontents Expo`s Makuhari Messe Red Stage on Saturday, 26th March, 2011. However, the Animecontents Expo was cancelled following the Great Tohoku Earthquake.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7137">8.42</permanent>
<temporary count="7224">8.24</temporary>
<review count="11">7.46</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221330.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12368</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9989</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4859</identifier>
<identifier>vmfhii</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.anohana.jp/tv/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Anohana:_The_Flower_We_Saw_That_Day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>あの日見た花の名前を僕達はまだ知らない。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2156</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>338894</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13391</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14583</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3848" parentid="6348" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-02">
<name>preview in ed</name>
<description>For some reason the director decided to show the preview during the ending sequence.
In some cases the preview might be after the ending animation, but still during the ending theme.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4477" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>communication with the dead</name>
<description>This character is able of some manner of communication with the dead, or at least with one dead person. This includes talking to the dead, seeing the dead, outright mediumship, or any form of unidirectional or bidirectional form of communication that ordinary characters are not generally able to achieve.
This does not apply in environments where characters are expected to be dead, or where nobody is alive to begin with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5956" parentid="2862" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>broken friendship</name>
<description>For a broken friendship a group of three friends is a must, the break up can be caused by betrayal or death, a love triangle is also possible. The ghost of the old friendship will be the cause of many flashbacks and reminiscences. A dreaded face to face could be a major event or just used as plot device.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6348" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2015-02-19">
<name>old animetags - OP ED</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18057" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="10">2.80</rating>
<name>JK</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>JK is an occult dowser who specializes in using dowsing rods to locate individuals. Like http://anidb.net/ch18061 [Kozue], he is also an occult manic and often accompanies the other characters when occult-related events occur. He is able to engage in combat using his dowsing rods, but usually calls for http://anidb.net/ch18058 [Smile] when in trouble.</description>
<picture>53546.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18058" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="10">4.81</rating>
<name>Smile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smile acts as the mechanic for the http://anidb.net/ch20888 [Academy]. He first meets http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] and the others when http://anidb.net/ch18063 [Ami] requested his and http://anidb.net/ch18057 [JK]`s help to find the possessed former principal. Smile is shown to be very adept at physical combat although he often carries an enormous wrench as a weapon. He is usually shown to be with http://anidb.net/ch18057 [JK].</description>
<picture>53547.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18061" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="21">3.11</rating>
<name>Naruse Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naruse Kozue is first shown to be a http://anidb.net/ch18063 [Ami]`s friend and classmate at the http://anidb.net/ch20888 [Academy]. She is deeply embracing of the occult, shown through her endeavors to prove to http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] that the occult is very real as well as agreeing to go through a near death experience for a class demonstration. Kozue is portrayed as a being very clumsy, often being the first to fall victim to demons.</description>
<picture>53545.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18062" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-03-18">
<rating votes="90">8.24</rating>
<name>Kumashiro Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kumashiro Maya is a daughter of the Waldstein Academy`s late headmaster, http://anidb.net/ch19562 [Kumashiro Jun`ichirou]. She hates occult despite her good knowledge about it. Her hatred stemmed from her father`s obsession with it which caused a strained relationship between his wife and daughter. After her father`s death, Maya becomes headmistress of the school and vows to destroy the school. But after the arrival of http://anidb.net/ch18060 [Uchida Fumiaki], she teams up with him in order to find the key of Nostradamus which will cause an alien invasion in 1999.</description>
<picture>48517.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18063" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="16">4.97</rating>
<name>Kuroki Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuroki Ami is http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya]`s childhood friend as well as classmate in the Academy. She genuinely cares for http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] and tries to mend http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya]`s relationship with the occult. Ami is often seen with http://anidb.net/ch18061 [Kozue], http://anidb.net/ch18057 [JK], and http://anidb.net/ch18058 [Smile].</description>
<picture>53544.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="28414" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="58">6.93</rating>
<name>Hisakawa Tetsudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hisakawa Tetsudou, nicknamed Poppo, is the first friend that Jinta reconnects with. As a child, Poppo was uncontrollably energetic and friendly. These traits have not changed. Presently, Jinta reunited with him when he was searching for Menma. He visited their old clubhouse and found that Poppo was living there. Poppo explains that he works part-time jobs to earn money. When he makes enough, he goes on trips around the world. Because of this, Poppo does not attend high school.
Poppo seems to have questionable interests: Jinta found several pornographic magazines upon entering the clubhouse. Poppo also seems to have an obsession for foreign girls, especially Vietnamese girls. Overall, he has a lewd personality.</description>
<picture>66681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="465" picture="56019.jpg">Kondou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28415" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="130">7.35</rating>
<name>Anjou Naruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anjou Naruko is a childhood friend of Jinta and Menma. While she displays a cold attitude towards Jinta, she is secretly concerned for him. She is perhaps the closest to him at present and is enrolled the same school (although Jinta stopped attending school). Chiriko comments that Naruko has not changed over the years: she is still easily persuaded by everyone around her. Naruko seems to be popular in high school and gets along well with girls that Chiriko deems "sluts."
While they have grown apart, Naruko seems cares deeply about her childhood friends. She works at a video game store and has a large collection of manga and video games herself. Because of this collection, she started reconnecting with Jinta and Poppo.</description>
<picture>66590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28416" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="75">5.63</rating>
<name>Yadomi Jinta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yadomi Jinta is the main character of the series. In the past, Jinta was an energetic, young boy and the leader of his group, the Super Peace Busters. When Naruko asked him if he had a crush on Menma, he said, "Why would I be in love with such an ugly—?" He had plans to apologize to her the next day, but she died later that night in a drowning accident.
Unable to forgive himself, Jinta spent the next years of his life in a constant state of gloominess. He became withdrawn and eventually became a hikikomori, or a shut-in. He currently lives with his father. While he is enrolled at the same high school as Naruko, he stopped attending.</description>
<picture>66591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28417" type="main character in" update="2015-01-05">
<rating votes="157">6.37</rating>
<name>Honma Meiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honma Meiko, nicknamed Menma, is a ghost girl who suddenly appears to Jinta several years after her death. Menma asks him to reunite their group of friends so her wish can be granted. She does not seem to remember what is her wish, but she knows she has to reunite her friends in order to remember.
It is hinted that she has feelings for Jinta, and that only Jinta is able to see her.</description>
<picture>66592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28418" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="61">3.13</rating>
<name>Matsuyuki Atsumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsuyuki Atsumu is a childhood friend of Jinta and Menma. In the present, Atsumu holds a condescending attitude towards Jinta. He becomes agitated when Menma is mentioned and is still distraught over her death. He, together with Chiriko, attend the same high school, which Jinta failed the entrance exams to enter. It appears that he is dating Chiriko.</description>
<picture>66589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28419" type="main character in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="58">5.22</rating>
<name>Tsurumi Chiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As a child, Tsurumi Chiriko was a shy girl and a member of the Super Peace Busters. Now, she is enrolled at an elite school with Matsuyuki. She is serious, stoic, and cocky. Upon meeting with Naruko, Chiriko insults both her and her friends. While the other members of the Super Peace Busters have fallen apart, Chiriko and Matsuyuki have remained friends after Menma`s death.</description>
<picture>66588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30633" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="13">6.78</rating>
<name>Yadomi Jinta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30634" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="10">5.17</rating>
<name>Hisakawa Tetsudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30635" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="13">5.05</rating>
<name>Matsuyuki Atsumu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30636" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="9">2.45</rating>
<name>Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aki is Naruko`s friend.</description>
<picture>70676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30637" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="19">4.93</rating>
<name>Yadomi Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yadomi Atsushi is Jintan`s father.</description>
<picture>70385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30638" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="12">3.25</rating>
<name>Haruna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruna is Naruko`s friend.</description>
<picture>70675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30646" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="14">6.09</rating>
<name>Tsurumi Chiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30648" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="62">7.41</rating>
<name>Honma Meiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30652" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="15">6.84</rating>
<name>Anjou Naruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31465" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="5">3.93</rating>
<name>Naruko no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naruko`s mother.</description>
<picture>70379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31466" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="5">4.71</rating>
<name>Honma Manabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honma Manabu is Menma`s father.</description>
<picture>70382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31467" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="10">3.67</rating>
<name>Honma Irene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honma Irene is Menma`s mother.</description>
<picture>70383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31468" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="7">6.33</rating>
<name>Honma Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Honma Satoshi is Menma`s younger brother.</description>
<picture>70384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31664" type="appears in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="6">5.24</rating>
<name>Yadomi Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yadomi Touko is Jintan`s mother.</description>
<picture>70677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32806" type="appears in" update="2011-05-27">
<rating votes="2">2.37</rating>
<name>Yama-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33041" type="appears in" update="2011-06-03">
<rating votes="4">6.42</rating>
<name>Honma Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34049" type="appears in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="5">8.26</rating>
<name>Chou Heiwa Busters</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The group Jinta and his friends created together when they were kids.</description>
<picture>156838.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="128598" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="46">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超平和バスターズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Peace Busters</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Super busters della pace</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Super protectores de la paz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Heiwa Busters</title>
<summary>One day, Jintan (Jinta Yadomi), a teenage shut-in, suddenly finds himself face-to-face with his childhood friend, Menma (Meiko Honma). After struggling with Menma`s request to have her (unknown) wish granted, Jintan meets with his former friends. Soon, she recalls that the dream was to have their friends all together again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791540</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129065" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="53">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの夏に咲く花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blooming Flower of That Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il fiore sbocciato quell`estate</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Las flores que crecen este verano</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Natsu ni Saku Hana</title>
<summary>Even though the group is able to launch their rocket, Menma doesn`t disappear. Jintan and the others are dumbstruck and wonder what might have happened. But finally, Jintan discovers what Menma`s wish really was...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791557</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129066" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="32">9.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fireworks</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fuochi d`artificio</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Fuegos artificales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanabi</title>
<summary>The time has finally come...the day they can grant Menma`s wish. However, Menma discovers that her hand has started to become transparent. Holding on to all their strongest feelings, the Super Peace Busters blast off as true feelings are revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791555</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129067" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="29">8.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなとめんま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyone and Menma</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Tutti e Menma</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Menma y los demás</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna to Menma</title>
<summary>Although they`re still hesitant, Anaru and the others begin to believe in Menma`s existence after she serves them the steamed bread she prepared. Yukiatsu, however, still can`t understand why Jintan is the only one who can see Menma, while Anaru is upset that she can`t compare to her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791553</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129068" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="35">9.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">I wonder</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Wonder</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I wonder</title>
<title xml:lang="es">I wonder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">I Wonder</title>
<summary>When the group finds out that Menma`s father opposed their plan to launch fireworks for her, they`re left in a state of shock. Desperate to grant her wish, they pay a visit to her mother to ask about the fireworks, but she refuses, showing anger and sadness towards them about how they were able to grow up while Menma died years ago.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791551</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129069" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほんとのお願い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Real Plea</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il vero desideriao</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El verdadero deseo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honto no Onegai</title>
<summary>Looking through Menma`s old diary that they got from her mother, Jintan and the others find Menma`s wish. And as they resolve to grant it, the time that had seemed to freeze for all five of them begins moving forward again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791549</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129070" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="32">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わすれてわすれないで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forget It, Don`t Forget</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Dimenticami, ma non dimenticarmi</title>
<title xml:lang="es">No me olvides</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wasurete Wasurenaide</title>
<summary>Jintan decides to try going to school one more time, for Menma`s sake. When he arrives, he discovers that Anaru is having some serious issues of her own. Unable to stand by while Anaru suffers, Jintan stands up for her, and both leave class right away.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791548</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129071" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="34">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トンネル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tunnel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Tunnel</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Túnel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tunnel</title>
<summary>The Menma that Yukiatsu "saw" was just him in women`s clothing, a revelation that leaves the rest of the group stunned. Yukiatsu lies motionless on the forest floor after taking a spill, where Jintan tries to talk to him about his situation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791546</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129072" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="34">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白いリボンのワンピース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">White Ribbon Dress</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il vestito bianco con un fiocco</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El vestido blanco de una pieza y la cinta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiroi Ribbon no One-Piece</title>
<summary>Yukiatsu tells Jintan and the others that he has just seen Menma. This puzzles Jintan, since Menma was standing next to him the entire time. Jintan and company head out together to search for "Menma" and get to the bottom of this little mystery.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791544</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129073" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="37">8.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めんまを探そうの会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Search for Menma Association</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il circolo "cerchiamo Menma"</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Buscando a Menma, recuerdo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Menma o Sagasou no Kai</title>
<summary>Thinking that Menma`s wish may be for him to begin going to school again, Jintan decides to give it a shot. This also happens to fulfill a promise he made to Anaru...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791542</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129074" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="38">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆうしゃめんま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Menma the Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La favolosa Menma</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Menma la valiente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha Menma</title>
<summary>After running into Poppo (Tetsudo Hisakawa) for the first time in years, Jintan explains how Menma appeared before him and how she has some kind of wish she wants granted. Poppo believes every word he says, and suggests that Jintan has to catch a rare monster from a Nokémon video game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791541</identifier>
<identifier>anohana-the-flower-we-saw-that-day</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="129554" update="2011-04-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="129603" update="2011-04-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176700" update="2016-06-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Picture Drama</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
