<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8778" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2013-10-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gekijouban Meguca</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">madoka movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 魔法少女まどか☆マギカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Puella Magi Madoka Magica the Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Madoka Magica The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">劇場版 魔法少女小圓</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">剧场版 魔法少女小圆</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8069" type="Alternative Setting">Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica</anime>
<anime id="11793" type="Other">Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica: Concept Movie</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="202" approval="2" total="17">Shinseiki Evangelion Gekijouban: Air / Magokoro o, Kimi ni</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="106569">3rd Madoka movie, Story of Rebellion,
manages to outdo the TV series.

However you MUST finish watching the TV series first before watching the 3rd movie, otherwise the movie`s ploy won`t work for you.

If you don`t finish the TV series first and try watching the 3rd movie,
your reaction will be like "huh? so what?"
when others that finished the TV series
will be like "omg..... how could this happen...."</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="545610">In the first 2 movies there is only about 3 minutes of ORIGINAL animation (not just a giant game of spot the difference) and only one line of "important" information, so if you have seen the series you are fine to skip.

Now for Rebellion, First third was so cute that I gagged (a high complement). Second third was great with plot developing on par with the series. And then the last third approaches End of Evangelion levels of convoluted story telling. But the last 5 minutes is the reason I regret watching Rebellion. The ending (which I think is total BS) definitely does not make a "complete" story.

So watcher beware, you could be like all the other Recs and love it, or (like me) you will pretend it does not exist until there is a 4th movie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="600311">amazing artwork! great story and development!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="717410">If you haven`t seen this, I would probably stop what I`m doing and watch at least the first movie. Even if this isn`t necessarily your genre, the overall character development, story line, concept, and animation will win you over. 

Absolutely superb plot. One of the best I`ve seen.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="301367">SHAFT at their best (in my opinion).
The plot will blow your mind, especially the finale (3rd movie).
The visuals are (probably) the best I have seen so far in anime.
The characters are well developed and likable (well most of them).
Recommended for both new audience (all 3 movies) and TV version`s fans (especially the 3rd movie, being the TV version`s sequel).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="596734">After watching the regular series, I thought it wasn`t possible to continue its plot and keep the same level of brilliance. However, after watching Rebellion, I happily realized that I was completely wrong.

It`s very difficult to continue a masterpiece and make from it an even more epic masterpiece. However, they achieved this goal by making this movie as a kind of continuation of the regular series, and this is very meritorious.

The first time I watched the series, I thought that Madoka Magica was probably the best thing I had seen in my whole life. Now, after watching Rebellion, I can surely delete that "probably" word from the previous sentence.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="402218">Without any doubt will be a marker on the anime industry. Perfect closing for the plot started on the TV series, as expected another deconstruction was made here.

Good plot, unexpected turn of events and an ending yet to be seen by me in other series.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.madoka-magica.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="4147" type="Character Design">Kishida Takahiro</name>
<name id="704" type="Music">Kajiura Yuki</name>
<name id="59" type="Chief Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="59" type="Film Composition">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="9789" type="Film Composition">Tou Fuyashi</name>
<name id="3528" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamura Hiroki</name>
<name id="14125" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takahashi Mika</name>
<name id="1512" type="Direction">Miyamoto Yukihiro</name>
<name id="39802" type="Original Work">Magica Quartet</name>
<name id="7866" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="7866" type="Character Design">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="7866" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="4147" type="Character Design">Kishida Takahiro</name>
<name id="1512" type="Direction">Miyamoto Yukihiro</name>
</creators>
<description>Beginnings — In the city of Mitakihara, http://anidb.net/ch25644 [Kaname Madoka], along with her friend, http://anidb.net/ch25643 [Miki Sayaka], encounter a creature named http://anidb.net/ch25645 [Kyuubee] and are saved from witches by magical girl http://anidb.net/ch25163 [Tomoe Mami]. Kyuubee offers Madoka and Sayaka the chance to have any one wish granted in exchange for becoming a magical girl and fighting witches, whilst http://anidb.net/ch25024 [Akemi Homura], another magical girl and recent transfer student, is strongly against Madoka becoming one. Before Madoka can make a decision, however, Mami is killed by a witch, leaving Madoka too afraid to become a magical girl. Sayaka, however, decides to become a magical girl herself in order to heal the hand of her childhood friend, http://anidb.net/ch27647 [Kamijou Kyousuke]. As Sayaka soon comes into conflict with another magical girl named http://anidb.net/ch27945 [Sakura Kyouko], they, along with Madoka, learn the shocking truth that their Soul Gems, the source of their magical powers, literally contain their souls.
Eternal — Madoka learns from Kyuubee, whose real identity is Incubator, that his species makes contracts to make girls into magical girls that inevitably become witches in order to use the energy that spawns from their despair to counter entropy in the universe. Kyouko, hoping for a chance that Sayaka can be made human again, takes Madoka with her to try and reach her humanity. This ultimately fails, with Kyouko choosing to sacrifice herself to destroy Sayaka with her. Meanwhile, it is revealed that Homura comes from another timeline, having relived the same month several times in the hope of saving Madoka from a grim fate at the hands of the ultimate witch, Walpurgisnacht. Homura attempts to face Walpurgisnacht, but is ultimately defeated and draws close to despair, feeling her efforts have become pointless. Just then, Madoka appears and uses the built up energy from several timelines to become a powerful magical girl capable of eliminating witches before they are born.
Rebellion — Madoka used to be a normal girl living happily. This all ended when she sacrificed herself in order to save other magical girls from the utterly cruel fate that awaited them. Unable to let her memories of Madoka die, Homura continues to fight alone in the world that Madoka left behind for humanity in order to see her smile once more.
Source: ANN
Note: The first two films are a compilation of the http://anidb.net/a8069 [television series] and the third film is an all-new story. http://anidb.net/cr2442 [Urobuchi Gen] said that the third film`s story coincidentally matches the lyrics to http://anidb.net/cr3034 [Kalafina]`s television ending theme song http://anidb.net/s39375 [Magia] if one examines them carefully.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2386">8.55</permanent>
<temporary count="2397">7.99</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224384.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14363</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>14850</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>14364</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23831</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>11981</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>11979</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>11977</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madoka-magica.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Puella_Magi_Madoka_Magica_(film_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版_魔法少女まどか☆マギカ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3216</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>342981</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>342979</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>346263</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15473</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>16407</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>madoka_magica</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15783</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15830</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>16103</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1179" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-21">
<name>indecisive</name>
<description>This character has trouble taking their own decisions, and may rely on others to do that instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1816" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-09">
<name>uniform -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>The "uniform" tag is to be split and removed. Please help by tagging the character with the appropriate kind of uniform (e.g. school uniform, maid dress, etc) and removing this tag from them, and by not adding this tag to any further characters. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2467" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-22">
<name>sword</name>
<description>A sword is a long, edged piece of metal, used as a cutting, thrusting, and clubbing weapon in many civilizations throughout the world. Before firearms became commonplace, and fast enough to render other weapons pointless in the battlefield, they were the main kind of weapon for war and duels alike. A sword fundamentally consists of a blade and a hilt, typically with one or two edges for striking and cutting, and a point for thrusting. That aside, however, they may come in all sorts of designs: the medieval European swords used to be big, heavy weapons that did not actually cut but instead broke the enemy`s bones under their armor; conversely, the Chinese jian sword (called "ken" in Japanese) attempted to exploit the armor`s joints and perforate the enemy`s flesh in those places, but was useless against the armor itself, and did not take the strikes, preferring to redirect them, to this day being considered a highly "circular" weapon and associated to taijiquan; on the other hand, the Japanese katana was a balanced all-purposes weapon that could be used even in an axe-like way, but which a master swordsman could use in many other, more elaborate manners.</description>
<picurl>127113.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3834" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>impending death -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>At least one character in this show is going to or very likely to die soon because of a http://anidb.net/t2574 [terminal illness], of a http://anidb.net/t2874 [disaster] such a http://anidb.net/t2925 [war], an http://anidb.net/t5466 [epidemic] (including the zombie apocalypse), or of other life-threatening reasons. Please assign the appropriate disaster tags to the anime, the terminal illness tag to the relevant characters, and any other relevant or necessary replacement tags to the corresponding entities, and then remove this tag from the anime in question. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>protection complex</name>
<description>A character has a protection complex if the character is overly protective of other characters, beyond what would be considered a "normal" or "expected" duty of care.
The magnitude of overprotection can vary. It can be as low as constantly nagging someone to "stay safe". It can be as extreme as the protector making it their mission in life to protect the other character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5335" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>dreams and reality</name>
<description>This genre of anime is typically set in both the world as we know it (reality) and a world of dreams, mythology or imagination.
Sometimes this dreamworld is actually real, sometimes it is not. Other times what we think is the real world is the dreamworld, and vice versa. They are not always easy to distinguish from each other, neither by the characters nor the viewer.
Whatever is real, and whatever is reality, both worlds are integral in shaping both the plot of this anime and the development of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5665" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-12-04">
<name>trapped</name>
<description>The anime takes place inside a building or some kind of landform from which the characters can`t get out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="24746" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="200">4.68</rating>
<name>Kaname Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25024" type="main character in" update="2011-07-30">
<rating votes="239">8.87</rating>
<name>Akemi Homura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akemi Homura is a smart, graceful, athletically-talented girl. Cool if not chilly, her personality can even be seen in her posture.
She seems to be a magical girl, but there are a lot of mysteries surrounding the way she acts. Her fighting style is also unidentified.</description>
<picture>60588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25163" type="main character in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="101">5.59</rating>
<name>Tomoe Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoe Mami is a Puella Magi contracted to http://anidb.net/ch25645 [Kyuubee] and a third year student at Madoka`s school, living alone in a penthouse after her parents`s deaths. She has the ability to produce a near-infinite amount of flintlock rifles, can use ribbons to suspend her enemies, and is also able to perform healing magic. Due to being involved and seriously injured in a car accident (which also claimed the lives of her parents) at the time Kyuubey approached her, she was forced to use her wish to save herself. Unlike other Puella Magi, who mostly focus on obtaining valuable Grief Seeds, Mami is particularly focused on saving those around her. Though she often has a cheery disposition, she is also often lonely and scared due to the nature of her work and is pleased when Madoka offers to become her partner.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>60589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25315" type="main character in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="115">4.87</rating>
<name>Miki Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miki Sayaka is Madoka`s classmate who, after helping Madoka rescue Kyubey, ends up getting an offer to become a Puella Magi herself. She cares deeply for her friends, and wants to help an ill boy named Kyousuke Kamijou, whom she has a crush on. She becomes a Puella Magi after using her wish to cure Kyousuke`s hand, which was damaged in an accident which robbed him of his ability to play the violin. Sayaka`s weapon of choice is a sword and, like Mami, she can produce multiple swords at a time. She also has regenerative powers stronger than anyone else due to the nature of her wish. Sayaka hates people that only think of themselves at the cost of hurting others and is easily provoked into a fight.</description>
<picture>60591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25641" type="main character in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="384">8.75</rating>
<name>Akemi Homura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akemi Homura is a Puella Magi who first appears in Madoka`s dream, and then transfers into her school the day after the dream. A beautiful yet mysterious individual who performs exceptionally well in school, be it academically or athletically, making her popular at school despite her awkward personality. It is unknown whom she is contracted to, with Kyuubey identifying her as an irregular. Homura has extensive knowledge concerning different Puella Magi and is well aware of the dark sides of becoming one, believing those with kind hearts are unfit to become one. As such, she tries to keep other girls from making contracts, particularly Madoka, whom she seems to know well before their meeting. Though she is seen as something of a rival, she often strives to protect Madoka and the others from life-threatening danger. Homura has a small discus-like object strapped to her left forearm and uses it like a shield, and is able to produce various military weapons such as grenades and pistols. It is later revealed that she is from another timeline, as she has the ability to temporarily stop time, allowing her to travel quickly and get an advantage on her opponents.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>60587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25642" type="main character in" update="2010-12-10">
<rating votes="122">6.87</rating>
<name>Tomoe Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25643" type="main character in" update="2012-04-01">
<rating votes="104">5.11</rating>
<name>Miki Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Magical Girl form of Miki Sayaka.</description>
<picture>60592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25644" type="main character in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="154">4.53</rating>
<name>Kaname Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 14-year-old girl whose life changes when she encounters the Puella Magi Homura and the familiar Kyubey, who offers to transform her into a Puella Magi herself. She sees herself as a person without special qualities or talents, and after seeing Mami fighting against witches, wants to help people as a Puella Magi the same way Mami does. Madoka becomes uncertain about becoming a Puella Magi after Mami`s death in battle, though she still accompanies her friend, Sayaka, on witch hunts. She is averse to fighting and wishes that everyone would get along. She is implied to have large amount of magical potential within her, and Kyubey is particularly interested in forming a contract with her; however, she has yet to take him up on the offer.</description>
<picture>60593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25645" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="170">6.36</rating>
<name>Kyuubee</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyuubee is a familiar who can grant any wish to a certain girl, on the condition that she become a Puella Magi and fight against witches.
When someone makes a contract with him, he extracts their soul and places it inside a Soul Gem, replacing their body with a shell that`s more resilient to fighting witches. He has so far made contracts with Mami, Kyouko and Sayaka, and shows particular interest in making Madoka a magical girl. It is yet to be revealed if there are other familiars besides him. As a magical creature, he can only be seen or heard by Puella Magis and those with magical potential. He is shown to consume used Grief Seeds, though for what reason is unknown. His true motives are unknown, and he constantly tries to find chances to persuade girls with magical potential to form a contract with him despite knowing the dangers that a Puella Magi faces. He tends to have little understanding of human values and doesn`t believe what he`s doing is cruel. If he is killed, another Kyuubee takes his place and consumes the previous one. Homura recognizes his true identity as Incubator.</description>
<picture>60594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26540" type="appears in" update="2011-01-07">
<rating votes="3">2.38</rating>
<name>Nakazawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26541" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="29">5.98</rating>
<name>Kaname Junko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname Junko is Madoka`s mother, an executive who wears a lot of make up and sometimes comes home drunk, making it hard to wake her up in the morning. Other than this, she is a caring and gentle person and often gives Madoka advice whenever she is troubled.</description>
<picture>62416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26542" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="5">3.46</rating>
<name>Kaname Tomohisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname Tomohisa is Madoka`s father, who seems to be the one in charge of the house.</description>
<picture>62419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2044" picture="21387.jpg">Iwanaga Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26543" type="appears in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="8">5.42</rating>
<name>Saotome Kazuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saotome Kazuko is Madoka`s teacher, who constantly has trouble keeping a boyfriend.</description>
<picture>62420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26544" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-05">
<rating votes="31">2.65</rating>
<name>Shizuki Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizuki Hitomi is http://anidb.net/ch25644 [Madoka] and http://anidb.net/ch25315 [Sayaka]`s classmate and friend, quite popular with the boys. She seems to believe Sayaka and Madoka are in a relationship and often feels she is being left out. In episode seven, she tells Sayaka that she loves http://anidb.net/ch27647 [Kyousuke] and that she plans to confess to him if Sayaka does not.</description>
<picture>244313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26545" type="appears in" update="2020-02-05">
<rating votes="9">4.27</rating>
<name>Kaname Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaname Tatsuya is http://anidb.net/ch25644 [Madoka]`s younger brother.</description>
<picture>244314.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27647" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-05">
<rating votes="18">2.20</rating>
<name>Kamijou Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamijou Kyousuke is a disabled boy whom http://anidb.net/ch25315 [Sayaka] constantly visits in hospital. He used to be a violin player, but an accident crippled him and destroyed the feeling in his fingers, making him unable to play an instrument again, which causes him a lot of grief and despair. Sayaka uses her wish to cure his hand, allowing him to play the violin once more.</description>
<picture>244312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5641" picture="228630.jpg">Yoshida Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27945" type="main character in" update="2020-02-23">
<rating votes="133">7.40</rating>
<name>Sakura Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28165" type="main character in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="114">7.54</rating>
<name>Sakura Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura Kyouko is a rival Puella Magi who comes to the city after Mami is killed by a witch. A girl with red-colored long hair and an equally fiery personality to match. Amusingly, she is always seen eating something, even while she is battling Sayaka. When Kyouko learns Sayaka had become a Puella Magi just before she arrived, she becomes Sayaka`s enemy for allegedly stealing her territory, although she later tries to help her after learning the truth about Soul Gems. She comes from a poor church family and used her wish so that people would listen to her father`s preachings. However, when her father learned of this, he went mad and killed his entire family. As such, Kyouko decided only to use her magic for herself, since using it for others will only cause despair. Having grown up in a poor family, she often has to steal food and hates wasting it, a logic she also applies to Grief Seeds, as she only goes after fully grown witches. Kyouko wields a spear which can extend itself, split into multiple sections, and produce a ball at the end of the chain, which can constrict and hit others at the same time.</description>
<picture>64987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28261" type="appears in" update="2011-02-04">
<rating votes="4">2.44</rating>
<name>Kyousuke no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1630" picture="1887.gif">Tasaka Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29575" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="9">4.00</rating>
<name>Oktavia von Seckendorff</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oktavia von Seckendorff is the witch form of Miki Sayaka. She briefly appears at the end of Episode 8 and battles with Sakura Kyouko in Episode 9. Her Labyrinth is filled with calls for attention -- probably to Kamijou Kyousuke. Initially, the outer areas of her Labyrinth are filled with train tracks, perhaps a reflection of the train station where she became a witch. Later on, the entrance area becomes a long corridor filled with concert posters. The center of the Labyrinth appears to be a distorted concert hall, where the seats fill the domed ceiling. Her weapons appear to be manifested wheels, and the concert hall is populated with a spectral string orchestra.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68010.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30153" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="3">3.82</rating>
<name>Gertrud</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gertrud is a witch born from negative emotions, who loves roses more than anything else--her barrier is full of them. She uses humans` life energy to feed her roses and hates humans entering her barrier. Her minions are Anthony and Adelbert. She and her barrier are presented in a surreal manner with bizarre cut-and-paste-style photo collages. She also seems to like mustaches as both of her minions have some. The special page has confirmed that the mustaches are set by the witch herself. Her "body" has parts from a butterfly, and butterflies are seen in her barrier at many points.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68011.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30154" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="3">3.82</rating>
<name>Anthony</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anthony is Gertrud`s minion. His duty is landscaping. His mustache is set by the witch.</description>
<picture>68012.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30155" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="3">3.82</rating>
<name>Adelbert</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Adelbert is the rose garden witch`s minion. His duty is to act as lookout. Upon seeing a human, he will sound a warning bell and headbutt him mercilessly. They have 2.5 (20/8) vision. The smaller type can change into rose vines to hinder intruders.</description>
<picture>68013.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30156" type="appears in" update="2014-05-21">
<rating votes="11">6.75</rating>
<name>Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The dessert witch, with a tenacious nature. She desires everything. She will never give up. Though she is capable of creating infinite amounts of any dessert she desires, she is unable to make the cheese that she loves most. One could easily catch her off-guard with a piece of cheese.
The head of her first form is shaped like piece of candy in wrap. In her fight against Mami, after it looks like she is defeated, she suddenly transforms into her second form, a huge caterpiller, and kills Mami.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68014.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30157" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="3">3.82</rating>
<name>Pyotr</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The dessert witch`s minion. His duty is to search for cheese. However, one shouldn`t expect much from him.</description>
<picture>68015.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30158" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="3">3.82</rating>
<name>H.N. Elly (Kirsten)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The box witch with a covetous nature. She is a staunchly reclusive witch. Anything she covets she locks away within glass. The thoughts of her prisoners are laid bare, but one can strike her without thought without problems.</description>
<picture>68016.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30159" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="3">3.82</rating>
<name>Daniyyel + Jennifer</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The box witch`s minions with the duty of transportation. Anything they touch becomes easy to carry.</description>
<picture>68017.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30162" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="3">4.98</rating>
<name>Elsa Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elsa Maria is a witch who battles Sayaka at the end of Episode 7. Her barrier is full of dark shadows with a white background. Her symbolism includes Christian crosses, and the terrain forms a large arm holding either a torch or a monstrance. Elsa Maria appears to be praying before this object when Sayaka engages her. She fights with fanged snake-like minions and tree branches that extend from her body.
The shadow witch with a self-righteous nature. She continually prays for all of creation. She drags all life equally into her shadow without breaking her posture. One hoping to defeat her must know the blackest anguish.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68020.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="30176" type="appears in" update="2011-03-17">
<rating votes="9">2.73</rating>
<name>Kriemhild Gretchen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kriemhild Gretchen is the witch form of Kaname Madoka. She appears in the fourth timeline of Episode 10 as a mountain-sized creature. Her name was not shown during initial broadcast, but was added in a Nicovideo broadcast version one week later.
Nothing is known about the specifics of her powers or personality, but her formation in the second timeline involves thunderclouds coalescing into a giant humanoid (the name is not shown then, however, and thus it is not known whether that witch is also called Kriemhild Gretchen). According to Kyuubey, her strength in the fourth timeline is of such a magnitude that she could obliterate the planet within ten days.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>68045.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31463" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-27">
<rating votes="75">6.18</rating>
<name>Kaname Madoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>141993.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59397" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-21">
<rating votes="5">8.07</rating>
<name>Momoe Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momoe Nagisa is a magical girl introduced in the movie The Rebellion Story.
During the movie, Nagisa disguises herself as her witch form Charlotte, which the other characters call Bebe.</description>
<picture>142318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67569" type="appears in" update="2014-05-21">
<rating votes="1">9.97</rating>
<name>Homulilly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Homulilly is the witch form of Akemi Homura. She is the Nutcracker Witch. Its nature is self-sufficiency. Its gallant form, which once split many nuts, is now useless. Without any other purpose, this witch`s last wish is her own execution. However, a mere decapitation will not clear away the witch`s sins. This foolish witch will forever remain in this realm, repeating the procession to her execution.
Second Form (on the right)
Her teeth are exposed, her skull has melted, and her eyeballs have fallen out. A promise is the only thing that pitifully planted in that head which can no longer crack any nuts, but within the husk of the awakened witch is the distinct form of a magical girl. Her servants shamefully refer to that thing as a good-for-nothing.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>155823.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67570" type="appears in" update="2014-12-14">
<rating votes="40">8.57</rating>
<name>Akemi Homura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>At the end of Rebellion arc, Homura transforms into a new form, growing a pair of black wings. She is no longer a magical girl or a witch. Instead, she calls herself a demon.</description>
<picture>155824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67571" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-21">
<name>Bebe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious creature who suddenly appeared in Mami`s home. Was christened Bebe but it is actually the Dessert Witch who arrived from the Law of Cycles. She was expressionless and silent when she was first encountered, but took on its current appearance out of the blue. A bit loud. Mami made its clothes by hand. Mami resembles someone who appeared in the final nightmare the witch saw.
Source: Puella Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>155830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67574" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-21">
<rating votes="4">8.39</rating>
<name>Momoe Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magical form of Momoe Nagisa.</description>
<picture>155829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70742" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<rating votes="2">2.28</rating>
<name>Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Charlotte`s second forme.</description>
<picture>162919.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70743" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<name>Sebastian</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sebastian is the shadow witch`s minion. His duty is to blindly believe. He is the aggregate of the lives who have found salvation thanks to the shadow witch. He continually seeks out companions.</description>
<picture>162920.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70744" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<name>Polina</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The dessert witch`s minion. Her duty is to nurse the cheese. However, one shouldn`t expect much from her.</description>
<picture>162921.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70745" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<name>Walpurgis Night`s Minions</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>They are the stage-constructing witch`s minions. Their duty is to be clowns. Countless souls drawn to her vast magical power. Nobody knows whether Walpurgis Night was initially a single person, or if it was a phantom born from the gathering of many spirits.</description>
<picture>162922.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70746" type="appears in" update="2014-10-19">
<name>Walpurgis Night</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Walpurgis Night is the stage-constructing witch. Her nature is helplessness. She symbolizes the fool who continuously spins in circles. The witch`s mysteries have been handed down through the course of history; her appellation is "Walpurgis Night." She will continue to rotate aimlessly throughout the world until she completely changes the whole of this age into a drama. When the doll`s usual upside-down position reaches the top part of the witch, she completely roils the civilization on the ground in a flash through her gale-like flight.</description>
<picture>162923.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="137992" update="2012-09-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>130</length>
<airdate>2012-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="33">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">始まりの物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1: Beginnings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140039" update="2012-10-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2012-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="30">8.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2: Eternal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140045" update="2014-04-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>120</length>
<airdate>2013-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="41">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">叛逆の物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3: Rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hangyaku no Monogatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152087" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Movie CM4 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152088" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Movie CM4 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152089" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Movie CM3 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152090" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Movie CM2 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152091" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Movie CM1 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152092" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Movie CM1 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152093" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Movie PV2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152094" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">2nd Movie PV1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152095" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Movie CM4 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152096" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Movie CM4 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152097" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Movie CM3 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152098" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Movie CM3 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152099" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Movie CM2 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152100" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Movie CM2 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152101" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Movie CM1 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152102" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Movie CM1 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152103" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1st Movie PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152104" update="2014-04-14">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152105" update="2013-07-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158845" update="2014-04-03">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158846" update="2014-04-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158847" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Magica Quartet x Nisioisin 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158848" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Magica Quartet x Nisioisin 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158849" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Magica Quartet x Nisioisin 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158850" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Magica Quartet x Nisioisin 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158851" update="2014-04-03">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159938" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T29</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie CM5 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159939" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T28</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie CM4 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159940" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T27</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie CM3 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159941" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T26</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie CM3 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159942" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T25</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie CM2 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159943" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T24</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie CM2 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159944" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie CM1 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159945" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie CM1 (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159946" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie PV4 (45s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159947" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie PV3 (40s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159948" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie PV2 (100s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159949" update="2014-05-16">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Movie PV1 (40s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159950" recap="true" update="2014-09-21">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2014-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場版公開記念 2時間でわかる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Parts 1 and 2 Summary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijouban Koukai Kinen 2-jikan de Wakaru!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
