<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8827" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-03-09</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hanasaku Iroha: Home Sweet Home</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">劇場版 花咲くいろは HOME SWEET HOME</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">꽃이 피는 첫걸음: Home Sweet Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gekijouban Hanasaku Iroha: Home Sweet Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gekijouban Hana-Saku Iroha: Home Sweet Home</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">剧场版 花开伊吕波: Home Sweet Home</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">花咲くいろは HOME SWEET HOME</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hanasaku Iroha the Movie: Home Sweet Home</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7874" type="Parent Story">Hanasaku Iroha</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="389161">Solid continuation of Hanasaku Iroha series. Worth watching.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.hanasakuiroha.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2243" type="Character Design">Sekiguchi Kanami</name>
<name id="141" type="Direction">Andou Masahiro</name>
<name id="2243" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sekiguchi Kanami</name>
<name id="2019" type="Music">Hamaguchi Shirou</name>
<name id="1385" type="Original Work">P.A. Works</name>
<name id="1385" type="Animation Work">P.A. Works</name>
</creators>
<description>* Сontinuation of the original http://anidb.net/a7874 [Hana-Saku Iroha] project produced as the http://anidb.net/cr1385 [P.A. Works] studio`s tenth anniversary work.
Although initially perplexed at the sudden turn of events which led her to live in the hot spring inn Kissuisou, now Ohana is perfectly accustomed to the new lifestyle; she has started to even notice a positive change in herself lately. One day from a neighboring inn Fukuya comes Wakura Yuina on a mission to train herself as an okami, where Ohana is told by her grandmother to assist this naive young girl.
Upon tidying up the storeroom Ohana discovers a box amid piles of items scattered around, which is packed with business logs Denroku has made over the years. She picks up a log and finds in it her mother`s name, together with the fact that her mother once said she wanted to shine, and there she realizes the minds of both mother and daughter work the same.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1044">7.56</permanent>
<temporary count="1047">7.61</temporary>
<review count="1">7.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>237141.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14337</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14175</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.hanasakuiroha.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3460</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344211</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15833</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=toOo9iRyV9k</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=oboVwo5mo2E</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=M6ovM4QGJOI</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=1JZxVAVN190</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01CH59312</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2378" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>hard-working</name>
<description>Describes someone, who is constantly, regularly, or habitually active or occupied.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4017" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-13">
<name>old woman acting young</name>
<description>This series portrays an old woman that tends to act inappropriately for her age. She either wears a schoolgirl uniform, tries to seduce young guys, or attempts to act overly energetic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="22132" type="main character in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="68">5.70</rating>
<name>Wakura Yuina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuina is a 16-year-old teenager who is daughter of the Fukuya Inn owners that are rivals with Kissuisou. She, together with Ohana, Minko and Nako are in the same class at high school.</description>
<picture>60581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22133" type="main character in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="83">7.54</rating>
<name>Oshimizu Nako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nako is a 17-year old cleaning maid and waitress working part-time at Kissuisou. She has a shy and timid personality, with a tendency to avoid unwanted social interaction. She is, however, confident about her swimming ability, having been swimming since she was three, she was nick named the "kappa girl". She, together with Ohana, Minko and Yuina are in the same class at high school.</description>
<picture>60580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22134" type="main character in" update="2011-05-01">
<rating votes="142">8.31</rating>
<name>Matsumae Ohana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Main character of the story. She was born in Tokyo, but is forced to leave the city to work at a hot springs hotel. There she tries to find out and fulfill her dreams in life.</description>
<picture>60578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22135" type="main character in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="96">4.65</rating>
<name>Tsurugi Minko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsurugi Minko is a 17-year-old apprentice chef and resident at Kissuisou. She has a very cold demeanor, often telling Ohana to `die` following their first encounter, though when this is considered too harsh by Ohana, she settles for calling her a balut instead. Though she is hard working, she becomes passive when being scolded for her mistakes and is usually victim to Ohana`s mishaps. She displays great jealousy when Ohana is praised by other staff. She, together with Ohana, Nako and Yuina are in the same class at high school.</description>
<picture>60579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1679" picture="38587.jpg">Omigawa Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25555" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-17">
<rating votes="26">5.69</rating>
<name>Sukegawa Denroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25556" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<rating votes="31">7.10</rating>
<name>Shijima Sui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ohana`s grandmother that runs Kissuisou.</description>
<picture>60937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19174" picture="50012.jpg">Kubota Tamie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25557" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-01">
<rating votes="24">2.65</rating>
<name>Shijima Enishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satsuki Matsumae`s brother, Ohana`s uncle.</description>
<picture>60938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25558" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<rating votes="27">6.50</rating>
<name>Miyagishi Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A chef working at the Kissuisou.</description>
<picture>60584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25559" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-06">
<rating votes="22">7.36</rating>
<name>Togashi Renji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Head chef at Kissuisou.</description>
<picture>60939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2893" picture="240353.jpg">Yamaguchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25560" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-12-17">
<rating votes="31">3.10</rating>
<name>Kawajiri Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25561" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-01">
<rating votes="43">6.19</rating>
<name>Matsumae Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ohana`s mother who is a writer.</description>
<picture>60936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25562" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-01">
<rating votes="21">3.06</rating>
<name>Jiroumaru Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tarou Jiroumaru is a writer.</description>
<picture>60941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25563" type="appears in" update="2011-05-01">
<rating votes="29">3.61</rating>
<name>Tanemura Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ohana`s best friend, who is in love with her.</description>
<picture>60583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25564" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-03">
<rating votes="55">5.37</rating>
<name>Wajima Tomoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Senior serving attendant at Kissuisou who likes to gossip. Tends to be jealous of any younger girl/woman who has a boyfriend.</description>
<picture>60582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35078" type="appears in" update="2011-07-31">
<rating votes="4">4.11</rating>
<name>Oshimizu Tomoya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35080" type="appears in" update="2011-07-31">
<rating votes="4">2.91</rating>
<name>Oshimizu Mana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23484" picture="151668.jpg">Keichou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60770" type="appears in" update="2013-10-25">
<rating votes="2">6.58</rating>
<name>Matsumae Ohana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144800.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60771" type="main character in" update="2013-10-25">
<rating votes="5">7.22</rating>
<name>Matsumae Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60772" type="appears in" update="2013-10-25">
<rating votes="4">4.11</rating>
<name>Shijima Enishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60773" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-25">
<rating votes="2">6.21</rating>
<name>Shijima Sui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19174" picture="50012.jpg">Kubota Tamie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60774" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-25">
<rating votes="2">6.77</rating>
<name>Matsumae Ayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10750" picture="186166.jpg">Takeuchi Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="144616" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>2013-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147740" update="2013-02-27">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">本予告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hon Yokoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147741" update="2013-02-27">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-02-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">予告TVCM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TVCM</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokoku TVCM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147742" update="2013-02-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特 報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flash News</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toku Hou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149978" update="2013-04-23">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">予告TVCM 第2弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TVCM 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokoku TVCM Dai 2 Dan</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
