<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9134" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2013-06-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">My Little Sister Can`t Be This Cute 2</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Моята сестричка не може да е толкова сладка</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">我的妹妹哪有这么可爱 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">oreimo2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Oreimo.</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">俺の妹がこんなに可愛いわけがない.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Oreimo 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Ore no Imouto ga Konnani Kawaii Wake ga Nai. (saison 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">내 여동생이 이렇게 귀여울 리가 없어.</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">Mijn Zusje kan Onmogelijk zo Schattig zijn.</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">我的妹妹哪有這麼可愛</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我的妹妹哪有这么可爱.</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7525" type="Prequel">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9546" approval="4" total="9">Saikin, Imouto no Yousu ga Chotto Okashiinda ga.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="725935">for fans that don`t get disappointed too easy.
Season 1 is a must watch.
Season 2, is annoying at best.  If I were her brother, I`d have a dead sister; the amount of abuse is appalling, I`m still wondering why everyone is putting up with her shit and not telling her to eff off.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="80989">Very good show. Must see.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.oreimo-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="12860" type="Character Design">Oda Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="17862" type="Original Work">Fushimi Tsukasa</name>
<name id="2155" type="Direction">Kanbe Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="8138" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawakami Tetsuya</name>
<name id="32443" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Keisuke</name>
<name id="9259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishida Kana</name>
<name id="530" type="Music">Kousaki Satoru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series of the same name by http://anidb.net/cr17862 [Fushimi Tsukasa], illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr17314 [Kanzaki Hiro].
http://anidb.net/ch17524 [Kousaka Kyousuke], a normal seventeen-year-old high school student, had not gotten along with his fourteen-year-old sister, http://anidb.net/ch17525 [Kirino], in years. For longer than he could remember, Kirino had ignored him entirely and even abused him. It seemed their relationship would continue that way forever.
However, one day he found out that Kirino was secretly addicted to anime, manga and visual novels, including adult games, and had a gigantic collection of them all. Having discovered her secret, he was forced into a long chain of events that included helping hide it all, but would lead him to help her learn to deal with her hobby in a better way, including eventually finding real-life friends with similar tastes, and with whom he, too, would get acquainted. Several months passed.
The time spent so far may be fairly long time for their ages, but still little has changed. Kirino is still less than nice to her brother, her inability to deal with her hobby properly has not quite subsided, and she is still very passionate about her favourite anime, Hoshikuzu Witch Meruru (Stardust Witch Meruru), and her adult games. While now Kyousuke has means of reaching some of her friends, a few of whom are also his friends, her behaviour still forces him into dealing with a lot of unexpected trouble. Meanwhile, it could be said that, among her friends, there are one or two who might be interested in being more than just friends with him... Or could it?
— written by Hinoe
Note: All three final episodes (14-16) were screened on August 9, 2013 on a high-definition screen with 1,700 seats at Otakon Fest.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3414">5.59</permanent>
<temporary count="3437">6.99</temporary>
<review count="1">7.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221834.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14208</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19845</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>13659</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18857</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>23363</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5143</identifier>
<identifier>zhqakc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.oreimo-anime.com/stream/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.oreimo-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ore_no_Imōto_ga_Konna_ni_Kawaii_Wake_ga_Nai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>俺の妹がこんなに可愛いわけがない_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2916</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>345279</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15828</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5299</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=CshdT1uZ_Yc</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=em-V_Ti3nTI</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2739" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>brother-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two siblings of opposite sex.</description>
<picurl>210881.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2927" parentid="2676" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Akihabara</name>
<description>Akihabara is a common name for the area around Akihabara Station in the Chiyoda ward of Tokyo, Japan. It gained the nickname Akihabara Electric Town shortly after World War II for being a major shopping center for household electronic goods and the post-war black market. Nowadays, Akihabara is considered by many to be an otaku cultural center and a shopping district for video games, anime, manga, and computer goods.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214314.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4573" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>Comiket</name>
<description>Comiket, also known as the Comic Market, is the world`s largest self-published http://anidb.net/t6989 [comic book fair], held twice a year in Tokyo, Japan.</description>
<picurl>167005.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="17519" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="272">5.97</rating>
<name>Aragaki Ayase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aragaki Ayase is Kirino`s best friend, and like her also works part-time as a fashion model. She is initially very prejudiced against otaku culture, being biased by the treatment of otakus in the media. When she discovers that Kirino has such proclivities she breaks off their friendship, but Kyousuke manages to reconcile them, and he manages to get Ayase to grudgingly accept that part of Kirino.</description>
<picture>55758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17521" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="135">4.70</rating>
<name>Kurusu Kanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurusu Kanako is a friend to Kirino and Ayase, and like them also works as a model, but is also a budding idol and can sing and dance very well. Like Ayase she is also biased against otaku culture, but Ayase manages to trick her into cosplaying as the main character in Kirino`s favorite anime Stardust Witch Meruru for a contest, whose prize is a limited edition Stardust Witch Meruru figurine. She manages to win the contest because of her uncanny resemblance to the main character, and her ability to sing the anime`s main theme so well despite never having sung it before.</description>
<picture>143826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17522" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="195">5.55</rating>
<name>Saori Vageena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saori Vageena is one of the active female members of the anime forum that Kirino wound up frequenting, and organized the get-together in Akihabara where she met Kirino and Kuroneko for the first time. She is the peacemaker of the group, and her friendly disposition helps to defuse tensions between Kirino and Kuroneko, keeping their arguments about each other`s tastes from getting out of hand. She tends to speak in a very quirky way, always using a very polite and antiquated mode of Japanese generally heard today only in samurai movies. Not much is known about her for certain, not even her real name (Saori Vageena is her handle on the anime board and evidently a pseudonym), but brief scenes of her at home show her in what looks a large mansion, attended by maids and butlers, implying that she is very wealthy, although neither the Kousaka siblings nor Kuroneko seem to be aware of this.</description>
<picture>55757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17523" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-18">
<rating votes="196">5.69</rating>
<name>Tamura Manami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamura Manami is Kyousuke`s classmate and childhood friend. She lives with her younger brother and grandparents, who are proprietors of a sweets shop a short distance from the Kousaka house. She has been friends with Kyousuke since childhood, and has a rather obvious crush on him that he seems oblivious to. She is rather frumpy and plain-looking and a little clumsy, but is also very kind and good-natured.</description>
<picture>55759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17524" type="main character in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="354">4.17</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Kyousuke is the main protagonist of the series, and acts as the narrator. He is a fairly ordinary second-year high school student who wishes for nothing more than a peaceful life until he accidentally discovers his little sister Kirino`s otaku hobbies. Even though Kirino is mean and disrespectful to him, he tries to be a good elder brother to her, giving her advice as best he can, and helping her to continue in her hobbies and make new friends. He is a responsible and reliable person who cares deeply about the welfare of his sister and of his friends.</description>
<picture>55755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17525" type="main character in" update="2011-12-17">
<rating votes="921">4.94</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kirino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Kirino is the main heroine of the series. She is a 14-year old girl who seems normal on the outside, but is in secret a hardcore otaku obsessed with anime and visual novel eroges, especially those involving little sisters. She works part-time as a model, which is how she managed to purchase her most impressive collection of figurines, visual novels, and anime DVDs. She has a talent for writing, and loves track and field.
She is initially cold and disrespectful towards her brother Kyousuke, but after he discovers her secret hobby and he supports her in it, they gradually grow closer.</description>
<picture>53292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17526" type="main character in" update="2013-04-21">
<rating votes="1020">8.54</rating>
<name>Gokou Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuroneko (a.k.a. Gokou Ruri) was one of the anime otaku girls Kirino had met in a gathering organized by Saori. Though their tastes in anime and games greatly differ, they nevertheless began to be good friends. She also became a good friend to Kyousuke, and it is hinted that she may have feelings for him. As befits the Kuroneko epithet, she is usually seen wearing a black Gothic Lolita-style dress, and is sharp-tongued and antisocial.
She enters Kyousuke`s high school later in the series, and joins the Game Club at his urging, displaying her considerable talents at writing and graphic design.</description>
<picture>55756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22009" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-04">
<rating votes="36">5.31</rating>
<name>Kousaka Yoshino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22010" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="34">4.53</rating>
<name>Kousaka Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Daisuke is the father of Kyousuke and Kirino. He is a police officer and takes a very dim view of otakus and otaku culture.</description>
<picture>55854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24930" type="appears in" update="2010-11-08">
<rating votes="14">4.15</rating>
<name>Akagi Kouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25121" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="10">3.10</rating>
<name>Meruru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meruru is the main character in Kirino`s favorite anime Stardust Witch Meruru. This metafictional anime seems to be a pastiche of the various clichés prevalent in the magical girl genre. She is voiced by Tamura Yukari, who, not coincidentally, also voices Kirino`s friend Kurusu Kanako.</description>
<picture>59341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25122" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="5">2.95</rating>
<name>Comet-kun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meruru`s animal sidekick in the metafictional anime Stardust Witch Meruru. Its appearance seems to be based roughly on Mokona/Soel from CLAMP`s Magic Knight Rayearth, Tsubasa Chronicle, and xxxHOLIC.</description>
<picture>59342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25426" type="appears in" update="2013-11-28">
<rating votes="24">6.73</rating>
<name>Gokou Tamaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gokou Tamaki is Kuroneko`s younger sister. She is in 1st grade.</description>
<picture>146454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25428" type="appears in" update="2010-11-29">
<rating votes="8">3.98</rating>
<name>Miyabi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60027.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25570" type="appears in" update="2010-12-06">
<rating votes="29">6.49</rating>
<name>Bridget Evans</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>60349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20806" picture="182700.jpg">Kuno Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31644" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="44">5.46</rating>
<name>Akagi Sena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouhei`s little sister and a member of the Games Research club, as well as Ruri`s classmate. Similar to Kirino, she has an obsession with eroges, albeit she prefers the yaoi genre to an extent that she`ll even fantasise about her other clubmates, pairing her brother and Kyousuke as a couple. The relationship she has with her brother is quite strong yet unclear how they feel each other. She joined the Games Research club in order to learn how to become a games designer. She is also very good at games, having the high score before Kuroneko beat it. This also attributes to her skill in programming being able to debug very easily.</description>
<picture>130803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31646" type="appears in" update="2011-04-28">
<rating votes="9">5.58</rating>
<name>Miura Gennosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The president of the Games Research club at Kyousuke`s school, which both Kyosuke and Ruri end up joining. He is also into little sister-themed eroge, as Kyosuke first meets him when trying to borrow a bike to ride home following a midnight eroge launch.</description>
<picture>70670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31647" type="appears in" update="2011-04-28">
<rating votes="11">3.23</rating>
<name>Makabe Kaede</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37272" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="476">6.85</rating>
<name>Asuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend of Kirito and is a sub-leader of the guild Knights of Blood (KoB), a medium-sized guild of about thirty player, also called the strongest guild in Aincrad. Being one of the few many girls that play SAO, and even more so that she`s extremely pretty, she receives many invitations and proposals. She is a skilled player earning the Title "Flash" for her extraordinary sword skill. The KoB has assigned her two bodyguards, one of whom despises Kirito. Her game alias is the same as her Real World name. She later on falls in love with Kirito, eventually leading to them being married.</description>
<picture>83185.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37273" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="395">5.84</rating>
<name>Kirito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main protagonist of the series. He is the protagonist and is a "solo" player, a player who hasn`t joined a guild and usually works alone. When it is announced that the players of Sword Art Online can no longer logout, he is surprised like everyone else, but unlike everyone else he quickly gets over it and accepts it, to an extent. He mainly uses a one-handed sword and usually wears all black in game, as it adds to stealth. He can also use two blades at once, a unique skill to him and he only uses it in emergencies to avoid attention for being one out of the two people to have unique skills. His game alias is Kirito, which is created by taking the syllables of the first and last Kanji of his real last and first names respectively: (Kirigaya Kazuto). In the real world, he lives with his mother and younger sister in a family of 3.</description>
<picture>83186.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41185" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="130">5.36</rating>
<name>Silica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Silica (in real world Ayano Keiko) is a side story character in SAO. She is one of the rare beast tamers in the game. Very early in the game, she was able to tame a small dragon, Pina, who becomes her only real friend in the game; this feat gave her immense fame, but she was just a mid-level player. Due to her fame and being a girl, many tried to get on her good side, causing her to get a bit of an inflated head. She usually stay away from the males, who tried to marry her despite the fact that she was only 13. After getting lost in a forest, she lost Pina to a monster attack. Kirito rescued and helped her, as she resembled his sister, and helps her revive Pina. She gained feelings for him, but once she realized his skills, she realized that they could never be together in the game.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>87804.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41186" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-04-03">
<rating votes="114">6.00</rating>
<name>Lisbeth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A side story character in SAO, who is a blacksmith with her own shop. Lisbeth or "Liz" is a close friend of Asuna who recommended her to Kirito. Kirito commissioned Liz to forge a custom-made sword for him and accompanies her in a quest for the special ore required for the job. During the quest, she also develops feelings for Kirito. She is devastated when she finds out that Kirito is Asuna`s crush. However, she finds some solace after Kirito thanks her for giving him a renewed determination to fight on and clear the game. Liz later becomes a regular player in ALO, and frequently joins Kirito and his friends in quests and takes up the task of upgrading their equipment.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>85684.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43014" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-10-10">
<rating votes="10">7.11</rating>
<name>Nanahara Kaoruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126674.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43015" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-07-09">
<rating votes="7">9.14</rating>
<name>Kisakinomiya Chihaya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90736.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43708" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-04-23">
<rating votes="16">6.66</rating>
<name>Kanou Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86389.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="46807" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-07-11">
<rating votes="11">7.34</rating>
<name>Tsukayama Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90790.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50977" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-11-30">
<rating votes="17">8.21</rating>
<name>Yoshino Charles</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Charles is a student in the same class as Rikka. She is Kiyotaka`s cousin and is half Japanese. She is a member of the newspaper club.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>128796.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54797" type="appears in" update="2013-04-11">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kyousuke (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4780" picture="28006.jpg">Fujita Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54830" type="appears in" update="2013-04-08">
<name>Alpha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54831" type="appears in" update="2013-04-11">
<name>Shikaisha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135160.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10906" picture="200861.jpg">Yanagita Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54948" type="appears in" update="2013-04-11">
<rating votes="11">7.39</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kirino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55005" type="appears in" update="2013-04-16">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Ayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayaka is the heroine in Love Touch game.</description>
<picture>135300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55205" type="appears in" update="2013-04-21">
<rating votes="3">6.37</rating>
<name>Hoshino Kirara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55206" type="appears in" update="2013-04-21">
<rating votes="5">6.28</rating>
<name>Makishima Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makishima Kaori is Saori`s seven years older sister who has a lot of interests.</description>
<picture>135557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55207" type="appears in" update="2014-07-27">
<rating votes="6">5.41</rating>
<name>Kurusu Kanata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurusu Kanata is one of the former members of the dissolved otaku community "Pretty Garden". She is the older sister of Kanako, and the original author of Ruri`s favorite anime series Maschera.
Source: oreimo.wikia.com</description>
<picture>135559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55208" type="appears in" update="2013-04-21">
<name>Sanada Shinya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55217" type="appears in" update="2013-04-21">
<rating votes="18">7.42</rating>
<name>Makishima Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Her real appearance which she keeps hidden.</description>
<picture>135556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55415" type="appears in" update="2013-05-02">
<rating votes="6">6.30</rating>
<name>Ria Hagry</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55578" type="appears in" update="2013-05-04">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Fujima Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136226.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55606" type="appears in" update="2013-05-05">
<name>Yousei-san</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="35415" picture="146334.jpg">Chisuga Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55607" type="appears in" update="2013-11-28">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Mikagami Kouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12623" picture="151646.jpg">Iguchi Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56133" type="appears in" update="2013-11-28">
<rating votes="18">8.83</rating>
<name>Gokou Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gokou Hinata is Kuroneko`s younger sister. She is in 5th grade.</description>
<picture>146453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56896" type="appears in" update="2013-06-08">
<rating votes="2">6.16</rating>
<name>Miyamoto Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56997" type="appears in" update="2013-06-09">
<name>Ayase Mama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="28860" picture="65896.jpg">Imase Michi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97097" type="appears in" update="2018-08-03">
<rating votes="2">4.11</rating>
<name>Alpha Omega</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66384.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="144697" update="2012-10-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第2期 プロモーションビデオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Second Season PV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 2 Ki Promotion Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147748" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="20">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹が再び帰ってくるわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sister Can`t Come Back Home Again</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petite sœur n`est pas censée revenir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto ga Futatabi Kaettekuru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>After Kirino is brought back from her study abroad in America by Kyousuke, she spends time getting back into her normal routine as she surrounds herself with Aragaki Ayase and other friends who are excited to see her back. In contrast to that, Kyousuke is feeling dissatisfied with the fact that Kirino is ignoring him like she used to before their last year together. So Kirino responds by...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622451</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148203" update="2017-04-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹のライバルが来日するわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sister`s Rival Can`t Come to Japan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rivale de ma petite sœur n`est pas censée venir au Japon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto no Rival ga Rainichi Suru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>When Kyousuke comes home from school and opens his door, he finds a young, naked girl who just got out of the bath. Kyousuke is completely shocked, but the young girl is Ria, Kirino`s roommate from when she studied abroad. She`s staying with the Kousaka family while she`s in Japan, but the innocent young girl asks Kirino and Kyousuke to take her sightseeing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622457</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148204" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="20">4.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の友達が眼鏡を外すわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Friend Can`t Take Off Her Glasses</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon amie n`est pas censée enlever ses lunettes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Tomodachi ga Megame o Hazusu Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>Kirino, Kyousuke, and Kuroneko visit Saori`s apartment to try and surprise her, but the two girls start reproaching Kyousuke when he realizes he doesn`t know her room number. As the three of them stand there arguing, an elegant young woman appears before them. The moment she realizes it`s Kyousuke and the others, she covers her face and crouches down, crying out with a voice they all recognized.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622455</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148205" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信じて送り出したお兄さんが携帯美少女ゲームにドハマリしてセクハラしてくるようになるわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Onii-san I Trusted and Sent Off Can`t Get This Addicted to a Mobile Dating Sim and Commit Sexual Harassment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je n`en reviens pas que son frère me persécute à cause d`un jeu de drague</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjite Okuridashita Onii-san ga Keitai Bishoujo Game ni Dohamari Shite Sekuhara Shite Kuru You ni Naru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>When Kirino gets hooked on a portable bishoujo game and starts ignoring her friends, Aragaki Ayase asks Kyousuke for help in breaking her addiction. To help her out, Kyousuke talks to Kirino and persuades her to cut back on the game, but ends up borrowing it from her instead. Then, when Kyousuke tries playing it...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622453</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148906" update="2013-04-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149616" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹が家に彼氏をつれてくるわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s No Way My Sister Would Bring Her Boyfriend Home!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petite sœur n`est pas censée amener son petit ami à la maison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto ga Ie ni Kareshi o Tsuretekuru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>While attending comiket, the group coincidentally happens on a young man, Mikagami, who turns out to be a fashion model and designer that Kirino knew from work. As the two of them start enjoying a friendly otaku conversation, Kyousuke finds himself wondering about their relationship. Then Kirino comes forth and confesses the shocking truth to him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622461</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149617" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺が妹の彼氏なわけがないし, 俺の妹に彼氏がいるわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Be My Little Sister`s Boyfriend and My Little Sister Can`t Have a Boyfriend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne suis pas censé être le petit ami de ma petite sœur, et elle n`est pas censée en avoir un</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Imouto no Kareshi na Wake ga Naishi, Ore no Imouto ni Kareshi ga Iru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>Kirino confesses that she wants Kyousuke to be her boyfriend, and he`s confused. She had her reasons, though. Once Kyousuke hears why Kirino asked that, he goes on a date with her as her boyfriend, but Manami and the others see them while they`re on their date.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622459</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149621" update="2015-12-07">
<epno type="3">C17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149824" update="2013-04-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149825" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150148" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150149" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺が後輩とひと夏の思い出を作るわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Create a Summer Memory with My Underclassman</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne suis pas censé me faire des souvenirs d`été avec ma disciple</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Kouhai to Hitonatsu no Omoide o Tsukuru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>Now that he`s going out with Kuroneko, Kyousuke is really excited. Kuroneko fels the same too. Although neither are used to dating and both are a bit hesitant, they still enjoy their time spent going out together. During their date, Kuroneko pulls out her notebook, but what`s written on that page...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622465</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150150" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="19">9.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺が後輩と恋人同士になるわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Become a Couple with My Underclassman</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne suis pas censé sortir avec ma disciple</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Kouhai to Koibito Doushi ni Naru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>Kyousuke decides not to answer Kuroneko`s confession and asks her for a day to think it over. As Kirino and Manami give him their support, he ends up spending a day with her trying to organize how he feels. On their way home from the comiket after-party together with everyone else, Kyousuke finally gives Kuroneko his answer.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622463</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150388" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150389" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150390" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150391" update="2014-02-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150497" update="2013-05-11">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150498" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150614" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="24">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジ天使すぎるあやせたんが一人暮らしの俺んちに降臨するわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Total Angel Ayase-tan Can`t Descend Upon My Place While I Live Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ange Ayase n`est pas censée descendre dans le studio où je vis seul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maji Tenshisugiru Ayase-tan ga Hitorigurashi no Orenchi ni Kourin Suru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>At Manami`s suggestion, everyone is invited to Kyousuke`s new apartment for a moving-in party. All of Kyousuke`s usual friends are gathering at his new place on the day of the party when Kirino arrives and she`s forced to confront Manami...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622473</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150615" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一人暮らしの兄貴の部屋に妹たちが押しかけるわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Sisters Can`t Barge in on Their Brother Who Lives Alone</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petite sœur et ses copines ne sont pas censées se ruer chez le grand frère qui habite seul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitorigurashi no Aniki no Heya ni Imouto-tachi ga Oshikakeru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>The Kousaka household holds a family meeting. Their mother, Yoshino, has grown suspicious of how Kirino and Kyousuke have grown too close lately. The two of them desperately try to smooth over the situation, but their father, Daisuke, orders Kyousuke to leave the house and focus on his studies until he can earn an A on his mock exam.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622471</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150616" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="20">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹がウェディングドレスを着るわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sister Can`t Wear a Wedding Dress</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petite sœur n`est pas censée porter une robe de mariée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto ga Wedding Dress o Kiru Wake ga Nai</title>
<summary>Once Ayase learned that Kyousuke was dating Kuroneko, she called him to her room and interrogated him. Several days later, she receives word from Manami that Kyousuke and Kuroneko broke up. Ayase believes it`s all her fault, so she calls Kyousuke...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622469</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150617" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹がこんなに可愛いわけがない!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sister Can`t Be This Cute!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petite sœur ne peut pas être aussi mignonne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai!</title>
<summary>After going to the fireworks display with Kuroneko, Kyousuke can no longer get a hold of her. He can`t get his mind off the line she showed him in her notebook, and when he goes to school he suddenly learns that Kuroneko transferred away without telling him. Unable to accept the truth and hanging his head in despair, Kyousuke turns to Kirino for advice that night...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622467</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150618" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C22</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150619" update="2013-05-18">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150671" update="2014-09-12">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺と赤城のアダルトな一日 『らぶドール』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Doll</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore to Akagi no Adult na Ichinichi: Love Doll</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150780" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="20">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹[あたし]が兄[あいつ]に恋なんてするわけない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Sisters Can`t Fall in Love with Their Older Brothers!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne suis pas censée être amoureuse de lui</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atashi ga Aitsu ni Koi nante Suru Wake Nai</title>
<summary>Going back 8 years ago... When Kyousuke comes home, Kirino comes running to him in tears. When she holds out a broken doll between her hands, Kyousuke gives her a confident smile and starts fixing the doll. Kirino watches with anxiety, but he easily fixes it. That was the Kyousuke that Kirino used to admire...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622475</identifier>
<identifier>oreimo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150786" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C23</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150787" update="2013-05-25">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151054" update="2014-02-08">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151075" update="2015-12-07">
<epno type="3">C24</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151159" update="2013-06-15">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151203" update="2014-09-12">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="26">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹がこんなに可愛いわけがない.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sister Can`t Be This Cute.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petite sœur ne peut pas être si mignonne.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151204" update="2014-09-12">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="23">3.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹がこんなに可愛い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sister Is This Cute</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petit-sœur est si mignonne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151205" update="2014-09-12">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="25">3.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺が彼女に告白なんてするわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Confess to Her</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne ferai pas de déclaration à ma petite amie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Kanojo ni Kokuhaku nante Suru Wake ga Nai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151260" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C25</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151273" update="2013-06-22">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151394" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C26</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151395" update="2013-06-29">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151569" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Animated Commentary 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151570" update="2013-07-08">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺と赤城のアダルトな一日 [BLショップ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BL Shop</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore to Akagi no Adult na Ichinichi: BL Shop</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151738" update="2013-07-08">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151739" update="2013-07-08">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151741" update="2015-12-07">
<epno type="3">C16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152432" update="2013-08-08">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">全世界同時公開用PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Worldwide Simultaneous Streaming PV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zensekai Douji Koukaiyou PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152582" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C28</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152583" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C27</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152584" update="2013-08-18">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1m</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152585" update="2013-08-18">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1l</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155444" update="2014-05-03">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">来栖姉妹の日常『マスケラvsメルル 場外乱闘編』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Kurusu Sisters: Maschera vs. Meruru - Curb Brawl Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurusu Shimai no Nichijou "Maschera vs. Meruru: Jougai Rantou Hen"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155447" update="2013-11-02">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 05</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155448" update="2013-11-02">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156582" update="2013-12-06">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 07</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156583" update="2013-12-06">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 06</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156586" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Animated Commentary 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156587" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Animated Commentary 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156590" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156633" update="2014-05-02">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156792" update="2014-05-02">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156793" update="2014-05-02">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156794" update="2014-05-02">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 09</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156795" update="2014-05-02">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 08</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156796" update="2014-05-03">
<epno type="3">C30</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156797" update="2014-02-16">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1n</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156798" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2013-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Animated Commentary 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156799" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲーム研究会活動報告 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Game Study Group Activity Report 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Game Kenkyuukai Katsudou Houkoku 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156800" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲーム研究会活動報告 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Game Study Group Activity Report 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Game Kenkyuukai Katsudou Houkoku 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156898" update="2014-05-02">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156899" update="2014-05-02">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156900" update="2014-05-03">
<epno type="3">C31</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156901" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突撃乙女ロード!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assault Otome Road!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsugeki Otome Road!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156902" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺が御鏡に人生相談するわけがない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s No Way I Can Talk to Your Life Mirror</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore ga Okagami ni Jinsei Soudan Suru Wake ga Nai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157501" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲーム研究会活動報告 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Game Study Group Activity Report 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Game Kenkyuukai Katsudou Houkoku 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157502" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2013-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">次回予告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Next Installment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikai Yokoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159676" update="2014-05-02">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159677" update="2014-05-02">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159678" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹がこんなにエロゲーなわけがない ~逆襲の秋美~ バレンタイン編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sister Can`t Be This Erotic ~Akimi Strikes Back~ Valentine Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Eroge na Wake ga Nai ~ Gyakushuu no Akimi ~ Valentine Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159679" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺の妹がこんなにエロゲーなわけがない ~逆襲の秋美~ 初詣編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sister Can`t Be This Erotic ~Akimi Strikes Back~ Hatsumode Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Eroge na Wake ga Nai ~ Gyakushuu no Akimi ~ Hatsumoude Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159680" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Animated Commentary 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159681" update="2014-05-03">
<epno type="3">C29</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161568" update="2014-07-29">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2014-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギャルゲー風特典映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Galge Style Bonus Content</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Galge-Fuu Tokuten Eizou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
