<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9208" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-10-20</startdate>
<enddate>2012-10-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nerawareta Gakuen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Haunted Academy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">neragaku</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ねらわれた学園</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Psychic School Wars</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12605" approval="6" total="8">Uchiage Hanabi, Shita kara Miru ka? Yoko kara Miru ka?</anime>
<anime id="8742" approval="5" total="16">Kokoro Connect</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="401808">If you`re looking for a sense of completion after watching this, you`ll be greatly disappointed. Yes, the visuals are great and everything-- but the end felt like a total mind f*ck that I don`t feel good about it. It makes me want to watch it again just in case I missed out, but it`s not the case. Good OSTs, great animations, sadly a big gaping hole for where the strong story line should be.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="532954">Animation is amazing , pretty romantic but it felt like something was missing from the end..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="389161">There was a romantic touch - no doubt about that. Superb animation on par with Makoto Shinkai. The character development was good, but I did not understand the psychic thing (and what`s with the familiar?) -- it needs more explanation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="102269">if I`d a need to present this anime in a string of random words then it would be as follows - &amp;gt; slice of life teenage love drama with sci fi time traveling world ending clusterfu*k.

Visually beautiful fruit salad. With a pronounced taste of bitter lemon from time to time. And some unexplained ingredients too, that are present, you see them, but don`t get their taste, as they melt away the moment you get it on your tongue.

Not bad, just a bit too a-little-bit-of-everything without a clear aim. 

7/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="432674">Great Movie. Animation was amazing, but I can`t 100% agree that the breathtaking scenes were on par with 5cm/s or Kotonoha no Niwa. Nice soundtrack, liked the 1st music that was played.

Its true that there were big information that was left out. But I wouldn`t call it crucial for the story to be confusing nor leaves a big question. Whats notable is the love polygon / romance scene especially that, that and maybe that.

And if they say this is like Makoto Shinkai movies then I would retort this is a more cheerful one, it put me on smiles in many scenes. I would probably JUST probably prefer more of this than Makoto Shinkai`s works.

PS. Im not sure if bias because I recognize the voices of of many of my favorite anime characters to the the cast here but I loved it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.neragaku.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="8969" type="Original Work">Mayumura Taku</name>
<name id="12437" type="Character Design">Hosoi Mieko</name>
<name id="12437" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hosoi Mieko</name>
<name id="9594" type="Music">Murai Shuusei</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="726" type="Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="7779" type="Direction">Nakamura Ryousuke</name>
</creators>
<description>Spring marks the start of another new school year at a junior high school in Kamakura. A new transfer student, http://anidb.net/ch45526 [Kyougoku Ryouichi] joins the 8th grade. He has a very special proficiency in telepathy and has been ordered by his father to use this ability to scan other people`s minds and take over the school.
He instantly gains popularity at school from his good looks and charisma and he sets about taking control of the school. As people begin to fall under Ryouichi`s spell, he covertly manipulates his followers and pushes aside anyone who gets in his way.
With the school almost completely under the control of Ryouichi, only one boy seems unaffected - http://anidb.net/ch45529 [Seki Kenji]. Does Kenji have what it takes to save everyone from the clutches of mind control?
Source: lovesanimation.com
Note: Premiered at Scotland Loves Anime film festival at the Filmhouse in Edinburgh (October 19-21, 2012). In Japan, the movie was screened starting from November 10, 2012.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1122">5.47</permanent>
<temporary count="1128">6.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>93405.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14328</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14293</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5297</identifier>
<identifier>opdxxe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.neragaku.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nerawareta_Gakuen</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ねらわれた学園_(2012年の映画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3022</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343041</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15384</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01M8IJREW</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1730" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-24">
<name>mobile phone</name>
<description>Character is often or always using a mobile phone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5917" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-24">
<name>classical music</name>
<description>Classical music is art music produced or rooted in the traditions of Western music (both liturgical and secular). It encompasses a broad span of time from roughly the 11th century to the present day.
Anime tagged have classical music as a central theme.</description>
<picurl>169132.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7089" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-28">
<name>Kamakura</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="45526" type="main character in" update="2012-06-01">
<rating votes="8">4.27</rating>
<name>Kyougoku Ryouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45527" type="main character in" update="2012-06-01">
<rating votes="15">5.93</rating>
<name>Harukawa Kahori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45528" type="main character in" update="2012-06-01">
<rating votes="14">5.41</rating>
<name>Suzuura Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32475" picture="86884.jpg">Watanabe Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45529" type="main character in" update="2012-06-01">
<rating votes="9">4.45</rating>
<name>Seki Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3189" picture="81680.jpg">Honjou Yuutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57423" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="1">9.11</rating>
<name>Ryouura Natsuki (Kodomo)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37901" picture="138975.jpg">Endou Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57424" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="1">9.11</rating>
<name>Seki Kenji (Kodomo)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16805" picture="45972.jpg">Yoshinaga Takuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57425" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="6">2.71</rating>
<name>Yamagiwa Yuriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57426" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-24">
<name>Kyougoku no Tsukaima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57427" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="3">6.64</rating>
<name>Seki Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57428" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="2">7.90</rating>
<name>Saitou-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57429" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Endou Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57430" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="1">9.11</rating>
<name>Jinno Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57431" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="2">7.26</rating>
<name>Soga Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="443" picture="145927.jpg">Ishikawa Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57432" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="1">1.92</rating>
<name>Amano Daito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9114" picture="201075.jpg">Kikumoto Taira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57433" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<name>Kondou Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32332" picture="86559.jpg">Sasaki Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57434" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<name>Ishikawa Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37900" picture="138976.jpg">Uchida Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57435" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<name>Chounouryokusha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30034" picture="151713.jpg">Shimizu Hidemitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57436" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<rating votes="1">9.11</rating>
<name>Shiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35751" picture="131610.jpg">Mugiho Anna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57437" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<name>Natsuki no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37899" picture="170968.jpg">Mizuno Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57438" type="appears in" update="2013-06-24">
<name>Natsuki no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7532" picture="238364.jpg">Shimizu Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="139975" update="2012-06-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teaser (30 sec)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144015" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>110</length>
<airdate>2012-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>When transfer student Ryoichi Kyogoku appears things take a turn for the weird. Students are missing school, the student council bans cellphones, and Kyogoku begins changing students by awakening their psychic abilities to prevent a future disaster on Earth. Kenji Seki and his friends get caught in the middle and must try to figure out what is going on in time to save their friends and the future.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="145995" update="2012-12-16">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロングPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Long Promo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Long PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145996" update="2012-12-16">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">本予告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honyokoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151675" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151676" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo (15s) 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151677" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo (15s) 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151678" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD DVD CM 2 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151679" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD DVD CM 1 (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151680" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞台挨拶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Talk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Butai Aisatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151681" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2012-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151682" update="2013-07-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2012-10-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
