<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9311" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2013-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">GJ-bu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">GJ Club, Junior High School Division</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">GJ部</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">GJ 중등부</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-x-nan" type="official">GJ部</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">GJ部</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10016" type="Sequel">GJ-bu@</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6556" approval="22" total="27">Seitokai no Ichizon</anime>
<anime id="4777" approval="4" total="11">Lucky Star</anime>
<anime id="11735" approval="2" total="8">Kono Bijutsubu ni wa Mondai ga Aru!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="571871">A fun slice of life with a large serving of moe. Great characters and MC isn`t that bad and plays well with the jokes. Nice OP&amp;ED. For fans of this genre. Anyone will like it if they know what they`re getting into beforehand.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="30310">At first glance this show contains nothing to set it apart from the massive amount of high-school comedies. It`s got mind numbing arch-types such as the gluttony that really does eat constantly. However the comedic routines are easily digested, and somehow the show appealed to a few of my fetishes, ie there is a good amount of hair play/combing.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ntv.co.jp/gj/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1067" type="Animation Work">Doga Kobo</name>
<name id="3779" type="Character Design">Ooshima Miwa</name>
<name id="6898" type="Series Composition">Koyasu Hideaki</name>
<name id="30322" type="Direction">Fujiwara Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="34082" type="Original Work">Araki Shin</name>
<name id="2424" type="Music">Hyakkoku Hajime</name>
<name id="10771" type="Chief Animation Direction">Soga Atsushi</name>
<name id="2423" type="Music">F.M.F</name>
<name id="3779" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ooshima Miwa</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a series of light novels written by http://anidb.net/cr34082 [Araki Shin] and illustrated by Aruya.
Within the old school building of a certain high school, is the clubroom of the http://anidb.net/ch50793 [GJ (Good Job) Club], into which http://anidb.net/ch50693 [Shinomiya Kyouya] finds himself forcibly conscripted.
The other members are:
http://anidb.net/ch50692 [Mao], the short and egotistical president;
http://anidb.net/ch50691 [Megumi], Mao`s sister who`s as generous as an angel;
http://anidb.net/ch50690 [Shion], a genius lacking in common sense; and
http://anidb.net/ch50689 [Kirara], who is perpetually hungry.
~ translated and adapted from official site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1599">5.47</permanent>
<temporary count="1607">6.89</temporary>
<review count="1">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>157009.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14671</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14811</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5226</identifier>
<identifier>dsjjjy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ntv.co.jp/gj/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>GJ-bu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>GJ部</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2877</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344510</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15690</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2558" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>catgirl</name>
<description>A catgirl (nekomusume, 猫娘) is a girl that has a cat`s characteristics, a form of zoomorphism.
They can appear either as normal girls without any obvious cat traits —such as eyes, ears, paws, or a tail— or as girls who have one or more of these traits. In the former case they are usually cats that have become human through the means of magic. The feline features are added for moe and/or sexiness appeal, with the most common features being cat ears and tail. Nya~, the Japanese equivalent of meow, is often used by girls acting cute and is not a trait exclusive to catgirls.
Not to be confused with characters who simply are wearing a http://anidb.net/t1622 [cat ears accessory] (nekomimi, 猫耳) as a fashion accessory. Catgirls with cat ears should also be tagged with http://anidb.net/t2541 [animal ears].</description>
<picurl>150775.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2756" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>board games</name>
<description>People here play a board game. It can vary from chess and Go, to Monopoly, to Dungeons and Dragons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2873" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>Valentine`s Day</name>
<description>Valentine`s Day is a festive day celebrated every February 14.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China, Valentine`s Day is one month before http://anidb.net/t3147 [White Day], a celebration unique to those countries.
In the rest of the world:
On Valentine`s Day, both males and females will express their feelings of affection towards their loved ones, by exchanging gifts (such as cards, candies, and chocolates), going on dates, and other signs and actions of affection. Some people also take the opportunity to confess and propose for marriage. In Western countries, it is generally expected of the male to offer gifts to the significant other.
In many countries, friends and co-workers also exchange small gifts to show their friendship towards each other.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China:
On Valentine`s Day, many women feel obliged to give chocolates to all male co-workers, except when the day falls on a Sunday, a holiday. This is known as giri choco (義理チョコ, "obligation chocolate"), with unpopular co-workers receiving only chougiri choco (超義理チョコ, "ultra-obligatory chocolate") cheap chocolate.
This contrasts with honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate"), chocolate given to a loved one.
Friends, especially girls, may exchange chocolate referred to as tomo choco (友チョコ, "friend chocolate").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160891.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2917" parentid="2756" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>chess</name>
<description>Chess is a game for two players. It is played on a square board, made of 64 smaller squares, with eight squares on each side. Each player starts with sixteen pieces (eight pawns, two each of knights, bishops, and rooks, and one king and queen). One player`s pieces are a light color, he is called "White", and the other player`s pieces are a dark color, he is called "Black".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="50689" type="main character in" update="2012-11-21">
<rating votes="49">7.03</rating>
<name>Kirara Bernstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34452" picture="128255.jpg">Arakawa Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50690" type="main character in" update="2018-05-13">
<rating votes="55">8.45</rating>
<name>Sumeragi Shion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50691" type="main character in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="44">7.14</rating>
<name>Amatsuka Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Middle Amatsuka sister, quite well mannered and responsible unlike her elder sister.</description>
<picture>128400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4432" picture="200731.jpg">Miyamoto Yume</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50692" type="main character in" update="2013-03-01">
<rating votes="56">5.35</rating>
<name>Amatsuka Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eldest Amatsuka sister despite her looks and President of the GJ-bu.</description>
<picture>128399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50693" type="main character in" update="2012-11-21">
<rating votes="31">3.88</rating>
<name>Shinomiya Kyouya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>128398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50793" type="appears in" update="2012-11-22">
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<name>GJ-bu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>128464.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="52517" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-10">
<rating votes="54">8.52</rating>
<name>Mori-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53042" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-10">
<rating votes="35">4.08</rating>
<name>Kannazuki Tamaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>First year who was forced to join GJ Club in the same way Kyouya was forced to join 1 year ago.</description>
<picture>135065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53051" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-30">
<rating votes="30">6.05</rating>
<name>Shinomiya Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Younger sister of http://anidb.net/ch50693 [Kyouya]. She seems to have a brother complex.</description>
<picture>135062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53052" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-10">
<rating votes="29">5.05</rating>
<name>Geraldine Bernstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Younger sister of Kirara who recently came from Canada to live with her sister.</description>
<picture>135063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36270" picture="133606.jpg">Aoi Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53053" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-10">
<rating votes="31">2.59</rating>
<name>Amatsuka Seira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Youngest daughter of the Amatsuka family.</description>
<picture>135064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53811" type="appears in" update="2013-03-13">
<rating votes="7">3.14</rating>
<name>Kyoroko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyouya when he was forced to dress up as a girl by the rest of the GJ-bu members. He looks disturbingly attractive.</description>
<picture>133605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53812" type="appears in" update="2013-03-13">
<name>Neko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53813" type="appears in" update="2013-03-13">
<name>Waitress</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="33660" picture="92231.jpg">Takano Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53814" type="appears in" update="2013-03-13">
<name>Cabin Attendant</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="33660" picture="92231.jpg">Takano Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54427" type="appears in" update="2013-03-28">
<name>Ayame</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="37021" picture="136081.jpg">Tajiri Ayame</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54428" type="appears in" update="2013-03-28">
<name>Yurika</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="37019" picture="136079.jpg">Takahashi Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="146359" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私がグッジョブだ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am the GJ Club!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-x-nan">我是GJ部</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi wa Good Job Da!</title>
<summary>Shinomiya Kyoya joins the mysterious "GJ Club."
Surrounded by the small but determined club president Mao, her opposite and younger sister Megumi, the universally recognized genius Shion, and the mysterious Kirara, who knows what will happen?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620513</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146693" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="x-unk">友情, 愛情, 少女的異常</title>
<title xml:lang="ja">友情・愛情・彼女の異常?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friendliness, Loveliness, and Her Strangeness?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuujou, Aijou, Kanojo no Ijou?</title>
<summary>While drinking a can of coffee, Shion complains it tastes strange. A worried Kyoya tries tasting it, but...
One sunny afternoon, the president takes a nap. What is the reason for the unbelievable words she says in her sleep?
Their unique personalities become increasingly apparent??
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620515</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="146831" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GJ線上のキョロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kyoro on the GJ String</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-x-nan">GJ線上的京張</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GJ Senjou no Kyoro</title>
<summary>Kyoya is accepted as a member of the GJ Club. He receives a club member badge with a function unknown even to the president...
The usually strong president is unusually sweet to Kyoya, and the other club members begin approaching him as well.
Could this be what it means to be popular?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620517</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147123" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">放課後文化祭パーティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After School`s Cultural Festival Party</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-x-nan">放學後的校慶派對</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Houkago Bunkasai Party</title>
<summary>With the cultural festival approaching, the GJ Club works to prepare something for the festival. The club chooses to provide wedding catering for their exhibit.
While working on their exhibit, the members spot a baked potato vendor passing by and stop for a snack. Who will eat the last potato?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620519</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147132" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダブルなファンタジー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Double Fantasy</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-x-nan">雙重幻想</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Double na Fantasy</title>
<summary>The season is an eventful winter. The GJ Club breaks out their kotatsu and lounges around every day. The president begins knitting socks before Christmas. When he learns she actually believes in Santa Claus, Kyoya takes on the role of Santa...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620521</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147307" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="x-unk">來了4個妹妹!?</title>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹が4人いる!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Four Little Sisters Enter!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto ga Yonin Iru!?</title>
<summary>Kyoya is nowhere to be found in the club room. It seems he has taken the day off to do something with his younger sister. Furthermore, Kirara has her own younger sister, and Mao and Megumi have a third younger sister. Meanwhile, Mao suddenly invites Kyoya out, and she is clearly dressed strangely...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620523</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147451" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="x-unk">新社員現身!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja">新入部員あらわる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New Club Member Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinnyuu Buin Arawaru!</title>
<summary>Spring. A new member is kidnapped while walking past the club room. The new club member`s name is Tamaki. Will her seniors accept her insolent speech and attitude? Kyoya transforms again to roar at them!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620501</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147571" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばGJ部と言おう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let Us Say Good Bye, GJ Club</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-x-nan">說聲GJ部再見</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba GJ-bu to Iou</title>
<summary>Even on the morning of the graduation ceremony, the members gather in their club room. At Shion-san`s request, Kyoya follows her out to the vending machines... Once he returns to the club room, he receives a text while alone with Kirara...
Finally, after school, the club`s last activity together begins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620511</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147572" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">協・定・解・除</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Agreement Cancelled</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-x-nan">協・定・解・除</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoutei Kaijo</title>
<summary>Winter, the season of kotatsu and tangerines. Curled up inside the kotatsu is not a cat, but... Shion wearing cat ears? Their second Valentine`s Day! This year they will cancel their agreement, but will Kyoya receive any chocolate!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620509</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147573" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="x-unk">藝術, 食慾與襲擊之秋</title>
<title xml:lang="ja">芸術と食欲と襲撃の秋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Autumn of Arts, Appetite, and Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Geijutsu to Shokuyoku to Shuugeki no Aki</title>
<summary>The autumn of arts. Kyoya is drawing something in his sketchbook. Mao thinks it is a monster, but actually...
Just before Halloween, the sisters invade the GJ Club room!! Apparently, they have formed a middle school GJ Club.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620507</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147574" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GJ線上のキョロ・REBIRTH</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kyoro on the GJ Line, REBIRTH</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-x-nan">GJ線上的京張・REBIRTH</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GJ Senjou no Kyoro, Rebirth</title>
<summary>Kyoya is forced to wear a white coat. It seems today`s club activity is playing doctor.
The members of the GJ Club appear before Kyoya one by one as his patients.
As Kyoya is getting used to it, he notices Kirara staring at something on the ceiling and grows concerned. Apparently they need a sacrifice to exorcise the thing!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620505</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147575" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="x-unk">妹妹・突擊!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja">シスターズ・アタック!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sisters Attack!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sisters Attack!</title>
<summary>In the beginnig of summer, Kyoya`s sister Kasumi comes to hang out in the club room. Mao convinces Kasumi she is younger than her and calls herself "Ma-chan." Meanwhile, the members of the GJ Club decide to go to the pool to escape the persistent heat... with Kasumi and her friends.
The names of Kasumi`s friends sound awfully familiar...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>620503</identifier>
<identifier>gj-club</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="147982" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147983" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147984" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147985" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147986" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147987" update="2013-03-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロモーション映像集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Promotional Eizou Shuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147988" update="2013-03-08">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147989" update="2013-03-08">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147990" update="2013-03-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148988" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148989" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148990" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150342" update="2013-05-04">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150343" update="2013-05-04">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150344" update="2013-05-04">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151196" update="2013-06-17">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151197" update="2013-06-17">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web preview eps 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195417" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
