<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9665" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-09-15</startdate>
<enddate>2013-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Machine-Doll wa Kizutsukanai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="synonym">Machine-Doll wa Kizutsukanai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Unbreakable Machine Doll</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kikou Shoujo wa Kizutsukanai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">UMD</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機巧少女は傷つかない</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Unbreakable Machine-Doll</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">기교소녀는 상처받지 않아</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">机巧少女不会受伤</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9996" approval="22" total="34">Seikoku no Dragonar</anime>
<anime id="10745" approval="19" total="24">Absolute Duo</anime>
<anime id="9508" approval="11" total="15">Rozen Maiden (2013)</anime>
<anime id="10181" approval="4" total="4">Black Bullet</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="176836">Good show to watch for the story. Hentai/Ecchi parts are bonus and can always be fast-forwarded through.
It`s OBVIOUSLY more Ecchi than other shows, at time even coming out almost like soft pron (boobs, nakedness!)...and there`s a TON of fanservice for guys with panty shots and entire scenes with just boobs in the picture.
 HOWEVER, the story behind the fanservice has been good enough to keep me going. Fight scenes are decent with a blend of CG and Animation. Character design for the DOLLs are really good. The lead girl (not a doll) is pretty much stereotypical tsun-tsun and boring. But I like the lead guy who is at times predictable (lead anime dude unable to handle handsy girl) but when he`s going into the deeper parts of the story he`s pretty multi-faceted which is rare nowadays in male leads.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.machine-doll.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="35309" type="Original Work">Kaitou Reiji</name>
<name id="3012" type="Character Design">Watanabe Atsuko</name>
<name id="5071" type="Series Composition">Kakihara Yuuko</name>
<name id="27220" type="Work">Lerche</name>
<name id="708" type="Direction">Yoshimoto Kinji</name>
<name id="3326" type="Music">Yokoyama Masaru</name>
</creators>
<description>During the early 20th century, along with technological advancements, scientists were able to develop sophisticated magic. The combination of science and sorcery was called Machinart: circuits made from spells that were put into objects to bring them to life and even gain a personality. It was developed as a military weapon and has spread throughout the world.
http://anidb.net/ch55490 [Akabane Raishin] is now attending the Walpurgis Royal Academy of Machinart in Mechanical City to become the best puppeteer in the world. Accompanied by the lovely teenage girl http://anidb.net/ch55491 [Yaya], who is actually Raishin`s puppet weapon, he plans on rocketing to the top of the class. However, his test scores come in nearly dead last, 1,235th of 1,236 to be exact, although his combat skills and determination are second to none. Raishin has to compete with the deadliest of classmates if he wants to come out on top.
Source: Moetron
Note: The first episode was pre-aired at a special event on 15.09.2013, regular TV broadcast started on 07.10.2013.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2137">4.92</permanent>
<temporary count="2150">6.72</temporary>
<review count="3">4.27</review>
</ratings>
<picture>186023.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15107</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21415</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17247</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.machine-doll.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Unbreakable_Machine-Doll</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機巧少女は傷つかない</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3143</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>346827</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16500</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=DAHHkFduUCA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3283" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>fighting dolls</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6900" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-23">
<name>gaslamp fantasy</name>
<description>Gaslamp fantasy is a subgenre of both fantasy and historical fiction, similar to but distinct from http://anidb.net/t2870 [steampunk], to which it is loosely related. While steampunk focuses on fantastic Industrial Revolution technology and as such is a genre of science fiction, gaslamp fantasy focuses more on supernatural elements and frequently includes magic and supernatural creatures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="55490" type="main character in" update="2016-04-22">
<rating votes="31">6.27</rating>
<name>Akabane Raishin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young puppeteer who came from an island nation in the far east. He transferred in as a sophomore of the academy. He placed 1235th out of 1236 students during his first academic exam, so Professor Kimberly named him Second Last. Although he was born to the Akabane Clan, a renowned family of puppeteers, he has very little experience as a puppeteer, and uses a very unique fighting style combining magic and martial arts to compensate.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55491" type="main character in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="71">8.13</rating>
<name>Yaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raishin`s automaton. She`s one of Karyuusai Brand`s greatest automatons, the Moon in their Setsugetsuka Series, and she`s worth enough to buy a warship. She loves Raishin too much, and gets extremely jealous when he`s with other women and often loses control. Using her magic circuit, Kongouriki, she converts the monad in her personal territory into a super-hard material and raises her physical strength several thousand times, granting her both huge offensive and defensive power. Her favorite food is anmitsu.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55862" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-22">
<rating votes="26">7.43</rating>
<name>Charlotte Belew</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s a sophomore like Raishin. She`s a blonde-haired blue-eyed beauty at first glance, but she`s a talented young girl who`s placed her name amongst Walpurgis Night`s top rankers, the Magi of round. Her nickname is Charl. She manipulates a dragon-form automaton, Sigmund. She was the daughter of an Earl, but she`s been disowned for certain reasons. Her breasts are unfortunately faked with padding.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1445" picture="33610.jpg">Takamoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55863" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="10">6.06</rating>
<name>Sigmund</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He`s Charl`s automaton, and has the form of a four-winged dragon. Normally he`s small enough to fit under Charl`s hat or on her shoulder, but he grows in since when she pours magic into him. His magic circuit, Gram, possesses the powerful ability to annihilate any material it cuts. His favorite food is chicken.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55864" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="10">5.84</rating>
<name>Loki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He`s a sophomore with pearl white hair and crimson eyes. He manipulates Cherubim, an automaton produced by D-Works. He`s one of the Magi of round, and other students call him Sword Emperor with respect. He`s Frey`s younger brother.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55865" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="29">7.89</rating>
<name>Frey</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s a third year student whose unique traits are her pearl white hair and her crimson eyes. She has an ample bosom belying her delicate frame. She`s plotting Raishin`s assassination for certain reasons, but she`s kind at heart and she often fails due to her clumsiness. She manipulates Rabbi, one the Gram series automatons developed by D-Works. She`s Loki`s older sister.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57476" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="20">7.20</rating>
<name>Karyuusai Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The woman who lent Yaya to Raishin. She`s the greatest puppeteer of the current age and the one who produced Yaya and the rest of the Setsugetsuka Series. She`s a sexy woman who wears her kimono open around her large breasts, and she`s famous for her indulgences in wine and women.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57477" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="13">6.11</rating>
<name>Kimberley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She specializes in machinart physics as a professor at Walpurgis Royal Machinart Academy, and she`s in charge of Raishin. She researches the fundamental theories behind magic items, magic circuits. She quickly climbed her way to professor in this meritocratic academy. Apparently she considers herself an elite mage.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57478" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="18">6.29</rating>
<name>Komurasaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s one of Karyuusai Brand`s greatest automatons, the Flower in their Setsugetsuka Series. Her magic circuit, Yaegasumi posses the ability to shut off the targets sight, sound, and scent. She`s Yaya`s little sister and she calls Irori Onee-sama. She`s bright, freewheeling, and very friendly.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57479" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="20">6.75</rating>
<name>Irori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She`s one of Karyuusai Brand`s greatest automatons, the Snow in their Setsugetsuka Series. Her magic circuit Himokagami steals heat from around the target, creating a huge pillar of ice and freezing the very air. She`s the greatest of her sisters in simple offensive power and area control. She`s Yaya`s older sister, and she often scolds her.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58123" type="appears in" update="2013-12-26">
<rating votes="10">7.22</rating>
<name>Henriette Belew</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4616" picture="170439.jpg">Nishi Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58124" type="appears in" update="2013-11-12">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Cruel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58125" type="appears in" update="2013-12-26">
<rating votes="3">2.54</rating>
<name>Cedric Granville</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58126" type="appears in" update="2016-04-22">
<rating votes="1">4.27</rating>
<name>Felix Kingsfort</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58127" type="appears in" update="2016-04-22">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Lisette Norden</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58128" type="appears in" update="2013-12-26">
<name>Singh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58129" type="appears in" update="2013-12-09">
<rating votes="5">6.50</rating>
<name>Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58130" type="appears in" update="2013-10-29">
<rating votes="3">8.55</rating>
<name>Magnus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58224" type="appears in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="2">5.74</rating>
<name>Cherubim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The automaton manipulated by Loki. It possesses scant autonomy, so manipulation is difficult. It attacks with the twin blades on its forearms and excels at combat.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140575.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58225" type="appears in" update="2013-07-29">
<rating votes="2">7.09</rating>
<name>Rabbi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140573.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60272" type="appears in" update="2013-10-08">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60273" type="appears in" update="2013-10-08">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33633" picture="151771.jpg">Takahashi Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60896" type="appears in" update="2013-12-26">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Eliza (Lisette Norden)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60897" type="appears in" update="2013-10-29">
<rating votes="2">7.19</rating>
<name>Edward Rutherford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>144995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61142" type="appears in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Bronson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61143" type="appears in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<name>Akabane Nadeshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61437" type="appears in" update="2013-11-12">
<rating votes="2">7.19</rating>
<name>Yomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145771.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="494" picture="17485.jpg">Ichijou Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62199" type="appears in" update="2013-12-09">
<rating votes="4">5.04</rating>
<name>Charlotte Belew</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1445" picture="33610.jpg">Takamoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62592" type="appears in" update="2013-12-26">
<rating votes="3">5.46</rating>
<name>Alice Bernstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="150372" update="2013-05-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">AT-X PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">AT-X PV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 1 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154621" update="2015-12-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「機巧少女は傷つかない」一夜限りの夜会SP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Machine-Doll wa Kizutsukanai" Ichiyakagiri no Yakai SP</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154622" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Cannibal Candy" IV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Cannibal Candy" IV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Cannibal Candy" IV</title>
<summary>It`s time for the final battle with Cannibal Candy, but is Yaya too wounded to fight?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="154623" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Cannibal Candy" III</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Cannibal Candy" III</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Cannibal Candy" III</title>
<summary>Raishin and Yaya receive some unexpected visitors. Meanwhile, Felix and Charlotte each set out to capture Cannibal Candy, but their plans have irreconcilable differences.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="154624" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Cannibal Candy" II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Cannibal Candy" II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Cannibal Candy" II</title>
<summary>One of the Rounds makes Raishin an offer he can`t refuse. In exchange for a festival entry, he`ll have to investigate a mysterious puppeteer who eats automatons` hearts right out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="154625" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Cannibal Candy" I</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Cannibal Candy" I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Cannibal Candy" I</title>
<summary>Raishin Akabane, an exchange student from Japan, arrives at the Walpurgis Royal Academy of Machinart with a goal, use his beautiful automaton Yaya to become the world`s most powerful mage, gain access to the forbidden arts, and use them to kill a man.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="154851" update="2013-10-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155085" update="2014-06-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155204" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Sword Angel" IV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Sword Angel" IV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Sword Angel" IV</title>
<summary>Loki and Raishin form a hostile alliance--or something--to defeat the man who`s toying with them all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="155205" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Sword Angel" III</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Sword Angel" III</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Sword Angel" III</title>
<summary>With Raishin in intensive care hovering between life and death, brother and sister must battle each other on the second night of the festival.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="155206" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Sword Angel" II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Sword Angel" II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Sword Angel" II</title>
<summary>Raishin discovers the mystery behind Frey`s actions, but it`s not what he expected.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="155207" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Sword Angel" I</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Sword Angel" I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Sword Angel" I</title>
<summary>Raishin and Yaya come back from an exercise session to find a strange girl hanging from the ceiling of their room... and things only get weirder from there.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="156063" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Elf Speeder" IV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Elf Speeder" IV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Elf Speeder" IV</title>
<summary>One battle ends--but with the promise of many more in store.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="156064" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Elf Speeder" III</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Elf Speeder" III</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Elf Speeder" III</title>
<summary>Cedric and his butler are playing a game with no clear winners, and time is running out for Charlotte and Henriette.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="156065" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Elf Speeder" II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Elf Speeder" II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Elf Speeder" II</title>
<summary>Henriette and Raishin are trapped underground, with a cave-in threatening to happen at any moment. And as if that weren`t bad enough, someone else is lurking down there that nobody wants to be stuck in a small, enclosed space with...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="156066" update="2017-04-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Facing "Elf Speeder" I</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Facing "Elf Speeder" I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Facing "Elf Speeder" I</title>
<summary>Raishin learns about a troubled new transfer student, Charlotte`s acting strangely, and someone at the academy is under attack. With all that going on, can even a meddler extraordinaire like Raishin manage to help everyone?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="156946" update="2015-12-14">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">原作・海冬レイジ書き下ろし特典文庫原作OVA Vol.4「赤羽撫子, 夏の夜の夢」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nadeshiko Akabane, Midsummer Night`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensaku Kaitou Reiji Kakioroshi Tokuten Bunko Gensaku OVA Vol. 4: Akabane Nadeshiko, Natsu no Yo no Yume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156947" update="2015-12-14">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">原作・海冬レイジ書き下ろし特典文庫原作OVA Vol.3「シャルとフレイ, 戦慄のバスルーム」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charl, Frey, and the Bathroom of Terror</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensaku Kaitou Reiji Kakioroshi Tokuten Bunko Gensaku OVA Vol. 3: Charl to Frey, Senritsu no Bathroom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156948" update="2015-12-14">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">原作・海冬レイジ書き下ろし特典文庫原作OVA Vol.2「いろり, 露天風呂で粗相する」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Irori Has an Accident at the Open-Air Bath</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensaku Kaitou Reiji Kakioroshi Tokuten Bunko Gensaku OVA Vol. 2: Irori, Rotenburo de Sosou Suru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156949" update="2015-12-14">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">原作・海冬レイジ書き下ろし特典文庫原作OVA Vol.1「そして二人は学び舎へ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And So the Two Go to School</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensaku Kaitou Reiji Kakioroshi Tokuten Bunko Gensaku OVA Vol. 1: Soshite Futari wa Manabiya e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160443" update="2014-06-14">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160444" update="2014-06-14">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160536" update="2015-12-14">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">原作・海冬レイジ書き下ろし特典文庫原作OVA Vol.6「美少女集合! 水着だらけの大騒動」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pretty Girls Gather! Swimsuit-Studded Pandemonium</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensaku Kaitou Reiji Kakioroshi Tokuten Bunko Gensaku OVA Vol. 6: Bishoujo Shuugou! Mizugidarake no Ousoudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160537" update="2015-12-14">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">原作・海冬レイジ書き下ろし特典文庫原作OVA Vol.5「個人授業 ~医務室で美女ふたりと~」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Private Lesson: Two Beauties in an Infirmary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gensaku Kaitou Reiji Kakioroshi Tokuten Bunko Gensaku OVA Vol. 5: Kojin Jugyou Imushitsu de Bijo Futari to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161984" update="2014-08-11">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161985" update="2014-08-11">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161986" update="2014-08-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
