<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="100" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-04-11</startdate>
<enddate>2000-07-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Boys Be...</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Мальчишки есть мальчишки</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">爱情白皮书</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Boys Be</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">BOYS BE・・・</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Boys Be...</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Boys Be...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Boys Be...</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Boys Be...</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Boys Be...</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">วัยรุ่น วุ่นรัก</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6323" approval="12" total="14">Hatsukoi Limited</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.geneon-ent.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/boys/</url>
<creators>
<name id="754" type="Work">Hal Film Maker</name>
<name id="4138" type="Direction">Shimoda Masami</name>
<name id="6825" type="Character Design">Takeda Itsuko</name>
<name id="5961" type="Original Work">Tamakoshi Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="21904" type="Original Work">Itabashi Masahiro</name>
<name id="2323" type="Series Composition">Kanemaki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="754" type="Animation Work">Hal Film Maker</name>
</creators>
<description>Six High School students are about to embark on journey about love and life. http://anidb.net/ch17740 [Kyouichi] and http://anidb.net/ch17737 [Chiharu] have been childhood friends and suddenly their relationship is becoming more serious. http://anidb.net/ch17741 [Makoto] believes that his computer can help acquire love. http://anidb.net/ch17735 [Yoshihiko] is a talented baseball player, who is very unsure about himself. Chiharu`s friends http://anidb.net/ch17742 [Yumi] and http://anidb.net/ch17738 [Aki] are looking for a solution to their loneliness. The coming events will teach them serious life lesson.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1442">4.52</permanent>
<temporary count="1453">6.79</temporary>
<review count="6">6.96</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221926.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>105</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>84</identifier>
<identifier>felxno</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.geneon-ent.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/boys/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://boys-be.rightstuf.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Boys_Be...</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BOYS_BE…</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1609</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159783</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3696</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7166</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2678" parentid="2672" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Hokkaido</name>
<description>Hokkaido is the second largest island of Japan, and the largest and northernmost prefecture. The Tsugaru Strait separates Hokkaido from Honshu. The two islands are connected by the undersea railway Seikan Tunnel. The largest city on Hokkaido is its capital, Sapporo, which is also its only ordinance-designated city.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214292.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2753" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>track and field</name>
<description>A collection of sports events that involve running, throwing, and jumping.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="17735" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Kenjou Yoshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17736" type="appears in" update="2010-10-11">
<name>Sorimachi Takahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17737" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Nitta Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1983" picture="151694.jpg">Murai Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17738" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Mizutani Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17739" type="appears in" update="2012-02-12">
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17740" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="1">2.83</rating>
<name>Kanzaki Kyouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17741" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<name>Kurumizawa Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17742" type="main character in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="1">2.83</rating>
<name>Kazama Yumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29912" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Sayama Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29913" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Ueno Tsuyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29914" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Kurihara Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29915" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Morio Junna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4840" picture="77799.jpg">Komatsu Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29916" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Nitta Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9689" picture="36176.jpg">Ishibashi Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29917" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Horikawa Natsue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3294" picture="223278.jpg">Mizuno Manabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29918" type="appears in" update="2011-03-12">
<name>Takano Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49237" type="appears in" update="2012-09-23">
<name>Kawai Erika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49252" type="appears in" update="2012-09-23">
<rating votes="1">7.65</rating>
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49253" type="appears in" update="2012-09-23">
<name>Fujiki Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="542" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眠れない夜を抱いて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Autumn - Solitary Cross</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Serre-moi dans tes bras que je m`endorme...</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Abbracciando la notte insonne.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemurenai Yoru o Daite</title>
<summary>At night Kyouichi has strange dreams and wonders whether they indicate his loneliness. Makoto has a simpler name for this feeling: "need girlfriend syndrome".
At his school`s arts club Kyouichi meets Yokota-senpai who just completed a marvelous drawing of an inconspicuous female classmate whom he obviously adores. Suddenly Kyouichi becomes aware that they are colleagues at his part-time job at a video shop. The two young artists start to talk; Yokota confesses he never even had a girlfriend before, and Makoto tells Yokota about Kyouichi just having been dumped.
Soon Kyouichi and Yokota are spending a lot of time together, alienating Makoto formidably: Are these two boys starting a weird romance?</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="543" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">太陽がまた輝くとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer - Feeling Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand le soleil est au zénith</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il periodo della grande pesca.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiyou ga Mata Kagayaku Toki</title>
<summary>Makoto and Kyouichi are on their way to the sea for a holiday job at the Marine House Nitta, run by Chiharu`s older cousin Daisuke.
At the inn they are welcomed by a shy but beautiful girl who turns out to be Chiharu`s cousin Nao. Makoto is trying to have a go on her, only to learn how jealous Daisuke can become.
Burning hanabi at night, Aki and Yumi tell the boys about Nao`s frail health - that`s why she is always alone and hiding from the sun.
On the next day Nao walks to the beach with her parasol - and Yumi and Aki meet her just in time to see her fainting.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="544" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界中の微笑みを集めてもかなわない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Early Summer - Bitter Sweet Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tous les sourires du monde n`y changeront rien</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Irrealizzabile, nemmeno con tutti i sorrisi del mondo.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekaijuu no Hohoemi o Atsumete mo Kanawanai</title>
<summary>The girls are talking about "friendship and beyond", browsing Aki`s middle school photo album. On one photo Aki looked particularly angry but she won`t tell her friends what happened back then, and insists on going to the karaoke box instead.
On their way through the rain they meet a boy taking photographs of flowers; Aki is surprised to meet him there. "Ueno - my ex-boyfriend", she explains to her friends later. Which brings back memories of the time when they had to make the middle school graduation album together and he fell in love with the rain, right when she was falling in love with him.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="545" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天然恋愛ノススメ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring - After Kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le baiser</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`evoluzione di un amor sbocciato.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tennen Ren`ai no Susume</title>
<summary>At the baseball training the coaches are talking about talented but lazy Yoshihiko who might have become the leader of the team long ago if he even cared. Yoshihiko`s next hit is a major foul, driving the ball into an open window of the school library. While searching the library for the lost ball he knocks against some ladder, and the girl standing on it, just trying to put a book back onto the uppermost shelf, is falling down ... but Yoshihiko manages to catch her before she can hit the ground. And just moments later he`s rewarded with a kiss!</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="546" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙の天使に微笑みを</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Smile to the Tearful Angel: Memorial Essence</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Redonner le sourire à un ange</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un sorriso per l`angelo in lacrime.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida no Tenshi ni Hohoemi o</title>
<summary>Watching a kissing scene in TV while cooking for his mother`s restaurant (and destroying the frying pan in the process), watching a cute girl while driving back on his scooter with the freshly purchased replacement pan - only to awake in hospital... you can say this just wasn`t Makoto`s day: His hand-held is broken and his girls` database is gone as well.
In the hospital Makoto gets interested in the cute nurse apprentice Mizuki and starts to hit on her, with the help of a young girl named Lisa-chan, a patient like himself who knows the nurse quite well already. But the present he gives to Mizuki backfires completely.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="547" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サクラ・フワリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light Shower of Cherry Blossoms: Cherry-Blossoms</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cerisiers en fleurs</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La danza dei ciliegi.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura Fuwari</title>
<summary>Aki tells her friends about a cute boy she met on her way to school who might become her new love, but neither Yumi nor Chiharu are impressed by her story.
Later, Chiharu visits the place of her childhood friend Kyouichi, and her behavior (as well as a little teasing by Makoto`s older sister Sayaka) almost turns the boy`s head. After a little incident with Chiharu`s skirt, Sayaka orders Kyouichi to walk Chiharu home, and suddenly the boy has to face a strange question.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="548" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">幸せのカテゴリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Autumn - Leaves</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille idéale</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Le categorie della felicità.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase no Category</title>
<summary>Makoto is updating his database of "girls specifications" as his new "secret weapon" software will allow him to find the best match for himself. In fact the machine spits out the name of "Erika", the girl voted most popular attendee at the school festival. But Yumi tells him he`s absolutely not Erika`s type as the two girls have been friends since junior high.
Yumi`s specification is missing in Makoto`s database - he wouldn`t waste time to collect data about girls below "B rank". When Yumi detects hentai pictures on this hand-held the machine`s life span turns out to be surprisingly short. Now Yumi has to make up for the damage she caused, by arranging a date between Erika and Makoto.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="549" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">軌跡の果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Next Season - Let it Be</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au bout du chemin</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il limite delle traccie.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Hate</title>
<summary>While Chiharu is cramming for her university application, Kyouichi has traveled to Hokkaido in his summer holidays. Right after his arrival he literally runs into an attractive blond girl who offers him to take him along on her motorbike.
Kyouichi soon learns this girl is creating and selling wooden carvings. She constantly teases the naive boy, inventing ever new stories about her former boyfriend, and inviting Kyouichi to stay at her studio. But at the same time she can understand him very well, being a fellow artist - and she can read his drawings in a way Kyouichi couldn`t do by himself. And her name is "Chiharu".</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="550" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">輪舞~十六夜月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Autumn - Swallow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La lune, la nuit du 16</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Rondo` luna d`autunno.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rinbu - Izayoi Tsuki</title>
<summary>Kyouichi and Makoto notice their classmate Sayama Shouko listening to music (via headset) at class and getting very upset when the teacher confiscates her music player.
When Kyouichi is able to help an irate Shouko getting a drink from the school`s malfunctioning vending machine they start talking about music and some band whose singer retired and Shouko mulls over applying for the position. Shouko invites Kyouichi to join a concert of her own band tonight, and later on a special nightly excursion.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="551" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">1000年の誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Winter - End to Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les vœux du millénaire</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il giuramento dei mille anni.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sennen no Chikai</title>
<summary>Two days before the millennium is coming to an end, the boys are talking about how Nostradamus` prophecies were totally off the year before, and how much has happened since then.
Meanwhile, lots of rumors are spreading, such as: "If you`re together with the one you love at the end of the millennium then your love will grow." which is what Natsue read in a magazine and tells Yoshihiko. At the same time, Makoto and Yumi look up a rumor in the Internet claiming that "If you`re together with the one you love at the end of the millennium then you two will eventually part."
And Aki happens to read that Nostradamus foretold the collapse of the world on December 31st, 2000.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="552" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の終わり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer - Wind-Bell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin de l`été</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La fine dell`estate.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Owari</title>
<summary>During her summer training camp for track&amp;field Chiharu loses her way in the forest. Right when a giant beetle settles down on her back, a young man collecting beetles frees her from the unwanted guest and shows her the way back to her camp. But Chiharu can`t stand the pushy behavior of this show-off cabriolet driver, introducing himself as Okasagi Yuki.
Aki and Yumi visit Chiharu at the camp, telling her how comfortable their holidays at the sea together with Makoto and Kyouichi had been. Which brings back uncomfortable memories for Chiharu about her argument with Kyouichi... and during her next training race she loses concentration, stumbles - and falls.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="553" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬が来る前に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Autumn - First Snowfall</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Avant que ne vienne l`hiver</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Prima che arrivi l`inverno.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyu ga Kuru Mae ni</title>
<summary>Yoshihiko decides to go shopping alone - and he`s run over by a beautiful woman in a Santa dress! Everyone but Yoshihiko would have recognized her as the famous idol Morio Junna; as to escape the crowd immediately formed about these two, "Mori-Jun" addresses Yoshihiko as her manager and drags him away with her.
Mori-Jun can`t believe the boy never heard of her before. They grab a bite at a fast-food restaurant, but then one of Mori-Jun`s commercials is shown there on the screen. Mori-Jun asks Yoshihiko to accompany her but he`s still unimpressed about "dating an idol". Then Mori-Jun runs away with Yoshihiko`s jacket.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="554" update="2011-11-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">青空をあげたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer - Baseball Lovers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je veux toucher le ciel bleu</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Voglio darti il cielo azzurro.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aozora o Agetai</title>
<summary>Yoshihiko spends his time in the arcade instead of practicing, much to the annoyance of his baseball coach. Brought back to the sports field by the assistant coach, Yoshihiko suddenly faces a challenge by his exact counterpart, female team manager Horikawa who prefers baseball practice over a third meal every day. It`s just that no one had the guts so far to tell Horikawa that the finals at the Koushien stadium will be nothing but a dream for her as female players aren`t allowed in the league.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="85805" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsukoi</title>
<summary>All main characters are at their respective homes, some of them calling each other via telephone, while a radio show airs an interview with http://anidb.net/ch29912 [Sayama Shouko-san] from SAIL who then performs "http://anidb.net/s5096 [Hatsukoi]" (a song about a http://anidb.net/ch17740 [boy] who fell in love with a http://anidb.net/ch17737 [female track&amp;field athlete] but is unable to get his feelings across to her), to a collection of highlight scenes of the anime series.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108645" update="2009-09-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108646" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-04-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121091" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121092" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121093" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
