<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10022" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-12-31</startdate>
<enddate>2013-12-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sword Art Online: Extra Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Sword Art Online EE - Die Unterwasser-Quest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SAOEE</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ソードアート・オンライン Extra Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">Sword Art Online Extra Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sword Art Online: Extra Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Sword Art Online Extra Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Sword Art Online Ex</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">هنر شمشیرزنی آنلاین: ویرایش اضافی</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10376" type="Sequel">Sword Art Online II</anime>
<anime id="8692" type="Prequel">Sword Art Online</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="71837">Just a recap.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="371670">Basically a recap with an extra new scene which starts around 1h20min. Watch it since then if you don`t want to waste time. ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="403846">The recap is nice before S2, but the extra "episode" at the end just flat out sucked.

Only recommended for those who have seen S1 and are going to watch S2. To freshen up the memory :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="33154">Yes it`s a recap but with an extra story that was not in the light novel that I have read.

Then again this is a prep for those who haven`t seen the first SAO and wish to see SAO II that is going to come out which cover Phantom Bullet and Mother`s Rosario arcs.

So if you want to watch SAO II and don`t want to go back to watch SAO (which I wouldn`t know why you wouldn`t) then at less watch this first.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="382820">Pretty nice recap with some new stuff at the last 20minutes, i thinks its a great watch and gets you really pumped ab for SAO2</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="139484">Just a recap with some talks among the girls as reflection on their memories...   that 20 mins long new scene, the underwater quest at the end isnt in the light novels, so its just totally random.
Only for those who wanna knoew something about the 1st season of SAO before the 2nd season.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.swordart-online.net/extra</url>
<creators>
<name id="1303" type="Animation Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="8899" type="Character Design">Adachi Shingo</name>
<name id="28670" type="Original Work">Kawahara Reki</name>
<name id="8899" type="Chief Animation Direction">Adachi Shingo</name>
<name id="704" type="Music">Kajiura Yuki</name>
<name id="8068" type="Direction">Itou Tomohiko</name>
</creators>
<description>Kirito and the others decide to go on an underwater quest within the world of ALO to grant Yui her wish to see a whale. As they all prepare for the quest, they face a shocking revelation... Leafa (Suguha) is afraid of water. So, Asuna and the other female members decide to teach Suguha how to swim at a pool in the real world. Meanwhile, Kirito was meeting somebody...
Source: Aniplex</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2515">4.00</permanent>
<temporary count="2533">6.34</temporary>
<review count="1">6.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>151778.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15743</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21879</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20021</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.swordart-online.net/extra</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sword_Art_Online#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ソードアート・オンライン#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2588</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16669</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>SwordArtUSA</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>sao_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sword-art-online</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2467" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-22">
<name>sword</name>
<description>A sword is a long, edged piece of metal, used as a cutting, thrusting, and clubbing weapon in many civilizations throughout the world. Before firearms became commonplace, and fast enough to render other weapons pointless in the battlefield, they were the main kind of weapon for war and duels alike. A sword fundamentally consists of a blade and a hilt, typically with one or two edges for striking and cutting, and a point for thrusting. That aside, however, they may come in all sorts of designs: the medieval European swords used to be big, heavy weapons that did not actually cut but instead broke the enemy`s bones under their armor; conversely, the Chinese jian sword (called "ken" in Japanese) attempted to exploit the armor`s joints and perforate the enemy`s flesh in those places, but was useless against the armor itself, and did not take the strikes, preferring to redirect them, to this day being considered a highly "circular" weapon and associated to taijiquan; on the other hand, the Japanese katana was a balanced all-purposes weapon that could be used even in an axe-like way, but which a master swordsman could use in many other, more elaborate manners.</description>
<picurl>127113.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3097" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-29">
<name>underwater</name>
<description>Underwater is a term describing the realm below the surface of water where the water exists in a natural feature such as an ocean, sea, lake, pond, or river.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4379" parentid="6090" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>Yggdrasil</name>
<description>In Norse mythology, Yggdrasil (/ˈɪɡdrəsɪl/ or /ˈɪɡdrəzɪl/; from Old Norse Yggdrasill, pronounced [ˈyɡːˌdrasilː]) is an immense tree that is central in Norse cosmology, in connection to which the nine worlds exist.
This anime contains a system or other-worldly existence, based on Norse mythology, called Yggdrasil.</description>
<picurl>169458.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4462" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>barefoot</name>
<description>This character never seems to wear any shoes — possibly a martial artist that prefers to stay in close contact with the ground, or a girl from the country now living in the city.
Alas, under more dire circumstances this can also be a sign of real poverty.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6090" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Norse mythology</name>
<description>Norse mythology, or Scandinavian mythology, is the body of mythology of the North Germanic people stemming from Norse paganism and continuing after the Christianization of Scandinavia and into the Scandinavian folklore of the modern period. The Norse mythology consists of tales of various deities, beings, and heroes derived from numerous sources from both before and after the pagan period, including medieval manuscripts, archaeological representations, and folk tradition. [...]
Most of the surviving mythology centres on the plights of the gods and their interaction with various other beings, such as humanity and the jötnar, beings who may be friends, lovers, foes and/or family members of the gods. The cosmos in Norse mythology consist of Nine Worlds that flank a central cosmological tree, Yggdrasil. Units of time and elements of the cosmology are personified as deities or beings. [...]
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="37272" type="main character in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="476">6.84</rating>
<name>Asuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend of Kirito and is a sub-leader of the guild Knights of Blood (KoB), a medium-sized guild of about thirty player, also called the strongest guild in Aincrad. Being one of the few many girls that play SAO, and even more so that she`s extremely pretty, she receives many invitations and proposals. She is a skilled player earning the Title "Flash" for her extraordinary sword skill. The KoB has assigned her two bodyguards, one of whom despises Kirito. Her game alias is the same as her Real World name. She later on falls in love with Kirito, eventually leading to them being married.</description>
<picture>83185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37273" type="main character in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="395">5.84</rating>
<name>Kirito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main protagonist of the series. He is the protagonist and is a "solo" player, a player who hasn`t joined a guild and usually works alone. When it is announced that the players of Sword Art Online can no longer logout, he is surprised like everyone else, but unlike everyone else he quickly gets over it and accepts it, to an extent. He mainly uses a one-handed sword and usually wears all black in game, as it adds to stealth. He can also use two blades at once, a unique skill to him and he only uses it in emergencies to avoid attention for being one out of the two people to have unique skills. His game alias is Kirito, which is created by taking the syllables of the first and last Kanji of his real last and first names respectively: (Kirigaya Kazuto). In the real world, he lives with his mother and younger sister in a family of 3.</description>
<picture>83186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39515" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="98">5.45</rating>
<name>Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Originally a side story character in SAO, Yui later becomes an accompanying/support character in ALO. At first thought to be a lost child in SAO, she is actually an artificial intelligence program. Her full designation is «Mental Health - Counselling Program», MHCP version 1, codename, «Yui». She was designed to monitor the emotions of players and appear at their sides to hear and help them out. However, since the moment everyone was imprisoned in Sword Art Online, she was forbidden to come in contact with the players and complete her prime directive. Unable to do anything but suffer as she monitored the emotions of the trapped players, she came upon Kirito and Asuna whose emotions stood out as a beacon of joy and peace in a sea of fear and despair. She sought them out, appearing to them as an amnesia child whom they adopted. In the end she was nearly deleted by Cardinal, the management system of SAO. But Kirito saved her by converting and storing her data into his own Nerve Gear. Yui later shows up in ALO as a Private Navigation Pixie and helps Kirito along with Leafa to find Asuna. She refers to Kirito as "Papa" and Asuna as "Mama" and gets very annoyed if any girl other than Shinon, Leafa or Asuna gets close to Kirito.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>94193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39516" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="156">6.18</rating>
<name>Leafa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Leafa is Suguha`s avatar in Alfheim Online.</description>
<picture>126802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41185" type="appears in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="130">5.36</rating>
<name>Silica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Silica (in real world Ayano Keiko) is a side story character in SAO. She is one of the rare beast tamers in the game. Very early in the game, she was able to tame a small dragon, Pina, who becomes her only real friend in the game; this feat gave her immense fame, but she was just a mid-level player. Due to her fame and being a girl, many tried to get on her good side, causing her to get a bit of an inflated head. She usually stay away from the males, who tried to marry her despite the fact that she was only 13. After getting lost in a forest, she lost Pina to a monster attack. Kirito rescued and helped her, as she resembled his sister, and helps her revive Pina. She gained feelings for him, but once she realized his skills, she realized that they could never be together in the game.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>87804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41186" type="appears in" update="2014-04-03">
<rating votes="114">6.00</rating>
<name>Lisbeth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A side story character in SAO, who is a blacksmith with her own shop. Lisbeth or "Liz" is a close friend of Asuna who recommended her to Kirito. Kirito commissioned Liz to forge a custom-made sword for him and accompanies her in a quest for the special ore required for the job. During the quest, she also develops feelings for Kirito. She is devastated when she finds out that Kirito is Asuna`s crush. However, she finds some solace after Kirito thanks her for giving him a renewed determination to fight on and clear the game. Liz later becomes a regular player in ALO, and frequently joins Kirito and his friends in quests and takes up the task of upgrading their equipment.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>85684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43410" type="appears in" update="2019-12-06">
<rating votes="33">5.23</rating>
<name>Sachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A side story character in SAO. She was a member of "Black Cats of the Night" which was the first guild Kirito joined. Kirito was especially attached to her. However she died along with the majority of her guild members which led to Kirito wallowing in despair and self-loathing until he read the time delayed message she left for Kirito. Even after the message gave him the strength to live, he never joined another guild until he parties with Asuna.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>85683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43411" type="appears in" update="2016-06-15">
<rating votes="48">5.20</rating>
<name>Agil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bald axe wielder who owns a shop in SAO. Agil is 180 cm tall with a muscular build. Despite his intimidating appearance, he is kind-hearted and spent most of his earnings to help players in the middle floors. Kirito is a regular in his shop and they are friends. Agil runs a shop named "Dicey Cafe" in the real world, which was run by his wife during his two-year coma. The cafe later becomes Kazuto and company`s meeting place in the real world.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>85681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43412" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="39">3.46</rating>
<name>Kayaba Akihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kayaba Akihiko is the Director and creator of the Nerve Gear and Sword Art Online, as well as the main antagonist of the Sword Art Online arc. He traps all the players within Sword Art Online by using the Nerve Gear to cease sending signals to the users` body. Any in-game death or attempt at removal of the Nerve Gear would result in the real life death of the user. Later, it is discovered that he has been masquerading as Heathcliff, the leader of the Knights of the Blood Oath. Although he has the admin powers to make his avatar immortal, he is shown to be a powerful player even without his in-game immortality due to his intimate understanding of the SAO game mechanics which he himself had designed. He is defeated by Kirito at the end SAO arc, and at the end of ALO arc, leaves behind a program that grants Kirito the World Seed. His death was his own doing since he had also rigged his own Nerve Gear device to fry his brain when he was defeated and transferring his soul into a digital form.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>85680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43413" type="appears in" update="2018-10-31">
<rating votes="79">5.92</rating>
<name>Klein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Klein (in real world Tsuboi Ryoutarou) is a friendly player that meets Kirito at the start of the game, who quickly befriends and learns from Kirito. They go their separate ways shortly after when Kirito leaves for another town to power level, while Klein remains behind to help out his less experienced friends. Klein uses a katana to fight and later becomes a leader of his own guild. He regularly meets with Kirito and his friends and occasionally joins them in quests in ALO, especially after the release of the World Seed.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>85682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46770" type="appears in" update="2014-04-13">
<rating votes="10">4.03</rating>
<name>Kayaba Akihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kayaba Akihiko`s avatar in the official opening of SAO, when he declared it to be a death game.</description>
<picture>90677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46771" type="main character in" update="2018-11-01">
<rating votes="140">5.07</rating>
<name>Kirigaya Kazuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirigaya Kazuto, who uses the portmanteau "Kirito" as his character name, is a "solo" player who has been branded a "beater" (a combination of beta tester and cheater) by the players in Sword Art Online. When Kayaba announces that the players of Sword Art Online can no longer log-out without clearing the game, he quickly overcomes the shock. He power-levels to improve his odds of survival in the game, and emerges as a frontline floor-clearer known as the Black Swordsman. In SAO, he is the sole «Dual Blades» skill user. During his time in SAO, he falls in love with a female player, Asuna, and even marries her in-game.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>126810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46772" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="33">3.44</rating>
<name>Kirito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirigaya Kazuto`s first avatar in SAO. Was changed to his real appearance by special mirror item prepared by Kayaba Akihiko.</description>
<picture>90679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46773" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="15">4.30</rating>
<name>Klein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Klein`s first avatar in SAO. Was changed to his real appearance by special mirror item prepared by Kayaba Akihiko.</description>
<picture>90680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46906" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="158">5.93</rating>
<name>Kirigaya Suguha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suguha, alias Leafa, is Kirito`s younger cousin in the real world. She is a diligent worker and has been practicing Kendo for 8 years. Kirito/Kazuto calls her "Sugu". After Kazuto gets trapped in Sword Art Online, she begins playing Alfheim Online in an attempt to understand him better. She develops feelings for Kazuto after she learns that he is not really her brother, but understands that his feelings for Asuna are too strong. Coincidentally, she meets Kazuto`s avatar, Kirito, in Alfheim and aids him in his search for Asuna, unaware of Kirito`s true identity. After understanding the depth of Kazuto`s love for Asuna, she resolves to give up on him and instead becomes attached to Kirito in ALO, but later is heartbroken when she finds out that Kazuto and Kirito are one and the same. Nevertheless, she pulls herself together and aids Kirito in rescuing Asuna.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>126809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46907" type="appears in" update="2014-04-13">
<rating votes="11">1.70</rating>
<name>Kibaou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kibaou is an avatar of one of new players in Sword Art Online. He hates ex beta testers, as he claims it was their fault so many players died during the first month of the game.
Later on he becomes involved in Aincrad Liberation Force guild, even becoming its sub leader.</description>
<picture>90982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46908" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="12">3.95</rating>
<name>Diabel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Beta tester in SAO. He organized a raid group to defeat 1st level boss Illfang the Kobold Lord, but was killed by him in the process.</description>
<picture>90983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47117" type="appears in" update="2012-07-22">
<rating votes="6">5.47</rating>
<name>Tsukiyo no Kuroneko-dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Tsukiyo no Kuroneko-dan is a mid-level guild in Sword Art Online, formed with members of the same computer club in school. It was destroyed when most of its members were killed in an anti-crystal field and alarm trap, while the leader committed suicide after learning of his comrades death.
Source: Wikia</description>
<picture>91313.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47143" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="11">4.91</rating>
<name>Illfang the Kobold Lord</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Main boss of 1st level in SAO. Defeated by raid group including Kirito, Asuna and Egil.</description>
<picture>91315.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47146" type="appears in" update="2014-04-13">
<rating votes="7">6.57</rating>
<name>Ketsumei Kishidan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Knights of Blood is a guild in SAO established by Heathcliff. It is considered one of the strongest guilds consisting only of clearers - players fighting on the front lines.</description>
<picture>93345.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47148" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="4">6.04</rating>
<name>Fuurinkazan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Guild started by Klein in SAO.</description>
<picture>149933.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47349" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="33">7.95</rating>
<name>Pina</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blue Feather Dragon befriended by Silica. As her familiar Pina posses healing and scanning abilities.</description>
<picture>91654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47537" type="appears in" update="2018-12-09">
<rating votes="8">2.70</rating>
<name>Caynz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ex member of http://anidb.net/ch47739 [Golden Apple] guild and boyfriend of http://anidb.net/ch47538 [Yolko].</description>
<picture>91964.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47538" type="appears in" update="2018-12-09">
<rating votes="13">3.88</rating>
<name>Yolko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ex member of http://anidb.net/ch47739 [Golden Apple] guild and girlfriend of http://anidb.net/ch47537 [Caynz].</description>
<picture>91963.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47739" type="appears in" update="2018-12-09">
<rating votes="3">2.24</rating>
<name>Ougon Ringo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Small guild in SAO established by http://anidb.net/ch47740 [Griselda]. It consisted of 8 members, and was disbanded after Griselda`s death.</description>
<picture>92318.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48169" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="17">1.89</rating>
<name>Kuradeel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Two-Handed Sword user. Publicly a member of "Knights of the Blood Oath" and secretly a member of the red guild "Laughing Coffin". He was officially assigned as Asuna`s bodyguard and despite his grudge develops an obsession with Asuna and begins secretly following her everywhere. When he sees that Kirito and Asuna are developing a relationship, he challenges Kirito to a duel over who can protect her. Kirito wins and Kuradeel is forced to leave. He later tries to murder Kirito and then Asuna, but is instead killed by Kirito using an unarmed skill.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>92980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48170" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="11">5.31</rating>
<name>The Gleam Eyes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Main boss of 74th level of Labyrinth in SAO. He was defeated almost singlehandedly by Kirito using his exclusive Dual Wield skill.</description>
<picture>92981.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48396" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="24">5.15</rating>
<name>Heathcliff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kayaba Akihiko`s avatar in SAO.</description>
<picture>93344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48599" type="appears in" update="2016-06-15">
<rating votes="10">3.39</rating>
<name>Godfree</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Godfree was a commander of front team in "Knights of Blood Oath" guild in SAO. He was killed by Kuradeel during an attempt to take Kirito`s life.</description>
<picture>93746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48918" type="appears in" update="2016-06-15">
<rating votes="5">3.13</rating>
<name>Ginn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginn is Sasha`s protege living with her and other youngest players in Town of Beginnings on the 1st level of Aincrad. He is one of the three oldest children, who hunt monsters to be able to pay the rent and buy food for the whole group.</description>
<picture>149928.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48919" type="appears in" update="2014-04-10">
<rating votes="5">3.13</rating>
<name>Kain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kain is Sasha`s protege living with her and other youngest players in Town of Beginnings on the 1st level of Aincrad. He is one of the three oldest children, who hunt monsters to be able to pay the rent and buy food for the whole group.</description>
<picture>149929.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48920" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="10">4.43</rating>
<name>Sasha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sasha is a caretaker of the younger players of SAO in Town of Beginnings on the 1st level.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>94195.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="48921" type="appears in" update="2014-04-10">
<rating votes="9">3.65</rating>
<name>Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mina is Sasha`s protege living with her and other youngest players in Town of Beginnings on the 1st level of Aincrad. She is one of the three oldest children, who hunt monsters to be able to pay the rent and buy food for the whole group.</description>
<picture>94194.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49229" type="appears in" update="2016-06-15">
<rating votes="8">2.74</rating>
<name>Thinker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Thinker`s avatar in SAO. Thinker is the one who established Aincrad Liberation Force guild widely known as The Army.</description>
<picture>94743.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49230" type="appears in" update="2014-04-13">
<rating votes="13">4.60</rating>
<name>Yulier</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Assistant to Sinker, the leader of Aincrad Liberation Force.</description>
<picture>94742.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49232" type="appears in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="2">3.08</rating>
<name>Aincrad Kaihougun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Guild started by http://anidb.net/ch49229 [Thinker] in SAO.</description>
<picture>149930.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49824" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="127">6.10</rating>
<name>Asuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuna as shown in Alfheim Online as Titania the Fairy Queen.</description>
<picture>126806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49825" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="115">4.57</rating>
<name>Kirito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirito as shown in Alfheim Online as Spriggan Fairy.</description>
<picture>126807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49826" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="68">1.21</rating>
<name>Sugou Nobuyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nobuyuki Sugou is the main antagonist of the Alfheim Online arc. He is the one responsible for keeping 300 Nerve Gear victims, including Asuna, prisoner even after SAO had ended. He did this by transferring them all into ALO for experiments on human subjugation via fulldive technology. He also attempts to take over RCT Progress Inc. by marrying Asuna while she is unconscious. He displays a perverse interest in consummating this marriage while Asuna is still comatose. In ALO, he takes on the identity of Oberon the Fairy King and makes Asuna his queen, Titania. When he and Kirito finally meet, he flaunts his GM status as well as the results of his research by causing Kirito immense amounts of pain after increasing Kirito`s pain limit and impaling him. He is defeated when the "Ghost Program" of Akihiko Kayaba reminded Kirito how he was defeated by Kirito`s determination, before aiding him in overcoming Nobuyuki`s GM status. All 300 victims are released from ALO, but Nobuyuki makes another attempt to attack Kirito while he is making his way to Asuna in the real world. However, he is once again subdued by Kirito, who puts the unarmed combat skills he had learned in SAO to useful effect. Nobuyuki is then arrested and charged for his crimes.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>126808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49827" type="appears in" update="2015-02-25">
<rating votes="107">5.98</rating>
<name>Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yui as shown in ALO as a Private Navigation Pixie.</description>
<picture>169437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49857" type="main character in" update="2019-06-29">
<rating votes="204">6.93</rating>
<name>Yuuki Asuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuki Asuna is Asuna`s name in the real world.</description>
<picture>156375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49858" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="12">4.25</rating>
<name>Kirigaya Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kirigaya Midori is Suguha`s mother, as well as Kirito`s aunt and foster mother in the real world. She cares deeply for both her children.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>126841.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49859" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="7">3.32</rating>
<name>Yuuki Shouzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuki Shouzou is Asuna`s father and CEO of RCT Progress Inc.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>126842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="245665.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49983" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="18">2.08</rating>
<name>Recon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Recon (Nagata Shin`ichi in real world) is Suguha`s classmate. He introduced ALO to Suguha who asked him about VRMMO. In ALO, he is a Sylph dagger wielder and dark mage. He also displays an obvious romantic interest in Suguha, although the feelings are not mutual.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>127064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49985" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="6">4.25</rating>
<name>Kagemune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagemune is an Salamander player at ALO. He leads lancers team. While he attempts to hunt Leafa, his squad is taken down by Kirito. After Kirito`s fight with Eugene, he lied about an Undine being in the party that wiped the party he led the day before, in order to support Kirito`s story and convinced Eugene to believe that Kirito was an ambassador of a supposed Undine and Spriggan alliance.</description>
<picture>127066.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="49986" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="34">5.96</rating>
<name>Sakuya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakuya is the leader of Sylph in ALO. During a meeting with the Cait Sith, she is attacked by Salamanders led by General Eugene. At the same moment, Kirito flies in to challenge the general to a duel. After Kirito wins the battle, she attempts to seduce him along with Alicia Rue. Leafa smothers their attempt, saying that she is accompanying him to the World Tree. At the end of the arc, Lady Sakuya leads a combined force of Cait Sith and Sylph against the World Tree`s Guardians in an attempt to aid Kirito with the battle. After Kirito reached the top of the World Tree, she ordered her forces to pull back.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>127067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49987" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="32">6.25</rating>
<name>Alicia Luu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alicia Luu is the leader of Cait Sith in ALO.</description>
<picture>127068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49988" type="appears in" update="2016-06-16">
<rating votes="35">1.26</rating>
<name>Oberon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sugou Nobuyuki`s avatar in ALO.</description>
<picture>127069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50685" type="appears in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="15">4.52</rating>
<name>Eugene</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eugene is second in command of Salamanders in ALO as well as brother of their leader. He is considered strongest fighter in ALO, but is defeated by Kirito using his SAO Dual Wield skill.</description>
<picture>128248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51225" type="appears in" update="2012-12-10">
<rating votes="19">4.80</rating>
<name>Kirigaya Kazuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129277.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51226" type="appears in" update="2012-12-10">
<rating votes="25">6.53</rating>
<name>Kirigaya Suguha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51578" type="appears in" update="2015-01-20">
<rating votes="116">5.99</rating>
<name>Asuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Asuna`s avatar in Alfheim Online.</description>
<picture>167715.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51579" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="47">4.91</rating>
<name>Shinozaki Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinozaki Rika is Lisbeth`s name in the real world.</description>
<picture>129831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51580" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-10">
<rating votes="56">4.94</rating>
<name>Ayano Keiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayano Keiko is Silica`s name in the real world.</description>
<picture>129832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51590" type="appears in" update="2016-06-15">
<rating votes="22">3.80</rating>
<name>Agil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Agil`s avatar in Alfheim Online.</description>
<picture>148012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51591" type="appears in" update="2014-06-05">
<rating votes="54">5.58</rating>
<name>Silica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Silica`s avatar in Alfheim Online.</description>
<picture>156373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51592" type="appears in" update="2014-06-05">
<rating votes="59">5.51</rating>
<name>Lisbeth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lisbeth`s avatar in Alfheim Online.</description>
<picture>156374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51593" type="appears in" update="2015-01-20">
<rating votes="32">4.42</rating>
<name>Klein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Klein`s avatar in Alfheim Online.</description>
<picture>167714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62759" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-02">
<rating votes="35">3.54</rating>
<name>Kikuoka Seijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kikuoka Seijirou is a member of the Ministry of Internal Affairs and Communications, Technology, Second Separated Advanced Network Division, or Virtual Division.
Source: SAO wikia</description>
<picture>147999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62770" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<rating votes="5">4.92</rating>
<name>Counseling no Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62771" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<rating votes="1">3.08</rating>
<name>Nerakk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3273" picture="239376.jpg">Hazama Michio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62772" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<rating votes="3">2.36</rating>
<name>Kraken the Abyss Lord</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3273" picture="239376.jpg">Hazama Michio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62773" type="appears in" update="2014-01-02">
<rating votes="2">3.57</rating>
<name>Leviathan the Sea Lord</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82562" type="appears in" update="2016-06-15">
<rating votes="3">3.08</rating>
<name>Laughing Coffin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Laughing Coffin is an infamous Player Killing orange guild in «Sword Art Online», but due to the intensity of their Player Killing activity, are dubbed by the players as a "red guild".</description>
<picture>63894.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="82605" type="appears in" update="2016-06-17">
<rating votes="4">3.20</rating>
<name>Armachthys</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Armachthys is a monster found in the Undersea Temple in ALfheim Online.</description>
<picture>187729.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="154807" update="2014-04-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2013-12-31</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
<summary>Kazuto and Suguha meet with Asuna, Rika and Keiko at their high school where the latter trio had agreed to teach Suguha how to swim, in preparation for an Alfheim quest that they are planning to undertake. Meanwhile, Kazuto makes his way to the counseling office where he meets with Seijiro Kikuoka, a member of the Ministry of Internal Affairs. While investigating the SAO incident, Kikouka has Kazuto relate his experience so that he can unearth a firm grasp on Kayaba Akihiko`s motives while also forcing Kazuto to reflect on his actions throughout the death game. At the same time, Rika, Keiko and Asuna all relate to Suguha how they met Kirito during their time in the game and eventually causing Suguha to reflect on her feelings for her brother. After defeating Kayaba and gaining no insight on his goal, Kazuto`s story enters the ALO stage where Kikouka admits the Ministry`s lapse in monitoring Nobuyuki Sugou and his heinous human experimentation—leaving Kazuto to dive into ALO by himself, rescuing Asuna and freeing the captive players all with the help of his newfound friends. As Suguha eventually learns how to swim, Kazuto concludes his story by explaining the cost of power and leaves Kikouka.
Later on, Kirito, Klein, Agil, Asuna, Silica, Lizbeth and Leafa meet at Turtle Island in preparation for the undersea quest where they expect Yui to see a whale for the first time. With Kirito acting as the party leader, they dive into the ocean and arrive at an undersea temple where they are met by the NPC—Nerakk. Despite Leafa being slightly suspicious, the group begins the Deep Sea Invaders quest where they are to retrieve a stolen pearl from the temple and return it to Nerakk. After entering the temple, Kirito and Klein inadvertently activate a trap which unleashes a giant Armachthys monster. However with some difficulty the group eventually defeats it. After exploring the temple, the group recovers the pearl and just before Kirito gives it to Nerakk, Asuna notices that it had been an egg all along. Nerakk then reveals his malicious true form, the boss Krakken—The Abyss Lord, an overwhelmingly powerful monster which attacks and deals them severe damage. Just when all seems to be lost, Leviathan, the Sea King stops the Krakken and after a brief talk, the Krakken retreats. Leviathan then retrieves the egg, clearing the quest and returns the group to the surface on the back of a giant whale—their reward.
 In the epilogue, Kikouka once again tries to get in contact with Kazuto.
Source: Wiki</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648529</identifier>
<identifier>sword-art-online</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159972" update="2014-08-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">川原礫黙認「そーどあーと・おふらいん Extra Edition」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sword Art Offline: Extra Edition</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawahara Reki Mokunin "Sword Art Offline Extra Edition"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162930" update="2014-09-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (15 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162931" update="2014-09-27">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV for BD/DVD (15 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162932" update="2014-09-27">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (30 sec) AniplexUS Ver.</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
