<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10049" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-29</startdate>
<enddate>2015-01-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hybrid Child</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ハイブリッドチャイルド</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Hybrid Child</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8567" approval="3" total="4">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi 2</anime>
<anime id="5532" approval="3" total="4">Junjou Romantica</anime>
<anime id="8113" approval="3" total="3">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi TV</anime>
<anime id="9130" approval="2" total="3">Junjou Romantica (2012)</anime>
<anime id="9950" approval="2" total="3">Gekijouban Sekaiichi Hatsukoi: Yokozawa Takafumi no Baai</anime>
<anime id="10759" approval="2" total="3">Junjou Romantica 3</anime>
<anime id="6073" approval="2" total="2">Junjou Romantica 2</anime>
<anime id="7921" approval="2" total="2">Sekaiichi Hatsukoi</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.hybridchild.jp/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="4147" type="Character Design">Kishida Takahiro</name>
<name id="2177" type="Series Composition">Itami Aki</name>
<name id="10226" type="Original Work">Nakamura Shungiku</name>
<name id="125" type="Direction">Fukuda Michio</name>
<name id="9943" type="Music">Anze Hijiri</name>
<name id="10902" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirakawa Akio</name>
<name id="7635" type="Chief Animation Direction">Aono Atsushi</name>
<name id="6825" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takeda Itsuko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a one-shot manga written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr10226 [Nakamura Shungiku].
The Hybrid Child is an amazing doll that can grow if it is lavished with enough love and care from its owner. Neither fully machine nor fully human, the various Hybrid Child models develop strong emotional bonds with their owners.
Several short stories of love, sacrifice, and drama: Young http://anidb.net/ch67654 [Kotarou] learns the importance of responsibility when his Hybrid Child`s lifespan runs out. The tragic swordsman http://anidb.net/ch67656 [Seya] learns to love again with the help of his Hybrid child, http://anidb.net/ch67653 [Yuzu]. The final tale tells the story of http://anidb.net/ch67658 [Kuroda], the creator of the Hybrid Child designs, and how his lost love inspired their creation.
Source: DMP</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="189">6.10</permanent>
<temporary count="193">6.75</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>160002.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16194</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11135</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.hybridchild.jp/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hybrid_Child</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hybrid_Child</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349442</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18147</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3569" parentid="1278" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-17">
<name>human-android love</name>
<description>There is a romance going on between a human (often male) and an android (usually female).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6010" parentid="1278" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-12-29">
<name>human-replacement robots</name>
<description>In an usually sci-fi setting robots, or quite probably actually androids, take the place of humans.
Examples: Humans have become infertile and androids now take the place of children. Or it may be a more sinister undermining of human society by artificial intelligence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="67653" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="1">7.32</rating>
<name>Yuzu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67654" type="main character in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Izumi Kotarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67655" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-17">
<rating votes="1">7.32</rating>
<name>Tsukishima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67656" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-30">
<name>Seya Ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67657" type="main character in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Hazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67658" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<name>Kuroda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="160426" update="2014-06-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ただ一言俺がお前に言いたかった事は</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tada Hitokoto Ore ga Omae ni Iitakatta Koto wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160427" update="2014-06-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏草のにおい白雲の風ひとりとひとりとひとり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsukusa no Nioi Hakuun no Kaze Hitori to Hitori to Hitori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160428" update="2014-06-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">御主人様は花園の中にいつも一人でいらっしゃる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goshujin-sama wa Hanazono no Naka ni Itsumo Hitori de Irassharu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160429" update="2014-06-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺は葉月でないとダメだと言ったのだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore wa Hazuki de Nai to Dame Da to Itta no Da</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
