<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10091" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-07-10</startdate>
<enddate>2014-09-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya Zwei!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Fate/kaleid liner プリズマ☆イリヤ ツヴァイ!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">Fate/Kaleid Liner 프리즈마☆이리야 2wei!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya 2wei!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">F/K 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">fk 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Prillya Zwei</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Fate/kaleid liner プリズマ☆イリヤ 2wei!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya 2wei!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">Fate/kaleid liner 魔法少女☆伊莉雅 2wei!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10804" type="Sequel">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya Zwei! (2015)</anime>
<anime id="9900" type="Prequel">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya (2014)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://anime.prisma-illya.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
<name id="2900" type="Animation Work">Silver Link</name>
<name id="11820" type="Character Design">Ushijima Nozomi</name>
<name id="7052" type="Series Composition">Inoue Kenji</name>
<name id="927" type="Original Work">Type-Moon</name>
<name id="31124" type="Original Work">Hiroyama Hiroshi</name>
<name id="11181" type="Direction">Jinbou Masato</name>
<name id="1564" type="Chief Direction">Oonuma Shin</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by the same name by http://anidb.net/cr31124 [Hiroyama Hiroshi], itself a spin-off of the http://anidb.net/a3348 [Fate/stay night] erotic visual novel by http://anidb.net/cr927 [Type-Moon].
The Class Cards, which http://anidb.net/ch42302 [Illya] and http://anidb.net/ch49571 [Miyu] had captured under the directions of http://anidb.net/ch241 [Rin] and http://anidb.net/ch42327 [Luvia] and with the powers of http://anidb.net/ch54376 [Ruby] and http://anidb.net/ch54377 [Sapphire], had been disturbing the ley lines in Fuyuki City while they were free. Once captured, they should have stopped affecting the area, and the ley lines should have naturally stabilised; however, two weeks had passed since the last card had been captured, with no sign of their recovery.
Now, having received orders to fix the ley lines by forcing mana into them, Rin and Luvia once again draft Illya and Miyu into helping. The job is seemingly conducted without a hitch, but, as soon as they finish it, they find out that something went wrong, and the cave they`re in begins to collapse. In the midst of the crisis, Illya tries to protect everyone; once faced with insurmountable danger, a http://anidb.net/ch58979 [power hidden within her] awakens for the second time, and when this crisis is finally averted, she finds a http://anidb.net/ch65744 [clone of herself] sitting beside her... and this clone of herself seems to be set on murdering her.
— written by Hinoe</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1390">5.96</permanent>
<temporary count="1401">6.98</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>156550.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15630</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20509</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>25011</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anime.prisma-illya.jp/2wei/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fate/kaleid_liner_Prisma_Illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fate/kaleid_liner_プリズマ☆イリヤ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3446</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349447</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17323</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2761" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dodgeball</name>
<description>Dodgeball is any of a variety of games in which players try to hit other players on the opposing team with their own balls while avoiding being hit themselves. 
Don`t try this at home, kids.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5305" parentid="6234" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-29">
<name>tarot</name>
<description>The tarot is a pack of playing cards, most commonly numbering 78, used from the mid-15th century in various parts of Europe to play a group of card games such as Italian tarocchini and French tarot. From the late 18th century until the present time, the tarot has also found use by mystics and occultists for divination. Tarot cards are used throughout much of Europe to play card games. In English-speaking countries, where these games are largely unplayed, tarot cards are now used primarily for divinatory purposes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191977.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5915" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>French kiss</name>
<description>A kiss in which the tongue enters the partner`s mouth.</description>
<picurl>238326.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6234" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>motifs</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="241" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-20">
<rating votes="2756">8.36</rating>
<name>Toosaka Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toosaka Rin is a model student and idol of Shirou`s school, Rin is secretly a sorceress and Master in the Holy Grail War. She is descended from a long line of sorcerers, and though lacking a formal magic education, is extremely powerful in her own right. Her father was killed in the 4th Holy Grail War, and she has trained since his death to succeed him. She is perceptive, resourceful and avidly competitive. Although she tried to summon a Saber-class Servant, she accidentally called Archer instead.
Rin excels in transformation of energy, which includes storage of Mana in objects. She stores all of her mana in jewels that she charges daily to bypass her body`s natural limitations on releasing energy. She can detonate her jewels on contact with an object, resulting in a release of energy equivalent to an attack rank of "A". Her most common offensive spell is "Gandr", which fires concentrated mana in the form of a black orb from her finger. On contact, the spell amplifies physical conditions -- a person who is already sick, for example, becomes far sicker upon being hit. Rin is also proficient with reinforcement sorcery, which she uses on her legs to give herself more speed.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>172322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1904" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-20">
<rating votes="1261">2.88</rating>
<name>Emiya Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emiya Shirou is the main character of http://anidb.net/a3348 [Fate/Stay Night], a serious and honest teenager as well as a hard worker who enjoys helping others. He is in his second year of High School, and his hobbies include fixing a variety of broken things, from VCRs to stoves, as well as cooking and cleaning. He has some slight proficiency with reinforcement sorcery, though his foster father http://anidb.net/ch1919 [Emiya Kiritsugu] did not encourage him to improve it. Initially, he is confused about the Holy Grail War and irrationally attempts to shield others, even his own servant Saber, from danger.</description>
<picture>172321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1919" type="appears in" update="2014-10-21">
<rating votes="1013">7.67</rating>
<name>Emiya Kiritsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emiya Kiritsugu is a professional assassin and hitman. He dedicated most of his life to becoming a "hero of justice", a defender of humankind, through killing people who tended to bring catastrophe or war. He eventually noticed that he would never be able to do that with human abilities alone, and sought the miracle of the Holy Grail to stop conflict. In the aftermath of the 4th Holy Grail War, he saved the life of http://anidb.net/ch1904 [Emiya Shirou], later becoming the boy`s foster father and finally giving up on his quest. He is also a magus, but he never made any serious attempts to train the unskilled Shirou in his craft, in spite of the latter`s insistent requests. He dies in the years between the 4th and 5th Holy Grail Wars.</description>
<picture>163084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1921" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-20">
<rating votes="380">6.17</rating>
<name>Fujimura Taiga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taiga is an English teacher at Shirou`s school, homeroom instructor of Shirou`s class and the supervising teacher for the Archery Dojo. She is widely called "Tiger", a nickname she dislikes ("Taiga" and "Tiger" sound similar in Japanese), though Shirou refers to her as "Fuji-nee" (older sister Fuji). After Kiritsugu died, Taiga became Shirou`s guardian and has been living with him for several years. Taiga and Shirou are very close, and she regards him as a younger brother.
Taiga is largely a comic relief character; she is irresponsible, clumsy, and prone to sporadic bouts of extreme lethargy or zest. She lives with Shirou under the pretences of being his caretaker, although she cannot cook and lacks many other domestic skills, relying on Shirou to maintain her welfare. Shirou, however, appreciates Taiga`s company, and is more than happy to care for her. When Shirou is in any need of advice, Taiga can be depended on to be a confidante for his worries.</description>
<picture>172325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1934" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="69">4.17</rating>
<name>Sella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sella and Leysritt are Ilya`s maids, but they act as her caretakers and instruct her in the secrets of sorcery. Like Ilya, they both have silky blonde hair and deep crimson eyes. Sella is rather fickle and insecure (especially regarding her body), and is very suspicious of Emiya Shirou.</description>
<picture>137030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="247" picture="43238.jpg">Terada Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1939" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="89">5.77</rating>
<name>Leysritt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sella and Leysritt are Ilya`s maids, but they act as her caretakers and instruct her in the secrets of sorcery. Like Ilya, they both have silky blonde hair and deep crimson eyes. Leysritt is casual, and has affection for Shirou because his presence makes Ilya happy. Leysritt is skilled in combat, particularly with halberds.</description>
<picture>137031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="249" picture="46910.jpg">Miyagawa Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1944" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="62">8.01</rating>
<name>Kohaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kohaku is the older of the twin maids of the Touno house, as well as Akiha`s personal maid. She is very bright and cheerful, always having a smile on her face. She is quite intelligent, being a skilled practitioner of medicine, and has also shown to be an incredible tactician. She specialises in cooking, but tends to break things often when cleaning.</description>
<picture>47963.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1951" type="appears in" update="2014-02-11">
<rating votes="7">4.69</rating>
<name>Majutsu Kyoukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A trans-national, self-preservative organisation created by western magi for the purpose of controlling, concealing and developing Magecraft. Founded around the Middle Ages by those who foresaw the decline of Magecraft, they decided that in order to preserve their power Thaumaturgy should drift apart from society and become a secret known only by a necessary minimum number of people.
It has many laboratories and research bodies that seek to advance the progress of Thaumaturgy, as well as institutions that transmit their secrets to the next generation. Although the emphasis lies on the pursuit of knowledge, the Association also seeks to increase its own military strength so it can defend itself against those that might threaten it, such as the Holy Church, other mystic organizations and supernatural forces seeking punish mankind for meddling with areas that should not be touched.
The Mage`s Association is currently headquartered at the Clock Tower in London.</description>
<picture>150073.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1952" type="appears in" update="2014-02-15">
<rating votes="14">5.27</rating>
<name>Seidou Kyoukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Holy Church, also referred simply as "the Church", is a worldwide religious organisation, apparently styled after the real Roman Catholic Church. It is a powerful faction in the Nasuverse, with several important characters in the `verse works being its active or former members. On the surface, they coexist rather peacefully with the http://anidb.net/ch1951 [Mage`s Association], but that is only out of necessity, and neither group will waste an opportunity to backstab the other. They sometimes act as arbiters in the Association`s internal disputes; one such example are the Holy Grail Wars. Aside their regular duties as a normal religious group, they have a few special agencies dedicated to supernatural events.
The Assembly of the Eighth Sacrament, the lowest among the Church`s special agencies, is charged with researching, recovering and managing Holy Relics, items considered to have the holy attribute, scattered around the world. Their name comes from the seven Sacraments of the Catholic Church. As the Holy Grail is a Holy Relic, they`re in charge of managing every Holy Grail that appears; as such, in order to watch over the Holy Grail War, the priest stationed at Fuyuki City is always a member of this agency and is the one who acts as the war`s Supervisor.
The Church is also very active and relentless in the pursue and elimination of heretics, beings acting in disagreement with the Holy Scriptures. The members of the Church in that line of work are called Executors, and their specialties include magus hunting, demon killing, and vampire slaying. Among them, the most powerful ones are members of the Burial Agency, a group always composed of eight Executors, one of whom is the leader and another of whom is not an acting member, but a backup. Members of the Burial Agency work alone, and they will act without orders if they deem necessary, even going as far as skewering bishops, which earned them the reputation of the most heretic group inside the Church.
Among the items the Holy Church uses for its purposes, one can find the many types of Keys of Providence, Conceptual Weapons used for purification, and the Holy Scriptures, very powerful Conceptual Weapons used only by a few select Executors. Examples of Keys of Providence are http://anidb.net/ch1916 [Kotomine Kirei]`s most used weapons, the Black Keys, sword-shaped items that can be thrown at an opponent in order to pierce them and that do not have a blade when inside the priest`s frock. An example of a Holy Scripture is the Seventh Holy Scripture, used by http://anidb.net/ch1941 [Ciel], a massive metal weapon which can kill a vampire through physical power alone, shoots Bible pages, has an unicorn horn for a bayonet, and has a http://anidb.net/ch31725 [residing spirit].</description>
<picture>150288.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25939" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="388">6.84</rating>
<name>Irisviel von Einzbern</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Irisviel von Einzbern is the heroine of the Fate/Zero story, the mother of Illyasviel von Einzbern and Kiritsugu`s wife. A homunculus prototype created by the Einzbern family with the idea to give birth to an ultimate homunculus. Like many of the Einzberns, she is skilled in alchemy. Irisviel serves as Saber`s proxy Master, since Kiritsugu believes that he and Saber are incompatible.</description>
<picture>126277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31686" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-21">
<rating votes="35">4.99</rating>
<name>Caren Hortensia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caren is a member of the Church and Burial Agency, and she works as a priestess.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>6189.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38853" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-22">
<rating votes="53">5.82</rating>
<name>Bazett Fraga McRemitz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bazett Fraga McRemitz is a magus sent from the http://anidb.net/ch1951 [Mage`s Association] to fight the 5th Holy Grail War. She was born in Ireland as a descendant of an old family of magi that had detached itself from the Association, but she chose to join the Association regardless. Despite her rare lineage, she was dismissed, and decided to employ her abilities as a hunter of those that had been given a Sealing Designation.
She is mentioned very briefly in the http://anidb.net/a3348 [Fate/Stay Night] visual novel. She was the original Master of http://anidb.net/ch1908 [Lancer], but http://anidb.net/ch1916 [Kotomine Kirei] betrayed her and stole her command spells, fatally injuring her in the process. In Fate/Hollow Ataraxia, she is saved by the servant http://anidb.net/ch40363 [Avenger] and acts as his Master.</description>
<picture>77327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40361" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-11">
<rating votes="5">7.15</rating>
<name>Stheno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79796.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40362" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-01-11">
<rating votes="5">7.15</rating>
<name>Euryale</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79797.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40592" type="appears in" update="2015-08-30">
<rating votes="12">2.61</rating>
<name>Kischur Zelretch Schweinorg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kischur Zelretch Schweinorg is one of five living magicians capable of true magic beyond modern science or magecraft. He has control over the Second Magic, "Kaleidoscope", which allows for the "Operation of Parallel Worlds." He fought and defeated Brunestud of the Crimson Moon, the king of vampires, but was bitten in the process and became a Dead Apostle Ancestor, a vampire, thus attaining immortality.
He is one of the few characters who appear in more than one of the stories of the Nasuverse, appearing in http://anidb.net/a1015 [Tsukihime] manga and Prologue in the Plus Period artbook, and the Heaven`s Feel scenario of http://anidb.net/a3348 [Fate/stay night].
He supervised the creation of the Holy Grail War ritual, and was a master to the heads of Makiri, Toosaka and Einzbern families at the time.
Source: typemoon.wikia.com</description>
<picture>80028.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42302" type="main character in" update="2016-08-22">
<rating votes="132">8.76</rating>
<name>Prisma Illya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch83473 [Illyasviel von Einzbern], turned http://anidb.net/t2503 [magical girl].</description>
<picture>157694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15655" picture="44791.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42327" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-27">
<rating votes="116">7.23</rating>
<name>Luviagelita Edelfelt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Luviagelita or simply Luvia is a wealthy and proud young woman and mage.
In Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya she is assigned to work together with Rin to capture the Class Cards. After Sapphire abandons her, Luvia immediately adopts Sapphire`s new master, Miyu, and guides her to capture the Class Cards. She is indiscriminate in using her wealth, erecting a mansion across the street from Einzbern house in a single day, where she and Miyu are currently living. Her rivalry with Rin stems from their mutual crush on Shirou, who fails to notice their attraction to him
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>137014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49571" type="main character in" update="2015-09-05">
<rating votes="168">5.83</rating>
<name>Miyu Edelfelt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious girl who is chosen by Sapphire to become its new master and then adopted by Luvia. She takes her duties as a Magical Girl very seriously and is initially dismissive of Illya`s abilities, but gradually warms up to Illya. She comes to value Illya`s friendship greatly and is highly protective of her.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>177119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54376" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-14">
<rating votes="43">5.60</rating>
<name>Magical Ruby</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="488" picture="138714.jpg">Takano Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54377" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-14">
<rating votes="42">5.79</rating>
<name>Magical Sapphire</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Kaleidostick, the younger sister of Magical Ruby, that enables Miyu to become a Magical Girl. Sapphire was originally assigned to Luvia, but, as with Ruby, Sapphire abandoned Luvia after becoming tired of how she was constantly quarreling with Rin.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>137016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56113" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-14">
<rating votes="21">3.30</rating>
<name>Moriyama Nanaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56114" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-14">
<rating votes="44">5.63</rating>
<name>Gakumazawa Tatsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56115" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-14">
<rating votes="40">2.73</rating>
<name>Kurihara Suzuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56116" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-14">
<rating votes="25">2.99</rating>
<name>Katsura Mimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57870" type="appears in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="39">7.45</rating>
<name>Lord El-Melloi II</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58639" type="appears in" update="2013-08-07">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Iori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iori is a mascot character from Magical Bushidou Musashi anime which Illya watches. Iori is Musashi`s familiar and gives her magical power.
Note: Anime-only character.</description>
<picture>141073.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58640" type="appears in" update="2013-08-07">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Magical Bushidou Musashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magical Bushidou Musashi is a heroine of Magical Bushidou Musashi anime which Illya watches. She is a magical girl who is a self-proclaimed messenger of love, justice and humanity. She has a familiar Iori.</description>
<picture>141074.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="58979" type="appears in" update="2018-08-06">
<rating votes="18">7.99</rating>
<name>Prisma Illya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch65744 [Chloe] takes over http://anidb.net/ch42302 [Illya`s] body, and installs http://anidb.net/ch1906 [Archer`s] class card.</description>
<picture>221632.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59541" type="appears in" update="2018-08-12">
<rating votes="6">5.60</rating>
<name>Prisma Miyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch71988 [Miyu] installs http://anidb.net/ch38 [Saber`s] class card.</description>
<picture>222186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65744" type="main character in" update="2016-06-17">
<rating votes="164">8.73</rating>
<name>Chloe von Einzbern</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69249" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-11">
<rating votes="3">3.14</rating>
<name>Auguste</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69565" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-08-20">
<rating votes="2">5.55</rating>
<name>Aozaki Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159944.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69875" type="appears in" update="2014-12-12">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Prisma Miyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch71988 [Miyu] installs http://anidb.net/ch1909 [Rider`s] class card.</description>
<picture>160570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71988" type="main character in" update="2016-08-22">
<rating votes="53">7.38</rating>
<name>Prisma Miyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch49571 [Miyu Edelfelt], turned http://anidb.net/t2503 [magical girl].</description>
<picture>157695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83473" type="main character in" update="2016-08-22">
<rating votes="236">8.47</rating>
<name>Illyasviel von Einzbern</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In contrast with her http://anidb.net/ch1913 [Fate/stay night counterpart], Illya has had a normal childhood, growing up with no knowledge of magic or the Holy Grail War. She lives with her brother http://anidb.net/ch1904 [Shirou] and is looked after by her maids http://anidb.net/ch1939 [Leysritt] and http://anidb.net/ch1934 [Sella] when her parents http://anidb.net/ch1919 [Kiritsugu] and http://anidb.net/ch25939 [Irisviel] are away.
She is a fan of http://anidb.net/t2503 [magical girl] anime, and daydreams about becoming one. When she encounters a magic wand named http://anidb.net/ch54376 [Magical Ruby], Illya is tricked into signing a contract and http://anidb.net/ch42302 [becoming a magical girl].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>189556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15655" picture="44791.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="158538" update="2014-04-14">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">先行ショートPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (20 sec)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkou Short PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160625" update="2016-08-01">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">先行PV第3弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 03 (2 min 10 sec)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkou PV Dan 3-dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160626" update="2014-06-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">先行ロングPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1 min 45 sec)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senkou Long PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161160" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の転校生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wild Transfer Student</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Tenkousei</title>
<summary>Kuro transfers into Illya`s class, but then Team Stolen First Kiss challenges her to a dodge ball match! Kuro crushes her enemies one after another using her overwhelming physical prowess. But then Illya gets in her way in order to stop her normal life from breaking down any further!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657765</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161161" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">日常ブレイカー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Normal Life Breaker</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nichijou Breaker</title>
<summary>After being interrogated, Kuro escapes her confinement to Luvia`s house and for some reason starts boldly seducing Shirou in Illya`s living room. Truly sacrificing herself, Illya tries to put a stop to Kuro. Then, after noticing Kuro`s escape, Rin and Luvia barge in with Miyu in tow?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657763</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161162" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イリヤ×イリヤ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Illya x Illya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Illya x Illya</title>
<summary>Just as the morning`s fortune telling predicted, Illya was attacked by one misfortune after another on her way to school. A dump car charged at her, ferocious dogs chased her... But those were all caused by "another Illya" targeting Illya`s life?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657761</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161163" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イリヤgrow up!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Illya Grow Up?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Illya Grow Up!?</title>
<summary>After all their fierce battles, Illya and Miyu have finished collecting all the Class Cards and returned to an ordinary, peaceful school life. Then one day, they both join Rin and Luvia in a great cave in order to pour mana into the disrupted ley lines and stabilize them. It was supposed to be a simple mission for those magical girls, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657285</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161219" update="2019-11-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161379" update="2019-11-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161670" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女の名は</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Name Is</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Na wa</title>
<summary>After opening up to her classmates, Kuro and Illya were both enjoying a "normal" school life. Iri watches over both of them with her gentle hope--"I want them to be smiling in their future." However, that wish was in vain, as an intruder appears at Luvia`s mansion, signaling an end to their daily happiness.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657773</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161671" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! クッキン・シスターズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash! Cooking Sisters!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Cooking Sisters</title>
<summary>Now that Kuro is living with Illya`s family, her "normal" life starts! One morning Kuro says she`s going to make a delicious pound cake for Shirou, and Illya quickly turns it into a competition. Soon it breaks out into a battle of deserts over their feelings for their older brother!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657771</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161672" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘘と強がりの向こう側</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On the Other Side of Lies and Facade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso to Tsuyogari no Mukougawa</title>
<summary>Miyu faces Kuro alone in battle in order to protect Illya. Though Miyu puts up a fierce fight without giving an inch, her blade won`t reach Kuro. "So let`s all die together as good friends and end this. Wouldn`t that be nice?" As Miyu tries to defeat Kuro`s dual swords, Illya comes running to stop them both, and then...?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657769</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161673" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="12">2.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは, つまり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Well, in Other Words</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa, Tsumari</title>
<summary>"I want to go back to my normal life." When that nonchalant line of Illya`s enrages Kuro, she declares them both enemies who can never coexist and flees into the night. Illya is confused. The next day Miyu heads to the coast without telling Illya and the others. Waiting for her there is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657767</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162040" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その手が守ったものは</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Things Those Hands Protected</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Te ga Mamotta Mono wa</title>
<summary>After Installing Rider, Miyu attempts to finish Bazett using her Noble Phantasm, but it ends up countered by Bazett`s trump card. Bazett coldly approaches the seriously wounded Kuro to retrieve the final remaining Card. Despite the desperate situation and wounds all over her body, Illya makes one final attempt to stop her!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657777</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162041" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">独りの戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lone Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitori no Tatakai</title>
<summary>As Illya and Kuro stand agape at the destruction of Luvia`s mansion, Bazett appears with overflowing hostility. Illya and Kuro try putting up a fierce resistance as Bazett aims to claim the Class Cards. However, there is little they can do when faced with her overwhelming power, and both are backed into a desperate corner.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657775</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162186" update="2014-08-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファーストブラ イリヤ編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Bra: Illya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">First Bra: Illya Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162969" update="2014-09-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファーストブラ 美遊編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Bra: Miyu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">First Bra: Miyu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162970" update="2014-12-01">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2014-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おねえちゃんの人肌治療</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onee-chan no Hitohada Chiryou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164675" update="2015-02-18">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法少女プリズマ×××</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Girl Prisma XXX</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Shoujo Prisma XXX</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164676" update="2014-12-29">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2014-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小学生チャイナドレス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougakusei China Dress</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
