<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="101" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>1998-06-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Jikuu Tenshou Nazca</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dimension Movement of Nazca</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">時空転抄ナスカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Nazca</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Nazca</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Οι Ξιφομάχοι του Πεπρωμένου</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www10.ocn.ne.jp/~maturi/yorozudou/NASUKA-R/NASUKA.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="4364" type="Music">Saitou Tsuneyoshi</name>
<name id="777" type="Animation Work">Radix</name>
<name id="739" type="Animation Work">Genco</name>
<name id="2285" type="Character Design">Sano Hirotoshi</name>
<name id="114" type="Direction">Tokita Hiroko</name>
<name id="7918" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kuhara Shigeki</name>
</creators>
<description>Nearly 500 years ago, a bloody civil war erupted within the Inca Empire. The losing side decided to unleash a mystical weapon of awesome power that almost destroys the entire Earth.
Now in present-day Japan, http://anidb.net/ch39237 [Miura Kyoji] discovers that he is the reincarnated soul of an ancient Inca warrior. But Kyoji is not alone. His friend and teacher, http://anidb.net/ch39245 [Masanari Tate], is also a reincarnated Inca soul.
Tate decides to unleash this ancient weapon of total destruction once again. And so Kyoji must journey halfway around the world to discover the secret to his own past and fight against his closest friend, to save the world.
Source: AnimeNfo</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="182">2.93</permanent>
<temporary count="185">5.60</temporary>
<review count="1">4.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>223965.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>181</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1775</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>487</identifier>
<identifier>vmayym</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.genco.co.jp/works/1921/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nazca_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>時空転抄ナスカ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88870</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1645</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/493</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1998/nasuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6352</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1645" parentid="2751" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>kendo</name>
<description>Kendo, or kendou in Japanese, is a popular sport from Japan. It consists of swordplay with one or two http://anidb.net/t1817 [shinai], a two-handed bamboo sword which may also be held with one hand only, while wearing armour.</description>
<picurl>163593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2924" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>earthquake</name>
<description>*rumble rumble rumble rumble*
Upheaval of the Earth`s crust, usually resulting in widespread destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6401" parentid="2832" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-05">
<name>Peru</name>
<description>Peru, officially the Republic of Peru, is a country in western South America. It is bordered in the north by Ecuador and Colombia, in the east by Brazil, in the southeast by Bolivia, in the south by Chile, and in the west by the Pacific Ocean. Peru is an extremely biodiverse country with habitats ranging from the arid plains of the Pacific coastal region in the west to the peaks of the Andes mountains vertically extending from the north to the southeast of the country to the tropical Amazon Basin rainforest in the east with the Amazon river.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192316.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="39237" type="main character in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Miura Kyoji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39238" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Dan Takuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39239" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Daimon Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39240" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Yanagihara Tatsuko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3294" picture="223278.jpg">Mizuno Manabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39241" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Kiritake Yuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39242" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Seino Keita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39243" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Shiogami Shinri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39244" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-25">
<name>Kanya Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39245" type="main character in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Masanari Tate</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39246" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Miura Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5216" picture="29203.jpg">Yoshida Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39247" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-03">
<name>Auros</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7118" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">灯の向こうの明日へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyond Light, Towards Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au-delà de la lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Mi profesor</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7119" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イリャ・テッセ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Iriyatesse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Irra Tezze</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Irra Tezze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7120" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙!そして決別!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tears and Farewell!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les larmes, et puis l`adieu</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Lagrimas</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7121" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魂人の蠢動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meeting of the Sleeping Souls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`appel des Hommes-âmes</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Actividad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7122" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンデスの邂逅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion in The Andes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rencontre sur les Andes</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Encuentro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7123" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">目覚めし者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Awaken</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`éveil</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Despertar</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7124" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇を追う光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light Chasing Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La lumière qui chasse les ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Luz y oscuridad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7125" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束の地・アスカへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Promised Land</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La terre promise</title>
<title xml:lang="es">La tierra de promision</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7126" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして未来のために!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And for the Future!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et puis... l`avenir !</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Mañana!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7127" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶... それぞれの二人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory... Separate Ways</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Memoria de cada uno</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7128" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の頂に向かって</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Towards the Final Fate!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers la montagne du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="es">Punto mas suerte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7129" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦!虚無の街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle in An Empty Town!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat dans la ville morte</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Batalla decisiva!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121094" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121095" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
