<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10101" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004</startdate>
<enddate>2004</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hibike! Wadaiko</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ひびけ! 和だいこ</title>
</titles>
<description>*An educational film about the Convention on the Rights of the Child in Japan.
A group of children are practicing taiko drums for a recital at the community center. Local adult residents force them to stop, saying that it is selfish for kids to disturb their peace. However, the teacher tells the children about the Convention on the Rights of the Child so they have the courage to stand up to the adults.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4">10.00</permanent>
<temporary count="4">8.50</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>143249.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>26111</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="154487" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
