<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10119" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-03-26</startdate>
<enddate>2004-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ashita Kirarin</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あした・きらりん</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="53678" type="Music">Motoshuku Youko</name>
<name id="5511" type="Direction">Morita Hiromitsu</name>
<name id="7326" type="Character Design">Yanase Jouji</name>
<name id="53680" type="Direction">Matsubayashi Nobuya</name>
<name id="53685" type="Original Work">Watari Kunpei</name>
</creators>
<description>Ayako suffers from autism, and all kids in the class mock her except for Yuri - the only girl who shows some kindness towards her. Greatly appreciating that, Ayako gives Yuri a present - a beaded bracelet.
Later, the school is preparing for the summer cultural festival, and Ayako`s present inspires Yuri with an idea to make a decoration for one of the school`s exterior walls - a giant picture made of ropes beaded with empty cans of different colours. All kids including Ayako then gather empty cans from all around the city and start creating the picture. However, the day before the festival is scheduled to open a typhoon hits the city, threatening to ruin the kids` hard work.
— written by Singan</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3">5.08</permanent>
<temporary count="3">5.33</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>143298.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22305</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32255</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7640</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13562</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5276" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-25">
<name>typhoon</name>
<description>A typhoon is a mature tropical cyclone that develops in the north-western part of the Pacific Ocean between 180° and 100°E. This region is referred to as the north-west Pacific basin. Identical phenomena in the eastern north Pacific are called hurricanes, with tropical cyclones moving into the western Pacific re-designated as typhoons.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="154484" update="2014-09-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2004-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
