<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10181" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2014-07-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Black Bullet</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブラック・ブレット</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Black Bullet</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Black Bullet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Black Bullet</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Чёрная Пуля</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">블랙 불릿</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">黑色子彈</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">黑色子弹</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8109" approval="9" total="16">Hidan no Aria</anime>
<anime id="8480" approval="7" total="21">Guilty Crown</anime>
<anime id="9127" approval="5" total="20">Psycho-Pass</anime>
<anime id="9665" approval="4" total="4">Machine-Doll wa Kizutsukanai</anime>
<anime id="7900" approval="2" total="9">Freezing</anime>
<anime id="9789" approval="2" total="8">Freezing Vibration</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="9">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="591695">There are interesting points in the plot, and nice concepts in the Black Bullet universe. But I often find myself lost, they are trying to tell too much at the same time but without giving enough information. I mean wtf is varanium, and gastrea. There are many plot holes and logical fallacies but I suppose it`s alright when you really have nothing else to do/watch (i.e. me).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="600311">very nice story and loli action :p</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="477898">I came here for something like Kabaneri and AoT, what I found was actually something much more similar to Railgun. Despite the setting being so dire to mankind, modern society is still going strong, there are still schools, convenience stores, even magical girl anime. As such, mankind never really feels on the verge of extinction, as such the tone of the show is much more upbeat than the previous mentioned titles. The action scenes are a bit juvenile with shouts of technique names following almost every move. The show gets a lot of criticism, but I find myself unexpectedly fond of it. The character designs are superb for the girls. The banter is memorable and similar to Railgun; fight scenes followed by the MC getting harassed by a loli. The show would be great, if it could have exploited the emotional aspect of the story, the scenes are written into the story, but it`s lacking heavier emotional attachment. Good show, with lots of potential I wish could have been realized.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="386453">As many already noted the series is not bad and gets better over time. But that`s actually the problem. The Series has an end and i won`t bother if there is no sequel, but the whole story and all the twists and unexplained questions leave room for at least one more season. It feels like they have this great and huge idea of a dystopia, but not enough episodes to explain all.
Still: Nice idea, good story, that gets dark sometimes, some unnecessary loli moments, i don`t regret watching. :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="87321">if you like action with some loli to go with it, this is it!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="318709">Heart warming, traJody , action with a twist. Really great anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="418685">Nothing much to say except - IT`S A MUST SEE anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="416016">it starts a bit slow the first few episodes, but after that  hhhhrrrnngg those cliffhangers</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.black-bullet.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="4327" type="Direction">Kojima Masayuki</name>
<name id="2950" type="Animation Work">Kinema Citrus</name>
<name id="38580" type="Original Work">Kanzaki Shiden</name>
<name id="39770" type="Character Design">Umishima Senbon</name>
<name id="9888" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hasebe Atsushi</name>
<name id="39770" type="Chief Animation Direction">Umishima Senbon</name>
<name id="16800" type="Animation Work">Orange</name>
<name id="8584" type="Chief Animation Direction">Jitsuhara Noboru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr38580 [Kanzaki Shiden].
In the year 2021, mankind was decimated by an epidemic of a parasitical virus named Gastrea; the survivors were forced to live within Monoliths, structures created from Varanium, a metal that is able to subdue the virus. People then discovered the existence of Cursed Children, children born with the Gastrea virus who are able to control it, which gives them superhuman abilities; due to the virus` intervention, however, the Cursed Children could only be female. Groups known as Civil Securities were formed to specialize in fighting against Gastrea; they operated by pairing an Initiator, who is a cursed child, and a Promoter, whose job is to lead the cursed child.
Ten years after the epidemic, http://anidb.net/ch60244 [Satomi Rentarou], a high school student who is also a Promoter in his childhood friend http://anidb.net/ch62149 [Tendou Kisara]`s Tendou Civil Security, and his Initiator, http://anidb.net/ch60242 [Aihara Enju], receive a secret mission to prevent the destruction of the Tokyo Area.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3266">4.62</permanent>
<temporary count="3289">6.58</temporary>
<review count="3">4.61</review>
</ratings>
<picture>147799.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15769</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30100</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20787</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.black-bullet.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Black_Bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ブラック・ブレット</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3321</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347852</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17067</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2776" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>parasite</name>
<description>Parasites are life forms that feed off other beings in some way. In anime, they are often aliens and usually intelligent. For shock value, and to avoid having to draw aliens all the time, their prey is preferably human; they may see humans as food, as puppets for mind control, or simply as temporary body hosts. In every case, the human is the victim of a "merging", which is not to be confused with the more "amicable" symbiosis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3244" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>sexually dominant</name>
<description>Sexually dominant is a designation applied to those able to assertively assume and maintain control over the actions of their partner(s) during sexual activity, actively steering it towards their own intents and preferences and possibly to the detriment of those of their partner(s).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5466" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-17">
<name>epidemic</name>
<description>A rapid spread or increase of something (e.g. a disease) affecting many persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="60242" type="main character in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="65">7.84</rating>
<name>Aihara Enju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="129542.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60243" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="26">6.40</rating>
<name>Hiruko Kagetane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60244" type="main character in" update="2019-10-26">
<rating votes="36">5.53</rating>
<name>Satomi Rentarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62149" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-01">
<rating votes="44">6.06</rating>
<name>Tendou Kisara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62150" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="58">8.27</rating>
<name>Tina Sprout</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62151" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-23">
<rating votes="21">5.62</rating>
<name>Muroto Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62152" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-23">
<rating votes="30">4.44</rating>
<name>Seitenshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>150656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62153" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="23">5.86</rating>
<name>Hiruko Kohina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66368" type="appears in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="4">1.40</rating>
<name>Tendou Kikunojou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66524" type="appears in" update="2014-04-11">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Reporter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39786" picture="223840.jpg">Fukuyama Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66525" type="appears in" update="2014-04-11">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Tadashima Shigetoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66526" type="appears in" update="2014-04-11">
<rating votes="2">3.81</rating>
<name>Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37283" picture="238137.jpg">Itou Miku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66527" type="appears in" update="2014-04-11">
<rating votes="2">2.77</rating>
<name>Satomi Rentarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66684" type="appears in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Mikajima Shachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3156" picture="76983.jpg">Sakaguchi Shuuhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66685" type="appears in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Hisho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40095" picture="156243.jpg">Iwasaki Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66686" type="appears in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Jieikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33065" picture="90146.jpg">Kikuchi Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66687" type="appears in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Akai Me no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13791" picture="151660.jpg">Iwasaki Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66688" type="appears in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Isha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28505" picture="58972.jpg">Baron Yamazaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66689" type="appears in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Tannin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24404" picture="68958.jpg">Murakami Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66690" type="appears in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153815.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32612" picture="223330.jpg">Toujou Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66691" type="appears in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Matsuzaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66692" type="appears in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="2">1.39</rating>
<name>Ikuma Shougen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66726" type="appears in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="12">8.66</rating>
<name>Senju Kayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66727" type="appears in" update="2014-05-15">
<rating votes="12">6.14</rating>
<name>Shiba Miori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66728" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<rating votes="4">5.67</rating>
<name>Mibu Asaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66729" type="appears in" update="2014-07-31">
<rating votes="18">8.02</rating>
<name>Fuse Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66730" type="appears in" update="2014-06-08">
<rating votes="2">1.93</rating>
<name>Gadou Nagamasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66731" type="appears in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="9">5.15</rating>
<name>Katagiri Yuzuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66732" type="appears in" update="2014-07-31">
<rating votes="6">4.64</rating>
<name>Katagiri Tamaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66733" type="appears in" update="2014-07-31">
<rating votes="7">6.33</rating>
<name>Nagisawa Shouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67006" type="appears in" update="2014-04-23">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Soujuushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154882.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39077" picture="148735.jpg">Matsukawa Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67197" type="appears in" update="2014-05-06">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Operator</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67308" type="appears in" update="2014-05-15">
<rating votes="2">1.48</rating>
<name>Yasuwaki Takuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25023" picture="70106.jpg">Kimura Subaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67309" type="appears in" update="2014-05-08">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Saitake Sougen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67600" type="appears in" update="2014-05-23">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Ishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23437" picture="63755.jpg">Imai Akinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67650" type="appears in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Jieikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23529" picture="178469.jpg">Kawanishi Kengo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67651" type="appears in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="3">7.69</rating>
<name>Moumoku no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67652" type="appears in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Kaisetsusha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28505" picture="58972.jpg">Baron Yamazaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67867" type="appears in" update="2014-06-08">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Reporter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67868" type="appears in" update="2014-06-08">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Nigel no Initiator</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40079" picture="156197.jpg">Oomae Aika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67869" type="appears in" update="2014-06-08">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Brick Nigel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67891" type="appears in" update="2014-10-05">
<name>Tendou Minkankeibikaisha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Tendo Civil Security Corporation (天童 民間警備会社, てんどう みんかんけいびかいしゃ, Tendou Minkankeibikaisha) is an organization owned by http://anidb.net/ch62149 [Tendou Kisara].
According to Kisara, the president of the corporation, Tendou Civil Security would not be what it is today if not for http://anidb.net/ch60244 [Satomi Rentarou] and http://anidb.net/ch60242 [Aihara Enju], along with herself, making it a three-man team in the year 2030; the year Rentaro became a Promoter. The corporation`s exact founding date, however, remains unclear.
As a relatively new corporation, Tendou Civil Security`s existence is not known by many. The corporation is located on the second floor of a building near the city. Below the corporation, on the first floor, the tenant runs a gay bar, whilst the second floor tenant runs a cabaret, and lastly; the fourth floor, does black market finance. The inside of the corporation is spacious, containing three desks, with a multitude of supplies on top of them, two bookshelves, one by the window and the other by the door, and lastly, a board with several papers hanging, and a phone next to Kisara`s desk.</description>
<picture>61885.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="68024" type="appears in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Gadou no Buka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40346" picture="223801.jpg">Matsuda Shuuhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68025" type="appears in" update="2014-06-18">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Gadou Hidehiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68444" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Tendou Kazumitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68445" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Shiina Kazumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="158489" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の希望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le dernier espoir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Kibou</title>
<summary>Year 2031: Tokyo Area. Most of the human race has been wiped out by the parasitic Gastrea. Part of the Anti-Gastrea movement, high school student Satomi Rentaro works as a civil officer for Tendo Civil Securities. On a mission, he meets a suspicious man in a mask and a tuxedo: Hiruko Kagetane.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652879</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158750" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒の銃弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Bullet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La balle noire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro no Juudan</title>
<summary>Hiruko instantly takes care of 29 civil officer pairs and comes face to face with Rentaro and Enju again. Rentaro shows his true power to Hiruko, proving that he`s not the only one that was part of the New Human Creation Project and they battle again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653335</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158751" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の子供たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Children of Fate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les enfants du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Kodomo-tachi</title>
<summary>Enju is treated like an outcast at her school when it is found out that she is one of the Cursed Children, who have the Gastrea virus within them. Despite her sadness, they go look for the host Gastrea. She gives it her all and instantly is able to recover the case...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652883</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158752" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂気の仮面</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mask of Madness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Masque de folie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouki no Kamen</title>
<summary>Rentaro and President Kisara head to the Defense Ministry after being summoned. All of the reputable civil officers from the Tokyo Area show up there. The one who summoned them there is Seitenshi, in regards to destroying the host Gastrea and recovering the contents of the case that`s inside the Gastrea.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652881</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159159" update="2015-12-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159186" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅黒の暗殺者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crimson Black Assassin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`assassin de rouge et de noir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akakuro no Ansatsusha</title>
<summary>The Tendo Civil Security Agency gets a job from Seitenshi. The job is to act as her bodyguard. Rentaro isn`t very fond of the idea, but notices odd activity when it`s revealed that Seitenshi will be meeting with the head of the Osaka Area while Kikunojo is gone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653337</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159278" update="2015-12-19">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159409" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">境界線の石碑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monument on the Border</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La stèle de la frontière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoukaisen no Sekihi</title>
<summary>Rentaro had set up an outdoor classroom for the kids in the outer district and was enjoying class. Seitenshi suddenly appears and lets him know that one of the Monoliths is about to be destroyed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653343</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159410" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静寂の月夜, 夜明けの空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Still of the Moonlit Night, the Dawn Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Clair de lune silencieux, ciel d`aube</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seijaku no Tsukiyo, Yoake no Sora</title>
<summary>Rentaro gets hurt trying to protect Seitenshi from the sniper. The security plan that Seitenshi`s bodyguards had set up were leaked to the sniper. Enju had gone after the sniper and falls into a coma.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653341</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159411" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トラジック・アイロニー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tragic Irony</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ironie tragique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tragic Irony</title>
<summary>Seitenshi`s vehicle is hit by a sniper while she in enroute to her meeting. Rentaro realizes this is more than a mere assassination attempt and gets help from Miori to find out more about the attack.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653339</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159909" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クライシス・ポイント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crisis Point</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le point critique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Crisis Point</title>
<summary>Rentaro is condemned for a decision he made in battle, and is told that there is another Gastrea named Pleiades that is protecting the already supposedly immortal Aldebaran. Rentaro is forced to face the enemy alone, and is helped by someone rather unexpected: his enemy from the past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653351</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159910" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タウルスの心臓, 光の槍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Heart of Taurus, the Spear of Light</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cœur du taureau et la Lance de lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taurus no Shinzou, Hikari no Yari</title>
<summary>The outdoor classroom is completely destroyed because of the bombing. Hope is starting to be destroyed along with the Monolith as the JASDF and Gastrea face off. However, the ones to show up at the civil officers` base were JASDF who had been turned into Gastrea themselves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653349</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159911" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東京エリア防衛戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Area Defensive Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille pour défendre la zone de Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokyo Area Boueisen</title>
<summary>Before the battle against Aldebaran, Rentaro and Enju enjoy the outdoor class with the girls of the Outer District. Because the girls have very little hope and are unsure of their future, Rentaro takes them to a place where humanity had won their last battle against the Gastrea. Only three days remain until the destruction of the Monolith.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653347</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159912" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">結界の守人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Protectors of the Barrier</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les défenseurs de la barrière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kekkai no Morito</title>
<summary>The monolith finally starts to turn white. In fear of the great destruction to follow, the people of the Tokyo Area start panicking. Meanwhile, the civil officers start gathering around Monolith 32.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653345</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160414" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神を目指した者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ones Who Aspired to Be Gods</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ceux qui voulaient devenir des dieux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami o Mezashita Monotachi</title>
<summary>With the addition of Kagetane and Kohina, the adjuvant is complete. They choose the Flames of Revolution, the last place humanity won their battle against the Gastrea, as the ground for the final battle against Aldebaran.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656327</identifier>
<identifier>black-bullet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160559" update="2015-12-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164696" update="2015-01-13">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Tenchuu Girls CV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164697" update="2015-12-19">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Tenchuu Girls Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167200" update="2015-03-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Blu-ray Preview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
