<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="102" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>70</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2000-03-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Cardcaptor Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Cardcaptors</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Clow Master Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Cardcaptor Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Ловец карт Сакура</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Сакура - собирательница карт</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">카드캡터 사쿠라</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">آسرة البطاقات ساكورا</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="synonym">Cardcaptors</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Сакура - мисливець за картами</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">魔卡少女樱</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">CCSTV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">CCS</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">CCS TV</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">カードキャプターさくら</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Cardcaptor Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Card Captor Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Sakura, chasseuse de cartes</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Pesca la tua carta Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Sakura, Cazadora de Cartas</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">카드캡터 체리</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Zdobywczyni kart Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Cardcaptor Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Sakura, a Caçadora de Cartas</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Sakura Card Captors</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">Cardcaptor Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Οι Περιπέτειες της Νίκης</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">סאקורה</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">การ์ดแคปเตอร์ ซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Sakura , Stăpâna Cărţilor Magice</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="official">Thủ lĩnh thẻ bài</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Sakura Card Captor</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="514" type="Sequel">Gekijouban Cardcaptor Sakura: Fuuin Sareta Card</anime>
<anime id="2733" type="Alternative Setting">Tsubasa Chronicle</anime>
<anime id="513" type="Side Story">Gekijouban Cardcaptor Sakura</anime>
<anime id="4514" type="Other">Clamp in Wonderland 2 1995-2006</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9042" approval="24" total="34">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya</anime>
<anime id="516" approval="6" total="15">Princess Tutu</anime>
<anime id="842" approval="5" total="5">Hime-chan no Ribbon</anime>
<anime id="2435" approval="2" total="4">Gakuen Alice</anime>
<anime id="7413" approval="1" total="5">Himechan! Otogitic Idol Lil`Pri</anime>
<anime id="153" approval="1" total="4">Kimagure Orange Road</anime>
<anime id="4893" approval="1" total="2">Kamichama Karin</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="19">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="83424">Not the first, but the definitive "Magical Girl" anime. I that`s your thing, its easily a 9. Even if it isn`t your thing, its a solid anime full of cute and humor and action. Watch it subbed. the dubbed version takes a lot of liberties with the story to make it fit "Western sensibilities"</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="452392">Classic Magical Girl anime!  Not to be missed!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="320398">Clamp can be cute,serious and whatever you want them to be.Sakura is awesome and the other characters are not be missed!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="735478">A fun anime that is different from your usual "mahou shoujo", where the protagonist doesn`t transform. Lots of interesting characters and relationships.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="368571">My childhood anime, i laughed so hard back then and i still do. This is definetly a must-see , to me is the best clamp work since it was my first anime ever.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="375852">it`s a classic. Best mahou shoujo series, simple,cute and kodomo-ish soft</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="198715">The classics are sometimes still the best.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="350540">One of the best Magical Girl series out there!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="367736">If Sakura doesn`t make you happy, I`m pretty sure nothing will.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nhk.or.jp/anime/sakura/</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="1745" type="Series Composition">Ookawa Nanase</name>
<name id="2500" type="Music">Negishi Takayuki</name>
<name id="747" type="Original Work">Clamp</name>
<name id="1525" type="Direction">Asaka Morio</name>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="3331" type="Character Design">Takahashi Kumiko</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch1283 [Kinomoto Sakura] is appointed Card Captor by the Guardian of the Seal, http://anidb.net/ch7239 [Cerberus], when she accidentally opens the magical book of Clow Cards and scatters them to the four winds. To protect the world from disaster she must capture all of the Clow Cards with the help of her friend http://anidb.net/ch9580 [Tomoyo] and Cerberus.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4195">7.39</permanent>
<temporary count="4265">7.93</temporary>
<review count="11">8.30</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221338.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8498</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>126</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>232</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2424</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>96</identifier>
<identifier>nyoipr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ccsakura-official.com/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nhk.or.jp/anime/sakura/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Cardcaptor_Sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>カードキャプターさくら</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>371</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>90278</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1647</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/168</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4628</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1998/cc_sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="17">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ccsakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>카드캡터_사쿠라</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>百變小櫻</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20319</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20318</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6734</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6404</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07DNHH3PL</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1262" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-07">
<name>naive</name>
<description>A naive (also spelled naïve, keeping its French diacritic) person lacks worldly knowledge, experience, wisdom, understanding, or judgement.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1816" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-09">
<name>uniform -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>The "uniform" tag is to be split and removed. Please help by tagging the character with the appropriate kind of uniform (e.g. school uniform, maid dress, etc) and removing this tag from them, and by not adding this tag to any further characters. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-06">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>"Absolute Territory" (絶対領域, Zettai Ryouiki in Japanese) describes the area of uncovered thigh between the skirt and the knee sock.
As per usual for fandom who obsess about costumes, this can be considered a moe attribute and thus, present prominently in character designs and schoolgirl outfits. The term originates from http://anidb.net/a22 [Neon Genesis Evangelion] to designate an area of Absolute Terror, although it`s had considerable semantic drift. In this case, it may jokingly refer to the fact it emphasizes a shorter skirt without actually becoming creepy and showing the underpants.
As if that wasn`t enough, some even categorize it into five "Grades", from E to A. Only the top two (A and B) are considered true Zettai Ryouiki and they are only usable by female characters. Some researchers additionally introduce Grade S, the highest one which consists of Grade A plus further requirements to personality and hairstyle.
Just to make it clear, Zettai Ryouiki is made up of three components: socks, skin, and skirt. An Action Girl may trade the latter for hotpants but if it doesn`t include knee-highs and thighs, it`s not Zettai Ryouiki. Panty Shot is an entirely different zone.
For more information on sock lengths in general, see also: http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery]
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2662" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>school excursion</name>
<description>True for almost all anime with school setting, there will be a school excursion or field trip. Tokyo and Kyoto seem to be particularly popular as sightseeing destinations. So are hiking excursions into the local mountains. This also is a good excuse to present the prefecture`s / city`s food specialities.
Potential for ecchi moments: Obviously the "boys" will get all sorts of ideas with the "girls" sleeping so close by.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2755" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>inline skating</name>
<description>`Inline skates` (often called Rollerblades after the popular trade name) are a type of roller skate used for inline skating. Unlike quad skates, which are configured with two front and two rear wheels, inline skates have two, three, four or five wheels arranged in a single line.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2787" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-28">
<name>teacher x student</name>
<description>Suggests a relationship involving a teacher and their student, often times sexual in nature.</description>
<picurl>206646.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2886" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>New Year`s Day</name>
<description>It is tradition in Japan to celebrate the new year at a Shinto shrine (hatsumode). The protagonists will offer some money, ring a bell at the end of a thick rope, and then pray for good fortune.
This usually goes along with gorging yourself at the many temporary food stalls, playing various games, and drawing a fortune.
The female characters in the anime will usually dress up in a kimono, to show off their traditional Japanese clothing, while watching the fireworks.</description>
<picurl>161028.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3237" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-16">
<name>test of courage</name>
<description>As part of a summer excursion or festival, an anime with school setting may also have a test of courage (or kimodameshi in Japanese), where the male and female students are paired up (by lottery) to retrieve a "charm" by passing though a "haunted house" or a scary forest at night.
The teachers usually disguise themselves as monsters or ghosts, scaring the students out of their socks.
This seems to be some sort of Japanese "coming of age" ritual, providing a certain level of excitement under controlled and safe circumstances.
Frequently seen in the Festival Episode.</description>
<picurl>38866.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3590" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-17">
<name>transforming guardian</name>
<description>Guardian-like characters in this anime, e.g. Guardian Angels, will actually transform into another usually "powered up" version of themselves.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4248" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-13">
<name>zoo visit</name>
<description>A visit to the zoo can provide some `personal moments` in a school setting anime. Or the destination of a field trip. Or it might simply be to visit the animals at the zoo.</description>
<picurl>160811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4496" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>public aquarium</name>
<description>A public aquarium is the aquatic counterpart of a zoo, housing living aquatic species for viewing. Most public aquariums feature tanks larger than those kept by home aquarists, as well as smaller tanks. Since the first public aquariums were built in the mid-19th century, they have become popular and their numbers have increased. Most modern accredited aquariums stress conservation issues and educating the public.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>167001.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5305" parentid="6234" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-29">
<name>tarot</name>
<description>The tarot is a pack of playing cards, most commonly numbering 78, used from the mid-15th century in various parts of Europe to play a group of card games such as Italian tarocchini and French tarot. From the late 18th century until the present time, the tarot has also found use by mystics and occultists for divination. Tarot cards are used throughout much of Europe to play card games. In English-speaking countries, where these games are largely unplayed, tarot cards are now used primarily for divinatory purposes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191977.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5944" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-28">
<name>i got a crush on you</name>
<description>It happens when a person develops an interest in someone that seems mysterious, smart, sexy, cute, fun, etc. Basically just someone you would like to spend more time with. Crushes are usually one sided and they happen more frequently among middle and high school students.
A person with a crush usually has a hard time expressing or conveying his/her feelings to that other person. That other person is usually clueless of the situation. Sometimes that person knows about the crush, but feels annoyed or embarrassed by it for some reason.
Having a crush on someone does not mean you are in love with that person, at least not yet. Depending on the situation crushes could develop differently (for better or worse):
1) Larger scale interactions (love).
2) Dating relationships.
3) Scary obsession or stalker type situations.
4) Disappear over time or distance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6234" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>motifs</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1283" type="main character in" update="2019-01-08">
<rating votes="568">8.88</rating>
<name>Kinomoto Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura`s given name (桜) means "cherry blossom". Her surname, Kinomoto (木之本), literally means "the origin of wood".
At the start of the series, Sakura is 10 years old and living in a fictional town called Tomoeda in Japan, located not far from Tokyo. One day in early April, shortly after her birthday and only slightly into her fourth grade year at Tomoeda Elementary School, young Sakura stumbles across a mysterious old book called The Clow in her father`s study. Instantly upon touching the book, a confused Sakura mistakenly awakens one of the card`s guardians, Cerberus who was sleeping on the front cover where he was supposed to be guarding the Clow Cards: a deck of 52 magical cards with incredible powers. Upon emerging from the book, Cerberus admits to having let the cards slip away as he slumbered, and, realizing Sakura`s magical potential, cunningly tricks her into becoming the "Cardcaptor" and duty bound to collect all of the missing cards and return them to the book where they will then be under her control.</description>
<picture>179473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="483" picture="27541.jpg">Tange Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7238" type="main character in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="141">7.82</rating>
<name>Li Syaoran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Syaoran is a distant relative of Clow Reed (on Clow`s mother`s side), the creator of the Clow Cards. As a member of the Li clan of sorcerers from Hong Kong, of which Clow`s mother was a member, Syaoran believes that he should be the one to inherit the Clow Cards, not Sakura Kinomoto. He first appears as an antagonist in the story, capturing a few cards for himself in the anime (though none in the manga). He acted cold and nonchalant to Sakura. He never even says her name until the third season. As the series progresses, and especially after Sakura is officially deemed the new master of the Cards, Syaoran drops his rivalistic attitude towards her and becomes her ally and friend, eventually falling in love with her. However, Sakura is completely oblivious to these feelings and thinks of him simply as a close friend.</description>
<picture>82459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7239" type="main character in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="92">7.27</rating>
<name>Cerberus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cerberus is the guardian of the mystical yet dangerous book of Clow cards. He is the guardian of the sun, one of the two duty bound to protect the powerful cards, and opposite of the lunar guardian, Yue. For several decades he was locked away in the book of the Clow, which held the cards upon the death of their previous master, Clow Reed, until a new master appeared to take hold of the cards and their guardians. Cerberus` character first appears at the beginning of the series when this new master, Sakura Kinomoto, releases him from the book. Once Cerberus is awakened (he was napping on the front cover) and released from the book he discovers the Clow cards have vanished, and appoints Sakura the title of Cardcaptor, and sends her off to retrieve the cards.</description>
<picture>82458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9580" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="156">7.70</rating>
<name>Daidouji Tomoyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoyo is Sakura`s best friend and her second cousin on her mother`s side. The daughter of the president of Daidouji Toy Company, Sonomi Daidouji, Tomoyo lives a life of wealth and is watched over by a team of female bodyguards.
When she learns of Sakura`s new role as a Cardcaptor, she insists that Sakura must wear "special clothes" and begins providing Sakura with the various costumes she wears during her captures as well as accompanying her on missions to record the events with her video camera. She has access to a variety of prototype technological gadgets from her mother`s company, and supplies Sakura and Cerberus with different communication devices throughout the series. She is depicted as being mature, kind-hearted, and intelligent, and regularly speaking using more formal verb conjugations and expressions than normally seen in elementary students. She is a talented singer, and is shown performing in various school events.</description>
<picture>42195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9581" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="34">8.32</rating>
<name>Yue</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yue is the one of two Guardians of the Clow Cards, along with Cerberus. While Cerberus acts as the elector, choosing a candidate to become the next Master of the Clow, Yue is the judge who will test the candidate. On the outside he acts very cold and aloof and is much more serious and intimidating than his counterpart, Cerberus. He shared a special bond with Clow that made it hard for him to accept Sakura Kinomoto as a "replacement" for his creator during the Final Judgment, although Sakura manages to work her way into his heart at least as a very good friend. Yue has jurisdiction over all things wind and water, the elements "under him" which in part draw on him for their existence. The known Clow Cards under his jurisdiction are Dark, Windy, Watery, Wood and Time.</description>
<picture>42198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9583" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-29">
<rating votes="47">5.23</rating>
<name>Tsukishiro Yukito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukito is the classmate and best friend of Sakura`s brother, Touya Kinomoto. Yukito`s nearly omnipresent smile is evidence of his kind and gentle nature. Yukito also loves food and has an enormous appetite.
Yukito is the false form of the Moon Guardian Yue. Although Yue knows everything about Yukito, Yukito is initially unaware of Yue`s presence. Once Yukito learns of his alter-ego`s existence, the two are able to communicate mentally. It is suggested that Yue is the reason for Yukito`s large appetite, as he is in a sense "eating for two."</description>
<picture>42197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9721" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="41">6.03</rating>
<name>Kinomoto Touya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Touya is the older brother of Kinomoto Sakura. His birthday is on February 29th, which makes him a leap year baby, a person that can only "properly" celebrate their birthday once every four years. His blood type is O. He holds the belief that as Sakura`s older brother, he is the only person entitled to make fun of her, a belief that his best friend Tsukishiro Yukito refers to as a "sister complex." However, he is also protective and caring of her, which leads him to dislike Li Shaoran when he finds Shaoran cornering Sakura in the schoolyard. Though Shaoran and Sakura eventually stop fighting, Touya continues to dislike Shaoran when he becomes friends with Sakura.
He is often working, and a running gag in the series involves Sakura and Yukito running into him while he`s at work, which can happen virtually anywhere.
He is a perceptive young man and has had a vague idea as to what Sakura has been up to as a Cardcaptor, despite Sakura`s attempts to keep it a secret. Touya was born with some magical ability, allowing him to see ghosts (including the one of his late mother). His magical ability is also what helps him sense when Sakura is in danger or when she is doing other "magical" things.</description>
<picture>42196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9882" type="appears in" update="2009-06-25">
<rating votes="8">9.43</rating>
<name>Clow Reed</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clow Reed is the magician who originally created the Clow Cards, and their magical guardians Cerberus and Yue. Born of an English father and a Chinese mother, Clow created a new type of magic that blended both Eastern and Western magical elements. His plan was to hand down the magic to people who would use and protect it while meeting all of the qualifications, however few people could learn his brand of magic. The character of Clow is only seen in flash backs, as he has long been dead before the series starts. Few details are revealed about his character, personality, or life.</description>
<picture>29951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1985" picture="21285.jpg">Hayashi Kazuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14566" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="7">5.77</rating>
<name>Kinomoto Fujitaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinomoto Fujitaka is the father of titular character Kinomoto Sakura. A busy professor of archaeology at Towa University, Fujitaka is a kind and caring father. He met his late wife Nadeshiko while doing his first year as a teacher at her high school. Nadeshiko had climbed a tree to return a baby bird to its nest, but fell out of the tree, landing on Fujitaka. Upon seeing her, he stated that "an angel has fallen from the sky." They fell in love and married when she was sixteen. Though Nadeshiko died seven years before the start of the series, Fujitaka is shown to still be very much in love with her and devoted to her memory. He keeps a picture of her in the dining room, changing it each morning.</description>
<picture>42189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14574" type="appears in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="7">5.23</rating>
<name>Kinomoto Nadeshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinomoto Nadeshiko is the mother of the series titular character, Kinomoto Sakura, who died seven years before the series starts. Only seen in flashbacks, photographs, and as a spirit, Nadeshiko was a high school student and professional model when she met and fell in love with Fujitaka Kinomoto, who was her teacher.
Though Nadeshiko has died, her love for Fujitaka and her children, and vice versa continues to live on. She frequently visits the family as a winged spirit, though initially only Touya can see her. Throughout the series, she worries over Sakura as the young girl begins gathering the Clow Cards. When the Illusion card tricks Sakura into walking off a cliff, Nadeshiko`s spirit grabs her arm and keeps her from falling until Yukito arrives to catch her. Later in the series, when Sakura develops a high fever, Nadeshiko appears and puts her hand on Sakura`s forehead, lowering the fever.
The family is shown to also still love her, most noticeably through a picture kept in the dining area near the kitchen table. Fujitaka changes the picture each morning and Sakura always greets the picture while coming to breakfast.</description>
<picture>42190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14576" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="17">7.31</rating>
<name>Mizuki Kaho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mizuki Kaho is a shrine maiden and the daughter of the priest at the Tsukimine Shrine. She first appears in the series as a new substitute teacher at Tomoeda Elementary School for the math class of Sakura and Syaoran. While Sakura instantly likes the teacher and feels a connection with her, Syaoran is distrustful and believes she is up to no good.
When Sakura, Syaoran, Meiling, and Tomoyo are trapped by the Maze card, Kaho uses a mysterious bell to break through Maze`s walls allowing Sakura to capture it. After this incident, the readers learn that Sakura`s older brother Touya dated Kaho when she was his junior high school teacher and that they broke up when Kaho left to study in England. Before she left, she told them that when they met again, they would be in love with different people which he acknowledges is now true.
After meeting her, Cerberus incorrectly believes that Kaho is the false form of his fellow guardian Yue. Kaho`s role is to use the bell left at her family`s shrine to give Sakura another chance when she is unable to defeat Yue out of fear of hurting him. The bell changes Sakura`s staff into a new staff containing her own power of the stars and gives her the power to use the cards to defeat Yue. After fulfilling this duty, she returns to England. During the third season of the series, she is primarily "seen" through providing a steady, but oftentimes enigmatic exchange of letters with Sakura over the mysterious attacks. After Eriol Hiiragizawa reveals the truth behind the attacks, they learn that Kaho had met Eriol three years before Sakura discovered the Book of the Clow. As they leave for England, Kaho and Eriol confirm their feelings for one another and vow to remain together. Kaho is last seen in the second film expressing concern for Sakura and her friends due to the incidents with the final card.</description>
<picture>42191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14577" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-12">
<rating votes="10">8.78</rating>
<name>Hiiragizawa Eriol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiiragizawa Eriol is the principal antagonist in the second half of the series, commonly called the Master of the Clow arc. The reincarnation of http://anidb.net/ch9882 [Clow Reed], Eriol has both Clow`s memories and all of his magic power. He has a magical staff similar to Clow Reed`s, can control Clow`s creations http://anidb.net/ch9581 [Yue] and http://anidb.net/ch7239 [Cerberus], and has created his own similar pair of guardians: http://anidb.net/ch14581 [Ruby Moon] and http://anidb.net/ch14579 [Spinel Sun]. He moves from England to transfer to Tomoeda Elementary school after http://anidb.net/ch1283 [Kinomoto Sakura] passed the Last Judgement and became the official master of the cards. He is depicted as a quiet, mature boy while at school, though he also shows a mischievous side when he regularly joins classmate http://anidb.net/ch14585 [Yamazaki Takashi] in weaving complex lies about the history of objects, places, and events. While seeming a normal student to Sakura, Syaoran is suspicious of him. It is soon shown that Yue and Cerberus are able to detect his magical signature as being Clow`s, and Eriol must erase Yue`s memories after he is accidentally seen by him.
Eriol came to Japan in order to aid Sakura and force her to use her own magical powers to convert the Clow Cards into Sakura cards. This is necessary as the cards take their magical energy from their master, but until Sakura converted them, they could not use her magic and were slowly dying. The guardian Yue also was suffering the same fate, forcing Sakura`s brother to "feed" him all of his magical power to prevent Yue, and his false form Yukito, from dying.
Sakura does not become aware that Eriol is causing all of the magical disasters that are causing her to convert the cards until near the end of the series when Eriol reveals himself to her. He puts the city to sleep and challenges Sakura to convert the last two cards, the Dark and the Light, which must be converted together. He then takes Sakura, Syaoran, http://anidb.net/ch9580 [Tomoyo], Yue, and Cerberus to his home where he explains why he had to give her a reason to convert the cards, as her doing so without a need could have sent the cards out of control or drained Sakura`s own life.
Eriol`s true age is unknown, as he used his magic to halt his aging process to remain the same physical age as Sakura. He is romantically involved with http://anidb.net/ch14576 [Mizuki Kaho], whom he originally sent from England to aid Sakura in the Final Judgment and who offers Sakura support through letters during the second arc. In the second anime movie, they are shown together when Sakura calls for advice.</description>
<picture>42192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14579" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="8">3.68</rating>
<name>Spinel Sun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Spinel Sun is the cat-like magical guardian created by Eriol as a counter part to Clow Reed`s original guardian Cerberus. Spinel Sun`s true form is a winged black panther, while his false form is similar to a small winged cat. Nicknamed Suppi by Ruby Moon, Spinel Sun spends most of his time reading and projects a calm demeanor. Ruby Moon often teases him that he needs to have more fun. During the series, he mostly remains out of sight of the main characters, except when he once runs into Cerberus in his false form. Fortunately for him, Cerberus doesn`t suspect anything and instead declares him a monster and feeds him sweets, not realizing that the sweets would turn Spinel Sun into a hyperactive eating machine. Cerberus does not learn his true identity until just before the final battle where the two cats face one another. Initially, Spinel Sun appears to have the upper hand, however Cerberus` greater determination to protect Sakura enable him to defeat him.</description>
<picture>42199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14580" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="9">4.95</rating>
<name>Akizuki Nakuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruby Moon is one of two magical guardians created by Eriol. The counterpart to the original guardian Yue, Ruby Moon is genderless but prefers to act as a female. When Eriol transfers to Tomoeda Elementary, Ruby Moon created a false form named Akizuki Nakuru and enrolls in Seijou High School, entering the same class as Touya, Sakura`s brother, and Yukito, the false form of Yue who is unaware of his true nature. As Akizuki, she acts as a general annoyance, deliberately interfering every time Touya tries to talk to Yukito about the latter`s dwindling energy. She claims she wants to consume Touya`s energy herself, though it is never stated that she actually has a need for it nor why she couldn`t simply steal it. When Touya is finally able to speak with Yue and give him all of his magical energy to sustain Yue`s life, Akizuki gives up her pursuit. In the final battle, Ruby Moon battles Yue and initially appears to be winning. However, Yue is able to get past her due to his greater determination and desire to protect Sakura.</description>
<picture>42201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14581" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-02">
<rating votes="3">5.17</rating>
<name>Ruby Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruby Moon is one of two magical guardians created by Eriol. The counterpart to the original guardian Yue, Ruby Moon is genderless but prefers to act as a female. When Eriol transfers to Tomoeda Elementary, Ruby Moon created a false form named Akizuki Nakuru and enrolls in Seijou High School, entering the same class as Touya, Sakura`s brother, and Yukito, the false form of Yue who is unaware of his true nature. As Akizuki, she acts as a general annoyance, deliberately interfering every time Touya tries to talk to Yukito about the latter`s dwindling energy. She claims she wants to consume Touya`s energy herself, though it is never stated that she actually has a need for it nor why she couldn`t simply steal it. When Touya is finally able to speak with Yue and give him all of his magical energy to sustain Yue`s life, Akizuki gives up her pursuit. In the final battle, Ruby Moon battles Yue and initially appears to be winning. However, Yue is able to get past her due to his greater determination and desire to protect Sakura.</description>
<picture>42202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14582" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="15">7.68</rating>
<name>Sasaki Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sasaki Rika is a classmate and friend of titular character Sakura Kinomoto. She is considered to be very elegant and mature for her age, though she can also be shy. During the series, she is also shown to be a skilled cook and very good at crafts. During the series, Rika is affected by the Clow Cards several times. Early in the series, she buys a brooch that is actually The Sword card. The card takes her over and causes her to attack Sakura. Sakura is able to stop Rika by using The Illusion card to show her an image of her beloved, allowing Sakura to capture the card. During the second half of the series, she is nearly drowned during a magical trial Eriol created to cause Sakura to convert a Clow Card to Sakura Card.
During the series, Rika is shown to be in a romantic relationship with her teacher Terada Yoshiyuki. Rika gives Terada the hand-made teddy bear she made, and he names it after her. When Sakura uses the Illusion card to stop Rika`s attacks, she calls the image "Sensei" which means "teacher" in Japanese. During the final judgment when Yue shows Sakura a world where everyone has lost their feelings for the one they love the most, Rika is shown handing Terada a paper without her usual blush and shy look.</description>
<picture>42203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="563" picture="73156.jpg">Kawakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14583" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="8">6.72</rating>
<name>Yanagisawa Naoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yanagisawa Naoko is one of Sakura`s elementary school classmates and friends. She is also on the cheerleading squad with Sakura. Naoko loves to read, particularly fantasy stories and ghost stories. She finds mysterious situations fascinating and shows no fear of scary situations. In the 31st episode of the anime adaptation, Naoko accidentally acquires the The Create card, which had disguised itself as a book. In book form, The Create would create anything that Naoko wrote in the book, though she was unaware of it. This results in Sakura and company having to deal with a confusing area of odd mystical creatures and circumstances, including a fire-breathing dragon. When she goes to bed and closes the book, the card`s power is stopped and Sakura is able to capture it. When Naoko wakes in the morning to find the book gone, she thinks it disappeared from a supernatural experience and is happy.</description>
<picture>42204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3954" picture="173079.jpg">Motoi Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14584" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="9">5.09</rating>
<name>Mihara Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mihara Chiharu is a friend and classmate of Sakura, as well as a fellow member of the cheerleading squad. Chiharu is often in charge of stopping Takashi when he starts spinning lies about the history of objects and events. Though she is regularly seen jokingly strangling him or dragging him away by his collar, they have been friends since kindergarten and are a couple.
When Sakura is shown a world where everyone connected to the cards has lost their feelings for the one they love the most, Chiharu and Takashi are shown reacting to one another as virtual strangers.</description>
<picture>42205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6928" picture="211675.jpg">Matsumoto Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14585" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="4">2.57</rating>
<name>Yamazaki Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamazaki Takashi is a student in Sakura`s class, and the only male student in the class to be referred to by name before the introduction of Syaoran. Throughout the series, Yamazaki`s defining trait is his ability to fabricate highly detailed fake stories and histories about practically any subject. While most of his classmates see through these fabrications, Sakura and Syaoran often believe them. When the character Eriol is introduced in the second half of the series, he becomes Yamazaki`s storytelling ally. The two are able to respond to one another`s clues perfectly and spin complex stories on the fly.
Fellow classmate Chiharu often interrupts his stories so others know when he is lying, and proceeds to punish him for lying by pretending to strangle him or by dragging him away by his collar. While the two often seem to be arguing, they are actually a couple and have known one another since kindergarten. She is the only girl in the series that he addresses by her first name.
Yamazaki is the only character to be rarely shown with his eyes open. On the day of Judgement when Sakura is shown a world in which everyone losing their feelings for the person they love the most, Yamazaki and Chiharu lose their feelings for each other and are shown to be strangers.</description>
<picture>42206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2899" picture="79024.jpg">Miyazaki Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14586" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="31">3.19</rating>
<name>Li MeiLing</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Li Meiling is a character that appears only in the anime adaptation of Cardcaptor Sakura. Introduced in episode 19, she is Syaoran`s cousin and self-proclaimed fiancée. As children living in Hong Kong, they both trained in martial arts under the tutelage of Wang Wei. One night her pet bird escaped from his cage, and the normally quiet and withdrawn Syaoran told her not to cry, then left. After spending hours in the rain, he returned with the bird and Meiling was both grateful and touched. From that day, she devoted herself to him, eventually declaring that she liked him above all others and, reasoning that he liked her as well, she declared them to be engaged. At the same time, she promised that if he ever found someone he liked more than her, she would give him up.
In coming to Tokyo, Meiling intends to help Syaoran gather the Clow Cards, and actively dislikes Sakura. As the series progresses, Meiling develops a grudging respect for Sakura that turns into a good friendship by the time Meiling returns to Hong Kong in episode 43. During her initial visit, Meiling seemed to recognize that Syaoran was falling in love with Sakura, but it wasn`t until she briefly returned in episode 60 that she fully acknowledges and accepts Sakura as the person Syaoran loves. Wanting to keep his promise, Syaoran attempts to tell her that he loves Sakura, but Meiling interrupts and tells him that she knows because he is now calling Sakura by her first name, something he only does for his sisters and herself. She smiles at Syaoran with tears in her eyes and declares that the engagement is called off, then quickly leaves. Meiling spends the night at Tomoyo`s house to release all of her sadness through much screaming and tears without burdening Syaoran. At the end of the episode, Meiling returns home and is not seen again in the main series. She returns in the second movie, with Syaoran, and together with Tomoyo tries to help Sakura confess her own feelings to him.
Unlike Syaoran, Meiling has no magical abilities, relying solely on her physical fighting abilities and a healthy dose of pride. Her lack of powers, however, results in her hindering more than helping Syaoran in most battles against the cards. She challenges the The Fight card in episode 20, and was nearly badly wounded and had to be rescued by Syaoran. Recognizing that she was being a burden, Meiling grew upset and lashed out at Syaoran. However, she was then able to be an aid to him while fighting The Twin card, as their years of practicing martial arts together enables them to match the card`s synchronized fighting style.</description>
<picture>42208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16" picture="16592.jpg">Nogami Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47601" type="appears in" update="2013-04-16">
<name>Terada Yoshiyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3124" picture="24096.jpg">Furusawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47607" type="appears in" update="2014-02-01">
<rating votes="4">5.87</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47608" type="appears in" update="2014-01-29">
<rating votes="13">5.69</rating>
<name>Daidouji Sonomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47610" type="appears in" update="2012-08-08">
<rating votes="13">3.89</rating>
<name>Cerberus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47617" type="appears in" update="2015-07-07">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2439" picture="166338.jpg">Araki Kae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47618" type="appears in" update="2012-10-06">
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<name>Nakagawa Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47619" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="2">3.12</rating>
<name>Kimura Yukie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61185.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3062" picture="170303.jpg">Saeki Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47620" type="appears in" update="2018-12-15">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Tachibana Yuuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2792" picture="26717.jpg">Kawata Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47621" type="appears in" update="2012-08-08">
<name>Kouno Kouichi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47622" type="appears in" update="2013-10-13">
<rating votes="2">3.12</rating>
<name>Midori Makiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61184.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="5041" picture="28798.jpg">Hayami Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47623" type="appears in" update="2015-07-08">
<rating votes="2">3.12</rating>
<name>Tsujitani Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47624" type="appears in" update="2012-08-08">
<name>Abe Katsuya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="6937" picture="171392.jpg">Imamura Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47625" type="appears in" update="2012-10-30">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Amamiya Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10276.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47626" type="appears in" update="2012-08-08">
<name>Kurokawa Keiko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="17264" picture="31688.jpg">Kanamaru Hinako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60367" type="appears in" update="2013-10-12">
<name>Yamamoto Toshinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61187.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="60368" type="appears in" update="2013-10-12">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Tsutsumi Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61188.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60369" type="appears in" update="2014-09-24">
<rating votes="2">3.12</rating>
<name>Tachibana Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66290" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Wei Wang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wei Wang is the attendant that comes with Syaoran Li when he first moves to Japan. A kind elderly man he has been teaching martial arts to Syaoran and Meilin since there childhood.</description>
<picture>153020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2355" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと不思議な魔法の本</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and The Mysterious Magic Book</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das geheimnisvolle Buch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et le livre magique</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">Sakura e o Misterioso Livro Mágico</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับหนังสือเวทย์มนต์มหัศจรรย์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Fushigi na Mahou no Hon</title>
<summary>Say hello t the lovely Sakura Kinomoto? She`s in my 4th grade class and she`s amazing. She lives with her father, who`s a college professor, and her brother Toya, who`s in high school. Her mother Nadeshiko, died when Sakura was only three years old.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659167</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2356" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのすてきなお友達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Wonderful Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakura und Tomoyo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La merveilleuse amie de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="pt">A Maravilhosa Amiga de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เพื่อนแสนดีของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Suteki na Otomodachi</title>
<summary>Lately, some strange things had been going on at our school... We came to school one morning to find that the school grounds and classrooms had been completely trashed by someone, or something! Sakura sensed a Clow Card on the loose, so she, Kero, and I all snuck our way into the school later that night to investigate! There, we discovered the culprit- the Shadow card! Luckily, I was able to help distract the card and Sakura managed to coax Shadow back into the Clow Book. That was also my first chance to become the director and producer of all of Sakura`s incredible celluloid adventures to come! Ahh, I was so happy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659169</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2357" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのドキドキ初デート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Heart Racing First Date</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakuras erste Verabredung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le premier rendez-vous de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เดทแรกที่แสนตื่นเต้นของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Doki Doki Hatsu Date</title>
<summary>We all took a school trip to the aquarium, where Sakura witnessed the spirit of the Watery card! Afterwards, she wound up there again when she went on her lovely date with Yukito, her brother`s best friend (which I caught on film!). Later that night, she, Kero and I all snuck into the aquarium and put our plan into motion! Sakura managed to lure Watery into a giant freezer, where it quickly turned to ice, allowing Sakura to capture it with no trouble!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659171</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2358" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのくたくた日曜日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Tiring Sunday</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakuras anstrengender Sonntag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un sacré dimanche pour Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">วันอาทิตย์ที่แสนยุ่งยากของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Kuta Kuta Nichiyoubi</title>
<summary>One Sunday, Sakura`s turn came to clean her house. While the rest of her family was out for the day, she came across the Wood card, along with another card whose name was covered by an ink stain! She soon discovered that Wood was working on its magic on the house, and it began turning into a miniature rainforest! Soon after that, she realized that Wood wasn`t working alone- as it turned out, the mystery card she found before was the Rain card! And because of all the rain, Wood was growing out of control. But with the help of Watery, Sakura managed to snag both Wood and Rain together. With that, her work as Cardcaptor was done for the day- but her housework was far from over!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659173</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2359" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらの怪盗初挑戦!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s First Attempt as a Thief</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakura und der kleine Dieb</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et le mystérieux voleur</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ประสบการณ์ขโมยครั้งแรกของซากุระ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Kaitou Hatsu Chousen!?</title>
<summary>During a school grip to the local art museum, Sakura noticed a young child causing a commotion over a painting called "The Smile." Right at that moment, everything around her went dead silent! Suspecting that it was the work of a Clow Card, Sakura snuck into the museum later that night, along with Kero and myself. And when we were there, we ran into that child again, who turned out to be the son of the painting`s artist! The boy told us that someone had defaced his father`s painting, and so he snuck into the museum in order to restore the painting to its original glory. And as it turned out, the one responsible for both the altered painting and Sakura`s sudden loss of hearing was the card known as Silent. Sakura, of course, was brave and smart enough to eventually find a way to steal the card away again. She`s just so wonderful!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659179</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2360" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとパンダとかわいいお店</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Panda, and a Cute Shop</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakura und die Kuscheltiere</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une histoire qui rebondit</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับแพนด้าและร้านขายของน่ารัก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Panda to Kawaii Omise</title>
<summary>Sakura and the rest of us happened to meet Ms. Maki Matsumoto, the owner of a fancy toy store called Twin Bells. Chiharu decided to buy a cute and cuddly toy, but not long after she got it home, it went missing! As it turned out, there was a rumor going around that whenever someone brought something from Twin Bells, whatever they bought would go missing not long after. Thanks to that rumor, business wasn`t going so great for Ms. Maki. How sad... but Sakura, Kero and I decided to go investigate the store. And lurking among the cuddly toys, we uncovered the Jump card! After a very cinematic struggle, Sakura managed to seal the card away again, and the next day, Twin Bells found itself overflowing with new customers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659175</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2361" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのライバル, 登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Rival Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Austauschschüler</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rivalité</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ศัตรูของซากุระ ปรากฎตัว!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Rival Toujou!</title>
<summary>A new boy has joined our class! His name is Xiaolang Li, and he`s from Hong Kong. We also found out that he wants to collect the Clow Cards, too! On the way home from school that day, Sakura stumbled across the Thunder card. She got the impression that there was some connection between this and Xiaolang`s presence, so she asked Kero about it. He explained that Clow Reed was a magician, and created the Clow Book. He also revealed that Xiaolang is a relative of Clow Reed`s on his mother`s side. And as it happened, Xiaolang`s amazing knowledge of the Clow Cards helped Sakura seal Thunder away. At the same time, though, Xiaolang was overly dismissive of Sakura`s ability, claiming that her magic is too weak to capture all the cards on her own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659181</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="2362" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとおかあさんの思い出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Memories of her Mother</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakuras Mutter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et le fantôme magique</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับความทรงจำของแม</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Okaasan no Omoide</title>
<summary>A few girls from my class decided to go into the woods behind school to investigate he rumor about ghost sightings in the area. But instead of a ghost, an image of Sakura`s late mother appeared! In her scramble to chase after the vision, Sakura fell off a cliff. But then Yukito came to the rescue! Sakura, Kero and I went back to the area again later, and that`s when Sakura discovered that her mother`s image was just a vision conjured up by the Illusion card! Yukito right- the real ghost of her mother would never do anything to hurt her. Sakura had to force herself to ignore the spirit`s resemblance t her beloved mother. She simply gritted her teeth and sealed the troublesome card away.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659177</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3503" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとふしぎなブローチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Mysterious Brooch</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakura und die geheimnisvolle Brosche</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La broche mystérieuse</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเข็มกลัดมหัศจรรย์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Fushigi na Brooch</title>
<summary>Sakura was feeling a little down about her skills as a Cardcaptor, so Rika and I decided to take her shopping and try to cheer her up! But the second Rika put on the sword shaped brooch she`d bought, she got taken over by the Sword card and turned against us! Being careful not to hurt her spellbound friend, Sakura cleverly used her Illusion card to seal Sword back in the Clow Book and return Rika back to normal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659183</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3504" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと花の運動会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Sport`s Day of Flowers</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tomoyos Mutter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et le champion de sport</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับงานกีฬาดอกไม้</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Hana no Undoukai</title>
<summary>The setting this time was sports day at our school, Tomoeda Elementary! This was the first chance for Sakura to meet my mother, Sonomi. We were also really surprised to find out that Sakura`s father knew my mother! As it turned out, he used to teach both my mother and Nadeshiko. Later, Mr. Kinomoto and my mother faced off in the parents 100-meter dash. My mother had held a grudge against him for a long time, believing that if her beloved cousin Nadeshiko hadn`t married him, she wouldn`t have died so young. But before too long, the race almost came to a stop, because the track had suddenly been covered in mysterious flower petals. It turned out that the Flower card was to blame, and Sakura used her amazing talents to seal it away, just like always! But my mother ended up losing to Mr. Kinomoto, and she got... well, angry. To restore the peace, Sakura used Flower to call down a shower of nadeshiko blossoms in honor of her mother, and my mother was so touched that she totally forgot about her anger. Exactly what I would expect from the Cardcaptor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659185</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3505" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとキケンなピアノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Dangerous Piano</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le piano mystérieux</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเปียโนอันตราย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Kiken na Piano</title>
<summary>Poor Sakura had been really tired lately. I guess that was because changing the Clow Cards into Sakura Cards takes a lot of energy. While I was practicing singing- and thinking about Sakura, of course- the piano started trying to squish me! Sakura is so smart that she figured out it was attracted to my voice, and used the Song Card to save me. Sakura said she sensed Clow Reed nearby which didn`t make sense because he died a long time ago...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659263</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3506" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと不思議なおみくじ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Strange Written Fortune</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`étrange prédiction</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเซียมซีประหลาด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Fushigi na Omikuji</title>
<summary>My mother and I ran into Sakura and her family at Tsukimine Shrine for New Year`s rituals. They were supposed to meet Yukito, but he didn`t show up so Toya went to go find him. Sakura and I went to get our fortunes and were really surprised to find Eriol giving them out instead of a shrine maiden! My fortune said that my dream would come true this year. I think it meant that I`ll get to film Sakura just the way I always wanted to! Sakura`s fortune was a lot more confusing, though... It said she`d learn the truth in her first dream of the new year. She told me she had a pretty strange dream that night, too.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659289</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3507" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと夏休みの宿題</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Summer Holiday Homework</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakuras Sommerhausaufgaben</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Devoirs de vacances</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับการบ้านปิดเทอมฤดูร้อน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Natsuyasumi no Shukudai</title>
<summary>With just one day left in her summer break, Sakura had repeated her mistake from last year- she still had a mountain of homework to get through! I decided to invite her to go to the library so that we could finish our homework together, but Sakura couldn`t seem to find the book she needed for her book report. We did manage to track it down, but just as we reached for it, the Move card transported it to another spot! And it did that again and again and again... Eventually, we ran into Xiaolang, and the two of them desperately chased after the book. Just as Sakura got her hands on it, she suddenly fell into a nearby stream. Soaked, she went to Xiaolang`s apartment and changed into a spare shirt of his. Just then, Xiaolang`s fiance (and cousin) Meiling burst through the door, spotted Sakura wearing the shirt that she had given Xiaolang as a present, and flew into an energetic rage! So much excitement for one day!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659203</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3508" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとケロと小狼と</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Kero, and Shaoran</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vertauschte Körper</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans la peau d`un autre</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเคโระกับเชาหลางและ...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Kero to Shaoran to</title>
<summary>While capturing the Change card, Kero and Xiaolang accidentally switched bodies, and had to send an entire day as each other before the spell could be undone. Neither one of them was good at impersonating the other, so I figure out what happened right away. Just as we were getting ready to leave school, Mr. Terada mistook Xiaolang (in Kero`s body) for a stuffed animal, so we went to the toy store to get him back. Unfortunately, Xiaolang was in the crane game, so Kero had to win him so they could switch back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659229</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3509" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと不思議な転校生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Mysterious Transfer Student</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une rentrée mouvementée</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับนักเรียนใหม่ผู้แปลกประหลาด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Fushigi na Tenkousei</title>
<summary>We got back from summer vacation to discover that we had a new student in the class! His name is Eriol Hiiragizawa and he came here from England, but Sakura thought she had met him before. That night, Kero and Sakura were talking about Eriol`s arrival when they felt a strange presence. We all went to Penguin Park in the rain to check it out, but a big stream of water attacked Sakura! When she tried to stop it, she realized that her magic wasn`t working!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659259</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3510" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと大切なお友達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and a Precious Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un noël mouvementé</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเพื่อนคนสำคัญ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Taisetsu na Otomodachi</title>
<summary>Meiling flew all the way here from Hong Kong just for a day so that Xiaolang could tell her something important in person. Everyone was so excited to be able to see her again! We decided to get some juice near Penguin Park to celebrate, but all of a sudden, the penguin statues in the park came to life and attacked us! It`s a good thing Meiling was there with her martial arts, because Sakura was too surprised to react and would have been smashed! I think that was when Meiling realized that Xiaolang really liked Sakura. Meiling was pretty upset and spent the night at my place before she went home, so I got to comfort her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659285</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3511" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのこわーいきもだめし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Scary Test of Courage</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die geheimnisvolle Höhle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Courage Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การทดสอบความกล้าแสนน่ากลัวของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Kowai Kimodameshi</title>
<summary>Everyone in our class got to go camping by the seaside, where we all took part in a test of courage. Sakura was terribly afraid, and even clung to me as we headed into the cave. She scremed in terror when she saw our teacher dressed up as a ghost but then something even weirder happened- people started to disappear! It turned out to be the Erase card, and it erased almost everyone from the area- even me! But then Xiaolang showed up, and with his help, Sakura was finally able to seal the card away.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659199</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3512" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとケガをしたカード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Injured Card</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das 100 Meter Rennen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le championnat</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับการ์ดที่บาดเจ็บ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Kega o Shita Card</title>
<summary>Sakura tried to seal the Dash card, but it escaped into someone`s yard, and some lady said the battle costume I made for Sakura looked strange. Anyway, the girl who lives there, Rei Tachibana, took Dash in and bandaged its wounds. The next day, Rei, who was struggling with the 100-meter dash, began to set personal best times thanks to Dash`s influence. I went with Sakura and Kero to Rei`s house to try to get closer to Dash, but after talking to Rei, and hearing how hard she was trainignf or a big track meet, Sakura changed her mind about sealing Dash away. Two days before the big track meet, Xiaolang noticed Dash`s presence, which forced Sakura to seal the Dash card away, and left Rei frantically searching for Dash in the park near her house. Feeling bad for Rei, Xiaolang called upon Dash to show itself to Rei right before the 100-meter dash final, which cheered her up enough to win on her own!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659225</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3513" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと最後のクロウカード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Final Clow Card</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La dernière carte</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับโคลว์การ์ดใบสุดท้าย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Saigo no Clow Card</title>
<summary>Sakura figured out how to capture the Earthy card all by herself! That meant that all the cards had been captured. Sakura is so amazing! With all the cards caught, Kero returned to his true form, and so did Yue. It turned out that Yukito was Yue all along! Yue claimed to be administering the "Final Judgement" and took Xiaolang up on the roof and beat him up pretty badly. And then he said that Sakura was next.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659255</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3514" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとケロの大げんか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Kero`s Big Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf der Suche nach Kero</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De l`orage dans l`air</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การทะเลาะครั้งใหญ่ของซากุระกับเคโระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Kero no Daigenka</title>
<summary>Kero and Sakura got in a big fight, and Kero ran away from home... After falling asleep on the street, he woke up to find himself in a strange apartment. It turned out that a little girl named Akane had found him and brought him back to where she and her mother lived together, just the two of them. Sakura and I went looking for him, but it was no use. Meanwhile, Akane was left home alone while her mother went to work, and Kero decided he couldn`t just leave her there by herself. Just then, the Float card came and carried Akane high up into the sky. Kero tried his best to go after her; but he just couldn`t keep up. All of a sudden, Sakura rushed in and sealed Float away! She had asked me t help track down where he was, and managed to arrive just in time. A few days later, Akane was forced to part ways with Kero when she and her mother moved to a new city. A little embarrassed by the whole thing, Kero bashfully returned home with Sakura.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659195</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3515" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのさよなら苺鈴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Farewell to Meiling</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bon voyage Stéphanie !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระอำลาเหม่ยหลิง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Sayonara Meiling</title>
<summary>Meiling`s mother called to tell her she needed to go back to Hong Kong. Meiliing was pretty upset because Xiaolang didn`t seem concerned that she was leaving, but he said he just realized that there was no point in fighting it. The Twin Card made an appearance that night and started making doubles of everything, even Mr. Wei! Sakura and Xiaolang tried to capture them, but since they weren`t in perfect unison, it didn`t work! It`s a good thing Meiling and Xiaolang trained together so much, because they were able to kick the Twins` butts and let Sakura seal them away! Too bad Meiling still had to go home to Hong Kong, but at least she had made up with Xiaolang.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659251</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3516" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとゾウの力くらべ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Elephant`s Test of Strength</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Kraftprobe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épreuve de force</title>
<title xml:lang="sv">Sakura och Elefanterna</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระประลองกำลังกับช้าง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Zou no Chikara Kurabe</title>
<summary>On the news, they talked about how the Penguin King statue at Penguin Park got ripped out of the ground and flipped upside down! That was the same day our class headed to the zoo for a field trip, where the Power card happened to show up. Power just loves to compare its strength to others, so it was breaking open cage after cage, looking for a suitable opponent. The zoo turned into total chaos, with animals escaping and running around all over the place! Finally, Sakura challenged Power to a test of strength, and just when it looked like she was about to lose, Xiaolang saved the day with his Time card and helped Sakura win the challenge!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659191</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3517" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと二人の大ピンチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Double Trouble</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le double problème de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับวิกฤติของทั้งสอง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Futari no Dai Pinch</title>
<summary>Yue and Kero got stuck in their true forms! Sakura needed to figure out a way for them to change back into their temporary forms, but she had a lot of chores to do. Kero was helping her, but ended up making a huge mess with the flour. When Sakura talked to Kero and Yue about Clow Reed, she noticed that Yue seemed to really care about him. Still stumped for a solution to their problem, Sakura received a package of crab in the mail and had a brilliant idea! She decided to use the Shield card to protect Yue and Kero from any outside magic.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659281</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3518" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとおまじないカード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Enchanted Cards</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakura und die Zauberkarten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cartes magiques</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับการ์ดอธิษฐาน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Omajinai Card</title>
<summary>Charm cards, which look a lot like Clow Cards, became really popular at our school. Naoko and Chiharu bought several ones, but when I went with Sakura to get her a cooking one, Ms. Maki was all sold out. When we came back the next day, Sakura sensed that a Clow Card used to be in the shop, but was no longer there. We discovered Meiling had bought the Shot card, thinking it was just a charm card. Sakura and Xiaolang found her on the roof of the school, but Meiling activated the card by accident, and it targeted him! Sakura and Xiaolang worked together to seal the dangerous card away, and I got it all on tape!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659221</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3519" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと小狼と砂の海</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Li, and the Sea of Sand</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sables émouvants</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเชาหลางกับทะเลทราย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Shaoran to Suna no Umi</title>
<summary>our class got to perform "Sleeping Beauty" in the school arts festival! We were given random roles, and Sakura ended up being the prince and Xiaolang was the princess. Xiaolang didn`t seem too happy about it, at least until he found out Yukito was going to come watch. Then he decided to put in extra practice before school with Sakura so that he could impress Yukito. When they showed up early, their practice was interrupted by the Sand card! Xiaolang had another smart idea and they managed to capture it. Xiaolang thought it was strange that the card showed up to attack when they were alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659247</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3520" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと知世と大きなお家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Tomoyo, and a Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zu Besuch bei Tomoyo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gouter chez Tiffany</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับบ้านหลังใหญ่ของโทโมโยะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Tomoyo to Ookina Ie</title>
<summary>I decided to invite Sakura over to my house, and while she was there, my mother told us all kinds of interesting stories about Nadeshiko and Sakura`s father that we had never heard before. Afterwards, I told Sakura about a box of mine that had something very special in it, but which was stuck shut. Sakura figured out that the Shield card was what was keeping it from opening, so she used her Sword card to seal Shield away and open up the box! And with it open, I was able to show her the cherry blossom bouquet that Sakura`s mother had carried on her wedding day... along with my most precious possession- an eraser that my very best friend Sakura, had given to me.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659187</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3521" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとケロのお菓子な出会い??</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Kero, and a Candy Encounter??</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vente de charité</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเคโระกับการพบปะเพราะขนม??</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Kero no Okashi na Deai??</title>
<summary>We got to hand out sweets and juice to everyone who attended the school`s bazaar. Of course, Kero showed up because he can`t stay away from tasty food! Somebody snuck through and ate all the sweets! We thought it was Kero, but he said that while he was hiding in the woods, he ran into a panther-like version of himself! The other Kero was named Supie. Since Kero is super nice, he invited Supie to share some treats with him, but then Kero discovered that Supie turns into a sweets vacuum when he has sugar! That`s what Kero claimed happened anyway.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659277</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3522" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとすてきな先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Wonderful Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verloren im Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une prof pas comme les autres</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับอาจารย์แสนวิเศษ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Suteki na Sensei</title>
<summary>A beautiful woman caught Sakura as she was rushing on her skates. The woman turned out to be our new substitute math teacher, Ms. Mizuki. Sakura seemed to be distracted by her beauty, and Xiaolang warned us that he sensed something about her. Later that day, Sakura and I went to Tsukimine Shrine so she could get a charm that grants romantic wishes. At the shrine, we ran into Xiaolang and Meiling, who also wanted to get a charm, and then we were suddenly trapped in a giant maze! We tried to find our way out, but none of our tactics worked. Then, Ms. Mizuki showed up and used a mysterious bell to break down the walls until we found the exit! After that, Sakura was able to seal the card away, and Ms. Mizuki gave Sakura and Meiling the charms they had come for.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659217</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3523" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと思い出のカレンダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Calendar of Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le calendrier des souvenirs</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับปฏิทินแห่งความทรงจำ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Omoide no Calendar</title>
<summary>Sakura was so happy when her father gave her mother`s old calendar! After seeing all the dates her mother wrote down, Sakura realized that it was her great grandfather`s birthday. She was sad to find out that he didn`t like her father, and decided to show him how happy they all were together! Sakura put together a really thoughtful present for her great grandfather, just like her mother used to do. She made a handmade gift, and added pink flowers with the Flower card, and even wrote her great grandfather a beautiful letter so he`d know they were all happy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659273</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3524" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらの小さな大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Little Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakuras "kleines" Abenteuer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura a disparu</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การผจญภัยครั้งใหญ่ของซากุระตัวเล็ก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Chiisa na Daibouken</title>
<summary>One of the programs Sakura always watches on TV is about famous castles, because she dreams of living like a princess, I came over to her house the day after she watched one such program, to take her measurements for a new battle costume I was making fr her. While I was there, Sakura sensed a Clow Card inside the house! She tracked it to her father`s room, but the Little card made Sakura tiny and she got blown out the window. Kero and I couldn`t find her anywhere, but thanks to my good acting, Toya and Yukito had no idea she was missing. After being chased by a cat and praying mantis outside. Sakura managed to make her way back into the house. With Kero`s help, she was able to turn back to normal, and the seal card away.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659213</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3525" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと現れたクロウ・リード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura Meets Clow Reed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour vers le passé</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับโคลว์รีดในปัจจุบัน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Arawareta Clow Reed</title>
<summary>It turned out that the new Clow Reed was really Eriol! We were all so confused. Eriol told us that he was actually the incarnation of Clow Reed. He used his magic to darken the sky and put everyone without magical powers to sleep! When I woke up, Sakura said that to save everyone, she had needed to change the rest of the cards to Sakura Cards. I`m glad that she`s so strong! Eriol disappeared though, so we didn`t get any answer from him, but Xiaolang finally told Sakura about his feelings!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659303</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3526" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのふらふら熱曜日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Dizzy Fever Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jour de fièvre</title>
<title xml:lang="th">วันไข้ขึ้นสูงของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Fura Fura Netsuyoubi</title>
<summary>Sakura got sick! Since she had a fever, the nurse sent her home from school early. She didn`t get much rest though, because the Cloud card was out causing trouble. Since she`s such a hard worker, Sakura decided to capture the Cloud card even though she was sick and Kero told her not to. To fool Toya, she used Mirror to make a copy of herself before sneaking out. She looked pretty wobbly flying around, but luckily Xiaolang and Meiling were there to support her as she captured the card.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659243</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3527" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのひつじ注意報?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Sheep Warning?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura compte les moutons</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับการเตือนภัยแกะ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Hitsuji Chuuihou!?</title>
<summary>Sakura was still pretty tired from changing more cards into Sakura Cards, and had a hard time staying awake in class. Meanwhile, Yukito was starting to get concerned about how tired he was and how much he had been blacking out. It turned out that his issues were because Yue`s power was running out. If Yue were to run out of power, then both of them would disappear. Toya noticed something wrong with Yukito, and wanted to help, but Nakuru got in his way. When we went to Penguin Park that night, Sakura felt Clow Reed`s presence again, and we found a huge pit! After hopping in it, Sakura said she got covered in sheep, but she managed to escape and close it up!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659269</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3528" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとやさしいお父さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Her Kind Father</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Keine Zeit zum Schlafen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le grand sommeil</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับคุณพ่อใจดี</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Yasashii Otousan</title>
<summary>Sakura`s father had been working day and night getting ready for an upcoming presentation, even staying in his office overnight to finish it. So Sakura decided to visit him on campus to bring him some food, and she invited me along. Sakura`s so wonderful! But the Sleep card had also appeared and put Mr. Kinomoto and his assistants to sleep. Sakura managed to corner sleep in her father`s office and seal it away, but all of his lecture materials were destroyed in the struggle. Sakura tearfully apologized to him, and he gently replied that he would just start over. That night, Sakura saw that he stayed up all night rewriting his lecture, so the next day she offered to do whatever she could to help him. So he asked her to become his personal assistant for the day making her extremely happy that she was able to help her father.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659209</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3529" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと小狼と月峰神社</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Shaoran and the Tsukimine Shrine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une bien belle journée</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเชาหลางกับศาลเจ้าสึกิมิเนะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Shaoran to Tsukimine Jinja</title>
<summary>Sakura found out there was going to be a moon festival at Tsukimine Shrine and invited Xiaolang to go along with all of us. Sakura was really tired in the days leading up to the festival because she was staying up late knitting a scarf for Xiaolang as a thank you for all of his help. At the festival, I tried talking to Xiaolang into telling Sakura how he felt about her, but he was too worried that it would just give her something else to worry about. The lights at the festival went out, and after dealing with a magical horse (that I finally got to record!), Sakura used the Glow card to keep the festival going.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659299</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3530" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと消えた知世の声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Tomoyo`s Lost Voice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tiffany est sans voix !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเสียงที่หายไปของโทโมโยะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Kieta Tomoyo no Koe</title>
<summary>We had a singing competition coming up so i was spending a lot of time practicing my solo, but then I suddenly lost my voice! Sakura came rushing to hel me but she was too late... Still, I`m so glad she`s my friend! We found ou tthe Voice card had stolen my voice. Sakura was really upset, which made me sad, but I knew she could capture it and get my voice back. Xiaolang had a great idea to lure the Voice card out, and it worked! Sakura captured it and got my voice back just like I knew she would.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659239</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3531" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと小狼とみえない糸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Shaoran, and the Invisible Threads</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura, Lionel et les fils invisibles</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเชาหลางและด้ายที่มองไม่เห็น</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Shaoran to Mienai Ito</title>
<summary>We found out that making a handmade teddy bear and giving it to the person you like makes them liek you back, so Sakura decided to make one. We went to the craft store with Eriol and Xiaolang to get some supplies. Sakura told me that she sensed Clow Reed while she was makign her teddy bear at home that night, so she met Xiaolang to hunt down the source. But when they met up, Xiaolang started trying to attack Sakura! Luckily, Xiaolang helped Sakura figure out that he was being controlled by some mysterious threads so she could save him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659265</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3532" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとたたかう転校生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Transfer Student vs. Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Austauschschülerin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La nouvelle élève</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับนักเรียนใหม่จอมซ่า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Tatakau Tenkousei</title>
<summary>Just as the new school term began, another transfer student joined our class. It was Meiling, Xiaolang`s bride to be, and she`d just arrived from Hong Kong! Meanwhile, the Fight card appeared and began taking on skilled martial artists all across the city. Sakura headed to Penguin Park to seal it away, but out of nowhere Meiling appeared to challenge the card! Unfortunately, she was no match for it and started to lose ground, but then Sakura jumped in and used her Power card to seal Fight away! But Meiling couldn`t stand the fact that Sakura was the one to save her, and only made her view of Sakura as her rival that much stronger.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659205</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3533" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと雪兎と消えゆく力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Yukito and the Vanishing Power</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des avalanches de problèmes</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับยูกิโตะกับพลังที่เหือดหายไป</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Yukito to Kieyuku Chikara</title>
<summary>Yukito and Toya got cast as the main characters in a film for the high school`s fair! When Sakura stumbled into one of their scenes, Nakuru, the director, asked her to be in the movie too! I came along to the filming so that I could shoot some behind-the-scenes footage fo my own and capture Sakura`s debut on the silver screen. Yukito ended up getting super tired and fell off a balcony during a scene! It turned out that it was because Yue was almost out of energy, so Toya gave Yue his own magic power to keep Yue and Yukito from disappearing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659295</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3534" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのすてきなクリスマス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Wonderful Christmas</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampf der Elemente</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Noël de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับคริสต์มาสแสนวิเศษ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Suteki na Christmas</title>
<summary>Sakura got everyone Christmas presents except Yukito... It`s so hard to decide what to get someone you like that much! After some advice from Meiling, she invited Yukito to the amusement park to give him his gift. Of course, I couldn`t miss filming her romantic date, so Kero and I snuck after them. I guess everyone likes the amusement park, because while they were there, they ran into Xiaolang, Meiling, and even Toya (working, of course). Things started getting hot when everything burst into flame! It was the Firey card! I missed filming Sakura`s daring capture since Xiaolang used the Time card and Sakura put everyone to sleep with the Sleep card. After she captured Firey using Windy and Watery at the same time, they all took a ride on the Ferris wheel. While they were on it, Sakura gave Yukito his gift, and Kero used his power to make the whole sky glitter! It was so beautiful!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659235</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3535" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとプールと大きな波</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, the Pool and the Huge Wave</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vague</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับสระว่ายน้ำกับคลื่นยักษ์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Pool to Ookina Nami</title>
<summary>We went to the new water park in Tomoeda! It was so wonderful to have a chance to fim Sakura in her swimsuit, even in the winter! Sakura made Kero stay behind because we were with our friends and there were s many people nearby. After Sakura finished giving Rika a swimming lesson, we got some cream soda, and Kero showed up! I knew Sakura couldn`t keep Kero away from such tasty treats. All of a sudden, the wave pool started going crazy and Rika got trapped in it! Sakura couldn`t use her magic because there were so many people, but I noticed there was a waterslide that she could hide in. On her way down it, she and used Watery to stop the waves and save Rika.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659291</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3536" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのさむーいアイススケート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Cold Ice-skating</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein eiskalter Klassenausflug</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une journée à la patinoire</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ไอซ์สเก็ตอันหนาวเหน็บของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Samui Ice Skate</title>
<summary>Our class got to go to the ice rink for a field trip! Sakura was worried that she wouldn`t be good at ice skating, but I knew she would pick it up fast. And guess what? She did! The ice rink got really cold all of a sudden, though- so cold that we were all frozen! Luckily Sakura and Xiaolang were there, and saved us all from the Freeze card.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659231</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3537" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとめざめた星の鍵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Awakened Star Key</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cartes ont changé</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับกุญแจแห่งดวงดาวที่ถือกำเนิด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Mezameta Hoshi no Kagi</title>
<summary>Sakura was pretty sad that her magic wasn`t working anymore, but Eriol gave her a flower at school, and that seemed to cheer her up a bit. He`s so nice! Xiaolang saw what happened and got pretty upset... It still hadn`t stopped raining from the day before, and Sakura decided to do something about it. When we went to search for the cause of the rain, Sakura`s magic still didn`t work and we were all trapped in water geysers! Luckily, Clow Reed talked to Sakura somehow and she managed to get her star staff working! She was even able to change a Clow Card into a Sakura Card with her new star power!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659261</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3538" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとカードとプレゼント</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, the Card, and the Presents</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura jette un froid</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับการ์ดกับของขวัญ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Card to Present</title>
<summary>Christmas was just around the corner and everyone was figuring out their last minute presents. Sakura had everyone`s planned, but felt like she was still forgetting one. I had to get ready to film Sakura being super cute on Christmas day, so I didn`t wait for Sakura and Xiaolang to finish their school chores to walk home with them. Besides, Sakura had to go shopping with Toya for her father`s gift. When their school chores were finally done, they felt Clow Reed nearby and decided to check it out. Sakura had to call on the Mirror card again to go with Toya. After dealing with Clow Reed`s disturbance, Sakura realized she hadn`t gotten a gift for the cards and had Eriol help her record a hymn for them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659287</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3539" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと雪兎と夏祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Yukito, and the Summer Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Yukito und das Sommerfest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête de l`été</title>
<title xml:lang="th">เทศกาลฤดูร้อนของซากุระกับยูกิโตะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Yukito no Natsumatsuri</title>
<summary>A bunch of us decided to go to the summer festival at Tsukimine Shrine, and while we were there I saw a chance to give Sakura and Yukito a little time alone. As they were walking around together, they accidentally wound up behind the shrine, where they saw hundreds of tiny lights floating around like fireflies. The mood started to turn romantic, but it was ruined when Xiaolang and Toya showed up. Sakura suspected the lights might be the doing of a Clow Card, so she called out her staff and discovered that she was right- the lights were actually the Glow card! Sakura captured the card, but she`ll always be grateful to it for creating an air of romance for her and Yukito.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659201</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3540" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと名前のない本</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Nameless Book</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakura und der rote Drache</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le livre sans nom</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับหนังสือไร้ชื่อ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Namae no Nai Hon</title>
<summary>After school one day, the girls and I ended up going to a used bookstore, but Sakura noticed the presence of a Clow Card. Since the area was so crowded, we decided to come back later that night to capture the card. When we came back, Xiaolang and Meiling showed up, and Kero and Meiling started arguing until we saw a huge cat walking around toward us! The cat chased us, but was happy to just cuddle with Xiaolang until Sakura captured the Big card, and the cat returned to normal. Just when we thought we were done for the day, animals with strange wings and swirly eyes started popping up everywhere. It turns out someone was using the Create card and everything they were writing was coming true! We were going to save capturing it until the next day, but then a huge dragon appeared and started heading toward town, so Sakura used the Big card on herself and fought the dragon! Just when it looked like Sakura was going to lose, the person stopped writing, and Sakura was able to capture the Create card, too!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659227</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3541" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと最後の審判</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Final Judgement</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jugement final</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับคำพิพากษาสุดท้าย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Saigo no Shinpan</title>
<summary>Yue revelaed that if Sakura couldn`t defeat him, everyone would forget about the person they care most about. So that was the catastrophe we had heard about. Sakura had a really rough time trying to defeat Yue since he`s still Yukito on the inside and she didn`t want to hurt him. She almost lost, and saw how sad it would be if everyone forgot their most loved person. Luckily, Ms. Mizuki was there and rang her bell to keep Sakura in the fight! Sakura discovered her own special star power and managed to defeat Yue! After he declared her the new Master of the Clow Cards, sweet Sakura said that she would rather they all be friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659257</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3542" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと思い出の虹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Rainbow of Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ferien im Sommerhaus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et l`arc en ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับสายรุ้งในความทรงจำ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Omoide no Niji</title>
<summary>With Kero stuffed into her bag, Sakura joined her family (and Yukito) on a trip to a summer home her father was borrowing. Near the house, Sakura met an elderly man named Masaki living in an especially large home in the area, and they became fast friends. She visited him again the next day, and gave her a dress that used to belong to his now deceased granddaughter. Sakura was trying to think of some way to repay his kindness when she remembered the painting of a rainbow she`d seen in his granddaughter`s room. On the day she was set to leave, she asked Masaki to stand on his balcony and look up at the sky, then used her Rain card to create an impromptu rainbow. How sweet of her! And as it turned out, the painting had been done by Nadeshiko, and Masaki as actually Sakura`s great grandfather!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659197</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3543" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとケロと不思議な先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Kero, and the Mysterious Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La compétition de tir à l`arc</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเคโระกับอาจารย์พิศวง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Kero to Fushigi na Sensei</title>
<summary>Yukito was chosen to represent his school at a big archery competition. Sakura decided to do something really nice for him, and made a whole bunch of lunch boxes! We were surprised to find out that Ms. Mizuki was in the competition too. It ended up being her and Yukito in the finals, but Ms. Mizuki was distracted on her last shot and lost. After the match, Ms. Mizuki met Kero, and we found out that she knows about Yue, and some kind of "Final Judgement." On the way home, the last card, Earthy, started busting things up!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659253</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3544" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと桃矢でシンデレラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Touya, and Cinderella</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Theateraufführung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est la fête</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับโทยะและซินเดอเรลล่า</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Touya to Cinderella</title>
<summary>Ahh, school fairs are just the best! While Toya was busy getting ready for the school play, Yukito showed us around and then took us to the gym before the big performance. Onstage, Toya played the part of Cinderella, and he was just incredible. But suddenly... the Mist card appeared and the set began to crumble away! As the upper part of the stage began to collapse, Toya`s co-star Yoko (who also had a crush on him) took a tumble. Toya managed to grab her hand, but had to hang on for dear life to keep from dropping her! Sakura managed to seal the card away, saving Toya and Yoko in the nick of time. As the fair drew to a close, Yoko confessed her feelings to Toya, but he had to turn her away. She had half-expected that kind of answer, and after recovering she asked him to at least join her in a single dance. So romantic!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659193</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3545" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと知世とボールの罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Tomoyo, and the Ball Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura déchaîne les passions</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับโทโมโยะกับกับดักลูกบอล</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Tomoyo to Ball no Wana</title>
<summary>We all headed to the school after Sakura sensed Clow Reed there. When we arrived we noticed a basketball bouncing all by itself. We chased it into a classroom, but the door slammed shut like a trap! We tried to leave, but when we opened the door to the hallway, it just led to another classroom! I was too slow and got stuck in a classroom all alone. Every door just seemed to lead to a different classroom. I think Sakura started getting scared, so I began singing to let her know I was okay. Eventually, Sakura had the brilliant idea of using the Shadow card to find and save me, just like I knew she would!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659283</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3546" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのあまーいクッキング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Sweet Cooking</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Süße Geheimnisse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura fait la cuisine</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ตำรับแสนหวานของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Amai Cooking</title>
<summary>Sakura baked a cake with her father to practice for our home ec class. It turned out so well, we were sure our cake would turn out great, too. But our entire class baked cakes that were too sweet, so we had to try again the next week. During our second attempt, while the class took a break for lunch, Sakura and Xiaolang discovered that the Sweet card had been tampering with the cakes. With the help of salt, Sakura was able to seal the card away, and none of our cakes were too sweet this time!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659223</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3547" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのまっくら学芸会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Blacked Out School Arts Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La nuit tombe sur le festival...</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับงานโรงเรียนที่มืดมิด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Makkura Gakugeikai</title>
<summary>After all our practice, it was finally time for the play! I was so excited that I stayed up for two days making costumes for Sakura and Xiaolang. They looked so cute in them! Just as they were about to kiss in the play, the Dark card showed up and turned everything pitch black! Sakura noticed that she could still see herself though, and discovered it was because the Light card was within her! As she sealed up the cards, they hinted that Yue was somewhere nearby.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659249</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3548" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらの終わらない一日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Never-ending Day</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sakuras endloser Tag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une journée sans fin</title>
<title xml:lang="th">หนึ่งวันที่ไม่จบของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Owaranai Ichinichi</title>
<summary>One day, Sakura and Xiaolang both noticed that events throughout the day seemed to be repeating themselves. They soon discovered that the Time card was causing things to happen over and over again! Later that night, we all headed for our school`s clock tower, which was where Time had hidden itself. After a few efforts, we were finally able to invade the clock tower and reach the top. Time tried to flee, but Xiaolang used his magic to stop it and allow Sakura to seal it away. But Time didn`t go to Sakura like we expected- instead, it flew to Xiaolang. It was then that we learned each Clow Card returns to the person who actually succeeded in subduing its power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659189</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3549" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと小狼とエレベーター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Shaoran, and the Elevator</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sentiments et révélations</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเชาหลางกับลิฟต์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Shaoran to Elevator</title>
<summary>Xiaolang still didn`t seem to be able to get Sakura out of his head. Which makes sense since she`s so adorable! But he didn`t know why she was always on his mind, and seemed troubled by it. Eriol, Sakura, Xiaolang and I went to see the Teddy Bear Exhibit and I noticed that Xiaolang was always keeping an eye on Sakura. When I mentioned it, Xiaolang got embarrassed and wanted to go home, but instead, he and Sakura got stuck in the elevator together! Sakura said that she fell out of the elevator down the shaft, but used the Float card to save herself. Xiaolang was really worried about her though... I think the look cute together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659279</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3550" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="13">9.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと本当の想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Her True Feeling</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les vrais sentiments de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับความรู้สึกที่แท้จริง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Hontou no Omoi</title>
<summary>Sakura seemed a bit preoccupied at school... I wonder if it was because of Xiaolang or Eriol. After school, Eriol invited us over to his house to say goodbye and to explain everything. It turned out that all the crazy things that had been happening were actually because of him! He was trying to help Sakura become the true master of the cards. I talked to Xiaolang to find out what Sakura had said when he revealed her how he felt, and he told me that she didn`t say anything! I then found out that Xiaolang was going to leave for Hong Kong without hearing how Sakura felt! I couldn`t let that happen and made sure Sakura had a chance to see Xiaolang...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659305</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3551" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと思い出の神社</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Shrine of Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Schrein der Erinnerungen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour vers le passé</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับศาลเจ้าในความทรงจำ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Omoide no Jinja</title>
<summary>Kero sensed a Clow Card, which led him and Sakura to Tsukimine Shrine, where they were joined by Xiaolang, who also sensed the card, After searching for nearly an hour, they took a break, and Sakura got sucked into the shrine`s sacred tree! It turned out the Return card had sent Sakura back to the past, when Toya and Ms. Mizuki first met. Hidden up in the tree, Sakura overheard parts of their conversations as time jumped ahead to their meetings under the tree. But just as Sakura was about to get some clue, she found that she had returned to the present time, and was able to seal the Return card! However, it went to Xiaolang, who had used a lot of energy using the Time card to rescue Sakura.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659219</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3552" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと夢の中のさくら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Sakura in the Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rêve de Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับซากุระในความฝัน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Yume no Naka no Sakura</title>
<summary>We all decided to go into the city to go shopping and to see Tokyo Tower. Sakura seemed a little distracted, and said it was because of a dream she kept having. When we got to the tower, we were all excited to see the top, but as soon as Sakura went inside, she collapsed! Xiaolang sensed a Clow Card, but we couldn`t find it for a while, until he realized that Sakura had stepped on it. Xiaolang used the Time card and woke up Sakura so she could seal away what turned out to be the Dream card!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659245</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3553" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと不思議の国のさくら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Sakura from Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura au pays des merveilles</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับซากุระในแดนมหัศจรรย์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Fushigi no Kuni no Sakura</title>
<summary>Sakura started reading "Alice in Wonderland," and she loved it. But she ended up getting literally pulled inside the story! She said she saw everyone she knew turned into characters from the story; Toya was the Mad Hatter, Yukito was the White Rabbit, Xiaolang became Tweedledee and Tweedledum, and Eriol became the Chesire Cat! I turned into a pretty member of the queen`s court. Sakura even said that Kero got turned into the evil queen and chased her all around before she managed to discover a link back to the real world! I was so glad she got back safely!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659275</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3554" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらともう一人のさくら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Sakuras</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die doppelte Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et son double</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับซากุระอีกคนหนึ่ง</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Mouhitori no Sakura</title>
<summary>One day, Sakura came home after grocery shopping to find Yukito cutting Toya`s hair, so she asked him to give her a trip as well. I noticed right away when I saw her the next day, but Chiharu and Meiling said they saw Sakura causing trouble at the local stores. After seeing her double later that day, she realized that it must be a Clow Card! Kero taught Sakura how to read fortunes using the Clow Cards, and Sakura discovered that Toya was in danger. The fake Sakura lured Toya out into the woods, where he fell off a cliff! Sakura and Kero ran into Xiaolang in the woods while looking for Toya, and he helped them find Toya and the Clow Card. After her usual methods of capturing cards failed, Kero told Sakura that the only way to capture special cards is to call them by name. Since Sakura is so wonderful, she realized it was the Mirror card and sealed it away! She then vowed to collect all of the other cards so that they can`t harm anyone else.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659215</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3555" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとパニック自転車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Panicky Bike</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et la bicyclette enchantée</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับจักรยานตื่นเตลิด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Panic Jitensha</title>
<summary>The Clow Cards that Sakura hadn`t changed were starting to get cold, and Kero said that it was because they would become normal cards soon. Since Sakura wanted to save them, she tried transforming all of them at once, but it was too much for her. The Dash card didn`t finish being transformed, and escaped! She chased it down and cleverly used the Loop card to finally catch Dash. After Dash`s escape and wild behavior, I think Sakura realized that she needed to be more careful with her magic.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659271</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3556" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと知世とすてきな歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Tomoyo, and a Wonderful Song</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die geheimnisvolle Stimme</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le fantôme de l`école</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับโทโมโยะและเพลงแสนไพเราะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Tomoyo to Suteki na Uta</title>
<summary>Sakura had heard a rumor about a singing ghost in the music room at our school, but when she investigated it, she discovered it was actually a Clow Card! Xiaolang suggested that she should explore the school at night to find out the truth, despite how afraid she was, she decided to do it. Sakura`s so brave! We snuck in together, and when we got inside we were surprised to find Xiaolang and Meiling there. We all heard a voice coming from the music room, and even though Meiling scared it off, we were able to figure out what it was- the Song card had been practicing a song I`d been singing for class earlier! We figured out that Song will only appear when the person it`s copying- me in this case- sings for it. So I sang for everyone, and at last Sakura was able to seal the card away!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659211</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3557" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと過去とクロウ・リード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, the Past, and Clow Reed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et le mauvais sort</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับโคลว์รีดในอดีต</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Kako to Clow Reed</title>
<summary>Sakura had to deal with some more odd things- this time, it was a bunch of snowmen. There were a lot of strange things happening, and Sakura really wanted to get to the bottom of it, so she decided to use the Return card to go back and talk to Clow Reed himself. She told me about her conversation with him; it seemed very... cryptic. But Sakura really cares about Kero, Yue and the cards, so everything would definitely be alright! After she got back, we finally discovered the new Clow Reed!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659301</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3558" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらの楽しいいちご狩り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Fun Strawberry Picking Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura va aux fraises</title>
<title xml:lang="th">การเก็บสตรอเบอร์รี่แสนสนุกของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Tanoshii Ichigo Gari</title>
<summary>We finally got to go strawberry picking! It turned out that Toya and Yukito were both working there that day. What luck for Sakura! Sakura wanted to make some delicious food for Yukito using the strawberries she had picked, but we got locked in the preparation room by the Lock card! We looked everywhere for a key, and finally Sakura got a clue from Ms. Mizuki sitting in a tree. I wonder why she was there. Anyway, after Sakura managed to seal up the Lock card, she made some strawberry tarts. Yukito loved them so much that he ate them all! Sakura was so pleased, but I don`t think Kero was.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659241</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3559" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと大きなぬいぐるみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Big Teddy Bear</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura contre l`ours en peluche</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับตุ๊กตาตัวใหญ่</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Ookina Nuigurumi</title>
<summary>Xiaolang finisehd putting together the teddy bear kit that he got at the craft store. He was going to give it to Yukito, but Yue showed up and told him that he only liked Yukito because of the moon`s magic and that Xiaolang`s true love was actually someone else. When Sakura finished her teddy bear, she gave it to Yukito (just like I knew she would!), but it suddenly grew huge and tried to crush us! With a little advice from Yue, Sakura found the source of the magic, and stopped it. The source turned out to be a piece of paper with Clow Reed`s magic circle on it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659267</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3560" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのながーいマラソン大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Long Marathon Race</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Endlosschleife</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cours, Sakura cours !</title>
<title xml:lang="th">แข่งวิ่งมาราธอนแสนยาวนานของซากุระ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Nagai Marathon Taikai</title>
<summary>While they were practicing for an upcoming marathon, Meiling ended up losing to Sakura. Enraged, she began to train intently for the difficult race. And when the day of the race arrived, Meiling and Sakura found themselves quickly in the lead. However... they soon realized that they`d been going around and around in circles with no idea why! Sakura and Xiaolang then both sensed the Loop card, so they tracked it down and sealed it away. In the process, Meiling had hurt her leg and had to be carried on Xiaolang`s back. But still, they all crossed the finish line together. Despite losing the race, Meiling seemed happy with the outcome. And a little embarrassed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659207</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3561" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらの一番好きな人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Person Sakura Likes Most</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Confidence pour confidence</title>
<title xml:lang="th">คนที่ซากุระรักที่สุด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Ichiban Suki na Hito</title>
<summary>We went to the school fair at Toya and Yukito`s schol to see the film that Sakura was in. Everyone loved her just like I knew they would! They thought she was so cute! Afterwards, we ate and decided to see some of the displays. Nakuru sent us into the star display in pairs, and Sakura finally told Yukito how she felt about him. Xiaolang and I heard a loud crash while we were outside, and Xiaolang rushed in to help! When they made it out, I found out that Sakura had passed out! I was so worried. She said that she had run into someone she thought might be Clow Reed...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659297</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3562" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと雪の新学期</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Snowy New School Term</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rentrée scolaire</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับเปิดเทอมหิมะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Yuki no Shingakki</title>
<summary>We started a new term at school recently, Sakura and I are finally in the fifth grade! When Sakura met Yukito on the way to school, he gave her a birthday present- he`s so smooth! We all got to stay in the same class, but we had a new teacher who turned out to be Ms. Mizuki. Sakura was super excited about it; I think she really likes Ms. Mizuki. It started snowing a lot though, which was strange for spring. It snowed so much that the whole town was almost covered! Of course, Sakura realized it was the Snow card and went to capture it, btu she got caught in a snowy cyclone and lost the new watch Yukito had given gave her. She got really upset and used Firey to burn up all the snow. Luckily, Ms. Mizuki found the watch and returned it to Sakura!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659237</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3563" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと吹雪のスキー教室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Snowy Ski Class</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La disparition de Matthieu</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับบทเรียนสกีในพายุหิมะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Fubuki no Ski Kyuoushitsu</title>
<summary>Our class took a trip to a ski resort, Eriol is a really good skier! The first night, Naoko wanted to tell scary stories, and Eriol had one about a Snow Spirit! Sakura seemed a little scared that night... Since Sakura learned how to ski really quickly, the next day she decided to head up to a harder hill with Eriol. I didn`t go up because I wanted to film her coming down for "Sakura Dances on the Silvery White Mountain," but it started snowing pretty hard and everyone had to go inside. An avalanche started while Sakura and Eriol were still on the mountain! Sakura tried to stop it using the time and Firey cards, but it was too much power and she ended up passing out...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659293</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="3564" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと雪兎と昼の月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Yukito, and Midday Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Tomoeda-Quiz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le concours</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ซากุระกับยูกิโตะและจันทร์เที่ยงวัน</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Yukito to Hiru no Tsuki</title>
<summary>The city council decided to do a Sunday Scavenger Hunt! Sakura wanted me to be her partner, but when I wouldn`t be able to film her... It all worked out though, since Sakura got to be partners with Yukito instead. To finish the hunt, each team had to answer riddles and find a special tile. Sakura and Yukito are so smart that they solved them all and went to look for the tile in the woods. Sakura almost got hurt falling off a cliff, but Yukito saved her and got hurt instead... Still, even though he was injured, they eventually made their way to the finish line, where we were all waiting for them!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659233</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="5003" update="2012-02-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="3">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すてきですわ, さくらちゃん! 知世のカードキャプターさくら活躍ビデオ日記!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Lovely, Sakura-chan! Tomoyo`s Energetic Cardcaptor Sakura Video Diary!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteki Desu wa, Sakura-chan! Tomoyo no Cardcaptor Sakura Katsuyaku Video Nikki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5057" update="2012-02-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="2">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すてきですわ, さくらちゃん! 知世のカードキャプターさくら活躍ビデオ日記2!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Lovely, Sakura-chan! Tomoyo`s Energetic Cardcaptor Sakura Video Diary 2!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteki Desu wa, Sakura-chan! Tomoyo no Cardcaptor Sakura Katsuyaku Video Nikki 2!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5058" update="2012-02-24">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="3">9.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すてきですわ, さくらちゃん! 知世のカードキャプターさくら活躍ビデオ日記スペシャル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Lovely, Sakura-chan! Tomoyo`s Energetic Cardcaptor Sakura Video Diary: Special!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suteki Desu wa, Sakura-chan! Tomoyo no Cardcaptor Sakura Katsuyaku Video Nikki Special!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39201" update="2016-06-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1998-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39202" update="2011-10-01">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1999-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49675" update="2006-05-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">KidsWB Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90063" update="2011-10-01">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1999-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91627" update="2011-10-01">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1998-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91628" update="2011-10-01">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1999-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91629" update="2011-10-01">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1999-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116336" update="2020-02-15">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケロちゃんにおまかせスペシャルDX[デラックス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kero-chan ni Omakase Special Deluxe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116337" update="2020-02-15">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケロちゃんにおまかせスペシャルDX[デラックス]てんこもり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kero-chan ni Omakase Special Deluxe Tenkomori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116338" update="2020-02-15">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケロちゃんにおまかせスペシャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kero-chan ni Omakase Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116339" update="2020-02-15">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケロちゃんにおまかせ! Blu-ray BOXの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kero-chan ni Omakase! Blu-ray Box no Maki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133608" update="2016-06-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1998-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137334" update="2012-02-24">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>60</length>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カードキャプター誕生(ケルベロス責任編集版)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cardcaptor Tanjou (Cerberus Sekinin Henshuuban)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137335" update="2012-02-24">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">カードキャプターさくらSPECIAL『クロウカード編』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cardcaptor Sakura Special "Clow Card Hen"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137336" update="2012-02-24">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">カードキャプターさくらSPECIAL『さくらカード編』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cardcaptor Sakura Special "Sakura Card Hen"</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
