<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10208" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-05-20</startdate>
<enddate>2014-05-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ore no Nounai Sentakushi ga, Gakuen Lovecome o Zenryoku de Jama Shite Iru (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">내 뇌 속의 선택지가 학원 러브 코미디를 전력으로 방해하고 있다 OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">NouCome OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ore no Nounai Sentakushi ga, Gakuen Lovecome o Zenryoku de Jama Shiteiru (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">俺の脳内選択肢が, 学園ラブコメを全力で邪魔している (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">My Mental Choices Are Completely Interfering with My School Romantic Comedy - Kataomoi Otome</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9787" type="Parent Story">Ore no Nounai Sentakushi ga, Gakuen Lovecome o Zenryoku de Jama Shite Iru</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="1789" type="Animation Work">Diomedea</name>
<name id="20778" type="Character Design">Saita Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="3116" type="Chief Animation Direction">Noda Yasuyuki</name>
<name id="8315" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hara Yumiko</name>
<name id="37903" type="Series Composition">Kanasugi Hiroko</name>
<name id="37905" type="Original Work">Kasukabe Takeru</name>
<name id="8114" type="Direction">Inagaki Takayuki</name>
<name id="20778" type="Chief Animation Direction">Saita Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="36647" type="Music">Sakai Asuka</name>
</creators>
<description>After having to make another Absolute Choice, http://anidb.net/ch58137 [Kanade] ends up inside a visual novel called OSL Maiden. In order to come back to the real world, he needs to get to the ending of the novel. Kanade has marathoned this novel before, so he knows what choices he should make. However, the Absolute Choice interferes again and again to complicate the matters.
— written by Singan
Note: Unaired TV episode bundled with the light novel`s volume 8.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="764">4.94</permanent>
<temporary count="769">6.58</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>155817.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20939</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="57468" type="main character in" update="2013-08-09">
<rating votes="45">7.53</rating>
<name>Chocolat</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chocolat is a self-proclaimed servant of God who comes to http://anidb.net/ch58137 [Kanade] in order to lift the curse of absolute multiple-choice. However, she lost her memories and is of no help at all. She is such an big eater that words cannot describe. She is cute like a puppy, and has an emotional attachment to Kanade.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24067" picture="67787.jpg">Sadohara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58137" type="main character in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="25">6.40</rating>
<name>Amakusa Kanade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In Class 2-1 at Seikou Academy. His life is at the mercy of his Absolute Choice which forces him to choose one of the options that appears in his mind. He has good looks, but his personality and behavior issues earned him the foul label as a member of the Reject 5, a group of outcasts.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="303" picture="166016.jpg">Toyonaga Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58138" type="main character in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="54">7.07</rating>
<name>Yukihira Furano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanade`s classmate and a fellow Reject 5. She`s a cool type of person who never lets her emotion show and always spits poison or dirty jokes. She can never admit when she actually likes something, and she has a secret side... She`s also worried about the small size of her breasts.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34378" picture="127861.jpg">Kondou Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58139" type="main character in" update="2013-11-05">
<rating votes="49">7.03</rating>
<name>Yuuouji Ouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fellow classmate of Kanade and proud daughter of a powerful company. She has beautiful looks, but she has childish behavior and no knows what she`ll pull next. The damage from her rampages earned her a spot in the Reject 5 but she doesn`t seem to care.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>140433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1931" picture="238837.jpg">Tsuji Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60296" type="appears in" update="2013-10-31">
<rating votes="7">3.91</rating>
<name>Iinchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10391" picture="38277.jpg">Zougou Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69052" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-31">
<rating votes="5">4.34</rating>
<name>Katakoi Nozomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69426" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-14">
<rating votes="5">6.05</rating>
<name>Parfait</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24067" picture="67787.jpg">Sadohara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86433" type="appears in" update="2017-01-03">
<name>Haruhara You</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="155130" update="2013-10-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">(1)カタオモイ☆乙女 (2)肩重い☆トメ (3)片方ゲイ☆片方ホモ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">OAD</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">(1) Kataomoi Otome (2) Kataomoi Tome (3) Katahou Gei Katahou Homo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162030" update="2014-08-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162031" update="2014-08-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
