<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1020" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-07-17</startdate>
<enddate>1999-07-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Maboroshi no Pokemon Lugia Bakutan</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon - The Movie 2000</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pocket Monsters the Movie: Revelation Lugia</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pocket Monsters Movie 2: Mirage Pokémon: Lugia`s Explosive Birth</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Покемон: Появление призрачного покемона Лугии</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 ポケットモンスター 幻のポケモンルギア爆誕</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Pokemon The Movie 2000: The Power of One</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Pokémon 2: Die Macht des Einzelnen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Pokémon 2 : Le pouvoir est en toi</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Pokémon 2 - La forza di uno</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Pokémon 2: Uwierz w swoją siłę</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Pokémon 2 - Ensam är stark</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Pokémon 2 - O Poder Único</title>
<title xml:lang="no" type="official">Pokémon 2 - Den enes kraft</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Pokémon 2: Síla jednotlivce</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="official">Pokémon 2 - kun én har styrken</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Pokémon 2: Yhden voimalla</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Πόκεμον: Η δύναμη του ενός</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">פוקימון 2: כוחו של האחד</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Pokémon 2000 - Bízz az erőben</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Pokemonai 2000</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Pokémon 2: En Güçlü O</title>
<title xml:lang="sk" type="official">Pokémon 2000</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Покемон 2000 : Филмът</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="230" type="Parent Story">Pocket Monsters</anime>
<anime id="6797" type="Other">Pikachu Tankentai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.pokemon.co.jp/anime/movie/1999/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4464" type="Character Design">Ichiishi Sayuri</name>
<name id="2843" type="Work">Yagi Masao</name>
<name id="4464" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ichiishi Sayuri</name>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="13048" type="Work">Kawai Tsuneyoshi</name>
<name id="12958" type="Work">Miyagawa Kouichi</name>
<name id="12008" type="Work">Tomiyama Kantarou</name>
<name id="15412" type="Work">Fukuda Toshihide</name>
<name id="734" type="Work">Shogakukan Productions</name>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="5660" type="Music">Miyazaki Shinji</name>
<name id="25538" type="Work">Sakamoto Ken</name>
</creators>
<description>Ash Ketchum must put his skill to the test when he attempts to save the world from destruction. The Greedy Pokemon collector Lawrence III throws the universe into chaos after disrupting the balance of nature by capturing one of the Pokemon birds that rule the elements of fire, lightning and ice. Will Ash have what it takes to save the world?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1678">4.45</permanent>
<temporary count="1695">6.39</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221880.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>830</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1117</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2358</identifier>
<identifier>uodvri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pokemon.co.jp/anime/movie/1999/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Pokémon:_The_Movie_2000</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>劇場版ポケットモンスター_幻のポケモン_ルギア爆誕</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1863</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>182</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>161718</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6836</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="22" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="19">7.70</rating>
<name>Fushigibana</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Venusaur known as the Seed Pokémon, is the final stage in Bulbasaur evolution. The seed finally bloomed into a huge flower, vaguely resembling a Rafflesia. The flower constantly draws in sunlight for nutrition, characterized by vivid colors and a soothing aroma, and power, which is much more substantial in the summer. They are always on the move to absorb more sunlight, though they usually remain quiet and still while absorbing it. After it rains, the aroma is much stronger, which attracts other Pokémon. Female Venusaur have a seed coming out of the flower, possibly representing a pregnancy. Being the final form of Grass starter, Venusaur can learn Hyper Beam, Giga Impact and Frenzy Plant.</description>
<picture>195354.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="28">7.56</rating>
<name>Kamex</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Blastoise known as the Shellfish Pokémon, is the fully grown and developed form of the Squirtle species evolution line. In the main Pokémon game series, a Blastoise is only acquired when a Wartortle grows past experience level 36 and evolves into a Blastoise. As a Blastoise, two sections of the hefty shell open up to reveal cannon-like spouts on the Pokémon`s back that can fire pressurized water at a target with enough force that even concrete walls and thick steel can be punctured. The spouts are also very accurate, since a Blastoise can strike distant tin cans with the water from its spouts!</description>
<picture>64462.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2248" picture="170362.jpg">Kawashima Tokuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="16">9.08</rating>
<name>Butterfree</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Butterfree is a dual-type Bug/Flying Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves from Metapod starting at level 10. It is the final form of Caterpie. It also has a Gigantamax form.
Butterfree resembles a vaguely anthropomorphic butterfly with a purple body. Unlike true insects, it only has two body segments and four light blue legs. The upper pair of legs resembles small, three-fingered hands, while the lower pair resembles long, digit-less feet. Butterfree has two black antennae, a light blue snout with two fangs underneath, and large, red compound eyes. Its two pairs of wings are white with black venation. Two oval scales on a female Butterfree`s lower wings are black, but they are white on a male.
As Gigantamax Butterfree, its size increases to gigantic length with altered look. The wings and its pattern changes to light and dark green color with white. The antennae change to bright green and extends to the point where the tip bends, and three red clouds surround it. The eyes changes to bright glowing red. A fur-like circle is attached to both the wings and back of Butterfree. Several green scales can be seen floating around Butterfree, which are its most effective weapons, capable of releasing paralysis, poisoning, or sleep. The massive wings are powerful enough to lift a 10-ton truck through a simple flap. The wind it generates can scatter poisonous scales throughout the area, making it dangerous to be near it.
Butterfree`s wings are covered with poisonous powders that fall off continuously as it flies. It will defend Caterpie from bird Pokémon using this powder. This powder also repels water, enabling it to gather honey even in the rain. Butterfree will roam up to six miles (ten kilometers) from its nest in search of honey, which it carries with the hairs of its legs. Sometimes it has territorial disputes with Cutiefly over fields of flowers. It also consumes sap from trees pierced by Heracross, as seen in the anime. Butterfree is found in temperate forests and jungles, but it has also been observed flying near the ocean as part of its migratory breeding pattern.
Gigantamax Butterfree is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive G-Max Move G-Max Befuddle.</description>
<picture>68370.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="18">7.27</rating>
<name>Poppo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pidgey, known as the Tiny Bird Pokémon, is a bird-like Pokémon, whose original name in the English beta version of Pokémon Red and Blue was "Pidge". Pidgey was first introduced in the United States in Red and Blue. They are one of the first wild Pokémon that players encounter in those games. Pidgey does not like to fight, and will use its wings to stir up clouds of sand in an attempt to distract its would-be opponent and escape. Pidgey also uses this technique to bring its preferred prey of small insects into the open. Pidgey seems to possess magnetoception, as it is capable of returning to its nest from any location without fail.
Pidgey also appeared in the first television episode, Pokémon, I Choose You!, when the main character, Ash Ketchum, attempts to catch one. He fails when it uses its Gust attack to blow him away and escapes. Afterwards, it uses its Sand Attack to blind Ash, allowing it to get away.</description>
<picture>242941.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Pigeon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pidgeotto, known as the Bird Pokémon, is a bird-like Pokémon, is a larger and stronger form that Pidgey takes when it gains enough experience. In the main Pokémon game series, a Pidgeotto is only acquired when a Pidgey grows past experience level 18 and evolves into a Pidgeotto. A Pidgeotto is extremely territorial, generally claiming a large area with its nest built in the center. Full of vitality, it constantly patrols its territory, mercilessly attacking intruders. They fly about in circular patterns while hunting, and can spot the movements of their prey on the ground no matter how high they fly. The Pidgeotto attacks with its wickedly sharp talons and carries its prey, including Exeggcute and Magikarp, back to its nest from as far as 60 miles away - or more.
Pidgeotto was the second Pokémon Ash caught in the beginning of his career, eventually evolving into Pidgeot.</description>
<picture>242942.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="16">7.53</rating>
<name>Pigeot</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pidgeot, known as the Bird Pokémon, is a bird-like Pokémon, whose original name in the English beta version of Pokémon Red and Blue was "Pidgeott", is the fully grown and developed form of the Pidgey species evolution line. In the main Pokémon game series, a Pidgeot is only acquired when a Pidgeotto grows past experience level 36 and is evolved into a Pidgeot. Pidgeot are large, powerful birds admired for their glossy plumage and their battling ability. With their powerful chest muscles at work, Pidgeot can flap their wings fast enough to whip up gusts of winds to rival tornadoes. Pidgeot are very aerodynamic, capable of soaring to an altitude of 3300 feet and reaching speeds of up to Mach 2. Like Pidgeotto, Pidgeot feed on Magikarp by swooping from the sky and snatching them out of the water with their talons. Pidgeot appear very similar to Pidgeotto, so much so that one has been easily mistaken for the other, even by official sources.
In the Pokémon anime, Ash`s Pidgeotto evolves into a Pidgeot near the end of the Kanto saga, and remained in Pallet Town to watch over a flock of Pidgey and Pidgeotto while Ash went off to the Orange Islands.</description>
<picture>64488.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="62" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="14">3.20</rating>
<name>Koratta</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rattata, known as the Mouse Pokémon, are a basic Pokémon species found very commonly in the wild in the Kanto and Johto regions of the Pokémon world. Rattata are among the earliest Pokémon that can be caught by players, so much so that it is said that the presence of one Rattata indicates the presence of more than forty Rattata in the area. They make their nests almost anywhere and as extreme omnivores eat anything they can scavenge. A Rattata`s fangs grow continuously throughout its lifespan, so it whittles them down to a comfortable size by gnawing on hard objects.</description>
<picture>64416.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="64" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="10">1.31</rating>
<name>Ratta</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raticate, known as the Mouse Pokémon, is a larger and stronger form that Rattata takes when it gains enough experience. In the main Pokémon game series, a Raticate is only acquired when a Rattata grows past experience level 20 and is evolved into a Raticate. Compared to a Rattata, a Raticate is far more of a predator, and the majority of its features are adapted for this purpose. Its whiskers give it balance and it slows down if they are cut off. Its webbed feet allow it to swim as it hunts prey, and its fangs are tough enough to topple concrete buildings.</description>
<picture>64415.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="66" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Onidrill</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fearow is a bird Pokémon that evolves from Spearow at level 20. It has a large wingspan; elongated neck; and thin, long beak; all characteristics being a radical departure from its short-winged, stubby-beaked pre-evolved form Spearow. Fearow uses its great wings to catch air currents and effortlessly glide over large distances for as long as a day without having to land or rest. It flies high into the sky, and swoops down at its prey. By using a combination of its neck and beak, it has a large reach, allowing it to pluck bugs from the ground or easily pluck prey from soil or water as it swoops down. If it senses danger, it avoids it if possible.</description>
<picture>242944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20313" picture="215970.jpg">Izaki Hisayoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="9">2.82</rating>
<name>Arbo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ekans is a snake-like Pokémon that swallows whole the eggs of small bird Pokémon, such as Pidgey or Spearow. Its highly poisonous fangs make it a hazard in the wild. Ekans also shares other characteristics as snakes, such as using its tongue to test the air for the presence of prey, and shedding its skin.
The name Ekans is the word snake backwards. Ekans` Japanese name, Arbo, is a reversal by morae of the word boa. Ekans` name in the English beta version was also Arbo.
In the anime, the most notable Ekans was owned by Jessie, who had received it before episode 2 for her birthday. It later evolved into an Arbok and was released.
Ekans evolves into Arbok at level 22.</description>
<picture>242945.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="10">4.47</rating>
<name>Arbok</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Arbok are a larger and stronger form that Ekans take when they gain enough experience. In the main Pokémon game series, an Arbok is only acquired when an Ekans grows past level 22 and is evolved into an Arbok. It physically resembles a cobra and its name is the reverse of "kobra." The face-like pattern on the inside of its hood is regionally unique.
Along with Weezing, Arbok is often associated with Team Rocket because of its role in the anime.</description>
<picture>242946.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="160" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="10">10.00</rating>
<name>Raichuu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raichu is a taller, potbellied form that Pikachu takes when he is given a thunder stone, causing its tail to grow long and black with a lightning bolt on the end and fur to turn orange. It also has a white underbelly, brown stripes on its back, and yellow cheeks, in contrast to Pikachu`s red cheeks and Pichu`s pink cheeks. In the main Pokemon game series, a Raichu is only acquired when an item called a Thunderstone is applied to a Pikachu so that it evolves into a Raichu. Raichu can only learn moves in the Pikachu stage, so the only way to make Raichu learn more moves is by using a TM. Raichu can generate 10,000 or even 100,000 volts of electricity, enough to knock out Pokemon several times its size, such as a Dragonite, as stated in the anime. Raichu`s name is a portmanteau of the kanji 雷 rai, meaning thunder, or lightning bolt, and chuu, which is the Japanese onomatopoeia for a mouse`s squeak.</description>
<picture>64418.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="685" picture="24841.jpg">Takano Urara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="162" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="24">7.68</rating>
<name>Sandpan</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sandslash are a larger and stronger form that Sandshrew take when they gain enough experience to reach level 22. Generally they are a moderately large, bipedal hedgehog or pangolin-like creature with hard yellow skin, lengthy claws, and a back loaded with an assemblage of large brown spikes. These spikes are hardened sections of Sandslash`s hide that grow to form a natural self-defense when Sandslash curls into a ball. Each spike remains on Sandslash for one year, after which it falls off and a new spike grows in its place. Sandslash can be found in desert areas, particularly close to dry forests. Sandslash`s spikes serve a number of purposes to help cope with its environment, such as providing shade to protect it from the sun and heatstroke or using them offensively to harm both predators and prey. It uses its claws to climb trees, cut up food and dig, the latter being an activity that can cause them to break if done too quickly. It cannot run very quickly, but it is very quick with its claws.</description>
<picture>64419.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="163" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="22">5.81</rating>
<name>Nidoran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidoran are a species of poisonous rabbit-like Pokémon found in the Kanto, Johto, and Sinnoh regions of the Pokémon world. Male Nidoran are classified as a separate species of Pokémon from the females due to differences in appearance between genders, such as the female being light blue and having smaller horns than the male. It should be noted that these were the first Pokémon to have known genders until the release of Pokémon Gold and Pokémon Silver, although they remain as separate species to this date. This Pokémon protects itself with its venomous barbs.</description>
<picture>242947.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="164" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">3.20</rating>
<name>Nidorina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidorina are a larger and stronger form that female Nidoran take when they gain enough experience. In the main Pokémon game series, a Nidorina can be found as wild Pokémon in the Kanto and Johto regions of the Pokémon world, and it can also be acquired when a female Nidoran grows past experience level 16 and is evolved into a Nidorina.</description>
<picture>242948.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="165" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="10">7.27</rating>
<name>Nidoqueen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidoqueen are a fully grown and developed species of possum-like Pokémon. In the main Pokémon game series, a Nidoqueen can only be acquired when a Moon Stone item is applied to a Nidorina so that the creature is evolved into a Nidoqueen. Nidoqueen seem to be omnivores feeding on shrubs and fruit but they may snack on certain small Pokémon for protein. Also, Nidoqueen are much less aggressive than Nidoking and get along much better with others of their kind. Nidoqueen appears to be slightly weaker, but significantly more intelligent than Nidoking.</description>
<picture>242949.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="166" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="12">5.12</rating>
<name>Nidoran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidoran are a species of poisonous rabbit-like Pokémon found in the Kanto, Johto, and Sinnoh regions of the Pokémon world. Unlike most Pokémon, Female Nidoran are classified as a separate species from the males due to extreme differences in appearance between genders, such as the male having larger horns and completely different colors than the female. Male Nidoran are purple, and their horns secrete a powerful venom. The size of the horns determines the potency of the venom. Nidoran stiffens its large ears to sense danger.</description>
<picture>242950.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="167" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="9">3.20</rating>
<name>Nidorino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidorino are a larger and stronger form that male Nidoran take when they gain enough experience. Nidorino look somewhat like a rhinoceros and a rabbit with needles and horns covering its body. Nidorino is more aggressive than male Nidoran and is quick to attack when it notices a threat; its large ears are always on the lookout. The diamond-hard horn on its head secretes a powerful venom and on impact with an enemy, poison leaks out. If it senses a hostile presence, all the barbs on its back bristle up. Nidorino is the male counterpart of Nidorina.
In the main Pokémon game series, a Nidorino can be found as wild Pokémon in the Kanto and Johto regions of the Pokémon world, and it can also be acquired when a male Nidoran grows past experience level 16 and is evolved into a Nidorino. It is also notable for being one of the first two Pokémon seen in the anime and in the intro to the game Pokémon Red.</description>
<picture>242951.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="168" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="12">7.27</rating>
<name>Nidoking</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nidoking are a fully grown and developed species of male possum-like Pokémon and the final stage in the male Nidoran evolutionary line. Its horn is hard enough to pierce a diamond and contains secreted venom, making it a powerful stabbing tool upon prey and Pokémon battle opponents. Nidoking have immense upper-body strength, being able to snap a telephone pole like it were a twig. It uses its tail to smash down its target, then constrict it to break its bones. Its thick tail packs enormously destructive power capable of toppling a metal transmission tower.
As several Pokémon seem to have been designed to resemble other aspects of Japanese pop culture and mythology, it is interesting to note that Nidoking bears a resemblance to Baragon, a monster that has appeared in the Godzilla movie series.
In the main Pokémon game series, a Nidoking can only be acquired when a Moon Stone item is applied to a Nidorino so that the creature is evolved into a Nidoking. They are the masculine equivalent to Nidoqueen. Also, they are more primal, fighting other Nidoking for such matters as territory or food. (Or a Nidoqueen, in mating season.)</description>
<picture>242952.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="169" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="8">1.25</rating>
<name>Pippi</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clefairy are small, bipedal Pokémon. Popular as pets for their adorable features, Clefairy have short, pink fur, with a large brown patch on each of their two pointed ears. Between these ears is a large swirl of pink fur. They have two small eyes, no nose, and a small mouth with one tiny, protruding fang. They also have a patch of darker pink fur under each eye, which seems to resemble blushing cheeks.
Clefairy can be seen playing in groups, on the night of a full moon, retreating to their group slumber when dawn arrives. These Pokémon are noted to be able to store moonlight in the wings on their backs, giving them the power to float in mid-air. There have been sightings of Clefairy, with their evolutionary forms Cleffa and Clefable, using spaceships, and the Moon Stones used to evolve Clefairy are also rumored to come from extraplanetary locations. Clefairy seem to be based on fairies, as they are magical, winged creatures, lending credit to their name. Also, their game call seems to make a sound similar to their Japanese name.
Clefairy`s biology is somewhat unclear. While they cannot truly fly with their wings, they do travel in a bouncy skipping walk, as if walking on the surface of the moon. When they wave their finger, it stimulates the blood and triggers their brain to perform random attacks from any other Pokèmon, which is the basis of their signature Metronome attack.</description>
<picture>242953.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="171" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="13">8.73</rating>
<name>Rokon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vulpix is a fox-like creature with six curled tails, based on the Japanese fox spirit kitsune. Most commonly female, Vulpix are especially known for being beautiful. As Vulpix undergo Pokemon evolution, their red fur turns pale yellow and they grow three extra tails. Vulpix usually have a friendly, if not spoiled, temperament. Because of the flame in their bodies, when the temperature outside increases, they let flames out of their mouths to prevent their body temperature from getting too hot. In the wild, Vulpix will feign injury to escape from more powerful predators.
During the first season of the Pokemon anime, Vulpix appears often as one of Brock`s Pokemon. It was given to him by a girl named Susie who felt she could not take care of it well. Brock, who felt he was only "babysitting", gives it back to Susie in the season four episode called "Beauty and the Breeder".
Its Japanese name, Rokon is a portmanteau of six (六, roku) and kon (from kon kon, an onomatopoeic word describing the bark of a fox), or an alternate reading of the Japanese word for kitsune (狐, kitsune), meaning fox - in this case, the reading is ko (こ). Its English name may have been derived from the scientific name for a group of foxes, Vulpes.</description>
<picture>64414.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="172" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="10">8.73</rating>
<name>Kyukon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ninetales is a yellow nine-tailed fox, based on the kitsune, a Japanese fox spirit. Ninetales is highly intelligent and able to understand human speech, but also vengeful; Ninetales have been recorded as putting a 1,000 year curse on anyone who grabs one of their tails, which is a focus of the plot in Pokemon Mystery Dungeon: Blue Rescue Team and Red Rescue Team. They, along with Vulpix, have keen senses of smell, hearing, and sight. It can only be obtained by using a Fire Stone on a Vulpix. Its Japanese name Kyuukon comes from a combination of the Japanese number 9, kyu, and the sound of a barking fox.
In the anime, Ash and the gang find an abandoned mansion and Brock is deceived by a Ninetales, whose master strongly resembles Brock.
Since it has nine tails, the Pokemon`s name is very commonly misspelled as "Ninetails." Even the Game Boy Color port of the Pokemon Trading Card game uses this misspelling.</description>
<picture>64413.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="175" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">2.97</rating>
<name>Zubat</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zubat are a basic bat Pokémon species found commonly in the wild in most caves in all the regions of the Pokémon world. In caves and other dark places it navigates using ultrasonic waves. It appears that Zubat is weakened by sunlight, so it hides in caves or other dark places. At night, it will come out and hunt for fruit or Venomoth, or it sucks blood. The female`s fangs are smaller than the male`s.
In the anime, Brock catches a Zubat before entering Mt. Moon. Since then it has evolved to Golbat and then into Crobat. Crobat was given to Forest, with Onix and Geodude by Brock, becoming a Gym Leader.</description>
<picture>242957.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="176" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="10">3.20</rating>
<name>Golbat</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Golbat are a larger, stronger, and more developed form that Zubat take on when they gain enough experience. In the main Pokemon game series, a Golbat is acquired when a Zubat grows past experience level 22 and is evolved into a Golbat. Golbat are found in some cave areas.
Golbat is a fierce, nocturnal Pokémon, residing in the darkness of caves, and is most active in the pitch black of night, especially if the moon is in its new phase. It is widely known and despised for its feeding behavior: Sucking fresh blood from living things in large quantities. Once it has found a living target, it attacks in a stealthy manner, often striking without warning from behind, to harshly bite down on its prey with its four sharp fangs strong enough to puncture the hide of any animal-like Pokemon, however strong the hide might be. It then proceeds to drink ten ounces of blood instantly. Golbat enjoys blood so much that it does not want to stop, even though a lot of blood will weigh it down enough so that, if it is able to even fly afterwards, it flies clumsily.
Surprisingly, after each attack and feeding sequence, Golbat`s own blood type changes into that of its victim. Once it strikes, it will not stop draining energy from the victim even if it gets too heavy to fly. Like Zubat, the female`s fangs are smaller than the male`s.</description>
<picture>242958.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="177" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="23">9.04</rating>
<name>Nazonokusa</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oddish are a weed-like Pokémon found in all regions throughout the Pokémon world. (with the exception of Pokémon Blue and Pokémon Leaf Green) Oddish looks like a small animated onion/turnip plant with a rounded body. Its body is blue or purple with two small feet and red eyes. On top of its head grows a large clump of 5 long green blades of grass. Its name likely came from the words "odd" and "radish".
Oddish is a nocturnal Pokémon, using moonlight rather than the sun`s rays for photosynthesis. During the day, Oddish avoids the sun`s heat and brightness by burying itself into the earth, leaving only the leaves on top of its head visible above ground. In this way it disguises itself as a plant, misdirecting its carnivorous diurnal predators.
While buried, Oddish nourishes itself by absorbing nutrients from the soil using its feet, which are said to temporarily change into a root-like structure for this purpose.
Oddish has been known to use its leaves as hands, such as one who used this to climb a rope net and tried to fly like a Hoppip.
If anyone pulls at Oddish`s leaves and tries to uproot it while it is buried underground, Oddish will react by shrieking in a cute, high-pitched voice. This mirrors the behavior of the legendary mandrake in a similar situation, although it seems that Oddish`s squeaks do not have the same dire consequences as a mandrake`s.</description>
<picture>242959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="179" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="13">10.00</rating>
<name>Ruffresia</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vileplume is a huge flower-like Pokémon that is a larger and stronger evolution of Gloom. Vileplumes can be obtained by using a Leaf Stone with a Gloom.
Vileplume is known for its extremely offensive stench that comes from its large red flower. Vileplume uses this stench in battle, catching its foes off guard when they start to back away from the horrible smell. However, Vileplume`s flower can actually be a hindrance in battle due to it being very heavy and bulky. Due to of its weight, Vileplume walks very slowly, and it often must use its hands to help support the flower. Vileplume can be found in forests and they like to stay low to the ground. When they sleep, their huge petals droop over their head and they blend in more with the plants around them. They also release toxic, dense pollen into the air in this position so animals don`t go near them. At night, they sometimes gather together to perform odd rituals - during this time they release toxic pollen to deter intruders. The white markings on this flower are larger in the female than in the male. Paul uses Vileplume to battle Tyrogue, but his Vileplume is useless for Fighting-type Pokemon.</description>
<picture>242961.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="180" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Paras</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Paras is a basic parasite-like Pokémon that has two mushrooms on its back. Paras can be found in some caves and the Safari Zone in Kanto and in Ilex Forest and the Bug Catching Contest in Johto.
Paras is born with tiny spores covering their body, which grow as the Pokémon feeds, called tochukaso mushrooms. It is noted in that the relationship between the host and the mushrooms is a symbiotic relationship: the mushrooms will sap energy from the host, causing the Paras to continuously burrow underground in forest areas to gnaw on tree roots, since the tochukaso draws most of the energy from the roots. In return, the mushrooms defend the host by spraying toxic spores at enemies. The mushrooms themselves have strong healing properties, and are valued for their life extending properties.</description>
<picture>242962.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="181" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Parasect</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Parasect is a larger and stronger evolution of Paras that has one large mushroom on its back instead of two (see Paras). The mushroom has completely taken over the bug host. Parasect resides in dark and damp places, a preference of the mushroom, not the bug. The mushroom also has numerous medicinal qualities. Parasect can be obtained when a Paras reaches level 24. Parasect can be found in the Cerulean Cave and Safari Zone in Kanto and Silver Cave in Crystal. The Japanese and English names are a portmanteau of the English words "parasite" and "insect".</description>
<picture>242963.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="183" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="9">9.08</rating>
<name>Morphon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Venomoth is a large, lavender, moth-like Pokémon. It is rare in the wild, but can also be obtained by raising the more common Venonat to level 31. Its wings are covered in extremely toxic, dust-like scales. These scales are color-coded to indicate the effect they will have upon coming into contact with a living creature, darker colours meaning poison, and lighter colours meaning paralysis. Venomoth is similar to Butterfree in that they both flap their wings to release toxic powders. However, Venomoth seems to be the more dangerous of the two, as it is described as scattering its toxins with every flap of its wings. Much like Venonat, Venomoth is nocturnal and feeds upon small insects.</description>
<picture>242965.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="184" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="17">3.20</rating>
<name>Digda</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diglett is a basic mole-like creature that can be found only in Diglett`s Cave. Capable of burrowing at the speed of sound, it thrives in dark underground caves since exposure to bright light can weaken it. The burrow and excretions left by a Diglett, rather like those of a real-life earthworm, keep the soil aerated and fertile. For this reason, Diglett are prized by farmers.
The mysterious feet or hands of Diglett are unknown of what they look like, for the fact that Diglett can use moves such as slash and fury swipes. Only the head of a Diglett can be seen popping out of the ground.</description>
<picture>64422.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="221" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="27">8.05</rating>
<name>Koduck</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Psyduck is a duck-like Pokémon that can be found in some areas in Kanto, Johto, Hoenn, and Sinnoh. Psyduck is known for its never-ending headache; in the anime, its strongest attacks can be used only when its headache reaches extremely painful levels. It is slow-witted and clumsy by nature, and the vacant expression often unnerves its foes. It evolves into Golduck at level 33. Is thought to be cute and very smart!
In the anime Misty has a Psyduck.</description>
<picture>242966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="222" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="35">4.03</rating>
<name>Golduck</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Golduck are large bipedal ducks, with blue skin and strong, webbed appendages that given them the ability to swim at high speeds. Due to their bluish color and webbed hands and feet, Golduck are sometimes mistaken for Kappa. They have more formidable psychic powers than the Psyduck they evolve from, and they lose the headaches that they constantly suffer from. The gem on their heads glows when they use psychic powers as well as when they swim at full speed.
They live in fresh-water lakes and rivers, where they are seen gracefully swimming, especially at dusk. As the fastest swimmers out of all Pokémon, they can out swim even the most athletic of humans, though they often train with swimmers. As they are able to swim in severe storms, they are sometimes found rescuing people lost at sea from danger.</description>
<picture>242967.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="224" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Okorizaru</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Primeape is a larger and stronger evolution of Mankey. Vicious and frenzied, even making eye contact with it can anger it. If it is annoyed, it will never stop chasing the offender. Its frenzies are most dangerous when forcefully woken up, as it relentlessly chases the quarry while half-asleep. Primeape can be obtained when a Mankey has earned enough experience to level up to level 28. Primeape can also be found in some grassy areas in Kanto and Johto.</description>
<picture>242969.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="227" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="15">10.00</rating>
<name>Gardie</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Growlithe`s name is derived from the words growl, because it growls at its enemies, and lithe, which refers to its readily bent posture before it attacks. It is harder to catch in Pokemon because of one of its attacks that allows it to flee. Its name in the beta version was Flamie. This cute puppy Pokemon makes its home in active volcanoes, grassy plains, and scorched plains heated by geothermal energy. Growlithe is Naturally loyal and protective of its trainer. If trained correctly it will remain motionless until it is given an order by its Trainer, though if it is improperly trained, or mistreated it will bite without warning or unprovoked. In the wild Growlithe will bark fiercely at anything that dares to invade its territory. Don`t let its puppy like appearance fool you it will fearlessly stand up to opponents bigger and stronger than it. Growlithe also has a superb sense of smell. Once it smells anything, this Pokemon won`t forget the scent, no matter what. It can even use its sense of smell to determine the emotions of other living things.</description>
<picture>242970.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="232" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Nyorobon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Poliwrath is the evolution of Poliwhirl, and resembles it closely, save for a pair of white eyes, thicker arms, and a slightly differently-shaped "head area," giving more of the impression that it is like a boxer. Poliwrath is only humbled in its pack by Politoed, the leader of Poli packs.
Poliwrath is a master swimmer in every respect, due to its highly developed body and arm muscles that never fatigue regardless of use. Thanks to its incredible stamina, Poliwrath is said to be physically able to swim the entire diameter of Earth`s Pacific Ocean without obvious effort, and its swimming efficiency allows it to easily overtake the best human swimmers in any controlled competition.
Poliwrath has made several appearances in the Pokemon anime, first appearing in "The Battling Eevee Brothers" and later as an opponent in "Charizard Chills" and "Hook, Line, and Sinker."</description>
<picture>242974.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="235" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="8">9.08</rating>
<name>Foodin</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alakazam loses the thick tail it once possessed as Kadabra (which might explain why it is 19 pounds lighter than Kadabra). It stands on two legs and always holds two silver spoons. Parts of Alakazam`s body are brown, but its predominant coloring is gold. Alakazam has a long, gold moustache - nonetheless, some Alakazam are female, though in Pokémon Diamond and Pearl, females have dramatically smaller moustaches, while the males have longer ones.
Alakazam are described as extremely intelligent. With an IQ of 5,000, they can outperform supercomputers and can memorize anything. Alakazam use their superior intelligence to immediately identify their opponents` weaknesses and gain the edge in battles. This intelligence and superb memory are said to come from the fact that Alakazam`s brain cells never stop multiplying - as a result, the overly large head must be supported by its telekinetic powers. In fact, Alakazam use their psychic abilities to watch all "movement", as their muscles are too weak. Also their senses are incredibly strong: just by closing its eyes it can heighten all the other senses dramatically. Alakazam evolves from Kadabra when you trade it to another Pokémon game.
Alakazam is notable for having the highest Special Attack among non-legendary Pokémon, a statistic that affects the power of mental, fluid, and energy-based attacks, though it shares this title with another Pokémon, Porygon-Z. To balance its extremely high Special Attack, Alakazam`s other stats are atrocious, save for its high speed and average Special Defence, though this is offset by an awful HP stat. Alakazam made an appearance in Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Blue Rescue Team and Red Rescue Team, as the leader of Team ACT.</description>
<picture>64463.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="322" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">1.25</rating>
<name>Wanriky</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Machop loves to fight and train in martial arts to enhance its skills, and is very intelligent.</description>
<picture>242977.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="323" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="23">6.29</rating>
<name>Goriky</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Machoke evolves from Machop at Level 28. An interesting fact about Machoke is when seen in its "shiny" version, it shares a striking resemblance to that of The Hulk, being green in color.
Machoke`s name is a portmanteau of macho, meaning tough, and choke. The Japanese name Goriky is a pun on the Japanese word for superhuman strength (剛力) or godlike strength. Its name was originally "Kong-Fuu" in beta English versions of Red and Blue, which is a reference to Kung fu. Its signature moves include submission, cross chop and dynamic punch.
Machoke, along with its evolved form Machamp, is nicknamed as one of the bodybuilders of the Pokémon world, due to its humanoid appearance, huge muscles and the fact that it wears black speedos, and the belt round its waist makes it look similar to a wrestler (which is most probably what the pokemon was based on). The belt is known as a "Power Save" belt, which keeps Machoke`s power under control and helps to regulate its motions. The explanations of the belt`s purpose vary, but is quoted that because it is so dangerous, no one has ever attempted to remove it.
Machoke has had relatively few anime appearances, most of which were in the Jouto region, most notably in "Machoke, Machoke Man!", in which Machoke was Chuck`s signature Pokemon, and shared a very close bond with its trainer, who sparred and even used submission on during training. Machoke also appear as employed heavy lifters and construction workers, and can also be seen in the beginning of the games Pokémon Saphire and Ruby where a group of Machoke are seen carrying furniture into the players home, which are replaced by Vigoroth in pokemon Emerald.
Despite being measured at 4`11" in the Pokedex, whenever Machoke appear in the anime, they are always around the same height, or taller than, an adult male.</description>
<picture>242978.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="324" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="10">9.08</rating>
<name>Kairiky</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Machamp is a Fighting-type Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves from Machoke when traded. It is the final form of Machop. It also has a Gigantamax form.
Machamp is a large, humanoid Pokémon with four well-muscled arms. It has bluish gray skin, red eyes, and pale yellow lips. On its head, there are three brown ridges right above its eyes. It has two arms on each side of its body: a pair located in the normal position, and another pair directly above that attaches on the top of the shoulders. It has black markings that resemble briefs and wears golden power-save belt that resembles a championship belt. Its legs have considerable muscle tone, and its feet have two toes each.
Machamp punches extremely fast, throwing five hundred punches a second. With only one hand, it can move a mountain. Because of its four arms, it can hit from a multitude of angles and pin all of its foe`s limbs at once. Its arms also allow it to attack and defend simultaneously. The four arms react faster before Marchamp think. However, it has poor dexterity, and cannot handle delicate work without its arms becoming tangled. It is a rash Pokémon that rushes into action without forethought. Being the result of an evolution via trading, Machamp is rarely found in the wild, though they can be found in the mountains. In the past, it claimed Low Kick, Vital Throw, and Strength as signature moves.
As Gigantamax Machamp, it has become larger with several changes. Its blueish-gray skin becomes darker. The middle ridge located on head becomes longer compare to the other two. All three ridges are also darker now. The neck extends with black markings. The fours fists are now colored dark orange with yellow lines connecting to two orange spots on each arm. The golden belt extends with several more dots. The P in the middle of the belt is colored white and connected to a single yellow circle with nothing in between. The black markings on its leg extend to the legs but stopping near the ankle.
Due to Gigantamaxing, the arms are filled with power, the punches it makes can hit as hard as bomb blasts. There is a legend where Gigantamax Machamp saved a large ship that was in trouble before bringing it to a port.
Gigantamax Machamp is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive G-Max Move G-Max Chi Strike.</description>
<picture>68372.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="327" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="12">5.12</rating>
<name>Utsubot</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Victreebel is a carnivorous Pokémon based on the pitcher plant. It lulls its prey with a sweet, honey-like scent, and also the vine on its head (which waves as if it were an animal) before digesting it with powerful stomach acids that can even dissolve bone. Normally, its prey are bugs, but it has been known to attack and consume small animals. Victreebel cannot be caught in the wild in any of the Pokémon video games; it must be evolved from Weepinbell with a Leaf Stone.
In the anime, James of Team Rocket had a Weepinbell which evolved into Victreebel in the episode "The Breeding Center Secret." As a running gag, it usually tried to eat him as soon as it emerged from its Poké Ball (this tradition of James`s Grass-type Pokémon hurting him was continued by Cacnea in the Advanced Generation series, and Carnivine in the Diamond and Pearl series). While most Pokèmon speak in a vocabulary consisting of its own name, Victreebel, like Lapras, communicates through loud, high-pitched shrieks.</description>
<picture>242981.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="328" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="30">2.20</rating>
<name>Menokurage</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tentacool (メノクラゲ, Menokurage?) is an aquatic Pokémon based on the box jellyfish. It drifts aimlessly wherever the ocean currents take it, sometimes ending up in shallow waters where it may be accidentally caught in fishing lines. Tentacool may also end up stuck on beaches when low tide comes; since its body is largely composed of water, it will shrivel up, risking death from dehydration if it stays out of the sea for too long. Tentacool has two main weapons. At the tips of its tentacles are toxic feelers, which it uses to stab anything it touches with stinging acid. Due to its excellent camouflage in the water, Tentacool can often remain undetected by swimmers right up to the moment it stings them. Tentacool`s gelatinous, watery body can also absorb sunlight and refract it within, producing beam energy it shoots from its crystal-like eyes.
Tentacool is available in all Pokémon games to date. It is extremely common, especially while surfing on sea routes, and is in almost every single body of water.
In the anime, Tentacool was featured in the episode "Tentacool and Tentacruel" in which a raging mob of the titular Pokémon attacked the Porta Vista resort. The episode was banned after the attacks on September 11, 2001 due to its scenes depicting Tentacools and Tentacruels destroying buildings at a seaside resort.</description>
<picture>242982.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="329" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="8">2.75</rating>
<name>Dokukurage</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Tentacruel" is probably a portmanteau of "tentacle", the reason for which is obvious, and the adjective "cruel", referring to its personality. The name may have something to do with the deep-sea jellyfish called Tentaculata. Its name was originally going to be Man-O-War, which refers to the Portuguese man o` war. The Japanese name, "Dokukurage," is a portmanteau, of 毒 doku (poison) and 水母 kurage (jellyfish). It resembles its pre-evolution Tentacool to a small degree - the "head" of Tentacool has now been made into a hat-like shape on top of a black orb containing its eyes and two very large hooks which resembles a long nose. Also, unlike Tentacool, it has up to 80 tentacles, most of which are hidden, leaving up to 14 exposed.</description>
<picture>242983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="330" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="24">2.37</rating>
<name>Ishitsubute</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Geodude has a rock for a head, no nose, and two long arms that start with a bulging muscle and end with rock hands resembling a human`s. Geodude most frequently are found in fields and on mountains. People step or trip on them from time to time, mistaking them for rocks. Its arms are so strong that it can use them to climb mountains. Rhyperior sometimes accidentally shoot Geodude from their cannon-like arms. Geodudes are one of the few Pokémon to have appeared in every Pokémon game.
In the video games, Geodude is commonly found inside caves and mountains, and sometimes appears when Rock Smash is used. Geodude are also found in the Nintendo 64 game Pokémon Snap, hanging from mountainsides by their arms. In the Super Smash Bros. Melee battlefield "Poké Floats", a Geodude is the last float the fighters ride on before returning to the Squirtle float.
Geodude is a recurring character in the Pokémon anime. It first appeared in the fifth episode, "Showdown in Pewter City," used by Gym Leader Brock to battle Ash. Brock became a travel companion of Ash and owned Geodude for the first five seasons. Navel Island Gym Leader Danny and Rustboro City Gym Leader Roxanne have also used Geodude. In the anime, Geodude is able to levitate above the ground.
Geodude`s name comes from the word "Geode" as in a rock with a sparkly inside, and "Dude," usually used to describe a certain kind of male person.</description>
<picture>64427.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="332" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="26">6.17</rating>
<name>Golonya</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Golem is a megaton Pokémon made from living stone, and one of the heaviest of all Pokémon species. Golem inhabits rocky mountains and volcanoes, often disguising itself as an inanimate boulder. It will annually shed its skin like a reptile, with its new shell often being bigger than the one before. Its body is almost impenetrable, able to withstand dynamite blasts; it can even detonate its own body, launching itself great distances in order to travel from mountain to mountain. When earthquakes occur near where Golem live, they will tumble down mountains, rolling at an incredible speed.
In the video games, the only way to obtain Golem is to evolve a Graveler by trading it to another player.
Golem has made numerous appearances in the Pokémon anime. It first appeared in the episode "The Bridge Bike Gang," in which Chopper, the leader of a bicycle gang, uses one to battle Ash`s Charmander.
Golem`s name comes from the word "golem," which is a humanoid clay or stone statue associated with Jewish mysticism.</description>
<picture>64425.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="334" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="10">9.08</rating>
<name>Gallop</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rapidash is a Fire-type Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves from Ponyta starting at level 40.
In Galar, Rapidash has a Psychic/Fairy-type regional form. It evolves from Galarian Ponyta starting at level 40.
Rapidash is an equine Pokémon with cream-colored fur and a pointed horn on its forehead. It has small, red eyes and triangular ears with reddish interiors. Yellow and reddish-orange flames stream from the back of its head to form a long, flowing mane. A short version of the mane trails down its back to its equally fiery tail. Flames are also present on its fetlocks. It has slender legs, each with a single black hoof.
Rapidash is a very agile Pokémon. It runs at about 150 mph (240 km/h), chasing everything that moves in hopes of racing it. With incredible acceleration, it reaches its top speed in only ten steps. At full gallop, its hooves barely touch the ground. The faster Rapidash goes, the longer the swaying flames of its mane will become. At an all-out gallop, its blazing mane sparkles, a feature which is said to enhance its beautiful appearance. Rapidash lives in grasslands, but it can also be seen on mountains in Pokémon Snap.</description>
<picture>68385.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="335" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="13">7.27</rating>
<name>Yadon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Slowpoke is a dual-type Water/Psychic Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves into Slowbro starting at level 37 or Slowking when traded holding a King`s Rock.
In Galar, Slowpoke has a pure Psychic-type regional form, introduced in Pokémon Sword and Shield`s 1.1.0 patch. It will evolve into Galarian Slowbro using an item found on the Isle of Armor or Galarian Slowking using an item found in the Crown Tundra.
Slowpoke is a pink Pokémon that resembles a cross between a salamander and a hippopotamus. It has vacant eyes that never seem focused, curled ears, and a rounded, tan muzzle. It has four legs, each of which ends in a single white claw. Its long, tapering tail has a white tip. This tail drips a sweet, sappy substance that is attractive to many species of fish. Slowpoke uses the tail as a fishing lure. The tail often breaks off, but it will grow back. In Alola, its tail is often dried and used in home cooked stews.
Slowpoke has notoriously dim intellect, and often forgets what it was doing. It takes a long time to respond to outside stimuli. For example, it can take up to five seconds to process pain and can take an entire day to notice when its tail has been bitten. Slowpoke is commonly found at the water`s edge. In some places, it is believed that Slowpoke`s yawn causes rain. This Pokémon is worshiped in those areas.
In Galar, Slowpoke gains yellow markings on its forehead and tail.</description>
<picture>68399.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="339" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="33">6.04</rating>
<name>Coil</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magnemite is almost more of a machine than a creature, as it is a solid ball of metal with a pair of horseshoe magnets on either side, as well as a single, lidless eye. It has a pair of screws protruding from below the eye, and a large screw forming a sort of "cap" on top of its head.
It floats through the air, through a sort of electromagnetic antigravity field generated by the two magnets on either side of its body. When defending itself in the wild or fighting in a Pokémon battle at the orders of a Pokémon trainer, it can also generate powerful electric shocks. Magnemite consumes electricity, so they`re attracted to power lines and electronic gadgets. Magnemite tend to crowd around generators and power plants, and an individual Magnemite might be attracted to someone with a pocket radio or a Pokégear.
Despite their mechanical appearance, lack of gender, and alien tendencies, Magnemite are living things; they are not built, they feel the need to eat, and they have something similar to a mating urge. A trio of Magnemite may come together to create their evolved form, Magneton.</description>
<picture>242984.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="340" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">3.20</rating>
<name>Rarecoil</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magneton is composed of 3 Magnemite linked together by a strong magnetic force. It levitates on an electromagnetic anti-gravity field like its pre-evolution, Magnemite. Its electromagnetic powers are so strong that it has been known to cause total blackouts in cities in which it gathers.</description>
<picture>242985.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="342" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Dodo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Doduo resembles an ostrich or a roadrunner, with sharper beaks and an extra head. It may also be based on the kiwi. Its name is a portmanteau of the words dodo, the extinct flightless bird, and duo, in reference to its two heads. Doduo`s tracks are huge and very distinctive. It inhabits and races across grass-covered plains at 60 mph. It is well-adapted to dry and arid climates. Doduo`s second head is said to have been formed by a sudden mutation thousands of years ago. Both heads normally contain identical brains, although rare cases have been observed where a Doduo has two distinctly different brains.
Interestingly, Doduo can be caught in the wild in all of the Pokémon video games. Doduo can also be found in Pokémon Snap.
In the Pokémon anime episode "Bad to the Bone," Jessie of Team Rocket battles a Doduo with her Arbok. The battle is interrupted when the Doduo`s heads begin to fight with each other.</description>
<picture>242986.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="343" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Dodorio</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dodrio is a flightless bird Pokémon with long, powerful legs. Dodrio resembles an ostrich, and its movement is reminiscent of the roadrunner. Its name is a portmanteau of the words dodo, the extinct flightless bird, and trio, in reference to its three heads.
As the evolved form of the two-headed Doduo, Dodrio has three heads, the third head which is said to be formed by one of Doduo`s heads splitting during evolution. Each one of the heads constantly expresses a different emotion: joy, sadness, and anger. Having three heads allows Dodrio to collect more information from its surroundings, develop complex plans, and remain alert at all times by keeping watch in three different directions. On the other hand, a Dodrio`s three heads are commonly known to squabble amongst themselves, probably due to each one having a different attitude. Though Dodrio struggles to fly, it has three sets of hearts and lungs to match its heads, granting it extraordinary stamina while running at high speed. Like its pre-evolution Doduo, it inhabits dry, grassy plains.
In the video games, Dodrio are often used by Bird Keepers and Triathletes practicing in running. In Pokémon Ranger, a Dodrio is the partner of the Fall City Ranger Leader Joel. Dodrio also features in the Pokémon Stadium games as Dodrio Mode, which speeds up the games` GameBoy emulator, and in FireRed, LeafGreen, and Emerald in the mini-game Dodrio Berry-Picking.
In the Pokémon anime, Dodrio first appeared on the morning of the first episode, crowing in place of a rooster. Dario used one in the episode "The Flame Pokémon-athon," and Violet City Gym Leader Falkner battled Ash`s Pikachu with one. Gary Oak also evolved his Doduo into a Dodrio.</description>
<picture>242987.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="345" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Jugon</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dewgong`s name is derived from the real animal which has a similar, but much larger, body: the dugong. In the beta versions of Red/Blue, Dewgong`s name was originally going to be Manaty, a reference to the manatee. The Pokémon first appears in the arsenal of a trainer named "Allison" outside of Saffron City, who cites her similar body fat percentage as a reason for her choosing to utilize the Water/Ice type Pokémon.</description>
<picture>242989.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="356" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="15">8.07</rating>
<name>Iwark</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Onix is a subterranean creature that bores its way through the ground at a rate of 50 mph (80 km/h) in search of food. The tunnels it leaves behind as it burrows through the earth are used as pre-dug homes by other subterranean Pokémon such as Diglett and Geodude. Within Onyx`s member is a structure nigh identical to a magnet, which allows it to determine its heading, its depth underground, and other such information useful for a subterranean Pokémon to know. It acts quite like a compass. As Onix ages, it burrows deeper underground, and its rocky member becomes progressively harder, rounder, and smoother. Around the age of 100, the pressures exerted on its stone member become so high that it is compressed into a much harder, diamond-like composition, although it is closer to metal in nature.
In the anime, an Onix is owned by Brock as part of the many Pokemon owned by the training gym that Brock`s family runs. Brock had initially received the Onix from his father, who is a specialist in rock-type Pokemon. When Brock feels the need to travel with Ash Ketchum yet again, he entrusts the care of the Onix to one of his many younger brothers. This takes place in Pokémon Chronicles. It eventually evolves into a Steelix.</description>
<picture>242994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="357" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="7">9.08</rating>
<name>Sleep</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Drowzee is a creature with an elephant`s trunk, the body and color pattern of a tapir, and a hunger for dreams, traits that characterize Drowzee. Its name comes from the English word "drowsy", which reflects on the fact that Drowzee`s primary ability is to put foes to sleep. The "-zee" comes from the sleeping phrase "ZzZzZ". Its Japanese name, Sleepe, is a corruption of the English word sleep. Drowzee`s original biology was based on the tapir and its appearance and dream-eating behavior are inspired by the Japanese folkloric creature Baku. However, its nature is much unlike the real-world animal it was based on.
Drowzee eats dreams; in order to eat, it must put its prey to sleep. A nightmare or night terror will give it indigestion, and it prefers the dreams of human children to those of adults or other pokémon. It`s psychic, but it has limited abilities, compared to other Pokémon; it does not display telekinesis, for example. However, its telepathy allows it to detect people who are asleep, even while asleep itself. Its memory when it comes to dreams is eidetic, and it has the ability to show anyone any dream it has eaten. If one thinks he/she had a good dream, but is unable to remember it, it was possibly eaten by a Drowzee.</description>
<picture>242995.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="362" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="15">4.27</rating>
<name>Kingler</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kingler is a Water-type Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves from Krabby starting at level 28. It also has a Gigantamax form.
Kingler is a crustacean Pokémon resembling a crab. Its strong shell covers the outside of its body, featuring a red upper half and a light tan lower half. Its upper half is topped with six tall, thin spikes that resemble a crown. Its light tan arms are also connected to its upper body. Its lower half doubles as its jaw with six fangs overlapping its upper body. Its two outer fangs are much larger than the inner four and are roughly half as tall as Kingler`s entire body. Its hips visibly protrude from its lower body and connect to its four long, thin legs. Each leg has a single, claw-like foot. Kingler`s main feature is its red pincers. Its left claw is roughly twice as large as the other and hard as steel.
Kingler is often found on the edges of water, usually the ocean. It its powerful claws have 10,000 horsepower and are capable of prying open the shells of Shellder and Cloyster. While Kingler`s large, left claw is its main tool for offensive maneuvers, it is so large and heavy that Kingler can barely lift it. It causes balancing problems and Kingler may quickly become fatigued from continuous use. However, it has been shown to communicate with other Kingler by waving its pincers around. In the past, Crabhammer was its signature move.
Gigantamax Kingler is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive G-Max Move G-Max Foam Burst.</description>
<picture>242789.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="363" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="35">5.07</rating>
<name>Biriridama</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Voltorb are aggressive red and white ball shaped Pokémon that looks strikingly similar to a Poké Ball. Coincidently it was discovered shortly after Poké Balls were invented, some believe there is a connection. Though roughly ten times larger, many trainers get a surprise when they pick one up thinking it is a Poké Ball. The strength of their explosions is dependent on how much electricity they store in their bodies. When jarred or angered, a Voltorb can and will explode, causing massive damage to their aggressor and themselves (as seen in the video games when they use the moves `Self-Destruct` or `Explosion`, both of which causes fainting to the user). It is so unstable that even the slightest bump in the road will make it explode spontaneously. Voltorb do not have a mouth, but do have two eyes that are normally slanted into an aggressive or angry stare.</description>
<picture>242998.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="369" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="9">3.82</rating>
<name>Nassy</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Exeggutor`s name is believed to be derived from the name of its previous evolutionary stage (Exeggcute), whose name is derived from egg and the word execute so Exeggutor`s name is a combination of egg and executor. The Japanese name is derived from the words ココナッツ kokonattsu (coconuts) and 椰子 yashi (palm tree). A large Coconut Tree like Pokémon with three independent thinking heads. The heads are considered fruit or nuts and each has a different expression on its face similar to Exeggcute. When an Exeggcute evolves into Exeggutor, any and all cracks and breaks are mended as they turn yellow and combine to form the new Exeggutor. Living in a good environment will allow it to grow lots of heads, and it is said that they occasionally fall off to form new Exeggcute.</description>
<picture>64428.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="370" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="33">8.59</rating>
<name>Karakara</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cubone`s name is a combination of the words cub and bone, in reference to its young age and relation to bones, both as weapons and armor. The "Cu-" may also be derived from cute, as Cubone is rather referred to as cute and lonely, or the derogatory term "cue ball", referring to a bald person, which is a reference to the skull it wears. Its Japanese name is most likely a pun on 空 kara (emptiness), 殻 kara (shell), and/or からから karakara (dried-up). In the Pokemon Red, Blue and Yellow a Cubone is adopted by Mr. Fuji after its mother is killed by Team Rocket. Cubone is also a playable character in Pokémon Red Rescue Team and Pokémon Blue Rescue Team. The skull a Cubone wears on its head is said to be the skull of its mother, who dies whenever a Cubone is born. Because it never removes its skull helmet, no one has ever seen a Cubone`s actual face. Its cries for its mother are often heard echoing inside the skull.</description>
<picture>243001.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="373" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Sawamular</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hitmonlee is a fighting type Pokémon that evolves from Tyrogue. Hitmonlee`s name is a combination of hit (suggesting its role as a martial arts pokémon), mon (a common abbreviation for `monster` in various collectible monster games, such as Digimon and Pokémon), and lee (an allusion to actor and martial artist Bruce Lee). Its Japanese name is most likely a reference to Tadashi Sawamura. Hitmonlee`s anatomy, a humanoid with no discernible head who instead has a face on his chest, is similar to that of the classical Blemmyes. Hitmonlee have a natural wrapping around their powerful legs. They have three fingers on each hand, but their hands are used mainly to maintain balance during kicks. Any punch or hand based moves bred into or learned by a Tyrogue will carry into either of its evolved forms. This means that even a Hitmonlee can be taught punching moves, such as Mach Punch and Fire Punch.</description>
<picture>243002.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="374" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Ebiwalar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hitmonchan is a fighting type Pokémon that evolved from Tyrogue. Hitmonchan`s name is a combination of hit (suggesting its role as a martial arts pokémon), mon (a common abbreviation for `monster` in various collectible monster games -- such as Digimon and Pokémon), and chan (an allusion to actor and martial artist Jackie Chan). Its Japanese name is a reference to world champion boxer Hiroyuki Ebihara. Hitmonchan Have two natural Boxing Glove shaped hands as well as a training clothes. Unlike Hitmonlee, Hitmonchan have heads with spiky ridges similar to that of Tyrogue. Any kick or foot based moves breed into or learned by a Tyrogue will carry into either of its evolved forms. This means that even a Hitmonchan can know a move like High Jump Kick or Rapid Spin.</description>
<picture>243003.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="376" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">1.31</rating>
<name>Beroringa</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lickitung is a Normal type Pokémon that evolves into Lickilicky. Lickitung`s name is a combination of licking and tongue. Lickitung are known for their appetite as well as their extremely large tongue. A Lickitung can wrap an object or enemy with its tongue with ease and can swallow them it whole. Its tongue can also be used to paralyze its opponent.
In the Anime Team Rocket`s Jessie owned one until it was accidentally traded for her Wobbufet. Lickitung are the featured Pokémon of the Pokémon Stadium Mini Game Sushi Go-Round.</description>
<picture>243004.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="381" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="16">8.07</rating>
<name>Sihorn</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rhyhorn is a rhinoceros like Pokemon with a rock like hide consisting of plates. Ryhorn stands on all four legs and evolves into Rhydon. Rhyhorn is a portmanteau of rhinoceros (which it resembles) and horn. Its spelling is also influenced by the rock rhyolite. Its Japanese name is a portmanteau of sai (犀), meaning rhinoceros and horn (ホーン). Rhyhorn are easily angered and will not hesitate to charge at what ever or who ever angered it. Rhyhorn are powerful enough to topple buildings with their tackle. Rhyhorn are prime examples of "more brawn than brains", as they often charge head first into things but forget why. In Gold, Silver, and Crystal, Brock uses a Rhyhorn to battle. There is also a Rhyhorn in the Brock Gym Leader set of the trading card game.</description>
<picture>243006.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="426" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Monjara</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tangela`s name is a corrupted form of the word "tangle", which is both what it appears visually and what its vines often do to opponents. Its Japanese name comes from mojamoja (もじゃもじゃ, mojamoja?), which refers to shagginess. It is unknown what this Pokémon looks like underneath its vines, only its eyes and two feet are visible. If a vine is lost or damaged it will grow back the next day. The vines always jiggle, which easily unnerves its foes.</description>
<picture>243009.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="427" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="10">7.27</rating>
<name>Garura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kangaskhan`s name is a combination of the word kangaroo and the name of the famous ruler of the Mongol Empire, Genghis Khan. Its Japanese name is derived from "kangaroo" (カンガルー) and "ruler" (ルーラー). Unlike real kangaroos, Kangaskhan do not hop, though they do have pouches in which they carry their infants. Kangaskhan is a female-only Pokémon.</description>
<picture>64465.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="428" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Tattu</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Horsea`s name comes from an inverting of the parts of the compound word seahorse. It is also a pun on the word "Horsey" but is spelled "horsea" because of its habitat. Its Japanese name seems to be derived from 辰 tatsu, the zodiac dragon.</description>
<picture>243010.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="429" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Seadra</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seadra`s name is simply a shortening of "Sea Dragon", although there is a speculation it may have derived from Hydra, a mythic creature.</description>
<picture>243011.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="432" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="15">8.81</rating>
<name>Azumao</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seaking is a goldfish Pokemon. The "sea" in Seaking`s name refers to the fact that it is a water-inhabiting Pokemon. "King" is probably a reference to its unevolved form`s name, Goldeen (a portmanteau of "gold" and "queen"). Hence, its name means "king of the sea." Its Japanese name refers to Azumanishiki (東錦) for one kind of "goldfish" and Ou (王) for "king". Seaking was originally called Neptune in the beta. Seaking is a goldfish Pokemon with a sharp horn, much like a narwhal. It uses the horn for boring holes in a rock for its nest. In spawning season, they can be seen swimming up rivers and streams.</description>
<picture>243013.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="433" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="9">10.00</rating>
<name>Hitodeman</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Staryu is a basic, water-type Pokémon which resembles a starfish. At its core is a jewel like Starmie`s but Staryu`s is circular. It has the power to regenerate its points if any of them breaks off.
In the anime, Misty uses Staryu along with its evolved form Starmie in and out of battles.</description>
<picture>243014.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="434" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="13">8.07</rating>
<name>Starmie</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Starmie is an aquatic starfish Pokémon that evolves from Staryu through use of a Water Stone. It moves through the water by spinning its star-shaped body in a manner like that of a propeller. It consists of two five-point, purple star-shaped structures superimposed on top of each other. At its center is a large gem, surrounded by a golden crest like structure. Starmie`s center section - the gem - is known as its "core". This gem is considered very valuable among collectors. The gem`s hue can change to any color in the visual spectrum, earning Starmie the nickname "the gem of the sea". When Starmie is weak, the core grows dim and starts flickering whilst producing distinctive warning sounds.
In the Pokémon world, the aforementioned peculiar properties of Starmie`s anatomy leads some people to theorize that Starmie`s origins are not of this planet, and that its luminescent core is used to send electromagnetic signals into outer space. It may have some connection with Deoxys having a similar core and the ability to regenerate. In ancient times, Starmie was attributed an equally mystical origin: that it was created from the reflection of the stars upon the waves at night.
In the anime, Starmie is one of the Pokémon used in Misty`s team during the most of the Kanto arc, along with its pre-evolved form, Staryu. Misty also often used Starmie outside of battle for transportation through water or for fire-fighting purposes. Misty eventually left Starmie in the care of her sisters at the Cerulean City Gym, and later reobtained it upon her return.</description>
<picture>243015.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="439" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="9">7.27</rating>
<name>Eleboo</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Since Electabuzz is electric, he feeds on electrical currents. Its methods of securing its food vary: during thunderstorms, an Electabuzz climbs to the highest place possible, in hopes that it will be struck by lightning. As a result, many towns in the Pokémon world employ an Electabuzz in lieu of a lightning rod. Electabuzz also lurk around power plants, feeding off the electricity generated there. This behavior is dangerous to the public, as occasionally blackouts are caused by an Electabuzz overindulging itself at a power plant, or worse, walking down to a city and drawing electricity from there.
Due to its unique diet, Electabuzz`s body is constantly discharging stored electricity, to the point that it glows whitish blue in darkness and static electricity effects manifest. An Electabuzz can control the electric current coursing in its body to communicate with other Electric-type Pokémon, especially with another Electabuzz. It originally is lone in its evolutionary line, but it gains a previous form, Elekid, in Pokémon Gold and Silver, and an evolution, Electivire, in Pokémon Diamond and Pearl.
Like Scyther, as seen in the anime, Electabuzz is most likely provoked by the color red.</description>
<picture>243018.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="441" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="13">8.07</rating>
<name>Kailios</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pinsir is a bug-type stag beetle Pokémon covered with a thick exoskeleton. Its large pincers are adorned with sharp spikes which serve to damage foes caught in the pincers and to prevent escape. If it fails to crush its foe, it will throw the foe powerfully against the ground or into another object with its pincers. Pinsir requires warm habitats to survive. It becomes immobilized in cold climates. It burrows itself into dirt using its pincers and sleeps in the burrow through the night.</description>
<picture>64466.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="442" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="37">6.46</rating>
<name>Kentauros</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tauros is a bull known for its violent urges and rowdy, aggressive disposition in general, as supplied by a tremendous amount of natural stamina. Any given Tauros finds it impossible to keep up its spirits in life without near-constant rampaging. It always tries to find opponent Pokémon to battle outright to serve this purpose, but if it is alone, it will instead concentrate on charging at and knocking down thick trees to calm itself. By locking horns with other Tauros, it fights to assert dominance in a herd. The protector of the herd is usually noted by battle torn horns. As Tauros is based on a bull, it is a male-only Pokémon; its female equivalent is the more cowlike Miltank.
Tauros has a special habit that specifically affects its ability to battle, both in the wild and in trainer-directed Pokémon battles: It whips itself with its three long snapping tails. When it targets an enemy, it heightens its will to battle by whipping its own backside with its tails before charging at full speed.
In the anime, Ash Ketchum captures a herd of thirty Tauros in the Safari Zone (though the episode which features this was banned in America due to its flagrant gun use and politically incorrect humor). They usually remain in Professor Oak`s fields, Ash occasionally picks one up for various tournaments or important battles.</description>
<picture>243020.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="444" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="64">7.09</rating>
<name>Koiking</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magikarp is a commonly found Pokémon that can survive in rivers, lakes,and oceans. Despite its adaptability, the Pokédex states that the Magikarp species has grown weaker over time, and it is one of the least viable for battling in the series. It eventually evolves into another, far more powerful Pokémon, Gyarados.
Magikarp is commonly thought of as the weakest Pokémon. They are only able to learn three moves: Splash (does absolutely nothing), Tackle (a weak attack), and Flail (which does more damage as Magikarp is more damaged.)
In the anime, Magikarp has appeared several times, most notably as the subject of a running gag in which a salesman attempts to trick Team Rocket into buying Magikarp in various guises. (This man also appears in Pokémon Red, Blue, Yellow, FireRed, and LeafGreen.) Team Rocket later adopted a Magikarp-shaped submarine.
Magikarp also appear many times in the video games. They can be found in almost any pond, river, lake, or sea. Many trainers have them, along with other weak Water Pokémon like Goldeen or Horsea. In Pokémon Pearl, one trainer named "Ander," found outside Lake Valor, possesses a Magikarp whose move "Quake" replaces the normal Magikarp`s equally useless "Splash".</description>
<picture>243021.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="445" type="appears in" update="2020-01-05">
<rating votes="15">9.08</rating>
<name>Gyarados</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gyarados is the evolved form of Magikarp. It is a dramatically large change from Magikarp, going from a small fish to a long draconic, serpentine body. Gyarados tend to be very aggressive, and are powerful enough to destroy entire cities. They have a reputation for appearing where there is conflict, and shrivelling everything up with the Hyper Beam attack. Rampages like this have been known to last upwards of an entire month, and will not end until everything around them has been destroyed. Because they have been known to sink ships as well through the seastorms their rage causes, they are considered legendary among sailors, especially the red/ golden variety. Its big change in behavior is said to be attributed to a structural change occurring in its brain while evolving from Magikarp.
In the beta version of Pokémon Red and Green, Gyarados had the name of Skullkraken.
Shiny Gyarados is a particularly rare variety of Gyarados. While Gyarados are normally blue in color, there are some rare red/ gold scaled Gyarados. Though no more powerful than their more common blue counterparts, red Gyarados are valued for their rarity and individuality. This is caused in Pokémon Gold, Silver, and Crystal and the anime by a radio frequency transmitted by Team Rocket to force the Magikarp to evolve. The red coloration comes from the Magikarp evolving prematurely, and not undergoing the conversion from red to blue scale pigment. Thus, they retain the same color they had as a Magikarp. Red Gyarados are more commonly called Shiny Gyarados, or even Golden Gyarados due to the contrasting coloration.
In Generation II Pokémon games, a red Gyarados at the Lake of Rage is a main part of the plot. After its defeat or capture, a Red Scale is obtained, which can be given to Mr. Pokémon, or Marcus Spanier, in exchange for an Exp. Share. The red Gyarados is the only Pokémon in the Generation II games that will be shiny without fail.
In the anime, one is owned by Misty. At first, she fearfully dislikes Gyarados due to a traumatic experience, but manages to get over the fear, take over the Cerulean City Gym, and add one to her team. The red Gyarados in the anime is caught by Lance, the dragon trainer, to rescue it from Team Rocket. Team Rocket also uses a Gyarados-shaped submarine in early episodes, but trades it for a Magikarp-shaped submarine in later episodes.
Gyarados was noticeably larger in the Indigo Series, but has since become a lot smaller. Gyarados` most powerful attack is said to be Dragon Rage (however, this is not true in the games, given that Dragon Rage only ever does 40 damage), where many other Gyarados appear around the main Gyarados, then they start spinning around at such a speed they became one huge tornado, as seen in Episode #18: Island of The Giant Pokémon.</description>
<picture>64468.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="449" type="appears in" update="2020-01-08">
<name>Eievui</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eevee is a Normal-type Pokémon introduced in Generation I.
It evolves into one of eight different Pokémon through various methods. It also has a Gigantamax form.
Eevee is the game mascot and starter Pokémon in Pokémon: Let`s Go, Eevee!, as well as for the main characters of Pokémon XD: Gale of Darkness and Pokémon Conquest. It is also the rival`s starter Pokémon in Pokémon Yellow, although Professor Oak originally intended to give it to the player.
Eevee is a mammalian, quadruped Pokémon with primarily brown fur. The tip of its bushy tail and its large furry collar are cream-colored. It has short, slender legs with three small toes and a pink paw pad on each foot. Eevee has brown eyes, long pointed ears with dark brown interiors, and a small black nose. Eevee is rarely found in the wild and is mostly only found in cities and towns. However, Eevee is said to have an irregularly shaped genetic structure that is easily influenced by its environment. This allows it to adapt to a variety of habitats by evolving. Eevee is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive Z-Move Extreme Evoboost.
In Pokémon: Let`s Go, Eevee!, the player starts with a special Eevee known as a Partner Eevee. The Partner Eevee has purple eyes and a lighter shade of fur. These design elements likely taken from the anime, which implemented similar traits starting in the Advanced Generation series. The marking on the tip of a female Partner Eevee is heart-shaped. Before Pokémon Sword and Shield, this trait was unique and wasn`t found on other female Eevee. Partner Eevee has higher base stats and access to moves that normal Eevee do not. Partner Eevee is the only Pokémon capable of performing Bouncy Bubble, Buzzy Buzz, Sizzly Slide, Glitzy Glow, Baddy Bad, Sappy Seed, Freezy Frost, Sparkly Swirl, and the Partner Power, Veevee Volley. In Pokémon Sword and Shield, the unique pattern is present on all female Eevee as a true gender difference.
As Gigantamax Eevee, it has become larger and more fluffy. The fur collar becomes longer with several triangular furs pointing straight up. The right ear has three red clouds surrounding it like a circle. Due to the fur becoming fluffier and luxurious, any enemies caught in it will lose the will to fight due to being enamored by its presence. Due to Gigantamaxing, Eevee becomes even more playful and rambunctious, desiring to play with its opponent and often unintentionally crushing them with its size.
Gigantamax Eevee is the only known Pokémon capable of using the exclusive G-Max Move G-Max Cuddle.</description>
<picture>68375.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="450" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<name>Showers</name>
<gender>dimorphic</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vaporeon is one of the evolutions of Eevee that is caused by radiation from a water stone. Upon evolving, it gains fins and gills that give it the ability to live underwater. It has small scales that are hard to see. Its finned tail is similar to a mermaid`s, so it is often mistaken for one. Vaporeon`s cells are similar in structure to water molecules, and this allows it to have a unique control over the water around it. This includes being able to transform itself into liquid as a form of camouflage (this being portrayed in the games as its ability to learn the attack Acid Armor), and detect rain through subtle vibrations in its fins. Its base scale color is aqua with darker aqua that makes a line along the spine from the tail to the neck where it forms into a base for its white frill. A darker-aqua patch on the head is similar in shape to a diving cap, and upon the head are three yellow fins, two resembling ears, and the middle one, a Dorsal fin. Its ability is `Water Absorb`, which allows it to gain HP when struck with a water type move.</description>
<picture>243023.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="460" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">10.00</rating>
<name>Freezer</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Articuno is one of the three Legendary Birds along with Zapdos and Moltres. It is a large bird with blue plumage, a bluish-white-feathered chest, a three feathered crest adorning its nose, and a long, sparkling tail. It can create and manipulate ice freely. Its translucent wings are imbued with the essence of frigidity, and the flapping of its wings chills the air, causing the conversion of water particles in the air into snow or ice, causing snow to fall when it flies overhead. In legend, Articuno resides within the confines of icy mountains, because those who have seen its were often doomed explorers scaling such mountains, and therefore it is believed Articuno makes it a point to appear before them and save them.
It is interesting to note that the last letters of its name, "uno" ("one" in Spanish), suggest it is the first of the three legendary bird Pokémon. This is reinforced by the fact that the last letters of the names of its fellow legendary birds suggest that they are the second and third. They are Zapdos ("dos", which is "two" in Spanish) and Moltres ("tres", which is "three" in Spanish).
Articuno`s video game appearances occur in the very confusing mazes of the icy Seafoam Islands, on Route 20, between Fuschia City and Cinnabar Island. It is a unique Pokémon that usually appears alongside Zapdos and Moltres. Since only one of each exists in the games, players usually try to catch the Birds.
Articuno also makes appearances in the anime and manga, also as a unique Pokémon and a general species. They participate in various events and battles. Articuno was initially believed to be the large golden bird Ash saw in the very first episode, but it turned out to actually be Ho-Oh, though the earlier reference was kept in the Red, Blue, Yellow game versions when one looked into a telescope and saw it. Its largest role is in Pokémon: The Movie 2000. Lawrence III creates a battle between the three birds, and Ash Ketchum had to team up with Lugia to stop them. In the beginning of the Battle Frontier challenge in the anime, Noland, the battle factory frontier brain had befriended one. After reuniting with their photographer friend Todd, Ash and its friends hear a rumor that Articuno lives on a certain mountain. After several encounters with Team Rocket, Ash and Todd are saved by Articuno from a snowstorm, and Todd manages to snap a picture of it. Ash`s Charizard did battle with it and Articuno lost by a narrow margin.
In Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Blue Rescue Team and Red Rescue Team, Articuno is the third legendary boss as well as the third legendary bird you battle. He is also the hardest to convince of the three legendary birds that the main hero Pokémon is not responsible for the havocs in the Pokémon World. Absol prevents Articuno from ending the hero and partner by ensuring that Articuno knows the truth.</description>
<picture>243031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="461" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="12">7.27</rating>
<name>Thunder</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zapdos is one of the three Legendary Birds along with Articuno and Moltres. It may be based on the thunderbird. It is a bird with a yellow, angular body and wings. Also behind its main yellow wings is a second pair of thinner, jet-black wings. Its beak is long and extremely sharp. Zapdos, a creature that can freely manipulate electricity, is thought to live in thunderclouds, where it apparently only gains power when struck by lightning. It is seen emerging from clouds while dropping enormous lightning bolts, and even if it does not launch electricity its wings make peculiar crackling and snapping sounds as it flies.
It is interesting to note that the last letters of its name, "dos" ("two" in Spanish), suggest it is the second of the three legendary bird Pokémon. This is reinforced by the fact that the last letters of the names of its fellow legendary birds suggest that they are the first and third. They are Articuno ("uno", which is "one" in Spanish) and Moltres ("tres", which is "three" in Spanish).
Zapdos is found in a Power Plant off the coast of the Rock Tunnel near Cerulean City in Pokémon Red and Blue, and related games. It also plays small roles in the anime and manga. Zapdos is featured in Pokémon The Movie 2000 together with the other two Legendary birds, Articuno and Moltres. It appears that Zapdos communicates through electricity as it shocks Pikachu to communicate. Zapdos also appeared in the 9th Pokémon Movie.</description>
<picture>243032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="462" type="appears in" update="2020-01-09">
<rating votes="11">9.08</rating>
<name>Fire</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Moltres is one of the three Legendary Birds, along with Articuno and Zapdos. It is a large bird that is literally ablaze with fire, resembling something related to a phoenix. It has an orange body, a small pointed beak, and where its plumage should be are flames of a searing intensity. It can freely create and manipulate fire, and it constantly looses flaming embers from its wings. When its body is injured for any reason, it will head towards a volcano and dip its body in the molten magma to heal its wounds. Moltres is an elusive creature, seen about as rarely as the other two members of the Legendary Bird triad. When Moltres thinks it is in the least bit possible danger, it will summon a flash of fire and seemingly disappear, flying out of sight very fast.
The first video game appearance of Moltres was in Pokémon Red and Blue versions. In these Versions, Moltres was in a blocked off area of Victory Road, only accessible from the end of the cave. However, Moltres was moved from its lair in FireRed and LeafGreen, to Mount Ember, an active volcano, on 1 Island, the first of the new Sevii Islands.
The first official appearance of Moltres in the anime was in the episode that marks the beginning of the Pokémon League, where it lights the torch which is equivalent to the real-life Olympic Torch. It also plays a role in "Pokémon The Movie 2000: The Power of One", along with the other two Legendary Birds (Zapdos and Articuno). It was one of the two birds that the villainous collector, often referred to as both Gelardan and Lawrence III, captured to allow him access to Lugia`s power, but the upset of the balance that occurred as a result nearly caused a worldwide weather catastrophe as Moltres was driven to wage war with its two rivals. They were quelled once Ash and Lugia fulfilled the prophecy related to the legendary birds. In a later episode of Pokémon Chronicles, Ash`s rival Richie encountered a trainer named Silver who wanted to capture Moltres, battling him with its Salamence. Silver is interrupted by Team Rocket members Butch and Cassidy who attempt to kidnap Moltres, rather than catching him fairly. Richie and Silver team up to defeat Butch and Cassidy and rescue Moltres, although the firebird was badly weakened by the Rockets` attack. Silver let Moltres go, wanting to catch him in a fair fight when it was at full strength, although it promised it`d try again.
According to one of the trainers in Blaine`s gym on Cinnabar Island, Blaine decided to become a trainer of Fire-type Pokémon after having been rescued by a fiery bird when lost in the mountains.</description>
<picture>243033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1925" type="appears in" update="2011-03-03">
<rating votes="43">7.00</rating>
<name>Rocket-dan</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Team Rocket is a highly organized criminal syndicate "in pursuit of evil" headed by Giovanni (called "The Boss" by his underlings) and based in Kanto. Its main focus is in stealing or capturing, then selling, rare and/or strong Pokemon, but it also conducts cruel experimental research on Pokemon. According to the Generation II games, the Team Rocket Oath says: "Steal Pokemon for profit. Exploit Pokemon for profit. All Pokemon exist for the glory of Team Rocket." Team Rocket`s final goal is to take over the world using Pokemon.
In the anime, Team Rocket is based in Kanto, with many smaller branches reaching out in Kanto and Johto. Giovanni is the Gym Leader of Viridian City during the early part of Ash`s journey. There is also an underground school for training aspiring Team Rocket members. In addition, Team Rocket had its headquarters near Pallet Town and Viridian City, but this was destroyed by Mewtwo in its rage; it is unknown where the headquarters are now. All that is known is that the headquarters are now in a large building built at the end of a canyon and guarded by many grunts, seen when Jessie, James, and Meowth returned from the Hoenn region to report back to Giovanni.</description>
<picture>25950.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1937" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-03">
<rating votes="479">5.97</rating>
<name>Musashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jessie is one half of of the Team Rocket duo that follows around Ash Ketchum and friends in the Pokemon anime, usually trying to steal Ash`s Pikachu, but always failing.
Jessie`s mother, Miyamoto, was a high-ranking Team Rocket agent. When Jessie was around the age of three, Miyamoto left on a mission to the Andes Mountains to record the voice of the elusive Pokemon Mew. However, Miyamoto disappeared, and Jessie was put into a foster home which had very little money. There were times when she had no choice but to eat snow because of a lack of more nourishing food.
When she was old enough, she left home to become a Pokemon nurse in Jouto. However, the school she was enrolled in was literally for Pokemon nurses (i.e. Chansey), so she failed to graduate and left, leaving behind a Chansey she had befriended there. It is assumed that she then traveled back to Kanto, where she enrolled in Pokemon Tech, a trainer`s school, met James, and subsequently failed and dropped out. After this, Jessie and James joined a bicycle gang in Sunny Town, where Jessie was known for swinging a chain above her head as she rode her bike (nicknamed "Chainer Jess").
Due to conflicts in canon between Kanto and Johto episodes and the special episode "Training Daze", what happened between Jessie and James after the bike gang is unknown. What is known, as shown in the special episode, is that they joined Team Rocket separately and were on initially unfriendly terms after being grouped with Meowth. However, they quickly made up and the rest is history.
Sometime before joining Team Rocket, and it is not known when, Jessie obtained a Contest Pass in the Hoenn region. Also during the years before Team Rocket, she had several boyfriends, all of whom left her and/or treated her badly. In "Xatu the Future", she revealed that she had once worked at a T.V. station as the Weathergirl. In "From Cradle to Save" is also revealed that she once was a ninja.
She has a long-standing bitter rivalry with Cassidy, another member of Team Rocket. Another member, Wendy, held a grudge against Jessie for failing to pay for a drink (making Wendy pay), but got her revenge when she added the charge to Jessie`s overall Team Rocket bill.
In the episode "Ignorance is Blissey", Jessie was reunited with her friend Chansey from the Pokemon nurse school; Chansey had since evolved into a Blissey.
Starting in Hoenn, Jessie has become a Pokemon Coordinator, entering every contest that she could. She frequently makes it to the battle round, but usually loses there. However, in "Borrowing on Bad Faith", she finally succeeded in winning an (unofficial) contest by using Ash`s Aipom, which she had saved earlier in the episode. And, in "Team Shocker!", she finally wins an official contest with her Dustox in at Solaceon City. Later she also won a ribbon with help of her Yanmega. She has Contest Passes to compete in the Hoenn, Kanto, and Sinnoh regions.
While Jessie`s role in the Pokemon anime has not yet ended, in Toshihiro Ono`s manga, "The Electric Tale of Pikachu", she ended up married to James and with child.
Jessie seems to have a special preference for snake-like Pokemon, owning both an Arbok and a Seviper. In "The Ninja Poke Showdown", she expressed a preference for Poison-type Pokemon in general.
For unknown reasons, she, James and Meowth mostly use hot air balloons instead of faster ways of transportation.
In the Kanto contests, Jessie disguises herself as Jessebella (which is similar to James former fiancee Jessiebelle) wearing a red dress and glasses. Eventually, Ash, Brock, Max and May finds out her true identity at the last contest.
During the Kanto Grand Festival, Jessie dresses up as Jessadia (Japanese: キャンディ・ムサリーナ Candy Musalina). and wears glasses, long white socks, a yellow and orange dress, and has her hair in pigtails. She works there as an announcer and Lilian Meridian`s assistant; Lilian herself says she may not really like "Jessadia"`s style, but recognizes her talent. In the Latin American dub, she enters Super Contests under the name Jessiebella (referencing Jessiebelle again). Jessie currently still continues to use the Jessalina disguise while participating in Super Contests.
In "Pruning a Passel of Pals!" and "Strategy With a Smile!" she once again used her Jessadia disguise to report on the Wallace Cup.
Although Jessie had entered mostly every contest in Hoenn &amp; Kanto, she lost in every single one, whether it was the first match of the Battle Rounds or the finals. But in the Sinnoh Region, she has so far won 2 ribbons using her Dustox and Yanmega.</description>
<picture>2338.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1938" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="420">5.46</rating>
<name>Nyarth (Rocket-dan)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meowth is a very unique Pokémon as it has many of the characteristics of a human. It walks on two feet, talks and is as smart as any human. Meowth is currently a member of Team Rocket and he travels around with Jessie and James trying to capture Pikachu and other rare Pokémon for Giovanni.
Meowth generally finishes his sentences with "Nyaa (ニャー)" which is the equivalent of "meow" in English. This helps people remember that despite his ability to talk like a human, he still has cat character traits.
Meowth is also known for coming up with his many schemes to try to capture Pikachu. While Jessie and James always agree with Meowth and think his plans are brilliant, they are generally foiled by Ash and his friends.
Long Con to Access Raimon City Pokémon Center
Meowth schemed with Jessie, James and Doctor Zager to figure out a way for them to infiltrate the Raimon City Pokémon Center where high-leveled Pokémon are stored in a vault that is protected by a security machine scan system that would only open if Nurse Joy (Isshu) or Nurse Joy`s Audino were scanned. Meowth pretended to be no longer part of Team Rocket making up a story that his made an error while executing a certain operation and when headquarters hear of his mistake, they told him he was fired.
Ash, Iris and Cilan believed him and allowed Meowth to travel with him. Pikachu though didn`t trust Meowth even though Meowth proved on numerous occasion that it should be trusted. Meowth`s plan was put into action when they arrived at the Raimon City Pokémon Center and as soon as Nurse Joy`s Audino was scanned to open the door, Meowth turned on Pikachu and the other and captured all the Pokémon in the vault. The long con had been a success and Meowth met up with Jessie and James below the Pokémon Center. Unfortunately, they weren`t able to get away as Ash and his friends realized that Meowth had just been conning them and they were able to stop Team Rocket.</description>
<picture>56344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3832" picture="170554.jpg">Inuyama Inuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2611" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="370">7.66</rating>
<name>Kojirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>James is one part of of the Team Rocket trio that follows around Ash Ketchum and friends in the Pokémon anime, usually trying to steal Ash`s Pikachu, but always failing.
James is mostly a comedic parody of bishounen characters; the English dub in particular tends to give him a melodramatic and even campy tone. He is somewhat famous for carrying a rose, though in more recent episodes he does not display it often. Mostly, his rose is displayed in the Team Rocket motto.
The only child of millionaires, James was forced to endure formal society. At a young age, he was forcefully engaged to a girl of whom he was terrified, Jessiebelle, all because his parents wanted to have a wealthy daughter-in-law. Thus, he ran away from home, leaving behind his beloved pet Growlie. He attempted to enroll in Pokémon Tech, a trainer`s school, but, along with his new friend Jessie, flunked out. Then, with Jessie, he joined the Sunny Town bicycle gang, where he was popular for being the only gang member to have to use training wheels (nicknamed "Trainer Jim"). Eventually James, Jessie, and the bike gang went their separate ways.
Due to conflicts in canon between Kanto and Johto episodes and the special episode "Training Daze", what happened between James and Jessie after the bike gang is unknown. What is known, as shown in the special episode, is that they joined Team Rocket separately and were on initially unfriendly terms after being grouped with Meowth. However, they quickly made up and the rest is history.
Since he is proficient in several activities, including Pokémon haiku and PokéRinger, it is possible that he developed his skills during his temporary separation from Jessie, but this is not known for sure.
In the episode "Holy Matrimony!", James returned to his home as a result of a trap by his parents, who pretended to be dead. He was reunited with his old pet Growlie and managed to avoid marrying Jessiebelle. Growlie stayed behind when James returned to Jessie and Meowth.
James has a tendency to be swindled by a Magikarp Salesman, who has on many occasions tricked him into buying a Magikarp or other useless Pokémon and items for large sums of money.
James also has a tendency to cross-dress, but has not done it since "Pros and Con Artists". He does, however, dress up like famous celebrities as well, such as Professor Oak, Juan, and Norman.
James loves rare bottle caps and has an impressive collection of them. In the episode "All That Glitters!" it is revealed that he has "drunk enough soda pop to float an aircraft carrier".
For unknown reasons, he, Jessie and Meowth mostly use hot air balloons instead of faster ways of transportation. However in newer episodes the balloon is shown with `jets` attached to explain how they get from one place to another faster than walking.</description>
<picture>2423.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6693" type="main character in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="911">2.49</rating>
<name>Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
Ash is the main character of the Pokémon anime. Raised in Pallet Town, he started his journey to become a Pokémon Master at the age of 10. On the day that he started his journey, Ash carelessly woke up late despite being told by his mother, Delia Ketchum to get to bed. He rushed to Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory only to find out that the beginner Pokémon - Bulbasaur, Squirtle, and Charmander - had already been given out to trainers who arrived on time. However, Professor Samual Oak mentioned that there was one more Pokémon available - Pikachu. Despite constantly hitting Ash with Electric-type attacks and refusing to return to its PokéBall, Ash decided to take Pikachu along with him on his journey to become a Pokémon Master. Pikachu is cold towards Ash at first and laughs at his failures; however, when Ash saves Pikachu from a flock of wild Spearow, he begins to warm up to his new trainer and the two finally become friends. After the battle with the flock of Spearow, a Ho-Oh is seen flying towards a rainbow in the sky. The PokéDex reveals that the Ho-Oh is an unidentified Pokémon. Thus, the journey of Ash and Pikachu begins.
Captures in Viridian Forest
While making his way towards Pewter City and his first Kanto League Gym Battle, Ash came upon a wild Caterpie deep within Viridian Forest. Instead of using Pikachu to battle against the wild Pokémon, Ash took his chances and threw a PokéBall without weakining the Caterpie first. Luckily, he was able to catch the Pokémon without any trouble. The capture of Ash`s Caterpie marked Ash`s first capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Caterpie the second Pokémon to join his team.
The next day, while continuing the trek through the Viridian Forest, Ash came up on a wild Pidgeotto. He tried to just throw a PokéBall like he did with Ash`s Caterpie, but Pidgeotto swatted the PokéBall away. Misty informed that he must weaken the Pokémon first before attempting to capture it. He called out Ash`s Caterpie to battle against, but Misty quickly informed him that Bug-type Pokémon are weak against Flying-type Pokémon like Pidgeotto. After Pidgeotto dealt significant damage to Ash`s Caterpie, Ash recalled it and sent out Pikachu. Pikachu was able to use its Thundershock to weaken Pidgeotto and allow Ash to capture it with a PokéBall. Thus, this capture marked Ash`s second capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Pidgeotto the third Pokémon to join his team.
Later on, while still in the Viridian Forest, Ash was approached by Team Rocket, who attempted to steal his Pokémon. After defeating Meowth, James`s Koffing, and Jessie`s Ekans, Ash`s Caterpie evolved into Ash`s Metapod.
Some of Ash`s greatest accomplishments have been at the various Pokémon Leagues. He was the victor at the Orange League and the Battle Frontier. He also competed in the Indigo League and the Johto Silver Conference where he placed admirably in both those competitions as well.
Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup
Ash participated in the Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup at the Kagome Town stadium. In the first round he was in the fifth match and faced off against Marris. The match was quickly showcased and Ash won the battle and advanced to the second round while Marris was eliminated from the tournament.
The Isshu League
Ash participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where he was matched up against Trip. Trip`s Serperior was sent out to battle Pikachu and Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior`s speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter Trip`s Serperior speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round. The two met in the Pokémon Center after the battle, and Trip vowed that the next time they met that he would win. The two shook hands and parted ways.
In the first main round, Ash`s opponent was shown on the match up electronic board but not much else is known about the battle. Ash`s Scraggy participated in the second main round of the Isshu League tournament where it faced off against a Darumakka. It was able to defeat it so that moved on to the next round.
In the third round, Stephan was matched up against Ash. Cilan noted that the two of them have a very direct taste and that it would be a good battle. It was only a 3 on 3 battle but the both of them gave it their all. The first two battles of the third round setup the final match up of Stephan`s Sawk vs Ash`s Krookodile, both of which were very injured from the previous battles. Both of them did their best to muster up their reserve strength but in the end a surprise move of Aerial Ace by Ash`s Krookodile was super effective against Stephan`s Sawk and it knocked it out to give Ash the victory while eliminating Stephan from the tournament. Stephan realized after the battle that the reason that Ash withdrew Waruvial after the first battle was because Ash knew that Stephan would definitely send out Dageki, so he didn`t reveal that it knew Aerial Ace and saved until the end.</description>
<picture>6210.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8091" type="main character in" update="2017-10-30">
<rating votes="989">3.91</rating>
<name>Pikachu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
On the morning that Ash was to start his Pokémon journey, he woke up late and by the time he reached Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory, all of the beginner Pokémon were already taken. However, Professor Samual Oak did have one Pokémon left, a wild Pikachu. At first, Pikachu did not like Ash and would refuse to enter his PokéBall. He would often laugh at Ash`s failures and refused to listen to him. However, after Ash proved his loyalty to Pikachu by protecting him from a flock of Spearow, and thus began to earn Pikachu`s trust and respect. The two have since become best friends and Pikachu never leaves Ash`s side.
Since the day Team Rocket first encountered Pikachu, it has been their sole goal to capture it. Day after day, their plan to capture Pikachu has been thwarted mainly due to Pikachu`s amazingly powerful Thunderbolt that keeps on blasting them off.
On numerous occasions, Pikachu has made it evident that he is happy being a Pikachu and has no desire to evolve into a more powerful Raichu. It has proven time and time again that it is a powerful and worthy opponent to any Pokémon that dares to battle it.
Gym Battle against Burgh`s Leavanny
Pikachu was then sent out to battle Burgh`s Leavanny. Burgh`s Leavanny managed to tie up Pikachu with String Shot but unlike Ash`s Swadloon who was able to break free, Pikachu ended up getting hit with a couple of Leaf Storm attacks and a Hyper Beam before it rolled into another of Burgh`s Leavanny`s Leaf Storm attacks to break the string off its body so it could attack. Freed from the String Shot, Burgh`s Leavanny tried to tie it up again but Pikachu managed to avoid it with its speed and then knocked Burgh`s Leavanny out with a combination of Iron Tail and Electro Ball.
Gym Battle against Elesa
Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy and was then matched up with Pikachu. Pikachu made quick work of Elesa`s Emolga and knocked it out with one attack, its Iron Tail.
Elesa`s Tynamo was the last Pokémon that she used in her gym battle against Ash. It was matched up against Pikachu who had just defeated her Emonga. Pikachu had a hard time defending against the fast Tackle attack that Elesa`s Tynamo kept hitting it with but Pikachu used its Thunderbolt to create a large dust cloud leaving only a small corridor for Pikachu to focus on it and so Elesa`s Tynamo couldn`t maneuver out of the way. Pikachu one hit K.O`d Elesa`s Tynamo with a Iron Tail. The loss gave Ash the overall victory.
Battle against Alder`s Bouffalant
Ash challenged Alder to a battle and he accepted though he had been walking all night and was actually quite tired. Alder sent out his Buffron to battle Pikachu but just as the battle started, Alder fell asleep standing up and didn`t give any orders to his Buffron. Alder`s Bouffalant stood still as Pikachu began hitting it with attack after attack until it Alder`s Bouffalant finally got mad at Alder and charged at him and set him flying into a tree. After that, Alder`s Bouffalant no longer wished to battle and Alder conceded the battle.
Gym Battle against Skyla
In Skyla air battle simulation, Ash`s Tranquill was matched up against Skyla`s Unfezant and since her Pokémon was the highest evolved form, she determined that her Pokémon would be the winner in that match-up. In the actual gym battle, Ash`s Tranquill was up against Skyla`s Unfezant which was the match-up just after Ash`s Tranquill had defeated Skyla`s Swoobat. Skyla`s Unfezant proved to be stronger and faster than Ash`s Tranquill, so Ash recalled it and set out Pikachu. Pikachu had a definite advantage over Skyla`s Unfezant with its electric attacks and it quickly knocked it out with its Electro Ball attack.
Ash Just after Pikachu ended up knocking out Skyla`s Unfezant, Skyla`s Swanna was sent out to battle against it. Skyla had been watching her grandpa`s battle videos and noticed that he used the move Aqua Ring to defend against Electric attacks. She used that same defense against Pikachu which nullified its Electric attacks. It`s Iron Tail also couldn`t hit it so high in the air. Ash then noticed the rings in the air and Pikachu jumped up on them and managed to hit Skyla`s Swanna but not directly. Pikachu was now up in the air though and Skyla`s Swanna had the advantage there and it quickly knocked Pikachu out with a powerful Brave Bird attack.
Battle Against Trip`s Serperior at the Isshu League
Pikachu participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where it is was matched up against Trip`s Serperior. Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter its speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round.</description>
<picture>88041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8126" type="appears in" update="2011-01-12">
<rating votes="15">3.84</rating>
<name>Arbok (Musashi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Evolved from Ekans.
Released.</description>
<picture>56362.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8149" type="appears in" update="2011-01-12">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Matadogas (Kojirou)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Evolved from Koffing.
Released.</description>
<picture>56368.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12558" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="50">5.85</rating>
<name>Ookido Yukinari-hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a Pokémon researcher that was once a competitive Trainer, and is generally considered the best in his field. As such, his role in the Pokémon games and anime is that of a mentor to young Pokémon Trainers, a source of information and an occasional plot device. Amongst other things, he is credited with inventing the Pokédex. He also hands out a Bulbasaur, Squirtle, or Charmander to beginning trainers (depending on which Pokémon the trainer chooses) to start their adventure in the Kanto Region. Although he is an expert on all matters relating to Pokémon, Professor Oak specializes in Pokémon behavioural science. He appears in Pokémon 4Ever as a child who was pulled into the future by Celebi. Additionally, it is apparent after Pokémon 3: The Movie that he knew Delia Ketchum since she was a child; this most likely is the reason he occasionally exhibits parental-type concern (mainly in the form of scolding Ash as he is doing something that is dangerous). He also creates poems centred around Pokémon and is known as the rhyming professor by Dawn.</description>
<picture>37802.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16389" type="main character in" update="2018-10-29">
<rating votes="377">7.39</rating>
<name>Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misty is the Gym Leader of Cerulean City Gym. Ash first met her when she pulled him out of the lake while fishing. He took her bike and head off towards the nearest Pokemon Center to help Pikachu. Pikachu later fried her bike and she got mad and wanted Ash to replace it.
Misty has always had a bit of a crush on Ash and it was one of the reasons she decided to travel with him. After traveling with Ash through Kanto, the Orange Islands and the Johto regions, Misty returned to her position as the Cerulean City Gym Leader while her sisters went on a trip around the world.
Misty is a devote Water Pokémon trainer and she specializes in Water-type Pokémon. On the other hand, Misty completely despises Bug-type Pokémon and avoids them whenever possible.</description>
<picture>56342.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16390" type="cameo appearance in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="288">5.09</rating>
<name>Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brock was the Gym Leader of the Pewter Gym but during his travels abroad, his family has taken over the gym in his absence. Brock goal is to become a Pokémon Breeder and learn as much about Pokémon as he possibly can.
Brock was impressed with Ash during their first encounter when Ash challenged him to a Gym Battle. Brock decided to journey with Ash and together they have explored many regions.
Brock is also known for his obsession with girls. Almost every girl Brock sees, he immediately falls in love with. Misty, Max and most recently his Pokémon Croagunk have always been there to keep him in check before scaring off the girls with his overbearing introductions. He is also an expert on Nurse Joy and Officer Jenny as he recognizes all the differences in their personalities and features where as other people cannot tell the difference.</description>
<picture>56341.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="16470" type="main character in" update="2010-10-11">
<rating votes="53">5.52</rating>
<name>Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tracey is a Pokémon Watcher that traveled with Ash during the Orange Islands. He is currently staying and studying with Professor Oak in Pallet Town. He also takes care of Ash`s Pokémon that are residing at the Professors laboratory.
Tracey is a very good artist and enjoys drawing. His artistic skills have been a benefit to him as a Pokémon Watcher as he is able to quickly sketch a scene with great detail.
While journeying with Ash and Misty, Tracey replaced Brock in their group as Brock stayed with Professor Ivy for awhile. Tracey proved that he was quite knowledgeable about the many various aspects of Pokémon which greatly benefited Ash and Misty.</description>
<picture>56346.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22303" type="appears in" update="2010-10-12">
<rating votes="52">5.13</rating>
<name>Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Delia is the mother of Ash Ketchum and she resides in Pallet town with a Mr. Mime she befriended.</description>
<picture>56458.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22304" type="appears in" update="2010-10-12">
<rating votes="6">3.20</rating>
<name>Barrierd (Hanako)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mr. Mime wandered into Delia Ketchum`s house when Delia was expected Ash to return home in a Mr. Mime costume. Delia orginally thought Mr. Mime was her son in the costume and made it dinner. Mr. Mime enjoyed the dinner so much that it became fast friends with Delia and decided to help her by doing the household chores.</description>
<picture>56459.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22305" type="appears in" update="2010-10-14">
<rating votes="17">5.12</rating>
<name>Togepii (Kasumi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The egg that Togepi was inside was taken care by Brock mostly but once Togepi hatched, the first thing it saw was Misty and so this was inprinted in its mind.
Ash, Brock, Misty and Meowth all had a battle to see who would keep Togepi but even though Ash won, Togepi would only want to be with Misty as she was the first person it saw.
Misty`s Togepi evolve into Togetic in the Mirage Kingdom and soon left Misty to look after soon Togepi.</description>
<picture>56692.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22308" type="appears in" update="2010-10-12">
<name>Kabigon (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>56463.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22316" type="appears in" update="2010-10-12">
<rating votes="6">7.10</rating>
<name>Tosakinto (Kasumi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Goldeen was first seen distracting Team Rocket while Ash rescued the Pokémon in the Pokémon Center.</description>
<picture>56473.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22332" type="appears in" update="2011-01-20">
<rating votes="9">8.88</rating>
<name>Hitodeman (Kasumi)</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misty`s Staryu is one of the powerhouses on her water Pokémon based team and has seen action in numerous battles. This is one of her three original team members which also had Misty`s Goldeen and Misty`s Starmie, its final evolved form. The attacks it was commonly seen using were Water Gun and occasionally Rapid Spin.
Misty`s Staryu`s personality is largely a mystery due to the fact that it has no face and thus no facial expressions but has proven its self to be very dependable time and time again.</description>
<picture>56535.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22350" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="17">7.27</rating>
<name>Fushigidane (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanto Pokémon League Tournament
Round 4 - Vs Jeanette Fisher - Grass Field
Ash selected Bulbasaur as his first Pokémon whilst Jeanette choose her Beedrill. As the faster Pokémon, Beedrill charged at bulbasaur at full speed, however Bulbasaur mananged to evade and return a Razor Leaf attack. Once again Beedrill used its superior speed, avoiding the Razor Leaf attack whilst also getting itself in a good position to use a Twin Needle atttack on Bulbasaur. Despite being on the backfoot, Bulbasaur managed to dodge the Twin Needle attack and Beedrill`s Stinger. After jumping backwards, Bulbasaur created enough space to be able to use its Leech Seed attack which struck Beedrill on its attacking stinger. Beedril was stuck in Leech Seed forcing it to the floor and Ash had bulbasaur finish it off using a Tackle attack which gave Ash the Initial Advantage in the battle.
Like Beedrill, Scyther had an advantage in speed and used this by quickly trying to attack Bulbasaur with its blades. After beeing unsuccessful, Jeanette order Scyther to used a Swift attack which managed to hit Bulbasaur a few times and was useful in deflecting its Vine Whip attack. Jeanette ordered Scyther to use a Double Team attack to which Ash had Bulbasaur to attempt to hit the real Scyther. The attempt failed and Scyther was able to land a few strikes by charging at Bulbasaur and managed to evade Bulbasaur`s counter of a Razor Leaf and Vine Whip attack. Ash had Bulbasaur use its Vine Whip once more but told it to swing the vines towards all of the copies which Double Team created, knowing that Bulbasaur would have to hit the real one in the process. The plan worked and Scyther was struck by Vine Whip, eliminating it from the battle.
Jeanette released her final Pokémon of the round which was a Bellsprout. Her choice suprised her a few people including Bulbasaur, as by apperance alone Bellsprout could be considered a weak Pokémon.
Ash had Bulbasaur charge at Bellsprout but managed to flip it above its head using its own momentum against itself. Ash was stunned by Bellsprout`s agility. Bulbasaur was angered at being tossed aside so easily and charged once again at Bellsprout, but like before, was thrown away using its own momentum. Bellsprout took advantage of Bulbasaur being on the floor and thrown it towards Ash`s podium, showing great strength and eliminated Bulbasaur from the tie.
Ash quickly rushed Pikachu into battle to try and finish Bellsprout off.
Orange League Final - Vs. Ash Ketchum (Sand Field)
Bulbasaur was Ash`s fifth choice Pokémon in his winner`s trophy battle against Drake. Bulbasaur`s first opponent was against Drake`s Electabuzz.
Bulbasuar manage to shake of Electabuzz`s initial Thundershock attack and returned a Razor Leaf attack which struck Electabuzz, although, whilst being hit by Razor Leaf, Electabuzz manage to use a Thunderbolt attack that Bulbasaur quickly dodged.
Bulbasaur uses Tackle and causes some light damage to Electabuzz but taking advantage of how close Bulbasur was, it manage to hit Bulbasaur with a Thunderpunch which eliminated it.
After Ash had won the battle against Drake he called out all of his Pokémon that participated in the battle on the stage as Drake presented him with the Winner`s Trophy. Then Ash, Pikachu, Tauros, Lapras, Squirtle, Bulbasaur and Charizard all had their handprints set in stone to be remembered in the Orange Island Hall of Fame.</description>
<picture>56563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22353" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Zenigame (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Squirtle was abandoned by a Pokémon Trainer and managed to form a gang with other abandoned Squirtle that later became known as the Squirtle Squad.
The Squirtle enjoyed to play pranks on the locals and even managed to make Ash, Misty and Brock falls into one of their pitfalls.
Meowth managed to convinced the Squirtle Squad by sharing some food with him by persuading them that he does not take orders from humans just like the Squirtle Squad. Meowth then managed to get the Squirtle Squad to capture Ash, Misty, Brock and Ash`s Pikachu. However, Ash`s Pikachu was injured by a Goldeen just before Squirtle brough it back to Meowth.
Ash was released so he could get a potion from the nearby village but upon his return he found Misty, Brock and Pikachu had been untied. Ash then found out that the Squirtle were only messing around.
Jessie, James and Meowth attempted to capture the Pikachu by throwing explosives around the area and managed to set the nearby forest ablaze. Ash managed to shield the leader of the Squirtle Squard from the explosions and returned the favour by carrying him to safety.
After saving the nearby forest from the fire the Squirtle Squad was recruited by the nearby village to be apart of their firefighting squad.
The leader of the Squirtle Squad was touched by the was Ash treats all Pokémon and decides to travel with him.
Round 2 - Vs Nidorino Trainer - Rock Field
Ash`s second battle took place on the Rock Field and the battle went down to Ash`s and his opponent`s final Pokémon, which consisted of Ash`s Squirtle and his opponent`s Nidorino.
Ash played defensive as he order Squirtle to withdraw into its shell just before Nidorino charged at it and sent it rolling accross the field. Whilst still rolling, Squirtle used a rock as a ramp and was launched into the air which gave Ash the chance to order Squirtle to shoot a water gun at Nidorino. Nidorino was slammed into a rock from the force of the water gun which gave Squirtle the opportunity to land a Skull Bash which gave Ash his second victory of the tournament.
Just before the fifth round battle Ash needed Squirtle`s help whilst they fended off Jessie, James and Meowth whilst attempting to get to the stadium on time. This meant Squirtle was slightly tired before the battle.
Round 5 - Vs Ritchie
Squirtle was Ash`s first choice Pokémon and was pitched against Ritchie`s Butterfree. Both Pokémon traded blows until Ritchie ordered Happy to use Sleep Powder and managed to put Squirtle to sleep which eliminated it from the battle giving Squirtle a quick defeat.
Orange League Final - Vs. Ash Ketchum (Rocky Field)
Pikachu had given Ash the advantage by defeating Drake`s Ditto but was very Tired.
Drake selected Onix and Ash recalls an exhausted Pikachu to be replaced by Squirtle. Ash makes the first move and has Squirtle use Water Gun, but, before it can connect Drake has his onix use Dig and it goes underground. Squirtle headed towards the water pool in the middle of the arena but Onix emerged just before it reached it and then managed to trap Squirtle in Wrap.
Squirtle struggled to get free but the Wrap was too strong, however, Ash managed to get Squirtle to use Hydro Pump which managed to strike Onix and release Squirtle from the Wrap attack. Squirtle used Skull Bash on the Onix and eliminated Drake`s second Pokémon in the battle.
Drake choose Gengar as his third Pokémon and Ash swtiched in Tauros for Squirtle.
Orange League Final - Vs. Ash Ketchum (Sand Field)
Ash recalled Squirtle into battle for a second time and pitched it against Drake`s Dragonite. Ash order Squirtle to use Hydro Pump against Dragonite but gets pushed back by Dragonite`s Water Gun. Dragonite uses a Thunderbolt attack which Squirtle sees and withdraws into its shell and even though it took some damage, Squirlte continued to battle. Drake attempted to finish Squirtle by having it use Body Slam, however, Squrtle uses Bubble causing Dragonite`s Body Slam to fail although it then uses Tail Whip and strikes Squirle which then eliminates it from the battle.
After Ash had won the battle against Drake he called out all of his Pokémon that participated in the battle on the stage as Drake presented him with the Winner`s Trophy. Then Ash, Pikachu, Tauros, Lapras, Squirtle, Bulbasaur and Charizard all had their handprints set in stone to be remembered in the Orange Island Hall of Fame.</description>
<picture>56567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22368" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="10">9.08</rating>
<name>Lizardon (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Charizard evolves from Charmeleon during a battle with Aerodactyl but still remains disobient to Ash.
Kanto Pokémon League:
Fifth Round - Vs Ritchie.
Ash gambled on using a disobient Charizard and he was trailing in the battle and his other Pokémon were tired.
Charizard originally appeared like it was not going to do anything but after Ritchie`s Charmander narrowly missed with a flamethrower, Charizard decided to fight back with a flamethrower of its own with panicked Charmander and forced Ritchie to recall it.
Pikachu was Ritchie`s third and final Pokémon in the battle and was against Ash`s Charizard which had just forced Charmander to be switched. Charizard trembled the ground with a couple of stomps making Pikachu lose its balance and then blew Pikachu away using a gust from its wings. Seemingly thinking Pikachu was not a worthy opponent, Charizard took a nap in the middle of a battle and despite Ash pleaded with it to battle, it was eliminated. This gave Sparky the victory over Charizard and put Ritchie into round six.
Ash angrily recalled Charizard into its ball.
Orange Islands.
Ash called upon Charizard to battle Tad`s Poliwrath which had a reputation of being a very strong Pokémon. Charizard refused to listen to Ash`s orders and Poliwrath shoots a water gun on Charizards tail making the flame much smaller, then a subsuquent Ice Beam hits Charizard and freezes it. The battle left Charizard very injured and Ash had to keep its tail flame alive much like he did when he first found it as a Charmander.
Despite an intial struggle, Charizard saw how much Ash cared for him and once it reached full health in the morning Charizard became friendly with Ash and even obeyed Ash during Battle.
Charizard then went on to defeat Tad`s Poliwrath in a re-match.
Orange League Final - Vs. Ash Ketchum (Sand Field)
Ash chose Charizard to battle against Electabuzz and ordered it to use Flamethrower against Electabuzz, who quickly jumped into the air and landed a Thunderpunch onto Charizard and follwowed up by shocking Charizard with an electric attack. Charizard managed to release himself from the electricity by firing a Fire Spin and then Charizard flew towards Electabuzz quickly making sure it could not use it Thunderbolt attack. Charizard got a good grip on Electabuzz and flew into the air and used Seismic Toss on it which eliminated it and left Drake with one Pokémon left.
Drake`s final Pokémon was his prized Dragonite who he sent out to battle Ash`s Charizard.
Charizard moved first by using a Flamethrower attack but Dragonite countered by using Water Gun which cuts through the Flamethrower and hits Charizard, who then takes to the skies whilst avoiding Dragonite`s Ice Beam.
Dragonite then takes to the sky itself showing great speed as it does so. Dragonite and Charizard exchange Ice Beam and Flamethrower attacks respectively but it is Dragonite who manages to clip Charizard wing using Ice Beam which send Charizard spinning to the ground. Charizard recovers and flies close to Dragonite in an attempt to use a Seismic Toss attack, however, Dragonite avoids and gets a good grip on Charizard which gives it the opportunity to use a Slam attack.
Charizard gets up quick although it is clearly tired but it has enough stength to launch a Dragon Rage attack. Dragonite uses the same move, the attacks collide and both Pokémon are sent flying backwards. When the dust settles both Pokémon are standing but exhausted from the previous battle, after a few deep breaths Charizard falls to the ground and is eliminated.
After Ash had won the battle against Drake he called out all of his Pokémon that participated in the battle on the stage as Drake presented him with the Winner`s Trophy. Then Ash, Pikachu, Tauros, Lapras, Squirtle, Bulbasaur and Charizard all had their handprints set in stone to be remembered in the Orange Island Hall of Fame.</description>
<picture>56582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22374" type="appears in" update="2010-10-14">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Laplace (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Orange League Final - Vs. Ash Ketchum (Rocky Field)
After Gengar confused Tauros Ash quickly recalls Tauros and sends out Lapras in the water pool in the middle of the stage.
Lapras goes underwater to dodge Gengar`s initial attack and then resurfaced to shoot a water gun directly at Gengar who only manage to get out of the way after taking some damage. Gengar shoots Night Shade at Lapras who counter attacks with Ice Beam, the two attacks collide with each other and the resulting explosion eliminate both Pokémon which meant Drake has lost three Pokémon and Ash had only lost one.
After Ash had won the battle against Drake he called out all of his Pokémon that participated in the battle on the stage as Drake presented him with the Winner`s Trophy. Then Ash, Pikachu, Tauros, Lapras, Squirtle, Bulbasaur and Charizard all had their handprints set in stone to be remembered in the Orange Island Hall of Fame.</description>
<picture>56694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1937" picture="92109.jpg">Aikawa Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22405" type="appears in" update="2010-10-13">
<rating votes="52">8.55</rating>
<name>Koduck (Kasumi)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Psyduck pressed the button on Misty`s Pokeball and caught itself.</description>
<picture>56637.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22457" type="appears in" update="2011-01-11">
<rating votes="3">7.91</rating>
<name>Uchikido-hakase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Professor Felina Ivy is a good friend of Professor Oak. She lives on Valencia Island where she has a a house that also functions as her laboratory and large forest where she studies and breeds Pokémon.
She has three lab assistants: Charity, Hope, and Faith who help her with her research.
Until Brock arrived, Ivy was too wrapped up in her Pokémon research to keep her house tidy and she and her assistants nicknamed their house "Our Little Dump". Her table manners are also a bit lacking as she tends to eat fast and sloppily.
She is currently collecting data and studying "How Environment Causes Variation in all our Pokémon". She has breed all the Pokémon on the island to help with her research. She is very protective of the Pokémon there and she helped rescue a Radicate without worrying about her safety.
Ash Ketchum was sent by Professor Oak to pickup the GS Ball from her lab because Professor Ivy and her assistants were unable to open it and she hoped Professor Oak would have better luck figuring it out.
She has written a preliminary report in Pokémon Researchers Monthly on "Pokémon Adaptive Variation as a Function or Regional Distribution". Professor Oak told Professor Ivy that he found it quite persuasive.</description>
<picture>56691.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22461" type="appears in" update="2011-01-11">
<rating votes="4">2.25</rating>
<name>Kongpang (Kenji)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tracey`s Venonat was first seen using its Radar Eye to track the truck that Team Rocket was driving with Lapras in the back. Its Radar Eye proved to be very effective as they were able to track them down. It later helped Tracey look for Ash, Pikachu and Lapras who had fallen off a cliff. It was positive that they were near the beach on Tangelo Island and its tracking skills were proven yet again as they appears on the horizon.</description>
<picture>56706.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22496" type="appears in" update="2011-01-18">
<name>Maril (Kenji)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tracey`s Marill was revealed when Tracey decided that he needed a good Pokémon to help him find the Crystal Onix. Tracey`s Marill has very sensitive ears that can detect distant sounds and the round, rubbery tip of its tail can expand and contract, assisting Marill in the water. While swimming, Tracey`s Marill tail floats so he can see where it`s going.
Misty realized that Tracey and his Marill make a good team as Tracey`s Marill could hear a Pokémon long before Tracey could even see it. Tracey would often play a Pokémon cry on his dex for Marill to help it learn what the Pokémon sounded like so it could search for that particular Pokémon. Tracey`s Marill ears would twitch when it was searching or it found something.</description>
<picture>56740.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22636" type="appears in" update="2010-10-18">
<name>Strike (Kenji)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tracey`s Scyther is a former leader of a group of Scyther on Murcott Island in the Orange Archipelago. However, it lost its position as leader when a younger and stronger Scyther defeated it in battle and took over its leadership.
Defeated and wounded, Scyther was found by Tracey who managed to catch it despite Scyther putting up a brief struggle.
Due to its age, Syther`s wings are slightly shredded and it has additional fur around its cheeks.</description>
<picture>57140.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26800" type="appears in" update="2014-02-07">
<name>Lugia</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lawrence III attempted to capture this Lugia for his collection as he caused a conflict between the Legendary birds Moltres, Zapdos and Articuno to draw it out of the ocean. Lugia proved to be a strong Pokémon and with the help of Ash and his friends, they were able to stop Lawrence III from capturing it. Lugia can also talk and communicate with humans and it became friends with Ash as well.
Lugia helped Ash bring the final treasure back to the shrine but as Lawrence tried to capture it, Lugia fell into the ocean. Melody played the ocarina at the at the shrine which helped Lugia recover.
Lugia destroyed Lawrence III airship and then returned to the sea as the conflict between the Legendary Birds Moltres, Zapdos and Articuno was resolved.</description>
<picture>63455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26801" type="appears in" update="2011-01-16">
<name>Gelardan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lawrence III is a Pokémon Collector who captured the three legendary bird Pokémon Moltres, Zapdos and Articuno in the Orange Archipelago. He began his collecting with an Ancient Mew card and legendary Pokémon were always his passion. His goal was to use the legendary birds to summon Lugia so he could capture it.
He was very familiar with the ancient legend regarding the Legendary birds which states: Disturb not the harmony of fire, ice or lightning, lest these titans wreak destruction upon the world in which they clash. Though the water`s great guardian shall arise to quell the fighting, alone its song will fail, and thus the earth shall turn to ash. O Chosen One, into thine hands bring together all three. Their powers combined tame the Beast of the Sea. He thought that he was the Chosen One when he read this legend.
Moltres, Zapdos and Articuno all attacked his flying ship enough to disable it and cause it to crash but that did not stop Lawrence from attempting to still capture Lugia. Realizing that it would be captured, Lugia attacked his airship and destroyed the remains, thwarting Lawrence`s attempt to capture Lugia. Lawrence vowed to restart his Pokémon collection though after he picked up his Ancient Mew card off the ground near the ruble of his ship.
In the fifth Pokémon movie, Lawrence III appears in a book during the ending credits that Annie and Oakley were reading.</description>
<picture>63457.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26802" type="appears in" update="2011-01-16">
<name>Fleura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Melody lives on Shamouti Island in the Orange Islands with her Carol. She is a very snarky girl and is also quite derogatory when talking almost to the point of being rude. Misty originally thought that Melody was a `big showoff` and was a bit jealous of her but later became friends with her. She took over as the Legend Festival maiden from her sister where she had to learn how to play the ocarina.
Melody felt responsible for Ash and Maren getting caught in the storm and decided to go after them in her sisters boat to make sure they were okay. She proved to be quite good at driving the speedboat and she said that she had been around boats all her life.
She played the ocarina at the at the shrine that helped Lugia recover even though she wanted to go help Ash at the time. By the time Ash and his friends were leaving, she had formed a good friendship with them as the trials they went through together proved to be a strengthening force for her.</description>
<picture>63458.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26803" type="appears in" update="2011-01-16">
<name>Yadoking</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Slowking lives in the Orange Islands and it is very familiar with the ancient legend regarding the Legendary birds, Moltres, Zapdos and Articuno which states: "Disturb not the harmony of fire, ice or lightning..."
During the snow storm, it said it wish it had pants. When Ash arrived, he was surprised that it could talk when it told him to put the treasures on the stone mantle. Ash was also surprised that it knew his name as it had studied the legend and had realized that the "earth shall turn to ash" part referred to him.</description>
<picture>63462.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26804" type="appears in" update="2011-01-16">
<name>Michiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maren was ferrying Ash and his friends to another island in the Orange Archipelago when her boat got thrown off course by a storm that caused them to crash on Shamouti Island.
Maren is an acquaintance of Carol and they caught up with each other while on the beach. When Ash was given the task of getting the orbs from the islands, Maren volunteered to help Ash by ferrying him around on her boat. She then managed to get her boat repaired so that Ash and his friends could leave Shamouti Island and continue their journey.</description>
<picture>63471.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="26805" type="appears in" update="2011-01-16">
<name>Yodel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When she was younger, she was the Legend Festival maiden on Shamouti Island quite a few times. Her little sister Melody took her place a she was getting too old to be the festival maiden. Carol is an acquaintance of Maren and they caught up with each other while on the beach.</description>
<picture>63472.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="10582" update="2017-12-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>1999-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Pokémon 2 – Die Macht des Einzelnen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84092" update="2007-10-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212777" update="2019-02-19">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Theatrical Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212778" update="2019-02-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of the Soundtrack</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
