<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10200" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-03-01</startdate>
<enddate>2014-03-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ookii 1 Nensei to Chiisana 2 Nensei</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">大きい一年生と小さな二年生</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">若手アニメーター育成プロジェクト 2014 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Young Animator Training Project 2014 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Wakate Animator Ikusei Project 2014 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">大きい1年生と小さな2年生</title>
</titles>
<url>http://animemirai.jp/#ookii</url>
<creators>
<name id="5875" type="Character Design">Kaneko Shizue</name>
<name id="5317" type="Direction">Watanabe Ayumu</name>
<name id="1303" type="Animation Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="33733" type="Music">Katayama Shuji</name>
</creators>
<description>First-grader http://anidb.net/ch62004 [Masaya] is a crybaby despite his large stature, so he cannot walk by himself on the dark path to school. The one who holds his hand is http://anidb.net/ch62003 [Akiyo], a tiny but capable second-grader.
Masaya wants to be strong like Akiyo and admires her, but one day, something happens that leaves Akiyo in tears.
To lift Akiyo`s spirits, Masaya goes trekking to the distant Ipponsugi forest to find the spotted bellflowers that Akiyo loves.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="211">5.51</permanent>
<temporary count="211">6.16</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>144235.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15689</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20907</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://a1p.jp/works/2014/okii/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://animemirai.jp/#ookii</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>大きい1年生と小さな2年生</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3367</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348257</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16951</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4859" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-09">
<name>Wakate Animator Ikusei Project</name>
<description>The Young Animator Training Project is an annual project launched in 2010 and funded by the Japanese government`s Agency for Cultural Affairs. The project, which culminates in a series of shorts produced by various animation studios each year, means to address the concern that more of the Japanese animation process is being outsourced overseas, thus leading to a decline in opportunities to teach animation techniques within Japan. As such, the animation production for each short is required to be based in Japan, and professionals must impart their know-how to the young animators through on-the-job training.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="62003" type="main character in" update="2014-09-09">
<name>Akiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62004" type="main character in" update="2014-09-09">
<name>Masaya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62005" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<name>Mariko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20806" picture="182700.jpg">Kuno Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69889" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<name>Masaya no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69890" type="appears in" update="2014-09-09">
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28891" picture="66380.jpg">Oofuku Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69891" type="appears in" update="2014-09-09">
<name>Ayashii Ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33637" picture="245666.jpg">Yano Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69892" type="appears in" update="2014-09-09">
<name>Nouka no Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7641" picture="32436.jpg">Maruyama Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69893" type="appears in" update="2014-09-09">
<name>Tonari no Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69894" type="appears in" update="2014-09-09">
<name>Yonensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="156466" update="2014-04-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
