<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1022" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-07-17</startdate>
<enddate>2003-07-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="main">Wonderful Days</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ワンダフルデイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Чудесные дни</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Nuostabios Dienos</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Чудесни Времена</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Чудові дні</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="short">WD</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ワンダフル・デイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sky Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Wonderful Days - Die Tage der Hoffnung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Wonderful Days</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Фантастические дни</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">원더풀 데이즈</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Sky Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Wonderful Days</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Wonderful days - Mundos Paralelos</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Zkáza Ecobanu</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Ihania päiviä</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">ימים נפלאים</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Wonderful Days</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">สงครามผ่าโลกอนาคต</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Mavi Gökyüzü</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10932" approval="4" total="6">Harmony</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="526912">Beautiful visuals, dystopian futuristic world, great action, a bit of conspiracies.
Overall, a very recommended view to all cyberpunk fans. In fact, not just cyberpunk fans will enjoy this because the film carries a great message with it as well.
The CGI was a bit clunky at places, though it didn`t bother me at all.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="65577">A really good alt.world/future-scifi movie, I have no clue why it scores such a low rating.

Really good CGI (unlike Appleseed) and worth it`s watch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/wonderfuldays/</url>
<creators>
<name id="29545" type="Direction">Kim Mun-Saeng</name>
<name id="29516" type="Music">Won Il</name>
</creators>
<description>"How long has it been raining? Forever. Not forever, no! For a hundred years. They say billions of people once lived on the Earth. When the temperatures rose, the great cities fell, and this rain came, this terrible toxic rain. Our ancestors saw it coming, the catastrophe. They built Ecoban, the first living city, genetically engineered to survive in a poisonous environment. Ecoban became our refuge, our salvation. Survivors came by the thousands, begging to be let in. But our ancestors turned them away, left them to die in the wasteland. The ones who survived became our workers, mining the carbonite fields to feed our Ecoban. Diggers we call them. The Diggers need us, we need them, everybody wins. But some win more than others." — from intro
In the year 2142, the Earth has deteriorated into a murky hell due to an environmental disaster. An elite group of humans has built a fortified, "self-growing" city called Ecoban that converts the surrounding pollution into energy. Meanwhile, hordes of downtrodden survivors subsist outside the city in sprawling hovels under perpetually dark and cloudy skies. As the pollution levels slowly fall off, though, the threatened Ecoban leadership hatches the dastardly plan of wrecking the world beyond the city to secure more pollution for energy.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2501">5.67</permanent>
<temporary count="2515">7.22</temporary>
<review count="4">7.62</review>
</ratings>
<picture>72501.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2536</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>548</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/wonderfuldays/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Wonderful_Days_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ワンダフルデイズ_(映画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>322205</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>원더풀_데이즈</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3664" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>futuristic motorcycle</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4084" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-20">
<name>dark atmosphere</name>
<description>Usually metaphorical. Sometimes literal. At times both!
Typically this refers to the fact that the story is set in a grim, dog eat dog milieu — for example a decaying city.
Often the characters are just doing what they need to do to survive, with little or no expectation that their lives can be better. And often characters may feel they do not have any real choice in what they do.
And yes, occasionally the setting is actually dark — be it night or perpetually heavy cloudy sky and rain. It all adds to the oppressive, hopeless feeling of the show.
You probably will not feel uplifted or happy after watching this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6166" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-23">
<name>South Korean production</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/t6762 [North Korean production]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9847" type="main character in" update="2009-06-24">
<rating votes="7">6.90</rating>
<name>Shua</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9848" type="main character in" update="2009-06-24">
<rating votes="6">2.09</rating>
<name>Shimon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="629" picture="18154.jpg">Yokobori Etsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9849" type="main character in" update="2009-06-24">
<rating votes="7">4.70</rating>
<name>Jay</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99527" type="appears in" update="2018-11-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Woody</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227248.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="99529" type="appears in" update="2018-11-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>David</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>[b][/b]</description>
<picture>227250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38338" picture="141129.jpg">Paku Tongha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99530" type="appears in" update="2018-11-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Joe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="300" picture="226467.jpg">Gotou Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99531" type="appears in" update="2018-11-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Goliath</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99532" type="appears in" update="2018-11-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Eta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227253.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99534" type="appears in" update="2018-11-30">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Soutoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99535" type="appears in" update="2018-11-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Fukukan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="245665.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99536" type="appears in" update="2018-12-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Jay (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39733" picture="152493.jpg">Oka Tamaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99537" type="appears in" update="2018-12-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Shua (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32204" picture="216006.jpg">Ikeda Kyousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99538" type="appears in" update="2018-12-01">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227259.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="99539" type="appears in" update="2018-12-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Noah-hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="10605" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2003-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10858" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2003-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10859" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2003-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="32067" update="2005-09-06">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2003-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="32068" update="2005-09-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2003-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="32069" update="2005-09-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2003-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47063" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84320" update="2007-10-13">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
