<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10228" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2014-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Strange+</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Strange Plus</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ストレンジ・プラス</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">STRANGE+</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10610" type="Sequel">Shin Strange+</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="617782">its as the title says STRANGE</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.dreamcreation.co.jp/stpl/</url>
<creators>
<name id="39013" type="Original Work">Mikawa Verno</name>
<name id="12155" type="Character Design">Furukawa Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="31384" type="Work">Dream Creation</name>
<name id="17263" type="Direction">Nishikawa Takashi</name>
<name id="27343" type="Animation Work">Seven</name>
<name id="12155" type="Chief Animation Direction">Furukawa Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="40378" type="Music">G-angle</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch60830 [Kou] is searching for his older brother http://anidb.net/ch60829 [Takumi], who left home and has gone missing in the city. Worried that he is in trouble, Kou decides not to go home until he has found him, only to find him all too easily. Takumi, it turns out, has become head of the Mikuni Detective Agency, and has no intention of going back home. Kou decides that if he cannot make Takumi return, then he will join the agency himself.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="568">2.46</permanent>
<temporary count="575">4.97</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>147770.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15731</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21067</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dreamcreation.co.jp/stpl/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Strange+</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ストレンジ・プラス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3278</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347846</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2578" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-12">
<name>vulgar</name>
<description>Talking (and acting) in a way that is considered uncultivated, bawdy, common, coarse or unrefined, or "taboo" according to existing cultural standards. Includes boorish manners and obtrusive display of carnal "assets".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4117" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-01">
<name>rolling boulder trap</name>
<description>Nothing beats the rolling boulder trap in case you want to smash those tomb raiders to a blood pool to teach them a lesson. Its simplicity and versatility is matched only by its destructiveness and the sheer terror it evokes.</description>
<picurl>192783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="60827" type="main character in" update="2013-11-27">
<rating votes="8">5.14</rating>
<name>Miwa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60828" type="main character in" update="2013-11-27">
<rating votes="6">5.19</rating>
<name>Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60829" type="main character in" update="2013-11-27">
<rating votes="8">3.21</rating>
<name>Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60830" type="main character in" update="2013-11-27">
<rating votes="6">4.51</rating>
<name>Kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61844" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-28">
<rating votes="5">3.69</rating>
<name>Dorothy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2792" picture="26717.jpg">Kawata Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61845" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-28">
<rating votes="8">5.96</rating>
<name>Rusty Nail</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38838" picture="227845.jpg">Nagahiro Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61846" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-28">
<rating votes="4">5.66</rating>
<name>Ozu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61847" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-07">
<rating votes="5">2.82</rating>
<name>Mera</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61537.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61848" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-20">
<rating votes="3">6.08</rating>
<name>Kyouya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61580.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61849" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-28">
<rating votes="4">6.12</rating>
<name>Kiyoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38837" picture="146428.jpg">Terasaki Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61850" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-07">
<rating votes="5">2.82</rating>
<name>Kaori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>61536.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63448" type="appears in" update="2014-01-28">
<rating votes="1">1.94</rating>
<name>Doumoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40831" picture="160988.jpg">Horie Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="156692" update="2014-08-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-01-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156693" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">THIEF</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thief</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Thief</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Thief</title>
<summary>A phantom thief named Rusty Nail sends a letter to a mansion, saying they`re going to steal their treasure. The Mikuni Detective Agency is called to protect the treasure, but are they up to this challenge?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648805</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157126" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TRAP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trap</title>
<summary>The gang takes the job from Ozu to go save Dorothy, and find themselves in an underground lair filled with traps.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648811</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157127" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HOSPITAL</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hospital</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hospital</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hospital</title>
<summary>The gang decides to go to a doctor to get Masamune`s wounds treated. They were greated by a suspicious looking doctor and a little girl.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648809</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157128" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PRINCESS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Princess</title>
<summary>The Mikuni Detective Agency has been hired as bodyguards to protect a rich man`s only daughter. Despite her being difficult, they were going through with their mission.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648807</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157794" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">INTRUDER</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intruder</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Intruder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Intruder</title>
<summary>The team is put in charge of capturing the pervert that keeps showing up at Kiyoko`s school. Takumi and the others go undercover but will they be able to catch the pervert?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648819</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157795" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PROCESSION</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Procession</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Procession</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Procession</title>
<summary>Masamune is being targeted by someone so Takumi and the others help protect him. Who is the mysterious person after Masamune?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648817</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157796" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PRECIOUS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Precious</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Precious</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Precious</title>
<summary>The team randomly runs into Rusty Nail at a supermarket. Rusty declares that she will get back at them for ruining her last job by stealing something from their agency. Will Takumi and the others be able to protect their agency?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648815</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157797" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">MISTRESS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mistress</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mistress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mistress</title>
<summary>The team sneaks into some company building to steal some top secret information. Kou`s really not up for this mission, however Takumi and the others seem rather excited to complete this mission.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648813</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158366" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">GUARD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guard</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Guard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guard</title>
<summary>The detectives are put in charge of guarding a client by request of the Mikuni company. Will they be able to guard him?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648821</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158430" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">HERO</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hero</title>
<summary>The detectives are put in charge of doing a hero show in one of Mikuni`s buildings... of course things don`t go well.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648827</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158431" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ANTIQUE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Antique</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Antique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Antique</title>
<summary>The detectives accept a job to appraise an odd antique at Kiyoko`s house... and find a very shady treasure there.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648825</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158432" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">CURSE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Curse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Curse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Curse</title>
<summary>The detectives are asked to take care of a cursed medal that brings misfortune upon its owner. Will they be able to survive the series of misfortune that falls upon them?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648823</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159846" update="2014-05-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182182" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648961</identifier>
<identifier>strange</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
