<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10257" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-03-25</startdate>
<enddate>2008-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fabre Konchuuki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ファーブル昆虫記</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www6.big.or.jp/~1happy/fabre.htm</url>
<picture>145884.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www6.big.or.jp/~1happy/fabre.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14354</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="156077" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フンコロガシ1 / フンコロガシ2 / サソリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funkoragashi 1 / Funkorogashi 2 / Sasori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156078" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">センチコガネ / アワフキムシ / ハナムグリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senchi Kogane / Awafukimushi / Hanamuguri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156079" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バッタ / カミキリムシ / ハエ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Butter / Kamikirimushi / Hae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156080" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コオロギ / ゾウムシ / ツチハンミョウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kourogi / Zoumushi / Tsuchi Hanmyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156081" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コモリグモ / コガネグモ / シデムシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Komorigumo / Koganegumo / Shidemushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156082" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">カマキリ / ミノムシ / ゴミムシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamakiri / Minomushi / Gomimushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156083" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">モンシロチョウ / オオクジャクヤママユ / カメムシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monshirochou / Ookujakuyamamayu / Kamemushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156084" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">セミ1 / セミ2 / オサムシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Semi 1 / Semi 2 / Osamushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156085" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サムライアリ1 / サムライアリ2 / オトシブミ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samurai Ari 1 / Samurai Ari 2 / Otoshibumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156086" update="2013-11-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2008-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コハナバチ / ツチスガリ / トックリバチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kohanabatchi / Tsuchisugari / Tokkuribatchi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
