<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10283" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-02-26</startdate>
<enddate>2014-02-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Utopia</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ユートピア</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4325" type="Other">True Tears</anime>
<anime id="7874" type="Other">Hanasaku Iroha</anime>
<anime id="9077" type="Other">Tari Tari</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://infinitedayo.jp/portal/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1385" type="Animation Work">P.A. Works</name>
</creators>
<description>Utopia is a song that was specially created for the http://anidb.net/a4325 [True Tears] x http://anidb.net/a7874 [Hanasaku Iroha] x http://anidb.net/a9077 [Tari Tari] Joint Festival concert starring the main characters of these three anime titles from http://anidb.net/cr1385 [P.A. Works].
P.A. Works then animated a music video for the 90 second version of this song which is included on the BD release of this event.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="226">4.22</permanent>
<temporary count="227">5.71</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>146381.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21103</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.lantis.jp/special/jointfes/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://infinitedayo.jp/portal/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16042</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="885" type="main character in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="142">6.10</rating>
<name>Yuasa Hiromi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiromi is a girl Shin`ichirou`s age and goes to the same high school as him. After her father died, she came to live with Shin`ichirou`s family and has already been living with them for a year when the story begins. She has been in the same class as Shin`ichirou since elementary school, though despite being cheerful back then, she now acts cold when living at his home. In contrast, she normally smiles and is popular at school. She often helps out with Shin`ichirou`s father`s work as they are low on man power. She is a very good player on her school`s girl`s basketball team and is number six. It is clear that Hiromi has feelings for Shin`ichirou, but she decided to lock these feelings inside when she began living with Shin`ichirou.
It is suggested that she hides these feelings because Shin`ichirou`s mother told her, prior to the start of the story, that Shin`ichirou is her brother, which is later proven false.</description>
<picture>31466.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="886" type="main character in" update="2009-07-18">
<rating votes="105">5.60</rating>
<name>Isurugi Noe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isurugi Noe is an odd girl at Shin`ichirou`s school. He first meets her up in a tree where she is picking silverberries for a chicken she named Raigomaru in a coop on a campus. Shin`ichirou ends up having to catch her as she jumps from the tree since she was stuck and could not get down on her own. She likes chickens, though would only feed one of them since she says "it could fly" while the other cannot. After the chicken gets killed by a raccoon, Noe becomes saddened, but does not cry because she "gave away her tears". She later explains that after her grandmother died, she was unable to cry any more due to her grandmother telling her that when she dies she will take Noe`s tears away with her. Noe has an older brother, Jun, who is a basketball team captain at another high school. Noe is known to have a frank personality and speaks honestly to other people. She seems to be able to judge people`s feelings to a certain extent.</description>
<picture>31465.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="888" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="42">5.70</rating>
<name>Andou Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aiko is a girl one year older than Shin`ichirou who attends a different school than him. She is going out with his friend Miyokichi Nobuse, but instead has feelings for Shin`ichirou. Aiko continuously tries to get closer with Shin`ichirou, such as asking him to go shopping with her instead of Miyokichi, and when out with Miyokichi she does not have the same vigour as when she is just with Shin`ichirou. Aiko has known Shin`ichirou since they were kids, and was introduced to Miyokichi through Shin`ichirou. She helps out at her family`s Imagawayaki shop named Imagawayaki Ai-chan. She is shorter than Shinichirou, and enjoys teasing him from time to time.</description>
<picture>31472.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22132" type="main character in" update="2011-12-11">
<rating votes="68">5.70</rating>
<name>Wakura Yuina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuina is a 16-year-old teenager who is daughter of the Fukuya Inn owners that are rivals with Kissuisou. She, together with Ohana, Minko and Nako are in the same class at high school.</description>
<picture>60581.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22133" type="main character in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="83">7.54</rating>
<name>Oshimizu Nako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nako is a 17-year old cleaning maid and waitress working part-time at Kissuisou. She has a shy and timid personality, with a tendency to avoid unwanted social interaction. She is, however, confident about her swimming ability, having been swimming since she was three, she was nick named the "kappa girl". She, together with Ohana, Minko and Yuina are in the same class at high school.</description>
<picture>60580.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22134" type="main character in" update="2011-05-01">
<rating votes="142">8.31</rating>
<name>Matsumae Ohana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Main character of the story. She was born in Tokyo, but is forced to leave the city to work at a hot springs hotel. There she tries to find out and fulfill her dreams in life.</description>
<picture>60578.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22135" type="main character in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="96">4.65</rating>
<name>Tsurugi Minko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsurugi Minko is a 17-year-old apprentice chef and resident at Kissuisou. She has a very cold demeanor, often telling Ohana to `die` following their first encounter, though when this is considered too harsh by Ohana, she settles for calling her a balut instead. Though she is hard working, she becomes passive when being scolded for her mistakes and is usually victim to Ohana`s mishaps. She displays great jealousy when Ohana is praised by other staff. She, together with Ohana, Nako and Yuina are in the same class at high school.</description>
<picture>60579.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42693" type="appears in" update="2013-11-30">
<rating votes="10">3.83</rating>
<name>Wien</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wien (German for Vienna) is the new transfer student from Austria, where he lived for twelve years. Due to his time away, he is very unfamiliar with Japanese customs, and had thus consulted books on the proper mannerisms, often to humorous results when he misuses certain gestures, including performing a dogeza when introducing himself on the first day. He is in the same after-school class as Wakana. He often write a letter for someone he calls http://anidb.net/ch47425 [Yang].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>87070.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42694" type="main character in" update="2012-08-14">
<rating votes="38">6.65</rating>
<name>Sakai Wakana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakai Wakana lives with her father and her pet cat, Dora. Her mother is dead. Despite the fact that she is apparently very good at singing, she refuses to do so to the point of turning down Konatsu`s attempt to recruit her into her new choir club. When she was in her last year of middle school, she was too focused on her exams, she now lives with regret for being unable to say "I`m going", "sorry", and "thank you" to her mother. She is in the same after-school class as Wien.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>87066.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42695" type="main character in" update="2012-08-14">
<rating votes="35">5.87</rating>
<name>Miyamoto Konatsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyamoto Konatsu is a short, earnest girl who loves to sing and dance. She was previously affiliated with the choir club until she had a falling out with their supervisor, who prevented her from singing due to an incident a year prior when she was attacked by stage fright during their recital. After this incident, Konatsu began training herself by performing in the public park. She decides to create her own club so she can sing in front of the school. When this club falls short on members, she combines it with Taichi`s badminton club to form the Choir and sometimes Badminton Club.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>87067.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42696" type="main character in" update="2012-08-14">
<rating votes="55">6.79</rating>
<name>Okita Sawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Okita Sawa is Konatsu`s best friend. Apart from being an equestrian with her horse, Sabure, Sawa is also a member of the archery club, and is the first member invited by Konatsu into the latter`s new music club. She wishes to become a professional jockey in the future, which often leads her to dispute with her father, who believes it to be simply playing around.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>87068.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="42697" type="appears in" update="2012-10-02">
<rating votes="11">5.14</rating>
<name>Tanaka Taichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The sole member of the badminton club, Tanaka Taichi is a very serious yet insensitive person if it`s concerned about girls. He`s hoping to become a pro badminton player someday. He is also the student assigned to guide Wien around school on his first day. Taichi is also good at singing.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>87069.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="156395" update="2013-12-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156429" update="2013-11-30">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
