<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="103" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2002-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaze no Youjinbou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Bodyguard of the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Strażnik Wiatru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">KnY</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">旋風の用心棒</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kaze no Yojimbo</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1542" approval="1" total="7">Samurai 7</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="424780">Really interesting story, even if some may find it slow. The ending was really surprising and kind of morally ambiguous. Deserves more attention.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="214723">It begins slowly as a detective story and quickly evolves into a solid action movie you`ve never seen ;)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ntv.co.jp/yojinbo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4122" type="Original Plan">Toriumi Hisayuki</name>
<name id="9868" type="Music">Saitou Tsuneyoshi</name>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
<name id="6195" type="Character Design">Itou Takeshi</name>
<name id="3748" type="Series Composition">Sumisawa Katsuyuki</name>
<name id="3318" type="Direction">Date Hayato</name>
<name id="9464" type="Original Work">Kurosawa Akira</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on Academy Award Winner http://anidb.net/cr9464 [Kurosawa Akira]`s 1961 masterpiece, Yojimbo.
http://anidb.net/ch18233 [Kodama Jouji] is a pretty intelligent tough guy investigating an incident that occurred in the small town of Kimujuku over 15 years ago. However, the local town folk have been feeling a bit uneasy since the arrival of this wandering stranger.
Jouji is soon caught up in the middle of a bloody gang fight as both groups fight for overall control of the town. Amidst the fighting, shootings, and deadly alliances, will Jouji find the clues to his mystery or will he find himself face down in a body-bag?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="697">6.66</permanent>
<temporary count="704">7.45</temporary>
<review count="3">7.94</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221648.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1809</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1145</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>809</identifier>
<identifier>prxepv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://king-cr.jp/special/kaze/main.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kaze_no_Yojimbo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>旋風の用心棒</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236297</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4997</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/186</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2001/kaze_no_yojinbo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7620</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1563" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-27">
<name>femme fatale</name>
<description>A Femme fatale (french for "deadly woman") often leads men into compromising, dangerous, and deadly situations. She tries to achieve her hidden purpose by using feminine wiles such as beauty, charm, and sexual allure. Typically, she is exceptionally well-endowed with these qualities. In some situations, she uses lying or coercion rather than charm. She may also be (or imply to be) a victim, caught in a situation from which she cannot escape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2796" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>movie</name>
<description>Based on a live action film, Japanese or otherwise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3568" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-07">
<name>gambling</name>
<description>Gambling is the wagering of money or something of value (referred to as "the stakes") on an event with an uncertain outcome with the primary intent of winning additional money and/or material goods. Gambling thus requires three elements be present: consideration, chance and prize. The outcome of the wager is often immediate, such as a single roll of dice or a spin of a roulette wheel, but longer time frames are also common, allowing wagers on the outcome of a future sports contest or even an entire sports season.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18233" type="main character in" update="2017-11-10">
<rating votes="3">8.71</rating>
<name>Kodama Jouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18234" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-30">
<rating votes="3">8.57</rating>
<name>Tanokura Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18261" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-10">
<rating votes="2">7.91</rating>
<name>Araki Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18262" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-30">
<rating votes="2">5.01</rating>
<name>Tanokura Shuusaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48815.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18263" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-30">
<rating votes="2">7.91</rating>
<name>Tonbo no Master</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="385" picture="215702.jpg">Tsukada Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="902" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第五話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pursuit</title>
</episode>
<episode id="903" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第四話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beauty and the Poison</title>
</episode>
<episode id="904" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第三話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bodyguard</title>
</episode>
<episode id="905" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snake Swamp</title>
</episode>
<episode id="906" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第一話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gone With the Dust</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2395" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第七話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legend of the Demon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2396" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第六話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gate Wouldn`t Rise</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4008" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第九話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The 15-Year Truth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4009" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第八話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Casino Train</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4543" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Dreams, White Memories</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4828" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十一話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lurking in the Gloom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5274" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十二話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Echo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6034" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十三話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man Who Returned</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6756" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十四話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">False Reconciliation</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7524" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十五話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Counterattack</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7538" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十六話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Swapping Hostages</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7591" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十七話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Sting</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7924" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十八話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vendetta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8695" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第十九話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sniper</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9123" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二十話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bingo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10625" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二十一話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Search for the Truth</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10689" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二十二話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tanokura Manor Ablaze</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12788" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二十三話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Excursion</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12789" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二十四話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Close Call</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12790" update="2016-06-15">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第二十五話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">So Long</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121097" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121098" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
