<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10313" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-07-19</startdate>
<enddate>2014-07-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Omoide no Marnie</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Воспоминания о Марни</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">思い出のマーニー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">When Marnie Was There</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Erinnerungen an Marnie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Souvenirs de Marnie</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Marnie: Przyjaciółka ze snów</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">När Marnie var där</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Memórias de Marnie</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Marnie - tyttö ikkunassa</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="83001">Beautiful movie, moving, mysterious, nostalgic.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="561560">The combination of scenery, atmosphere and love to detail makes this movie a real rare gem. Yonebayashi succeeds in sucking you into this world instantly. All you can do, is being swept away by the tide.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="475247">Another masterpiece from Hiromasa-san. I really love both his movies (Arietty and Marnie) and can`t wait for next. Very touching ending. Beautiful animation. Atmospheric music. Imho better movies than Princess Kaguya or Wind Rises. Just watch it if you didn`t!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://marnie.jp/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="11846" type="Work">Hoshino Kouji</name>
<name id="11184" type="Direction">Yonebayashi Hiromasa</name>
<name id="38896" type="Music">Muramatsu Takatsugu</name>
<name id="38899" type="Original Work">Joan G. Robinson</name>
<name id="729" type="Work">Studio Ghibli</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr38899 [Joan G. Robinson]`s novel When Marnie Was There (Omoide no Marnie).
http://anidb.net/ch66694 [Anna] lives with foster parents, a misfit with no friends, always on the outside of things. Then she is sent to Norfolk to stay with old Mr and Mrs Pegg, where she runs wild on the sand dunes and around the water. There is a house, the Marsh House, which she feels she recognizes — and she soon meets a strange little girl called http://anidb.net/ch62275 [Marnie], who becomes Anna`s first ever friend. Then one day, Marnie vanishes.
A new family, the Lindsays, move into the Marsh House. Having learnt so much from Marnie about friendship, Anna makes firm friends with the Lindsays — and learns some strange truths about Marnie, who was not all she seemed...
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1346">8.39</permanent>
<temporary count="1349">7.92</temporary>
<review count="2">8.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>166516.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21557</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://marnie.jp/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.marniefilm.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Omoide_no_Marnie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>思い出のマーニー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4658</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348091</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17400</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="165" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>painting</name>
<description>Painting is the practice of applying paint, pigment, color or other medium[1] to a surface (support base). The medium is commonly applied to the base with a brush but other implements, such as knives, sponges, and airbrushes, can be used.
In art, the term painting describes both the act and the result of the action. Paintings may have for their support such surfaces as walls, paper, canvas, wood, glass, lacquer, clay, leaf, copper or concrete, and may incorporate multiple other materials including sand, clay, paper, gold leaf as well as objects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="62275" type="main character in" update="2014-04-15">
<rating votes="9">8.98</rating>
<name>Marnie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153822.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39811" picture="153824.jpg">Arimura Kasumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66694" type="main character in" update="2016-11-05">
<rating votes="12">7.43</rating>
<name>Sasaki Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153821.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39810" picture="153823.jpg">Takatsuki Sara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67630" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-15">
<rating votes="2">1.30</rating>
<name>Baaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10039" picture="37273.jpg">Yoshiyuki Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67631" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-28">
<rating votes="3">3.44</rating>
<name>Ooiwa Setsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40287" picture="156873.jpg">Negishi Toshie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67632" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-28">
<rating votes="2">7.04</rating>
<name>Hisako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33751" picture="92721.jpg">Kuroki Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67633" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-28">
<rating votes="3">4.10</rating>
<name>Ooiwa Kiyomasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38712" picture="145252.jpg">Terajima Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67634" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-06">
<rating votes="2">5.78</rating>
<name>Roufujin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40128" picture="156356.jpg">Moriyama Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67635" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-28">
<rating votes="2">2.67</rating>
<name>Sasaki Yoriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32712" picture="88204.jpg">Matsushima Nanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90557" type="appears in" update="2017-07-22">
<name>Nobuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51046" picture="205372.jpg">Yoritsune Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90565" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-23">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42220" picture="167528.jpg">Sugisaki Hana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90566" type="appears in" update="2017-07-23">
<name>Toichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40413" picture="158226.jpg">Yasuda Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107849" type="appears in" update="2020-01-06">
<name>Emily</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242814.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="159393" update="2016-01-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>105</length>
<airdate>2014-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="11">9.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
