<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10366" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2014-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kenzen Robo Daimidaler</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">건전로봇 다이미다라</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">健全ロボ ダイミダラー DAIMIDALER THE SOUND ROBOT</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Daimidaler: Prince vs. Penguin Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">健全机斗士</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8660" approval="28" total="38">High School DxD</anime>
<anime id="8879" approval="17" total="27">Dakara Boku wa, H ga Dekinai.</anime>
<anime id="10323" approval="13" total="15">Ore, Twintail ni Narimasu.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="534780">This is how ecchi comedies should be done right! The first episodes (1-4) can be hard to watch and boring, but after that, the gags and plot start to run at a fast pace. If you are not a fan of fan service, you will probably outright hate the series, but if you don`t care, you`ll have a lot of fun. Another good point is the fact they stuck my their premise and developped it (yeah, a comedy doing better than your regular modern anime). Recommended to any anime self-respected anime fan. Beat Angel Escalayer meets parody Mecha, can`t be bad isn`t it?</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.penguin-empire.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="794" type="Work">TNK</name>
<name id="6445" type="Direction">Yanagisawa Tetsuya</name>
<name id="9771" type="Character Design">Gotou Junji</name>
<name id="3730" type="Series Composition">Yoshioka Takao</name>
<name id="9771" type="Chief Animation Direction">Gotou Junji</name>
<name id="38961" type="Original Work">Nakama Asaki</name>
<name id="9448" type="Music">Nakanishi Ryousuke</name>
</creators>
<description>A high school boy named http://anidb.net/ch62599 [Madanbashi Kouichi] has Hi-ERo particles, the power source to operate the robotic weapon Daimidaler. With the help of http://anidb.net/ch62597 [Sonan Kyouko] from the mysterious Prince Beauty Parlour organization, he stands up against the Penguin Empire that troubles humanity.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="721">2.84</permanent>
<temporary count="736">5.29</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221953.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15803</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21809</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>23735</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.penguin-empire.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kenzen_Robo_Daimidaler</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>健全ロボ_ダイミダラー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3349</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348551</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16957</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00MFDOPV0</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-08">
<name>teleportation</name>
<description>Teleportation is the transfer of matter from one point to another, possibly a distant one, without application of force, and generally instantly. This contradicts scientific law as we know it, and is therefore nowadays impossible. Sometimes it appears as a paranormal or supernatural ability, and sometimes it is shown in science fiction through technological devices backed up by scientific laws yet to be discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4021" parentid="36" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-08">
<name>evil military</name>
<description>The military is depicted as being of a nefarious nature in this anime. Be it through the heartlessness that their soldiers convey, or the ruthless killing of innocents, the military in this anime is not to be messed with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="62595" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="12">6.50</rating>
<name>Rikantz Seaberry</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62596" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="9">1.97</rating>
<name>Ameku Shouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62597" type="main character in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="17">6.20</rating>
<name>Sonan Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62598" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="13">4.89</rating>
<name>Kiyuna Kiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62599" type="main character in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="10">4.41</rating>
<name>Madanbashi Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147725.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63650" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="4">5.11</rating>
<name>Penguin Teiou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="417" picture="24695.jpg">Hori Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63652" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="5">4.22</rating>
<name>Matayoshi Kazuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65359" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-15">
<rating votes="9">6.04</rating>
<name>Tomoyose Moriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65360" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-13">
<rating votes="9">4.65</rating>
<name>Goya Sewashiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33509" picture="204529.jpg">Tadokoro Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65361" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-15">
<rating votes="8">4.04</rating>
<name>Majikina Soriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69000" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="6">5.68</rating>
<name>Kakazu Chieko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1439" picture="223493.jpg">Takahashi Ao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69002" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="2">1.64</rating>
<name>Henry</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69003" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="2">2.88</rating>
<name>Henry</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69004" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="4">4.83</rating>
<name>Macaroni</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69005" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="5">5.90</rating>
<name>Humboldt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="578" picture="193571.jpg">Tatsumi Yuiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69015" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<name>Daimidaler 2-gata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>158835.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69016" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Daimidaler 6-gata</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>158836.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69017" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<name>Nankyoku 8 Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>158837.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69018" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<name>Nankyoku 9 Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>158838.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69022" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<name>Nankyoku 8 Gou Ritz Custom</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>158841.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69023" type="appears in" update="2014-07-30">
<name>Nankyoku 11 Gou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>158843.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="158899" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">2.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">揉め!ダイミダラー出撃!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fondle! Daimidaler Goes Into Action!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Touché ! L’attaque des daimidalers !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mome! Daimidaler Shutsugeki!</title>
<summary>One day, pervy high school student Madanbashi Kouichi finds himself pursued by a mysterious beauty and a gang of strange penguins. On top of that, a giant robot starts rampaging through town! Could Kouichi`s Hi-ERO particles be the key to saving the city?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="158943" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Sixの挑戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge from Six</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi de Six</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Six no Chousen</title>
<summary>The Penguin Empire finally succeed infusing a penguin with Hi-ERO particles and Kyoko meets a mysterious and handsome stranger with no memories.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="158944" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脅威! 灼熱のジェイクあらわる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Menace! Fiery Jake Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Menace ! L’apparition de Jake le torride !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoui! Shakunetsu no Jake Arawaru!</title>
<summary>A mysterious girl who loves penguins suddenly appears within the Penguin Empire. At the same time, Kouichi must become worthy to pilot Daimidaler.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="158945" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危機! 奪われた太陽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger! The Stolen Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La crise ! Le soleil disparu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiki! Ubawareta Taiyou</title>
<summary>Unable to reproduce the original burst of Hi-ERO particles, Kouichi must discover the true power of Eros to defeat his new enemy, Antarctic Number 9!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159287" update="2015-04-15">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159288" update="2015-04-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
<summary>ep. 1-5, grey yellow-eyed robot after title and at the end.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159328" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">便利! 電動歯ブラシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Convenient! Electric Toothbrush</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pratique ! La brosse à dents électrique !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Benri! Dendou Ha Brush</title>
<summary>As Ritz and the others walk back to Penguin Castle, the Emperor continues testing the penguin particle device. Kiriko and Ritz face off, woman to woman!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159329" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">万歳! 南極11号登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hurrah! Antarctic Number 11 Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Banzai ! L`apparition du N°11 du Pôle Sud</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Banzai! Nankyoku 11-gou Toujou</title>
<summary>Kiriko and Shouma must work together to take down Antarctic Number 11, but Shouma refuses to touch Kiriko anymore. He must find another way!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159330" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">登場!ショウマとキリコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arrival! Shouma and Kiriko</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Apparition, Shôma et Kiriko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toujou! Shouma to Kiriko</title>
<summary>With Kouichi out of the picture, a new main character arrives. The Penguin Empire has almost grasped complete victory. Now, Kiriko must fall in love.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159331" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乱舞! 恐怖のペンギンビラ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mad Dance! The Fearsome Penguin Flyers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Danse folle ! Les tracks manchots de la terreur !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ranbu! Kyoufu no Penguin Villa!</title>
<summary>A new robot, the Ritz Custom, appears after the Emperor discovers the secrets of Daimidaler. Will Kouichi be able to survive such a powerful foe?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159962" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! 健全ロボ対ダイミダラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown! Sound Robots vs. Daimidaler</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille finale ! Robot salutaire, Daimidaler</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Kenzen Robo Tai Daimidaler</title>
<summary>The final battle has begun. Now Beauty Salon Prince must partner with the Penguin Empire to defeat a whole new enemy?! Stand up and fight, Daimidaler!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159963" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">動転! 帝王のセクハラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distraction! The Emperor`s Sexual Harassment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Transition ! Le harcèlement sexuel de l’empereur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Douten! Teiou no Sekuhara</title>
<summary>Madanbashi Kouichi is back, and he`s stronger than ever. Together, he and Kyoko are back in action, but what`s the deal with Daimidaler`s new upgrade?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159964" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発動! ヨーゼフのシンボル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invoke! Joseph`s Symbol</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Explosion ! Le symbole de Joseph</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsudou! Youzef no Symbol</title>
<summary>As Kyoko`s eyes begin to open, Kiriko`s most valuable possession is taken away. Kiriko unleashes an attack against Ritz and the city behind her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="159965" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">警報! 閉ざされたゲート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Warning! The Closed Gate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alerte ! Le portail fermé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keihou! Tozasareta Gate</title>
<summary>While dreaming of Ritz`s past, we find out how far her penguin family is willing to go for her. They must put the Super Antarctic to good use!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161730" update="2019-11-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大特訓! Hi-ERo粒子パワー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">mini-OVA 01</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daitokkun! Hi-ERo Ryuushi Power</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162866" update="2019-11-15">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボーリング・フォー・バインバイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bowling for Boing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bowling for BainBain</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163839" update="2019-11-15">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突!!リッツ対ペンギンコマンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Clash!! Ritz vs Penguin Commandos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu!! Ritz tai Penguin Commando</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163840" update="2015-04-15">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163979" update="2019-11-15">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リカンツ=シーベリー学園大襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rikantz Seaberry`s Great Academy Raid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rikantz Seaberry Gakuen Daishuugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164129" update="2019-11-15">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">饗宴!! ペンギン打ち上げ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Banquet!! Penguin Closing Ceremony</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouen!! Penguin Uchiage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164130" update="2019-11-15">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ペンギン一直線</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Penguin Straight Line</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Penguin Icchokusen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
