<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10365" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-10</startdate>
<enddate>2014-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fuuun Ishin Dai Shougun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Fuuun Ishin Dai Shogun</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">风云维新大将军</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">風雲維新ダイ☆ショーグン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dai Shogun: Great Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Dai-Shogun: Der große Wandel</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">風雲維新大將軍</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11769" type="Alternative Setting">Fuuun Ishin Dai Shougun Reboot</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10243" approval="9" total="14">Nobunaga the Fool</anime>
<anime id="279" approval="2" total="2">Seishoujo Kantai Virgin Fleet</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="413607">IT has nice plot ...
Big and small ...
Borderline hentai , with couple good characters...
Some kinda story ... duno was bussy watching the plot .</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.daishogun-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1793" type="Character Design">Iijima Hiroya</name>
<name id="3575" type="Series Composition">Satou Dai</name>
<name id="769" type="Work">ACGT</name>
<name id="720" type="Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="2120" type="Direction">Watanabe Takashi</name>
<name id="1793" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iijima Hiroya</name>
<name id="41995" type="Music">Bandai Namco Studios</name>
<name id="29469" type="Music">Kobayashi Keiki</name>
<name id="7889" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fukuyo Takaaki</name>
<name id="6241" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishio Kimitake</name>
<name id="46007" type="Music">Kawamoto Yoshinori</name>
<name id="46009" type="Music">Ookubo Hiroshi</name>
<name id="46010" type="Music">Kakino Kanako</name>
<name id="46011" type="Music">Jesahm</name>
<name id="46012" type="Music">Hamamoto Rio</name>
</creators>
<description>Steam became the cornerstone of civilization in the Edo period, giving rise to the creation of massive machines called the onigami. The prestige of the Tokugawa Shogunate was unshakable, and there wasn`t even the slightest hint of rebellion.
A bathhouse worker, http://anidb.net/character/65416 [Keiichirou] is shocked to discover that he is the secret heir to the dying Tokugawa shogun. While continuing to work in the bathhouse, he has to master the legendary the onigami, Susanoo. The mecha can only be piloted by a "perfect virgin of the Tokugawa blood" and a female virgin co-pilot, thus the choice lies between a female ninja (http://anidb.net/character/65417 [Hattori Kiriko]) and a fox-girl (http://anidb.net/character/65415 [Chiharu]).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="435">2.01</permanent>
<temporary count="441">4.62</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>147689.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15807</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21821</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.daishogun-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fūun_Ishin_Dai_Shogun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>風雲維新ダイ☆ショーグン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3364</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348563</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17004</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2690" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Tokugawa period</name>
<description>The anime takes place during a period of Japanese history running from 1603 to 1868.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3958" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>coup d`etat</name>
<description>A coup d`état (/ˌkuːdeɪˈtɑː/; French: blow of state; plural: coups d`état), also known as a coup, a putsch, or an overthrow, is the sudden and illegal seizure of a government, usually instigated by a small group of the existing state establishment to depose the established government and replace it with a new ruling body. A coup d`état is considered successful when the usurpers establish their dominance. If a coup fails, a civil war may ensue.</description>
<picurl>10266.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="65415" type="main character in" update="2016-04-17">
<rating votes="8">5.57</rating>
<name>Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She looks like a sweet little girl, but is actually half fox demon and half human. Her bushy tail is always sticking out from behind. She is a tomboy with and unyielding spirit, but has long lived as a social outcast because she is half demon. She meets http://anidb.net/ch65416 [Keiichirou] and starts to change as she develops an affection for him.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>151092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65416" type="main character in" update="2016-04-17">
<rating votes="3">1.24</rating>
<name>Tokugawa Keiichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Main hero raised in a public bathhouse in Nagasaki. He can`t control his fiery energy to become the strongest man, and spends his days taking on fights. He has dominated Nagasaki, but is not satisfied. There is a certain reason for which he breaks out in hives when he touches women, and that is why he is still a virgin. However, he does not know that being a virgin has great meaning to him.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>151090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65417" type="main character in" update="2014-04-11">
<rating votes="19">8.43</rating>
<name>Hattori Kiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Female ninja from Iga. She was raised with strict discipline as a ninja to carry out missions with loyalty and in cold blood. For this reason, she lacks human emotions such as sympathizing with others. Her actions place highest priority on the Tokugawa Shogun family and the mission, which leads to many conflicts with http://anidb.net/ch65416 [Keiichirou].
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>151091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65418" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="13">7.89</rating>
<name>Houkouin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A voluptuous and beautiful mystery woman. She talks like an Oiran (courtesan), and everything she says is erotic. She confronts http://anidb.net/ch65416 [Keiichirou] and http://anidb.net/ch65417 [Kiriko] several times for a particular purpose. Master of kung fu, she uses a giant iron fan.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>151094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65419" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="2">1.30</rating>
<name>Hyakusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch65416 [Keiichirou]`s sworn brother who adores him unconditionally and is always accompanying him. He`s not a fighter at all, but is fanatical about foreign countries and machinery and has invented many new machines. Physically weak, but tries desperately to support Keiichirou. He is proud of his slicked topknot hairstyle.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>151093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3295" picture="38451.jpg">Ogihara Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66113" type="appears in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Jouki Kugutsu Zanki (Kuro)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>152405.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66114" type="appears in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Jouki Kugutsu Zanki (Aka)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>152404.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66115" type="appears in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Houkouin Kugutsu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>152403.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66116" type="appears in" update="2014-03-28">
<rating votes="1">3.38</rating>
<name>Susanoo Senkou Fuujin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>152402.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66117" type="appears in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Susanoo Bakuryuu Juushin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>152400.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66118" type="appears in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Susanoo Gouten Raijin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>152399.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66119" type="appears in" update="2014-03-28">
<name>Sanagi Susanoo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>152398.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67340" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-09">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Otomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3240" picture="45305.jpg">Yokoo Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67341" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-09">
<rating votes="7">6.10</rating>
<name>Asai Hyougo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67342" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-09">
<rating votes="6">6.32</rating>
<name>Yurihara Maika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69579" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Hitotsubashi Shigeyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69580" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">1.67</rating>
<name>Sakamoto Ryouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2585" picture="22579.jpg">Tsuchida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69581" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="4">3.97</rating>
<name>Kondou Isami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5889" picture="30436.jpg">Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69582" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="5">4.97</rating>
<name>Hijikata Toshizou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34234" picture="228806.jpg">Bridcutt Sarah Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69583" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="4">5.73</rating>
<name>Okita Souji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10391" picture="38277.jpg">Zougou Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69584" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Doushin Oyabun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69585" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Toramaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69586" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Sakuragi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4616" picture="170439.jpg">Nishi Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69589" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Tsubaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27341" picture="74876.jpg">Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69591" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Ii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69592" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Matsudaira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69593" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Verbeck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3805" picture="125128.jpg">Kazuki Hiroto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72641" type="appears in" update="2015-01-09">
<rating votes="1">1.22</rating>
<name>Sutemaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105769" type="appears in" update="2019-10-01">
<name>Sakurayu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>239049.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="159174" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スサノオ強奪, 苛烈なる浅井兵庫!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Susanoo Hijacked! The Vicious Asai Hyogo!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vol de Susanoo; la sévère Hyôgo Asai !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Susanoo Goudatsu, Karetsunaru Asai Hyougo!</title>
<summary>Kei`ichiro goes hunting for girls in town, but ends up in a fight with a traveling samurai.  The samurai, who he thought was a man, was actually a woman in men`s clothes. Otomi saves this woman, Hyougo Asai, when she collapses from hunger, and puts her to work with Kei`ichiro at the bathhouse.  But she has something she`s after...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653223</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159175" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">倒錯の性魔, 法光院襲来!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sex Witch Houkouin Strikes!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La perverse sexuelle Hôkôin attaque !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tousaku no Seima, Houkouin Shuurai!</title>
<summary>Houkouin, the mysterious woman she has appeared around Kei`ichiro several times, attacks him in a giant robot.  She attacks him to learn the power of his own giant robot, Susanwo, but overwhelmes Kei`ichiro instead.  A surprising person saves him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653221</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159176" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">扇情の花街, 妖狐のちはる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Alluring Red Light District and the Foxy Chiharu!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La sensation du quartier de débauche, Chiharu, la femme-renarde !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senjou no Hanamachi, Youko no Chiharu!</title>
<summary>Because of his virginity curse, Kei`ichiro can`t touch a woman.  To work off stress and hopefully find a girlfriend, he goes into town with his buddy.  At a tea house they encounter a young girl, but she`s actually a transforming fox.  Kei`ichiro and his friend Hyakusuke are caught up in trouble over this.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653219</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159177" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世継ぎ騒乱, 慶一郎登場!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Succession Strife, Keiichiro Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Héritier en plein trouble, Keiichirô entre en scène !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yotsugi Souran, Keiichirou Toujou!</title>
<summary>In Nagasaki, in the 1870s, a young man named Kei`ichiro has defeated all his opponents and become famous for his incredible strength.  But he wants to be the strongest man in all of Japan, and his unification of Nagasaki is meaningless to him.  Then one day he`s suspected of a murder.  And lurking in the shadows is a beautiful woman...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653203</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159663" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出島の夜明け, 天下一の拳ぜよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dejima Dawn, the Greatest Fist in Japan!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lever du jour sur Dejima ; le poing le plus puissant du pays !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dejima no Yoake, Tenkaichi no Kenze yo!</title>
<summary>Sakamoto Ryouma and his two foreign friends steal the seal required to activate the Susanowo from Kei`ichiro.  To win it back he`s forced to play a game of strip rock paper scissors, with Kiriko stripping!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653231</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159664" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">情熱の忍者, 血の新撰組</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ninja of Passion, the Bloody Shinsengumi!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le ninja passionné ; le Shinsengumi ensanglanté !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jounetsu no Ninja, Chi no Shinsengumi</title>
<summary>Kei`ichiro learns that the curse is gone and goes out on the town with Hyakusuke.  Kiriko finds out and tries to stop them, but her old friend, Sutemaru has come to get her.  Kei`ichiro is jealous of Sutemaru.  Just then a powerful foe, the Shinsengumi, arrives!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653229</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159665" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大乱の重義, 江戸鮮血開城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shigeyoshi of the Rebellion, the Bloody Surrender of Edo Castle!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shigeyoshi l’insurgent ; la prise sanglante du château d’Edo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tairan no Shigeyoshi, Edo Senketsu Kaijou</title>
<summary>Hitobashi Shigeyoshi is another person like Kei`ichiro who can control an Onigami.  He defeated the Black Ships that came to Japan 17 years ago, and became the hero who protected the Tokugawa shogunate.  But now the other high ranking members of the shogunate hate him, and he is mostly kept in captivity.  He begins a plan to eliminate the rot in the organization.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653227</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159666" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">長崎晩夏, 灯籠流しの夜に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Later Summer in Nagasaki, on the Night the Lanterns Float</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fin de l’été à Nagasaki, le soir du lâcher de lanternes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagasaki Banka, Toronagashi no Yoru ni</title>
<summary>Kei`ichiro learns that a kiss from a virgin will break the curse open him and asks Kiriko and Chiharu for a kiss.  But his disregard for their feelings ruins the mood.  Meanwhile, Otomi tells Kiriko the secret behind Kei`ichiro`s virginity curse.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653225</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160276" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷雲切り裂け, スサノオ豪天雷神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Break the Thunderclouds, Heavenly Thunder God Susanoo!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Déchire les nuages d`orage, Susanoo : dieu de l`éclair, ciel courageux !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raiun Kirisake, Susanoo Gouten Raijin</title>
<summary>Kirikoto has been captured, and a badly injured Kei`ichirou goes to the final battle with Takemikadzuchi.  Will he be able to win back Kiriko and defeat Shigeyoshi Hitotsubashi?  And what is an Onigami?  The final battle begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653239</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160277" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼神導きて, 運命を別つ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Led by the Onigami, to Share Our Fate!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les onigami pour guides, des destinées opposées !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kishin Michibikite, Unmei o Betsutsu!</title>
<summary>Verbeck and Glover bring the black ships to attack Japan once more.  They have far more ships than they did last time, and Nagasaki is in grave danger.  Shigeyoshi Hitotsubashi`s Takemikedzuchi destroys them in a single strike.  Kei`ichirou tries to stand against him, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653237</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160278" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走の果て, 決意の二人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After the Rampage, the Two Make Their Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au bout de la furie, deux personnes déterminées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou no Hate, Ketsui no Futari</title>
<summary>Susanowo has gone out of control, and destroyed the Cherry Blossom Baths and put Kei`ichirou into a coma.  Chiharu blames Kiriko for this.  Faced with her own feelings of responsibility, Kiriko wanders through the city where she encounters Ryouma Sakamoto.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653235</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160279" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜湯恋慕模様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cherry Blossom Baths Love Stories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les situations amoureuses au bain Sakura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakurayu Renbo Moyou</title>
<summary>With Ryouma gone, Kei`ichiro and Kiriko begin to get closer.  But Kiriko is upset that unlike Chiharu and Hyougo she can`t pilot Susanowo.  Houkouin appears and reassures her, but Houkouin actually wants something else...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653233</identifier>
<identifier>dai-shogun-great-revolution</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163968" update="2014-11-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163969" update="2014-11-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
