<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10373" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2014-12-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shingeki no Bahamut: Genesis</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Гневът на Бахамут: Началото</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SnB Genesis</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">神撃のバハムート GENESIS</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Rage of Bahamut: Genesis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Rage of Bahamut: Genesis</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">巴哈姆特之怒 GENESIS</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11223" type="Sequel">Shingeki no Bahamut: Virgin Soul</anime>
<anime id="11544" type="Same Setting">Manaria Friends</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10278" approval="6" total="12">Garo: Honoo no Kokuin</anime>
<anime id="1543" approval="5" total="16">Samurai Champloo</anime>
<anime id="14491" approval="1" total="13">Dr. Stone</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="728642">definitely must see for fans of fantasy. Artwork and characters are both great. Story is fast paced and very enjoyable. It all seems to work out in the end though...like magic. That was the only not so great thing but the journey was an enjoyable watch. Gets a solid 7 from me!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="27155">Wery good anime. For all fantasy fans. Just one problem. That damn afro.... grrrr</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="173054">I`m all about diversity in anime, but this is a no holds-bar on uniqueness. You got heaven + humans vs. hell vs. a god-slaying dragon. I didn`t find the character designs very attractive, but the animation is wonderful. There`s plenty of action to boot, but it`s all just a little too crazy for my tastes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="440680">masterpiece</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="616779">yellow or red recommendation? -this show is one of the nicest 2014 title :: but somehow halfway, it slowed down wich made the issue of being a short show  more apparent to me -god,humans,hell,dragons,bountyhuters,lovers,kingdom- too much , too short , makes it at times flow a little akward and leaving no much room to subplots/dev. etc -- YET ! it still close from achieving it ! -Thats why i think it is still an AMAZING LITTLE SHOW to watch, characters and humor is actually good for a "action adventure show", its EPIC, everything EPIC could be is kind of packed in the show ::  its organic, art and animation is outstanding , music great  - but most of all the "daring" Direction and screenplay (slowmo, 360 etc) is to be recognized - i mean what esle to say - nothing u would expect from a cardgame adaptation -// Definitely Worth the Ride //-   ( ill give red for the awesome opening credits)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://shingekinobahamut-genesis.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="9083" type="Series Composition">Hasegawa Keiichi</name>
<name id="3728" type="Direction">Satou Keiichi</name>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="31375" type="Animation Work">MAPPA</name>
<name id="2163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="4410" type="Music">Ike Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="44461" type="Original Work">Cygames</name>
</creators>
<description>Mistarcia is a magical world where humans, gods, and demons mingle together. In the past, the black-and-silver winged Bahamut has threatened to destroy the land, but humans, gods, and demons overcame their differences to fight together and seal its power. The key to that seal was split in two, one half given to the gods and the other to demons, so that they would never be united and Bahamut never released. Now, two thousand years later, the world is in an era of peace - until the day a human woman steals the gods` half of the key.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2629">6.66</permanent>
<temporary count="2639">7.27</temporary>
<review count="4">7.45</review>
</ratings>
<picture>162425.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15791</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21843</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>28447</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>34642</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://shingekinobahamut-genesis.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rage_of_Bahamut:_Genesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神撃のバハムート</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3543</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>350298</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17562</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>bahamut_genesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00TKLPMNU</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1700" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>pirate</name>
<description>Pirates are people who attack ships on the high seas to rob others of their treasure. Well, at least usually. Other people calling themselves pirates are not unheard of, usually focusing on the freedom and romance involved in the piracy-related tropes and cliches. They may or may not be after the One Piece or a spaceship full of diamonds, too, if that`s what they see as treasure. Real-life pirates were extremely common a few centuries ago, and countries even sponsored their own pirates, called "privateers", to attack ships with flags of other countries. Nowadays, however, very few actual pirates still exist, and they rely more on terrorism and guerrilla warfare than anything else, demanding ransom in exchange for hostages instead of openly attacking the enemies with their swords. Another, more modern meaning for the word refers to people who illegally download copyrighted works they are not entitled to have a copy of. Be whichever it may, there are pirates around here. Arr, avast! Thar be pirates in these dark waters, matey!</description>
<picurl>126791.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3635" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-01">
<name>sea battles</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3797" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-13">
<name>trapped in the body of a child</name>
<description>For some reason, a character in this anime who is a late-teenager or an adult, has their mind trapped in the body of a child. E.g. a former late teenager or an adult is transformed into a child. This can be the result of magic, science, or otherwise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3932" parentid="6073" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-11">
<name>older female younger male</name>
<description>This tag indicates that this anime has a male and female lead, and the female is older. If the main cast is greater than two people, then the use of this tag would indicate a romantic relationship between those two.
In case of harems it translates to:
a) majority of the girls are older than the guy
b) the lead girl (or her main rival) is older than the guy</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4342" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-06">
<name>large-scale war</name>
<description>When the whole world, or, at least, a big part of it, partakes in the hell that is war.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4413" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-16">
<name>heaven</name>
<description>Heaven, the Heavens or Seven Heavens, is a common religious, cosmological or transcendent place from which heavenly beings (such as a God, angels, the jinn, and sky deities like King or Queen of Heaven, Heavenly Father, Heavenly Mother, Son of Heaven, heavenly saints or venerated ancestors) originate, are enthroned or inhabit.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5651" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-06-22">
<name>against destiny</name>
<description>Screw destiny and all the others who try to discourage them; they`re not going to fulfill the prophecy of world destruction because they`re the Big Bad`s descendant, or become a sacrificial magician. They`re going to become who they want to be. (source: TV Tropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5956" parentid="2862" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>broken friendship</name>
<description>For a broken friendship a group of three friends is a must, the break up can be caused by betrayal or death, a love triangle is also possible. The ghost of the old friendship will be the cause of many flashbacks and reminiscences. A dreaded face to face could be a major event or just used as plot device.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6090" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Norse mythology</name>
<description>Norse mythology, or Scandinavian mythology, is the body of mythology of the North Germanic people stemming from Norse paganism and continuing after the Christianization of Scandinavia and into the Scandinavian folklore of the modern period. The Norse mythology consists of tales of various deities, beings, and heroes derived from numerous sources from both before and after the pagan period, including medieval manuscripts, archaeological representations, and folk tradition. [...]
Most of the surviving mythology centres on the plights of the gods and their interaction with various other beings, such as humanity and the jötnar, beings who may be friends, lovers, foes and/or family members of the gods. The cosmos in Norse mythology consist of Nine Worlds that flank a central cosmological tree, Yggdrasil. Units of time and elements of the cosmology are personified as deities or beings. [...]
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7317" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-10">
<name>aboard ship</name>
<description>The story takes place aboard a vessel which sails on the surface of the sea, a river, or a similar body of liquid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7579" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2020-03-31">
<name>Judeo-Christian mythology</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="69468" type="main character in" update="2014-08-17">
<rating votes="54">6.70</rating>
<name>Amira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4659" picture="175153.jpg">Shimizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69469" type="main character in" update="2014-08-17">
<rating votes="23">4.72</rating>
<name>Kaisar Lidfard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69470" type="main character in" update="2018-01-04">
<rating votes="42">5.98</rating>
<name>Favaro Leone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Favaro Leone is a young bounty hunter who, after meeting http://anidb.net/ch69468 [Amira], ends up traveling with her in her quest to meet her mother.
Favaro is a young man with an orange hair styled into an afro, and green eyes. He has a large X-shaped scar on his face. He wears a rather sparse armor consisting of left pauldron, plate on his left elbow, plates on both of his knees and plated boots. He also wears a bounty hunter bracer. After "forging" a contract with Amira, Favaro gains a demonic tail.
Source: Shingeki no Bahamut Wikia</description>
<picture>159773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69811" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="29">6.11</rating>
<name>Jeanne d`Arc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69812" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-04">
<rating votes="3">3.89</rating>
<name>Lavalley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69885" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<rating votes="12">5.71</rating>
<name>Hamsa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69886" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<rating votes="8">4.94</rating>
<name>Bacchus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4841" picture="55063.jpg">Iwasaki Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70019" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-16">
<rating votes="10">3.90</rating>
<name>Azazel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70020" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-16">
<rating votes="18">4.95</rating>
<name>Cerberus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70193" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-29">
<rating votes="56">8.07</rating>
<name>Rita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rita is a seemingly young necromancer, known for being the only surviving citizen of the Nebelville massacre. For two hundred years she revived and lived with the zombified remnants of the town until she was, in the end, bitten by her own parents, driving a bypassing http://anidb.net/ch69469 [Kaisar Lidfard] into killing her out of mercy. After being spared by Kaisar and becoming an undead she now follow the former knight in his travels.
Source: shingeki-no-bahamut-genesis.wikia.com</description>
<picture>211385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70367" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="2">1.66</rating>
<name>Pazuzu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70544" type="appears in" update="2014-10-08">
<rating votes="7">1.49</rating>
<name>Gabriel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70545" type="appears in" update="2015-02-05">
<rating votes="2">2.42</rating>
<name>Michael</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29613" picture="78208.jpg">Aoi Shouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70546" type="appears in" update="2014-10-08">
<rating votes="4">8.44</rating>
<name>Raphael</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1931" picture="238837.jpg">Tsuji Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70547" type="appears in" update="2014-10-08">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Uriel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36024" picture="170957.jpg">Oozeki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71282" type="appears in" update="2014-11-10">
<rating votes="2">4.20</rating>
<name>Martinet</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71283" type="appears in" update="2014-11-10">
<rating votes="4">1.64</rating>
<name>Charioce XIII</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71874" type="appears in" update="2014-12-04">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Lucifer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71875" type="appears in" update="2014-12-04">
<rating votes="2">1.08</rating>
<name>Belzebuth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81468" type="appears in" update="2016-04-03">
<name>Bahamut</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185179.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81469" type="appears in" update="2016-04-03">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Garth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81470" type="appears in" update="2016-04-03">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Ghos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81471" type="appears in" update="2016-04-03">
<name>Gaurin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81472" type="appears in" update="2016-04-03">
<name>Nicole</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4659" picture="175153.jpg">Shimizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81473" type="appears in" update="2016-04-03">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Amon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1942" picture="50629.jpg">Amada Masuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81474" type="appears in" update="2016-04-03">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Barossa Leone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81475" type="appears in" update="2016-04-03">
<name>Ancient Forest Dragon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81476" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Jeanne d`Arc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jeanne D`Arc in her demon form.</description>
<picture>185187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81477" type="main character in" update="2016-04-03">
<rating votes="7">7.02</rating>
<name>Amira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amira in her devil form.</description>
<picture>185188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4659" picture="175153.jpg">Shimizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88771" type="appears in" update="2017-04-12">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Bunyan Leone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Favaro`s mother</description>
<picture>200941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93065" type="appears in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Rita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch70193 [Rita] as a human.</description>
<picture>161983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93067" type="appears in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="3">4.86</rating>
<name>Favaro Leone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch69470 [Favaro] after his encounter with Bahamut. He still calls himself a bounty hunter. Although he was knighted, he has cast off his title and set off for a meandering journey. His right leg is prosthetic.</description>
<picture>211399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93068" type="appears in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="2">1.29</rating>
<name>Kaisar Lidfard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch69469 [Kaisar] after the Bahamut incident. Once the disgrace of a long lineage of knights, he recovered his noble title and his honor by helping to seal away Bahamut. Ten years later he serves King Charioce as captain of the Orleans Knights. Kaisar is honest to a fault and serious as well. His left hand is prosthetic.</description>
<picture>211401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="162972" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Reunion at Ysmenport</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion at Ysmenport</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Reunion at Ysmenport</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reunion at Ysmenport</title>
<summary>Favaro and Amira arrive in Ysmenport where they look for a ship to take them to Helhiem. The captain named Amon turns out to be an old acquaintance of Favaro and his father`s who takes them aboard. It is revealed Favaro`s father, Barossa, was a bandit chief but Favaro chose to strike it out on his own as a bounty hunter. Meanwhile Kaisar continues his pursuit of Favaro with Rita the zombie necromancer tagging along. Rita finds out Kaisar and Favaro were childhood friends but Favaro used Kaisar to get information to sabotage Kaisar`s father`s mission, leading to the family`s downfall. However Barossa died not long after the raid when a demon attacked him and his men, leaving Amon the sole survivor. When a giant crab, the Shipwrecker, appears and wrecks havoc on the ship, which Amira fends off easily, Amon reveals he has a pact with a demon and planned both of Kaisar and Favaro`s fathers` downfalls. Kaisar`s then ship crashes into Amon`s, unleashing Rita`s zombie pirates on Amon`s goons. Favaro and Amon engage in battle only for Amon to be eaten by the Shipwrecker. As Kaisar confronts Favaro the demons pursuing Amira capture her and Kaisar who attempts to shield her from the attack. Kaisar and Amira are whisked away, leaving Favaro and Rita behind.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162973" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Fog of Nebelville</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fog of Nebelville</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fog of Nebelville</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fog of Nebelville</title>
<summary>With the God Key taken from sacred ground the boundaries between godkind and demonkind has begun to crumble. Favaro and Amira continue their way toward Helhiem but detour for a bounty to earn more funds for their journey. Amira recalls "the incident" that took one of her wings, leaving her flightless: when she stole the God Key by becoming it. Meanwhile Kaisar gets lost in a forest but is found and taken to Nebelville. Kaisar`s rescuers implore him for his help in dispatching monsters plaguing the town. Kaisar warms to the doctor`s young but serious and distant daughter, Rita, recalling his upbringing as a knight and the disaster that befell his family. Upon confronting the monsters it is revealed that a fog infects victim`s minds to believe an illusion: The village really is rundown and inhabited with zombies. Favaro and Amira show themselves and confront the bounty, the doctor`s daughter, who is a necromancer and has commanded the zombie filled town for the past 200 years.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162974" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Escape from Livian</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape from Livian</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Escape from Livian</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Escape from Livian</title>
<summary>Bewildered at suddenly having a tail Favaro tries to cut it off. After no success the mysterious woman from the night before appears, declaring she placed a spell on Favaro; until Favaro tells her the shortcut to Helhiem, she will not undo the spell as it is a contract. Since Favaro lied he declares he has to show the woman the way and they leave town. Later in town the Knights of Jeanne D`Arc appear, declaring they are searching for a demon. Kaiser, thinking it to be Favaro, declares he will capture and deliver it as he is a knight himself. He is quickly dismissed due to his bounty hunter band though he protests he was forced to become one after his family fell to ruin, something he blames Favaro for. With Favaro the demon woman, named Amira, she is looking for her mother who is in Helhiem. As Favaro contemplates killing Amira to free himself of the spell Kaisar appears, declaring Favaro a demon and guilty of kidnapping Amira, only to be knocked out by Favaro and the two escape again. In the next town the Knights appear, saying they`re looking for a female demon with one wing; Favaro who is alone seizes his chance by selling out Amira. The Knights chase Amira while Favaro hopes them killing her will release the spell. However he is forced back together with Amira; seeing she`s unharmed the two run from the knights who chase them to a bridge. The two tumble down into the river below and out of the knights` sight. Amira then asks Favaro if he is a liar and he protests, asking if his face looks that of a liar only to make a goofy devious expression.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162975" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Encounter Wytearp.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter Wytearp.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Encounter Wytearp.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Encounter Wytearp.</title>
<summary>After the epic battle against Bahamut who was sealed the story jumps forward two thousand years later to an era of overall peace. A long battle and chase that span across the town of Wytearp ends when Favaro Leone the bounty hunter escapes the grasp of Kaisar Lidfald, a disgraced knight who suffered humiliation by Favaro. After successfully tracking down and killing a criminal who summons demons, Favaro collects his bounty and celebrates at the local town`s tavern. While Favaro brags about his feats, a mysterious woman overhears him boasting about knowing how to get to Helheim quickly. She then confronts Favaro outside and demands directions to Helheim. The discussion is cut short when the criminal`s younger brother appears. Favaro underestimates the brother`s summoned demon and is overwhelmed only to be saved by the mysterious woman who reveals powers that like a demon. She easily overwhelms the demon while Favaro takes out the brother criminal. Busy gloating Favaro is caught in the way of debris and he passes out as the demon woman draws closer, appearing to kiss him. Favaro then awakens at an inn, thinking it all a dream only to find himself suddenly declared a "demon" and he has grown a tail.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163407" update="2014-10-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163408" update="2014-10-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163653" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Anatae, Part 3: Beyond the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anatae, Part 3: Beyond the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Anatae, Part 3 : Beyond the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anatae, Part 3: Beyond the Storm</title>
<summary>Amira stumbles upon the statue of Bahamut, triggering a vision of the beast being freed. Meanwhile The angels discuss Jeanne being worthy of becoming a Holy Knight to defeat an awakened Bahamut, later granting her another holy weapon: a sword. Amira tells the others about when she first woke up from a long slumber and was given her necklace by an unknown figure, promising to fulfill her dream in Helheim. The King then calls the group before him and Amira points out her father to Favaro and the others, Jeanne D`Arc`s lieutenant Lavalley. The King knights Favaro and Kaisar which Favaro begrudgingly accepts while Kaisar is ecstatic to have his honor restored. Elsewhere an injured Azazel confronts Beelzebub for scheming behind their leader Lucifer`s back and as Beelzebub incinerates Azazel he reveals he`s bringing about Judgement Day. The jealous King is tricked into thinking Jeanne is plotting his death after she is favored by the gods and not him. That night Favaro and Rita take Amira to see her father, Lavalley. Lavalley reveals Amira is half angel and half demon, her mother being the angel Nicole and that he is not her father but a human former bodyguard to her mother. When Amira was a baby the demons kidnapped her and accelerated her growth, Amira really being 5 years old. When Amira says she was promised to see her mother in Helheim if she stole the key Lavalley tells her that is impossible and uses the united pendents to reveal Nicole`s true location: Prudisia, the Valley of the Demons.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163654" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Anatae, Part 2: The Storm Rages</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anatae, Part 2: The Storm Rages</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Anatae, Part 2: The Storm Rages</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anatae, Part 2: The Storm Rages</title>
<summary>The demon legion descends upon the city to claim the God Key while the humans go on the defense. A happy Amira appears before Favaro, claiming she met her father within the city, before dashing off. The King`s forces battle the demons at a losing pace while Amira happily stuffs herself inside the kitchen while Favaro, Kaisar and Rita attempt to get information about her father. Azazel infiltrates the castle, leaving carnage behind as he seeks Amira who is now passed out. He proceeds to taunt Kaisar about his father`s death, admitting his involvement but Favaro takes the blame and challenges Azazel, buying time to get Amira and the God Key away. Eventually Kaisar comes back to aid Favaro and Azazel recalls he is actually the killer of both their fathers. Kaisar sacrifices himself to buy time for Jeanne to charge up her sacred weapon Maltet who then delivers a decisive blow to the distracted Azazel. The tide changes, the humans winning and Favaro manages to save Kaisar but in the meantime when Rita finishes fighting and goes back to wake Amira she finds her missing.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163655" update="2016-06-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Anatae, Part 1: Legendary Saint</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anatae, Part 1: Legendary Saint</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Anatae, Part 1: Legendary Saint</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anatae, Part 1: Legendary Saint</title>
<summary>The demon Azazel seeks the council with the demon clan`s leader but is turned away to capture the God Key that escaped his grasp. Favaro and the rest of the group are captured by knights and presented before the King in Anatae when three angels appear; they confirm that Amira is half angel and demon. The King orders their deaths but the angels proclaim they must be kept safe as the demons are trying to revive Bahamut. Favaro, Kaisar, Rita and Amira are permitted freedom within the capital but cannot leave, causing Amira to insist Favaro take her to Helheim as he promised but he says it was only because of her curse and he`s done with the dangers she draws. The angel clan schemes to use Amira to their advantage as her emotional state is tied to the God Key she is now the vessel of. Favaro encounters Jeanne who explains to him about Bahamut`s original sealing and the legendary knight, a saint, who will be the one to seal Bahamut again. In the cover of night, Amira is lured from her room by a cloaked figure who possesses the same pendant as her, leaving her to wonder about his true identity. At the same time Azazel prepares his attack on the city.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163656" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Rescue in Sword Valley</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rescue in Sword Valley</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rescue in Sword Valley</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rescue in Sword Valley</title>
<summary>Heaven`s forces try to maintain the barrier around the seal Bahamut as it beings to crumble. Elsewhere Favaro and Rita give chase to the demons who nabbed Amira and Kaisar though Favaro would rather leave them. In the demon Azazel`s foating fortress Amira is tortured for information about the God`s Key while Kaisar watches helplessly. Rita and Favaro manage to borrow the god Bacchus` flying carriage after Favaro proves his commitment by breaking his bounty hunter`s band, making him an ordinary outlaw. The two then manage to break into the fortress but get separated when Azazel goads Kaisar into fighting Favaro though Rita quickly breaks up the fight. Jeanne d`Arc`s Knights ambush the demon fortress, causing a diversion that allows Favaro, Rita and Kaisar to rescue Amira only to end up before Azazel. Favaro realizes Azazel is the demon responsible for his father`s death. When Azazel attacks Amira a mysterious force within her blows him off the fortress, sending him tumbling below, though he now understands who sent her.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164200" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Rage of Bahamut</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rage of Bahamut</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rage of Bahamut</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rage of Bahamut</title>
<summary>Beelzebub declares the war between demons and gods over with Bahamut`s awakening as he is its master, and commands the gods to bow before him. He then orders the great dragon to unleash its power to which it attacks Beelzebub before proceeding to blast everything in sight. Rita manages to save Kaisar and reveals that Lavalley is really, Gilles de Rais, a sorcerer with a bounty who is the one behind Bahamut`s revival as well as all the deception. The demons and gods team up to fight against the uncontrollable Bahamut. Kaisar attempts to attack Lavalley only to find they have no effect before Lavalley reveals he is Martient as well. Elsewhere a heavily wounded Beelzebub curses Martient`s deception of using Amira to be able control Bahamut before Azazel finishes him off, ending his revenge. A bloody Favaro appears, revealing he`s not dead and begins combat against Kaisar seemingly by Lavalley`s command. Favaro gains the upper hand before proceeding to cut Kaisar`s hand off, presenting it with the bounty armband to Lavalley. Favaro catches Lavalley off guard by warning him about having a bounty on his head before Kaidar recites the bounty armband`s incantation thus turning Lavalley into a bounty tablet. As Rita tends to Kaisar`s wounds Favaro reveals that Kaisar managed to shoot him with the antidote, turning him back to normal and the fight was an act. As Bahamut continues to rage Favaro declares it`s up to him to stop it and he`ll kill Amira as it`s the only way to stop the beast as well free her from sadness. Kaisar decides to join Favaro to save Amira, still believing there is a chance to separate her from Bahamut. In order keep Bahamut still for a minute the demons and gods work together to contain the beast to allow Favaro and Kaisar to approach it. With tears in his eyes Favaro screams Amira`s name as he stabs Bahamut, unleashing a beam of light. Amira then appears before him, chiding him for being late and he promises to take her somewhere better than Helheim. Amira proceeds to kiss Favaro after realizing he isn`t lying when he meets her with a serious, sincere gaze. She thanks Favaro before disappearing back inside Bahamut, causing the beast to explode though Kaisar escapes, leaving Favaro to be caught up in the blast that destroys his leg. Half a year later in the royal capital Kaisar, given a mechanical hand from Rita, commands the soldiers as a lieutenant with his knighthood intact. Favaro is alive with a mechanical right leg and is back to bounty hunting though he remarks Bahamut will never be forever gone. Kaisar then suddenly appears, forsaking his knightly duties, swearing not to be in Favaro`s debt and the two ride off.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164201" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">All Roads Lead to Abos</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All Roads Lead to Abos</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">All Roads Lead to Abos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">All Roads Lead to Abos</title>
<summary>With Favaro transformed into a demon, he is now under their control. Beezlebub and Martient prepare Amira for transportation but not before blasting Kaisar away to fall into the depths below. The god clan attempt to maintain the seal on Bahamut but sense the presence of the Transcendent Key now that it is formed. Meanwhile Azazel converses with Rita and Bacchus, revealing that Beezlebub is the one behind Amira`s actions as well Martinet; Rita theorizes Martient is not a demon like Beezlebub. While protecting the seal the angels are attacked by the corrupted Jeanne who slays Raphael and Uriel before going after Michael. Kaisar is saved by Bacchus in his flying carriage only to be attacked by Jeanne. While Bacchus fights Jeanne, Rita gives Kaisar a cure she made for the demon transformation and he taunts Azazel into helping him. Rita attempts to administer the last of the antidotes to Jeanne but fails only for Michael to successfully give it to Jeanne through a kiss after she impales him. Jeanne is freed, turning back into a saint while Michael`s physical form disappears and he reassures her the world needs her. As Beezlebub prepares to destroy the angels protecting Bahamut`s barrier Azazel attacks him and engages in battle for revenge. Kaisar duels with the demonic Favaro and upon seeing how he`s become a true demon shoots him in the chest. Amira emerges from the Transcendent Key`s orb, now with angel`s wings. Lavalley appears before Kaisar, only for Rita to warn to get way from the knight. With the barrier fallen Bahamut beings to absorb Amira while everyone looks on helplessly; as Kaisar watches in disbelief Lavalley shoves him over the edge of the flying fortress before reveling in Bahamut`s awakening.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164202" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Helheim, Land of Lies</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Helheim, Land of Lies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Helheim, Land of Lies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Helheim, Land of Lies</title>
<summary>Rita escapes from the castle after being confronted by a suspicious cloaked man who threatens to dispose of her. Meanwhile the King proceeds with Jeanne D`Arc`s death sentence for deceit and conspiracy carried out before a crowd of protestors who proclaim her innocence. As Jeanne burns she faces fiery visions of the gods forsaking her, including her patron angel, causing her to accept the words of the cloaked demon. Jeanne is converted from a saint into a witch by the demon and she escapes the capital by wielding a fierce and dark power as she is now a demon. Meanwhile Favaro thinks over the dragon`s words of killing Amira as the trio continues their journey to find Amira`s mother. They are intercepted by the cloaked man who is the same demon who tricked the king as well as Jeanne; Amira reveals him to be her mentor Martinet who in turn tells them they are in Helheim. Rita seeks out Bacchus and inquires about Martinet but the two run into a severely injured Azazel. The demon lord Beelzebub appears before the trio, capturing Kaisar and Favaro, telling Amira to fulfill her purpose before showing her mother. Martinet reveals in actually Beezlebub recreated Amira from Nicole as an imitation vessel and he is her "true" birth parent as all Amira`s memories are fabricated since as she is a mere tool to release Bahamut. Amira`s compromised emotional state causes the key`s seal to unlock, falling into the demon`s hands as the completed Transcendent Key. Azazel agrees to help Rita if she takes him to Abos while Favaro pretends to join the demons but Martient sees through the plan and forcibly makes Favaro a demon.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164203" update="2016-04-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Decision in the Wailing Woods</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decision in the Wailing Woods</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Decision in the Wailing Woods</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Decision in the Wailing Woods</title>
<summary>Amira and Favaro slip out of the city while Rita causes a diversion and Lavalley tasks Kaisar to track them down in order to aid them in his stead. Back in the Capital Jeanne is framed by an unknown demon for attempted murder on the king as well as slaughtering of guards and the officer Gaurin. The Angels continue to fight to maintain the seal on Bahamut as it grows increasingly unstable. Kaisar catches up to Amira and Favaro in a forest where they are transported to an alternate space and free an imprisoned dragon when they remove a poisonous barb of Bahamut from his foot. The dragon reveals that when Amira`s key meets the seal Bahamut will released, as it has been countless times before. Meanwhile the god clan and demon clan accuse the other of plotting against them and amass their forces to crush the other. Amira cries when she learns the world will end because of her, meaning her mother`s death though Favaro resolves to change fate after enduring a vision of Bahamut and recalling his father`s words. The King orders the death of Jeanne by burning at the stake and commands Lavalley to capture and kill any of her supporters while beneath the castle Rita investigates the cause of madness and trickery. The trio arrive in Prudisia while Favaro is troubled by what the dragon told him: Should Amira ever be close to Bahamut, she`ll fuse with it permanently due to her god and demon blood as only a human vessel can maintain the seal; only the way to prevent the fusing is to kill Amira.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164233" recap="true" update="2016-06-11">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Roundup</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roundup</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Roundup</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roundup</title>
<summary>A recap of all previous episodes. It shows Amira stealing the God Key after being promised what she most desired if she took it, meeting Favaro and how Kaisar met Rita, being abducted by demons while at sea, how they came together as a team in the demons` fortress, escaping and then ending up in the human capital.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="183370" update="2017-04-06">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2016-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Short Story #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184904" update="2017-02-21">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2017-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Short Story #2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Short Story #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189208" update="2017-07-19">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 Storyboard</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
