<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10384" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2014-08-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mushishi Zoku Shou</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Mushishi: Zoku-Shô</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Мушиши 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Mushishi: Zoku-Sho</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Мушіші Наступні глави</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Mushishi S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mushi2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mushishi2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">蟲師 続章</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mushi-Shi: Next Passage</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">虫师 续章</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10571" type="Sequel">Mushishi Zoku Shou (2014)</anime>
<anime id="10274" type="Prequel">Mushishi Tokubetsu Hen: Hihamu Kage</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="5"/>
<url>http://www.mushishi-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3517" type="Original Work">Urushibara Yuki</name>
<name id="2341" type="Music">Masuda Toshio</name>
<name id="2179" type="Series Composition">Nagahama Hiroshi</name>
<name id="999" type="Animation Work">Artland</name>
<name id="2208" type="Character Design">Umakoshi Yoshihiko</name>
<name id="2183" type="Chief Direction">Soutome Kouichirou</name>
<name id="2179" type="Direction">Nagahama Hiroshi</name>
<name id="2208" type="Chief Animation Direction">Umakoshi Yoshihiko</name>
</creators>
<description>Perceived as strange and alien, inferior and grotesque. These are beings that appear entirely unlike flora and fauna familiar to us. Since time immemorial, man has feared the misshapen ones. Over time, they came to be know as http://anidb.net/t502 [Mushi].
The appearance of Mushi can cause grave harm to humans, and only a select few humans know of their existence and can see them. http://anidb.net/ch1800 [Ginko], a http://anidb.net/t390 [Mushi-shi], travels the land to investigate the Mushi. But his special ability comes at a price: he cannot stay at any place for too long, or the Mushi will congregate there, endangering those close to him. So, the gentle and wise man must keep on traveling, trying to resolve Mushi-related supernatural occurrences.
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2300">9.41</permanent>
<temporary count="2320">8.60</temporary>
<review count="1">7.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>226101.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17219</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15895</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>24687</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>21939</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mushishi-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mushishi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>蟲師#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3327</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348112</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17440</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>17003</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01MT7ET90</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1032" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-10">
<name>fishing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3363" parentid="2876" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-04">
<name>Buddhism</name>
<description>Buddhism is a nontheistic religion or dharma, "right way of living", that encompasses a variety of traditions, beliefs and practices largely based on teachings attributed to Siddhartha Gautama, commonly known as the Buddha ("the awakened one").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169453.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3394" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>environmentalism</name>
<description>Environmental protection is a practice of protecting the natural environment on individual, organizational or governmental levels, for the benefit of both the natural environment and humans. Due to the pressures of population and technology, the biophysical environment is being degraded, sometimes permanently. This has been recognized, and governments have begun placing restraints on activities that cause environmental degradation. Since the 1960s, activity of environmental movements has created awareness of the various environmental issues.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3504" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>sake</name>
<description>Sake, generally referred to as a Japanese rice wine, is an alcoholic beverage made by fermenting rice.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215208.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3869" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>mono no aware</name>
<description>Literally "the pathos of things", also translated as "an empathy toward things," or "a sensitivity of ephemera"; a Japanese term used to describe the awareness of the transience of things and a gentle sadness (or wistfulness) at their passing.
Also frequently been translated as "the `ahh-ness` of things".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4753" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>disturbing</name>
<description>Watching the show may cause the viewer to have unpleasant feelings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4809" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>superstition</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5891" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-04">
<name>Taoism</name>
<description>Taoism refers to a philosophical or religious tradition in which the basic concept is to establish harmony with the Tao (道), which is the mechanism of everything that exists. The word "Tao" (or "Dao", depending on the romanization scheme) is usually translated as "way", "path" or "principle", although the word also means "nature" as in the nature of all things as well as the natural world. Taoism had not only a profound influence on the culture of China, but also on neighbouring countries. While the philosophical Taoism is not institutionalized, the religious Taoism is institutionalized and present in multiple countries. Taoist philosophy is deeply rooted in contemporary China, and is an unavoidable part of modern Chinese life. Taoist propriety and ethics emphasize the Three Jewels of the Tao: compassion, moderation, and humility.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5973" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-05">
<name>agriculture</name>
<description>Agriculture is the cultivation of animals, plants, fungi, and other life forms for food, fiber, biofuel, medicinal and other products used to sustain and enhance human life.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169456.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1800" type="main character in" update="2018-11-13">
<rating votes="746">9.39</rating>
<name>Ginko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginko is a rare person who attracts http://anidb.net/t502 [mushi]. This inspires his peripatetic lifestyle. Staying in one place too long will gather a potentially dangerous amount of mushi. He also smokes constantly in order to keep mushi away. In terms of personality, Ginko is rather laid back, but can be very serious when it comes to protecting people from mushi. He also often stresses that the mushi are not evil, but merely trying to survive like everyone else.
Ginko`s unusual white hair and green eye colour is the result of an incident involving a mushi that occurred when he was a http://anidb.net/ch5421 [child].</description>
<picture>226728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="422" picture="17278.jpg">Nakano Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5287" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-26">
<rating votes="21">5.37</rating>
<name>Adashino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5421" type="appears in" update="2018-11-10">
<rating votes="5">9.13</rating>
<name>Yoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5524" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-11-12">
<rating votes="55">9.22</rating>
<name>Tanyuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3092" picture="23997.jpg">Kobayashi Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5526" type="appears in" update="2018-11-12">
<rating votes="2">7.17</rating>
<name>Tama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34" picture="240893.jpg">Kyouda Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66263" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Kuramoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The owner of the sake brewery.</description>
<picture>152862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41307" picture="163828.jpg">Kouno Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66264" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Rokusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy working in a sake brewery.</description>
<picture>152861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37466" picture="225911.jpg">Uemura Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66265" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Rokusuke (Kodomo)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young Rokusuke.</description>
<picture>152864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41309" picture="163830.jpg">Noda Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66266" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Rokusuke no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rokusuke`s father.
He once found a mushishi gathering/trading place in the woods and drank some of their golden sake, forever trying to reproduce its fine notes as a sake brewer.</description>
<picture>152865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40640" picture="159487.jpg">Horikoshi Tomisaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66267" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Mushishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Various mushishi from the forest gathering.</description>
<picture>152866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66268" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Mushishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Various mushishi from the forest gathering.</description>
<picture>152866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="156" picture="227713.jpg">Ochiai Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66269" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Mushishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Various mushishi from the forest gathering.</description>
<picture>152866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18755" picture="49459.jpg">Akazawa Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66270" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Mushishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Various mushishi from the forest gathering.</description>
<picture>152866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66271" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Mushishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Various mushishi from the forest gathering.</description>
<picture>152866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34377" picture="127862.jpg">Kanno Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66272" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Isaza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A (kind of) grown up Isaza!</description>
<picture>152867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66273" type="appears in" update="2014-04-06">
<name>Okami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>"Saa..", the landlady.</description>
<picture>152868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40524" picture="158683.jpg">Miyazawa Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66529" type="appears in" update="2014-04-12">
<name>Shima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40081" picture="156195.jpg">Fujimoto Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66530" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-11">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40084" picture="156196.jpg">Tsuda Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66531" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-12">
<name>Sakichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66532" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-12">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Amimoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66845" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Tae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl from the snowy villlage. She is the one pointing Ginko in Toki`s direction.</description>
<picture>154335.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="66846" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Toki no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toki`s mother.</description>
<picture>154336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2087" picture="151693.jpg">Muta Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66847" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Sachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toki`s late younger sister.</description>
<picture>154337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40118" picture="156332.jpg">Komagata Rumina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66848" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Tae no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tae`s mother, and the local village`s innkeeper.</description>
<picture>154338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37600" picture="138358.jpg">Shirakami Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66849" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Toki no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toki`s father.</description>
<picture>154339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66850" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Toki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>After his younger sister died in the lake, Toki seemed to have snow follow him around...</description>
<picture>154340.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35857" picture="131961.jpg">Ueda Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68888" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-28">
<name>Tatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68889" type="appears in" update="2014-07-28">
<name>Usuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40522" picture="158684.jpg">Kijima Yasunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68945" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Masumi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40535" picture="158860.jpg">Miyazako Natsuho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68946" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Masumi no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32879" picture="223636.jpg">Fukumori Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68947" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Masumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33578" picture="225440.jpg">Shiraishi Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68959" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Saho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="429" picture="17306.jpg">Mutou Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68960" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Saho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158776.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68961" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Saho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40538" picture="236250.jpg">Kurimoto Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68962" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Mansaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40536" picture="158859.jpg">Koiso Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68963" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Masaki no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17523" picture="223264.jpg">Yamamoto Kanehira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68964" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68965" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Mansaku no Musuko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6126" picture="37816.jpg">Hamazoe Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68966" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="443" picture="145927.jpg">Ishikawa Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68970" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Teru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68971" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Ryou no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158787.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40546" picture="158844.jpg">Hatayama Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68972" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Yasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40543" picture="158847.jpg">Ozeki Toshikazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68973" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158789.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68974" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Teru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158790.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68975" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Yasu no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9360" picture="171916.jpg">Chikiri Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68976" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Yasu no Chichioya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68977" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Teru no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40544" picture="158846.jpg">Chiba Miharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68978" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Teru no Oji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18755" picture="49459.jpg">Akazawa Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68979" type="appears in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Teru no Oba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4206" picture="60199.jpg">Iseki Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69050" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="2">1.42</rating>
<name>Ibuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40551" picture="158937.jpg">Saitou Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69169" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-03">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Houichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40598" picture="159173.jpg">Matsushita Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69170" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Houichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159111.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69171" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<name>Houichi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32991" picture="89778.jpg">Takemoto Kazumasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69172" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<name>Houichi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159112.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40603" picture="159180.jpg">Saga Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69173" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<name>Houichi no Yome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40601" picture="159178.jpg">Kikkawa Kayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69174" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<name>Chiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40600" picture="159176.jpg">Tsuji Yoshie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69175" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<name>Houichi no Chounan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40599" picture="159175.jpg">Ueda Gen</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69176" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<name>Houichi no Jinan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159118.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69177" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<name>Houichi no Choujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159119.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69178" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<name>Houichi no Jijo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40602" picture="159179.jpg">Oota Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69617" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-23">
<rating votes="2">5.64</rating>
<name>Kumado</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17631" picture="172640.jpg">Mikami Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69618" type="appears in" update="2014-08-23">
<name>Minai no Jii-sama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3300" picture="24699.jpg">Kitagawa Yonehiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69619" type="appears in" update="2014-08-23">
<rating votes="1">2.14</rating>
<name>Kumado</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40737" picture="160068.jpg">Nishida Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69620" type="appears in" update="2014-08-23">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Tanyuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40736" picture="160067.jpg">Gamou Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="157024" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">野末の宴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Banquet at the Forest`s Edge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le banquet au bout des champs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nozue no Utage</title>
<summary>Kouki--a stream of light flowing deep underground, the font of all life. When a man ignorant of its effects on the living meddles with it, the mushi-shi must act before there are unintended consequences.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652157</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159040" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜を撫でる手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hand That Caresses the Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoru o Naderu Te</title>
<summary>A hunter roams the mountains at night without the tools of his trade. The being that toys with life, and then extinguishes it is a fragile "thing" caught between the realm of man and mushi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652607</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159041" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪の下</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beneath the Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki no Shita</title>
<summary>Snow constantly falls around him. Impervious to the freezing cold, the man is gripped by the searing memory of a winter he had spent together with his little sister.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652605</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159042" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="20">9.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">囀る貝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Warbling Seashell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saezuru Kai</title>
<summary>Birdsong is suddenly heard when a sea shell is held up to a girl`s ear. In a fishing village still reeling from a tragedy years before, a strange mushi indicates an ill omen. What misfortune will be brought to bear on the people?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652603</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159536" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風巻立つ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wind Raiser</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shimakitatsu</title>
<summary>A ship sails with wind in its sails across the calm seas. A boy able to command the mushi and call the wind must find his own path in order to see the horizon within himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652615</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159537" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">日照る雨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cloudless Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiteru Ame</title>
<summary>The woman continues her travels as she foretells the coming of rain. With every raindrop that falls from the clear blue skies, she is reminded of her curious fate, one that cannot be washed clean by any amount of tears.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652613</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159538" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花惑い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Floral Delusion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanamadoi</title>
<summary>The countless blooms adorning the branches are trees are an enthralling tableau showcasing the beauty of spring. Those who have a neverending desire for such beauty will eventually broach a taboo. For whom do the ephemeral flowers bloom?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652611</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159539" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鏡が淵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mirror Lake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagami ga Fuchi</title>
<summary>Who, or what, is reflected on the surface? When the boundary between the real and unreal collapses, only the self who lives in this world can determine how to continue one`s existence.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652609</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159544" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2014-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">棘のみち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Path of Thorns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Odoro no Michi</title>
<summary>Should darkness rise from the depths of the cavern, the boundary between and man and mushi will vanish. Life itself will become bereft of death, and the natural order will crumble. The world as we know it will be no more. Mishappen beings and taboos unique to man lie in wait along the path of thorns...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>659833</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159545" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬の底</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Depths of Winter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyu no Soko</title>
<summary>A mountain refuses to welcome spring. Snow continues to fall, and animals continue to slumber. It is the will of the mountain lord... as if he, himself, is waiting for death.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652619</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="159546" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">潮わく谷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Valley of the Welling Tides</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ushiowaku Tani</title>
<summary>Amidst the wintry snow, a valley is full of green and ripe for harvest. A man toils on without need for slumber, as if to make amends. He works for his family`s livelihood, and for his blood legacy...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>652617</identifier>
<identifier>mushi-shi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160019" update="2014-08-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">蟲語[むしがたり]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mushistory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mushigatari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160697" update="2014-08-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">蟲語[むしがたり] 第二夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mushistory 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mushigatari Dai Ni Yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163916" update="2014-11-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
