<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10392" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>5</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-05-16</startdate>
<enddate>2015-07-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Magi: Sindbad no Bouken</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Magi: Adventure of Sinbad</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マギ シンドバッドの冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">ماجي : مغامرات سندباد</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Маги: Приключенията на Синбад</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11672" type="Full Story">Magi: Sindbad no Bouken (2016)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.project-magi.com/sinbad/</url>
<creators>
<name id="8733" type="Character Design">Sako Souichirou</name>
<name id="14270" type="Original Work">Ootaka Shinobu</name>
<name id="3691" type="Direction">Miyao Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="31573" type="Music">Ookubo Tomohiro</name>
<name id="27981" type="Series Composition">Kishimoto Taku</name>
<name id="42709" type="Animation Work">Lay-duce</name>
<name id="43962" type="Original Work">Ootera Yoshifumi</name>
</creators>
<description>Not so long ago, mysterious structures called dungeons began appearing all over the world. No one knows what they are or how they came to be, but adventurers and armies around the world instantly took interest in them. Thousands set out to explore the dungeons, but so far, not a single person has returned.
In a Parthevia port, a young boy is about to make a name for himself. http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] is good-natured, strong, and craving adventure. A kind deed leads to his meeting with http://anidb.net/ch62750 [Yunan], an enigmatic traveler who is far more powerful than his frivolous personality lets on. Yunan instructs Sinbad to attain the power of the king and change the world — by conquering a dungeon. The eager boy readily accepts, setting out on the grand adventure he so craved.
Taking place 15 years before the events of the http://anidb.net/a9268 [original series], Sinbad no Bouken chronicles Sinbad`s youth as a dungeon conqueror. Along the way, the budding adventurer and merchant will have to face many obstacles, but anything is possible with the power of a king.
Source: MAL
Note: Bundled with special editions of 3rd-7th compiled volumes of the Magi spin-off manga Magi: Sinbad no Bouken.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="540">6.83</permanent>
<temporary count="546">7.31</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>156439.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16497</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22097</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.project-magi.com/sinbad/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Magi:_The_Labyrinth_of_Magic#Adventure_of_Sinbad</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マギ_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349190</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17253</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4052" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-23">
<name>treasure hunting</name>
<description>A significant part of the anime centres on the protagonists` search for some obscure artefact or other treasure, an epic adventure and wild goose chase for something unusual and quite valuable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5709" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>Anisun</name>
<description>Part of a series of anime OVAs and OADs released by http://anidb.net/cr1082 [Shogakukan] as part of their Anisun Sunday Anime Project.</description>
<picurl>62255.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6743" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-21">
<name>One Thousand and One Nights</name>
<description>One Thousand and One Nights is a collection of Middle Eastern and South Asian stories and folk tales compiled in Arabic during the Islamic Golden Age. The work was collected over many centuries by various authors, translators, and scholars across West, Central, and South Asia and North Africa. The tales themselves trace their roots back to ancient and medieval Arabic, Persian, Mesopotamian, Indian, Jewish and Egyptian folklore and literature. Some of the stories very widely associated with The Nights, in particular Aladdin`s Wonderful Lamp, Ali Baba and the Forty Thieves, and The Seven Voyages of Sinbad the Sailor were not part of The Nights in its original Arabic versions, but were added to the collection by Antoine Galland and other European translators.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191584.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="62750" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="16">5.83</rating>
<name>Yunan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yunan is one of the four Magi in the current era, known as the Wandering Magi, and is the Guardian of the Great Rift. He was the one that advised http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] to clear the 1st dungeon, http://anidb.net/ch80566 [Baal], stating it would give him the power he sought.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63160" type="main character in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="22">8.12</rating>
<name>Sinbad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sinbad was born and raised in Tison Village of the Parthevia Empire. When Sinbad was 14, he captured his first and the world`s first Dungeon, http://anidb.net/ch80566 [Baal], which was summoned by http://anidb.net/ch62750 [Yunan]. During his journeys, he recruited all of his future http://anidb.net/ch63616 [Kingdom]`s Generals.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>148637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63161" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="8">8.39</rating>
<name>Esra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Esra was the mother of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] and wife of http://anidb.net/ch63164 [Badr].
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>183773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63162" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="11">3.50</rating>
<name>Seredine Dikumenowlz Du Parthevia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63163" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="5">4.89</rating>
<name>Dragul Nol Henrius Gobias Medias Partenvonmias Dumid Os Koltanon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dragul is a former general of the Parthevia Empire. He is part of Parthevia`s Dragul Family, and son of the Parthevian General Draguliel Pertegomidus.
When 1st Dungeon, http://anidb.net/ch80566 [Baal], appeared in Parthevia, the Emperor wanted to obtain its power, since Parthevia was in war against Reim Empire. All the soldiers who were sent to the Dungeon died, and the Emperor decided to send Dragul as well. He recruited more people among the population, with Sinbad among them. Only Dragul and Sinbad managed to reach the Baal`s throne room, where they had a duel in order to decide who will take Baal`s power for himself. In the end, Sinbad won.
He was the first of the Eight Generals to meet http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] and the first member of Sinbad`s Household.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>156526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63164" type="appears in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="4">6.10</rating>
<name>Badr</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Badr was the father of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] and a former soldier of the Parthevia Empire.
Badr was a cheerful, fun-loving guy. He cared a lot about his family, just like how Sinbad cares for the people of his country like they were family. He had a serious side too, since when everybody in Parthevia was delirious with the war he asked himself if it was alright to continue like this. He and his son`s personalities are very similar.
Source: Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>183772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66049" type="appears in" update="2014-03-25">
<rating votes="2">2.54</rating>
<name>Rametoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70828" type="appears in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="5">6.03</rating>
<name>Pipirika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pipirika is a member of the Imuchakk Tribe. She is the daughter of one of the Patriarchs and the sister of http://anidb.net/ch84285 [Hinahoho]. She accompanied her brother when he challenged the Rampaging Unicorn in order to complete his coming of age ceremony.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>164249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71398" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="5">3.88</rating>
<name>Ja`far</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ja`far was born into Parthevia`s undercover unit, the assassins http://anidb.net/ch84317 [Sham Lash], and at one point became its leader. At the age of six, he was forced into killing both of his parents.
Source: Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>164245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71399" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="6">1.91</rating>
<name>Falan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71400" type="appears in" update="2016-09-22">
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<name>Mahad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mahad, along with http://anidb.net/ch84320 [Vittel] and http://anidb.net/ch71398 [Ja`far], was formerly an assassin of http://anidb.net/ch84317 [Sham Lash]. After http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] conquered the 6th Dungeon, http://anidb.net/ch84270 [Valefor], he became a merchant of Sindria Company and joined Sinbad in his travels. He`s a quiet person and good at observing people as well as taking care of his employees.
Mahad grew up with Vittel and they stuck together as they both shared the common fate as war orphans. They both started to steal for survival and eventually both were picked up by Sham Lash.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>164247.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="71401" type="appears in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="2">3.86</rating>
<name>Hinahoho no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164248.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="80566" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-26">
<rating votes="4">5.66</rating>
<name>Baal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baal is the lightning Djinn, also known as the Djinn of Wrath and Heroes, who ruled over the 1st Dungeon.
He`s is one of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad]`s seven Djinn.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84270" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-26">
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<name>Valefor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Valefor is the water Djinn, also known as the Djinn of Falsehood and Prestige, who ruled over the 6th Dungeon.
He`s is one of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad]`s seven Djinn.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84271" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-26">
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<name>Valefor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Valefor is the water Djinn, also known as the Djinn of Falsehood and Prestige, who ruled over the 6th Dungeon.
He`s is one of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad]`s seven Djinn.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84285" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="4">6.33</rating>
<name>Hinahoho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinahoho comes from Imuchakk, and is the son of one of its Patriarchs. He used to be very timid, lacked courage and often a crybaby, until he met http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad]. After they cleared the dungeon http://anidb.net/ch84270 [Valefor], he joined Sinbad in his travels.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84317" type="appears in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="2">1.56</rating>
<name>Sham Lash</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Sham Lash is an assassins`s guild and Parthevia`s undercover unit.</description>
<picture>190546.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84318" type="appears in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="2">6.51</rating>
<name>Rurumu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rurumu is the wife of http://anidb.net/ch84285 [Hinahoho] and the daughter of the Chief of the Imuchakk Tribe, Rametoto. Among the Imuchakk Tribe girls, she is noted to be the most beautiful.
Before Hinahoho went to conquer the dungeon, she seemed to like him and happily accepted his hand in marriage. Although Hinahoho loves his wife dearly, there are times when she frightens him.
Rurumu made it her job to teach http://anidb.net/ch71398 [Ja`far] and http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] how to read, write, and use mathematics as they sailed to Reim. Although she is a little rough with Ja`far, she stated she treated him as if he were her own son.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84320" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="2">6.65</rating>
<name>Vittel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vittel was a part of the Assassin`s Guild http://anidb.net/ch84317 [Sham Lash] from the Parthevia Empire before his defection to join http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] as one of the founders of Sindria Trading Company and eventually the nation of Sindria.
Source: Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>190549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84324" type="appears in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<name>Sinbad (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190556.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="157274" update="2014-05-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷宮[ダンジョン]バアル攻略篇・前篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dungeon Baal Kouryaku Hen Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160100" update="2014-06-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷宮[ダンジョン]バアル攻略篇・後篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dungeon Baal Kouryaku Hen Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164334" update="2014-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷宮[ダンジョン]ブァレフォール攻略篇・前篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dungeon Valefor Kouryaku Hen Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165429" update="2015-01-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷宮[ダンジョン]ブァレフォール攻略篇・中篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dungeon Valefor Kouryaku Hen Chuuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168614" update="2015-05-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷宮[ダンジョン]ブァレフォール攻略篇・後篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dungeon Valefor Kouryaku Hen Kouhen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
