<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="104" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-02-02</startdate>
<enddate>2002-02-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hoshi no Koe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="synonym">Tiếng gọi từ vì sao xa</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">星の声</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Stimmen eines fernen Sterns</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Voces de una Estrella Lejana</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">أصوات نجم بعيد</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="synonym">Stemmen van een Afgelegen Ster</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="synonym">קולו של כוכב</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Tolimosios Žvaigždės Balsai</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Гласовете на далечните звезди</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Голос зірок</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">voices</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hoshi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hnc</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ほしのこえ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Voices of a Distant Star</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">The voices of a distant star</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">The Voices of a Distant Star</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">La Voce delle Stelle</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Голос далёкой звезды</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">별의 목소리</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Głosy z odległej gwiazdy</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Hlasy z hvězd</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">เสียงเพรียกจากดวงดาว</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Kauge tähe hääl</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4568" approval="143" total="150">Byousoku 5 Centimeter</anime>
<anime id="469" approval="91" total="95">Kumo no Mukou, Yakusoku no Basho</anime>
<anime id="4158" approval="47" total="60">Pale Cocoon</anime>
<anime id="4556" approval="1" total="10">Soukou no Strain</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="493">Sad, but really good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="105473">25 minutes of your life very well spent</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="460944">Though it was short and overall slow paced (for its short length) it was emotionally and visually stunning, to say at least. I would like to encourage anyone who hasn`t watched this classic yet to pick it up next chance you get.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="479550">Makoto Shinkai made this at home. On a mac.
The only help he received was with voice acting (his wife) and music (his friend). [later two professional voice actors were brought in]
And yet the animation quality is pretty freaking brilliant [perhaps only `good` now but this was made over ten years ago (early 2002)].
It`s only 20 minutes long. The basic idea of it is so simple yet so perfectly executed.
It`s only 20 minutes but, yes, I choked up at the end.
Seriously, though. It`s only 20 minutes long so just go watch it! \o/

Apparently the manga adaptation goes  alittle farther, brings some more closure. But I`m more than fine with this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="320398">Best Shinkai piece ever!How epic can a love story get?Earth,Galaxy,Universe , here is the answer you`ve been looking for.It really makes all space/mecha/romance  things you`ve watched so far seem dull.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="552076">This is an amazing piece of work. Beautiful music and story, I cry like baby now when I hear the music. A note on the visuals, so many say that the sub-par art hurts this, but what they fail to realize is Shinkai did this all on his own. He drew and animated it all himself ( hand painted backgrounds in some scenes) his wife and him provided the voices for the characters and a friend in the industry helped with the music. I think we can cut him a break on this. The whole idea that he did absolutely all of this stunning piece himself is amazing and an inspiration. Absolute must-see</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www2.odn.ne.jp/~ccs50140/stars/</url>
<creators>
<name id="445" type="Original Plan">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="445" type="Direction">Shinkai Makoto</name>
<name id="3546" type="Music">Tenmon</name>
<name id="445" type="Work">Shinkai Makoto</name>
</creators>
<description>In 2046 after the discovery of the ruins of an alien civilization on Mars, man has been able to make leaps in technology and is planning to send an expedition into space in the next year. http://anidb.net/ch1284 [Nagamine Mikako] and http://anidb.net/ch1285 [Terao Noboru] are junior high school students. However, while Noboru will be entering senior high next winter, Mikako is selected to join the space expedition.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="6872">7.13</permanent>
<temporary count="6902">7.80</temporary>
<review count="13">7.45</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221653.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>256</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>893</identifier>
<identifier>ikcgjk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://shinkaimakoto.jp/distantstar</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Voices_of_a_Distant_Star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ほしのこえ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1923</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239072</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5019</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>별의_목소리</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>星之聲</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>voices-of-a-distant-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8110</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3974" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>star-crossed lovers</name>
<description>Two lovers — usually teenagers — destined to be kept apart no matter how hard they struggle to be together. It may be fate or just feuding families, or even something as mundane as a few hundred miles, but something will always be in their way. Often, the two can only be together in death. The phrase is astrological in origin, stemming from the belief that the positions of the stars ruled over people`s fates. To describe a relationship as "star-crossed" is to say that it is "thwarted by a malign star", or that the stars are working against the relationship. Shakespeare`s Romeo and Juliet is the most famous example of this archetype but it dates back at least as far as the ancient Greeks.
"From forth the fatal loins of these two foes, / a pair of star-cross`d lovers, take their life."
- Romeo and Juliet, prologue</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5213" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-04">
<name>the effects of time and distance on human relationships</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5409" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-22">
<name>longing</name>
<description>One or more characters yearn for some person or some place.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5561" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-08-16">
<name>lonely atmosphere</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5787" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>time dilation</name>
<description>Time dilation is a scientific phenomena related to relativity, basically stating that for an observer onboard a spaceship travelling at a certain speed, time passes more slowly than it would for an observer on Earth. 
When near-lightspeed travel becomes involved, the effects become quite drastic: a person might go on a space journey that seems to him to last one year and, on returning, find that 10 years have passed on Earth. This is sometimes extrapolated by sci-fi authors to apply to faster-than-light travel as well, though this would not necessarily be the case. 
Note that this effect occurs at considerably lower velocities as well, as an atomic clock on Earth and one in orbit around Earth will be ever so slightly desynced.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1284" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-16">
<rating votes="10">6.19</rating>
<name>Nagamine Mikako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikako Nagamine is in the third year of a junior high school when she is drafted to the UN Space Army in a war against a group of aliens called the Tarsians. As a Special Agent, Mikako pilots a giant mecha as part of a fighting squadron attached to the spacecraft carrier Lysithea.
When the Lysithea leaves Earth to search for the Tarsians with Mikako on board, Mikako`s boyfriend Noboru Terao remains behind. The couple continues to communicate across interplanetary, and eventually interstellar space via the e-mail facilities on their mobile phones.</description>
<picture>15582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="429" picture="17306.jpg">Mutou Sumi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="446">Shinohara Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1285" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-16">
<rating votes="6">5.77</rating>
<name>Terao Noboru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Terao Noboru is a classmate of Nagamine Mikako in the third year of her junior high school and part of the kendo team.
When the Lysithea leaves Earth to search for the Tarsians with Mikako on board, he remains behind and enters senior high school. The couple continues to communicate across interplanetary, and eventually interstellar space via the e-mail facilities on their mobile phones.
Years later after receiving Mikako`s last mail he eventually decides to go after her into space.</description>
<picture>15583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="445" picture="70836.jpg">Shinkai Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="555" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
<summary>It is 2046 when a mysterious alien force begins their annihilation of the human race. Leaving behind the one person she loves, Mikako joins the interstellar battle as a pilot. As Mikako flies further into space, her only connection with Noboru are text messages sent from her mobile phone. And so - while Mikako risks her life to save mankind - Noboru waits. The two lovers, worlds apart, desperately strive to remain connected as the gap between them widens at a frightening pace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>521660</identifier>
<identifier>voices-of-a-distant-star</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="11047" update="2003-09-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<rating votes="3">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40761" update="2014-12-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="40762" update="2014-12-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44988" update="2009-12-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailers</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85611" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Original Production Animatic</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121099" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
