<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10404" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-07-04</startdate>
<enddate>2014-09-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Futsuu no Joshikousei ga [Locodol] Yattemita.</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Обычные девочки пытаются стать "локодолами"</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">普通の女子校生が[ろこどる]やってみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Locodol</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Locodol</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">普通女高中生要做当地偶像</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">دختران طبیعی دبیرستان</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11286" type="Sequel">Futsuu no Joshikousei ga [Locodol] Yattemita. (2015)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12746" approval="3" total="4">Action Heroine Cheer Fruits</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="296921">Fun, fluffy slice-of-life kind of entertainment.
Very relaxed and light-hearted.
As long as you don`t bring any unrealistic expectations to it, you will see it`s quite a good example of the modern trend of strongly localized, tourism-friendly, happy feel-good stories.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="684617">This is what a true anime enthusiast with good taste should appreciate; the story actually makes sense and characters are actual human beings with humane emotions and beautiful souls instead of moeblob stock-characters that are used to satisfy the perversity of tasteless plebians. The patrician spirit emanates from this very fine work reminds me strongly of Ore Twintail ni Narimasu, which is a masterpiece in this degenerate epoch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/locodol/</url>
<creators>
<name id="21486" type="Series Composition">Ayana Yuniko</name>
<name id="1006" type="Animation Work">Feel</name>
<name id="581" type="Direction">Nawa Munenori</name>
<name id="4073" type="Music">Hasegawa Tomoki</name>
<name id="9743" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shimizu Yumi</name>
<name id="9743" type="Character Design">Shimizu Yumi</name>
<name id="40365" type="Original Work">Kosugi Koutarou</name>
</creators>
<description>High school girl http://anidb.net/ch63250 [Nanako] became her town`s local idol after being requested to do so by her uncle. Together with her upperclassman http://anidb.net/ch63251 [Yukari], a girl who seems perfect but is actually quite airheaded, as local idols, they get interviewed (by the town`s shopping centre), go on television (low-budget cable), and do concerts (on the roof of the department store). The girls` salaries come from the town`s taxes.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="614">4.93</permanent>
<temporary count="616">6.51</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>157636.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15915</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>25719</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>22189</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/locodol/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Futsū_no_Joshikōsei_ga_Locodol_Yattemita</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>普通の女子校生が【ろこどる】やってみた。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3438</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349324</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17314</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4907" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>small town</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="63250" type="main character in" update="2014-03-25">
<rating votes="18">5.92</rating>
<name>Usami Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37283" picture="238137.jpg">Itou Miku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63251" type="main character in" update="2014-03-25">
<rating votes="20">6.20</rating>
<name>Kohinata Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2903" picture="23287.jpg">Misawa Sachika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65997" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-25">
<rating votes="18">6.22</rating>
<name>Mikoze Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20576" picture="223363.jpg">Yoshioka Maya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65998" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-25">
<rating votes="12">5.85</rating>
<name>Nazukari Mirai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65999" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-25">
<rating votes="11">4.82</rating>
<name>Nishifukai Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67117" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Oota Mitsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67118" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<rating votes="2">2.34</rating>
<name>Usami Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67119" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<name>Usami Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4422" picture="228398.jpg">Iida Toshinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67120" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-18">
<rating votes="4">6.63</rating>
<name>Kashiwaba Satsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39921" picture="225566.jpg">Izawa Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67121" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-18">
<rating votes="3">4.99</rating>
<name>Mizumoto Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21823" picture="131326.jpg">Tsuda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67122" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-22">
<rating votes="6">4.96</rating>
<name>Mihara Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67123" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-18">
<rating votes="3">4.99</rating>
<name>Noda Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69340" type="appears in" update="2014-08-09">
<name>Anan Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69341" type="appears in" update="2014-08-09">
<name>Tsurugi Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69342" type="appears in" update="2014-08-09">
<name>Mima Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22170" picture="226837.jpg">Nitta Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69343" type="appears in" update="2014-08-09">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Isemi Rinon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4712" picture="27521.jpg">Nakamura Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69344" type="appears in" update="2014-08-09">
<name>Teragasaki Azuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34603" picture="175431.jpg">Natsukawa Shiina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69345" type="appears in" update="2014-08-09">
<name>Kashiwabara Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38858" picture="225369.jpg">Yoshimura Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69346" type="appears in" update="2014-08-09">
<name>Kurohime Manami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39748" picture="152660.jpg">Fukagawa Seria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70189" type="appears in" update="2014-09-22">
<name>Mihara Torata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="544" picture="238510.jpg">Ogawa Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="160980" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マネージャーとかついてみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Adding a Manager and Stuff.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé d`avoir un manager</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manager to ka Tsuite Mita.</title>
<summary>Nanako visits a cable TV station to tape a program. In her changing room, she discovers a suspicious person going through their outfits...!
Recently there have been multiple reports of people stealing clothes from popular idols, but have those people finally come after them?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656593</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160981" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">着てみた. 脱いでみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Putting It On. We Tried Taking It Off.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé de le porter puis de l`enlever</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kite Mita. Nuide Mita.</title>
<summary>Their next job is the "City Revival New Project Presentation".
Having received no details, Nanako and Yukari enter their dressing room while wondering if they`ll get a new member, where they find Nagarekawa`s local mascot Uogokoro-kun.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656591</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160982" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遊びに行ってみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Going and Playing.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé de s`amuser</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asobi ni Itte Mita.</title>
<summary>Nanako and Yukari begin working as Nagarekawa`s Locodols.
While they appear on cable TV as reporters, Nanako wonders if their actions are actually helping the community.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656589</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160983" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ろこどる】はじめてみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">[Locodol] We Tried Starting It.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé d`être des stars locales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">[Locodol] wa Hajimete Mita.</title>
<summary>Nanako Usami is a first year high school student living in the country town Nagarekawa.
Just as she starts getting used to high school life, she makes plans to visit the public pool with her friends after its renovation.
While she begs her mother for a new swimsuit for the special event, her mother refuses her flatly.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656533</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160993" update="2015-06-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160994" update="2014-07-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161644" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇気をだして, 呼んでみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Gathering the Courage to Call.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé de rassembler notre courage et d`être plus familières</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuki o Dashita, Yonde Mita.</title>
<summary>The new Uogokoro-kun actor Nazukari Mirai and Nanako are both first years students at the same school. However, due to Mirai`s extreme shyness, they haven`t become friends. Nanako talks to her friend Noda, who attended middle school with Mirai, in order to get closer to her, but her plans don`t go well.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656567</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161645" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いろいろ増えてみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Adding a Lot of Things.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé d`être plus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iroiro Fuete Mita.</title>
<summary>Today the Nagarekawa Girls are giving a report on a local hot spring. While taking a break after playfully completing their job, the girls discuss the Cute and Loose Characters Field Day they recorded previously. Both Yui and Yukari are excited for the broadcast, but Nanako isn`t too excited.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656565</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161646" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆるキャラ集めてみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Gathering Cute and Loose Characters.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé de rassembler des mascottes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuru Character Atsumete Mita.</title>
<summary>Uogokoro-kun represents the city of Nagarekawa in a field day for the nation`s cute and loose characters. Nanako and Yukari are worried when Uogokoro-kun appears nervous, but the Nagarekawa girls have their own job to do: promote Nagarekawa on a national TV broadcast. Concerned a mistake might ruin the image of Nagarekawa, Nanako loses her cool.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656563</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161647" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビッグな目標立ててみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Setting a Big Goal.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé de se donner un objectif énorme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Big na Mokuhyou Tatete Mita.</title>
<summary>Early afternoon. On the roof of their high school, the Nagarekawa Girls and Yui Mikoze hold a Nagarekawa Girls meeting.
The subject: their futures.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656595</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162280" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">【ろこどる】やってみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Being Locodols.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé d`être un groupe local</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">[Locodol] Yatte Mita.</title>
<summary>It`s finally the day of the Locodol Festival. However, Nanako and her friends continue moving at their own pace and enjoy a lively breakfast together. Though Nanako was triumphantly basking in the praises of her friends, a single word from Yui has her agitated again... Despite all their uncertainty and doubts, the Nagarekawa Girls` big moment at the Locodol Festival`s main stage begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656575</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162281" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロコドル集めてみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Gathering Locodols.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé de rassembler des stars locales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Locodol Atsumete Mita.</title>
<summary>The Nagarekawa Girls are prepared for the Locodol Festival and are making final adjustments.
Amidst the heat they prepare at city hall, but for some reason they choose to hold their meeting in a room without air conditioning. While they will be appearing on national television, the girls treat it like any other job. As the girls think about sightseeing after the festival, Saori informs them of some very important news...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656573</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162282" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4人の力でやってみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Working as Four.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé d`unir nos forces</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yonnin no Chikara de Yatte Mita.</title>
<summary>The Nagarekawa Girls decide to participate in the Locodol Festival. The girls are excited for the nationally broadcast gathering of Locodols from around the nation. With no prior contact with other Locodols, as the girls begin wondering what kind of work they perform, Mirai brings the other members back to reality with a certain message.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656571</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162283" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワガママ言ってみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Being Selfish.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé d’être égoïstes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wagamama Itte Mita.</title>
<summary>Oota and Nanako face off at Nagarekawa City Hall. The air was filled with an unprecedented tension. Nanako asks her uncle if he`s engaging in illegal activity with a look of unprecedented earnestness. The employees around them begin whispering. Yukari and Saori are among them.
With all eyes upon him, how will Oota respond?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656569</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162946" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流川, 案内してみた.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Tried Giving a Tour of Nagarekawa.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On a essayé de faire visiter Nagarekawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagarekawa, An`naishite Mita.</title>
<summary>The Awa Awa Girls visit the Locodols hoping for a guided tour of Nagarekawa.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>666445</identifier>
<identifier>locodol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169012" update="2015-06-14">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169013" update="2015-06-14">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
