<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10426" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2014-06-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Break Blade (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Broken Blade (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ブレイクブレイド BROKEN BLADE (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">破刃之剑</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7103" type="Alternative Setting">Break Blade</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="308191">Really good anime that would be a must see if not for my strong desire for a sequel, which has tey to come into existence.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://breakblade.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="14380" type="Character Design">Norita Takushige</name>
<name id="5332" type="Direction">Habara Nobuyoshi</name>
<name id="4999" type="Chief Direction">Amino Tetsurou</name>
<name id="18007" type="Original Work">Yoshinaga Yuunosuke</name>
</creators>
<description>A young man named http://anidb.net/ch13162 [Rygart Arrow] is a resident of a world where people can use "magic". This magic is the ability to control and empower quartz, doing many things from creating light to operating machinery to riding giant mecha called Golems. Rygart, however, is one of the few exceptions; as an un-sorcerer, he cannot utilize quartz, making many aspects of life difficult. Despite this, in his youth he managed to befriend http://anidb.net/ch13164 [Hodr] and http://anidb.net/ch13165 [Sigyn], the future King and Queen of the Krisna Kingdom; and http://anidb.net/ch13163 [Zess], the younger brother of the Secretary of War of the Athens Commonwealth.
Years later, Rygart is reunited with Hodr and Sigyn where he learns the Athens Commonwealth has begun an invasion of Krisna. Rygart is also shocked to learn that Zess is leading one of the strike forces. While at the capital, Rygart discovers that he has the ability to pilot a recently found ancient Golem which cannot be piloted by magic users. Despite its ancient origins, the Golem possesses capabilities and systems far more advanced than the current Golems, and could be key to turning the tide of battle. While hesitant at first, Rygart soon gets involved in the war between Krisna and Athens, in an attempt to save Hodr, Sigyn, and Zess.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: A recompiled version of all six earlier films with additional new scenes. The updated 12 episode television version of the http://anidb.net/a7103 [2010-2011 films] will add previously un-animated scenes, such as the battle to the death between the gifted warrior Girge and the specially selected Spartan robot unit. (Source: ANN)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="662">6.03</permanent>
<temporary count="665">7.03</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>157762.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17090</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22433</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>30573</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://breakblade.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Broken_Blade</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ブレイク_ブレイド#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E6.94.BE.E6.98.A0.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3378</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348408</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17062</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00BSX6NGS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1179" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-21">
<name>indecisive</name>
<description>This character has trouble taking their own decisions, and may rely on others to do that instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3252" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>history is written by the victors</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4640" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-14">
<name>social outcast</name>
<description>Someone who has been rejected or excluded from the majority, or all of the social groups in an area (school, work, etc.). A person that does not fit in society.
They typically look slightly high or depressed and they are usually alone most the time. Some are alone because they are too snobbish and see themselves above everyone else. Others are alone because they want to be. 
They are usually the victims of every negative stereotype and rumour. Some might even be called “freaks”.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5638" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-25">
<name>military is useless</name>
<description>The regular military force per se or certain units thereof are way out of their league when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes (e.g. powerful aliens). Thus the regular military is completely useless. 
Often, only children (of all people) with special abilities and/or powered suits can defend Earth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13162" type="main character in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="48">5.14</rating>
<name>Rygart Arrow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rygart is the series` main protagonist at the age of 25. He was born an un-sorcerer, meaning that he can`t use magic, unlike the majority of the worlds populace. Before he left to see Hodr, he worked on a farm with his brother who`s also an un-sorcerer, because of this, his father sold all Quartz operated tools and worked with tools without Quartz. After his father took out loans, he was able to attend a military school where he befriended Zess, Hodr, and Sigyn where the four of them were known as "the four problem children of Assam`s Military School", him being known as the "King of Make-up tests". He hates violence and believes he can win via his opponent tiring out before him. He later becomes the pilot of the Dirfringe, an ancient mecha designed for only an un-sorcerer`s use as a Heavy Knight for Krisna. He originally joins the war to protect his brother and friends but later admits he`s really fighting to protect Sigyn.</description>
<picture>45084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13163" type="main character in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="35">6.71</rating>
<name>Zess</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zess is 25 years old soldier of Athens. He met Rygart at military school, where he was called "straight-laced Zess". He was one of the best pilots and was the full of pride. He met Rygart when he was being bullied and not complaining or fighting back, scaring the bullies off and quickly befriended Rygart afterward. When he learns his nation plans to conquer Krisna, he leads a small commando strike force of mechs to the Krisna capital in order to make Hodr surrender quickly to spare his friends and their country from the wrath of the main Athens Invasion Army, unaware that the leaders of Athens wants the royal family executed. He is married and has a 2 year old daughter.</description>
<picture>45085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13164" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="23">5.13</rating>
<name>Hodr</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hodr is 25 year old king of Krisna and Sigyn`s husband. He befriended Rygart at the military school when he ditched class to help him save an owl after he spotted him from his classroom`s window. He was known as the "Crown Prince" for staring at the sky and scoring failing grades. He doesn`t want to be king, but tries to be a good leader and cares greatly for his people`s lives.</description>
<picture>45086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13165" type="main character in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="92">8.32</rating>
<name>Sigyn Erster</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sigyn is the 25 year old Queen of Krisna and Hodr`s wife and a close friend of Rygart. They went to the same military school as him, where she was known as the "Mad Scientist" for secluding herself in the school`s lab for 3 days and nights without eating or drinking. She pursues a career of science and cares deeply for her friends, to the point of pointing a gun at Rygart upon first seeing him to ask why he didn`t show up at her wedding and confirm that he doesn`t hate her. While she is the Queen, she rarely acts like one as she usually spends in the castle maintenance workshop tinkering with machines with the royal engineers. Even though she and Hodr are married, both of them are never seen sharing the same bed suggesting their union was an arrange marriage. It is later reveal Sigyn was in love with Rygart during their days in military school but Rygart purposely didn`t hear her confession to him when he returned to take over his father`s farm because he felt Sigyn deserved a better life with someone else. Even after being reunited and married, she still loves Rygart.</description>
<picture>45087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16046" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="30">7.29</rating>
<name>Narvi Strize</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Narvi is a 24 year old female Upper Class Heavy Knight from Krisna. She previously served under General Tool before being assigned to command her own squad.</description>
<picture>45079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16047" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="16">6.00</rating>
<name>Nile Strize</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nile is a 25 year old male Upper First Class Heavy Knight from Krisna who serves as a mech sniper.</description>
<picture>45080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16048" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-29">
<rating votes="43">7.49</rating>
<name>Cleo Saburaf</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cleo is 12 years old mech pilot who looks like a teenager which her friend Lee makes fun of her for being extremely developed for her age. She`s a quick learner, but despite this she is very clumsy and somewhat a slow thinker with other things. She states that her positive skills are cooking, laundry, and keeping watch without even getting tired. She and Lee graduated from military school after 2 years, when it ordinarily takes 6 years.
Lee later commits suicide to prevent from being captured under the belief that the enemy are barbarians, but Cleo believes Rygart killed her and initially wanted to kill him. After this, she meets Rygart in battle and shows a surprising amount of skill contrary to how she was before, almost fighting off Rygart. She is defeated shortly after securing Zess`s escape and taken prisoner, where she is treated very leniently and shares a room with Sigyn. She initially tries to escape by securing Sigyn`s gun and tries to kill Rygart, but fails because the gun actually had no ammo. She befriends Sigyn and doesn`t try to escape afterward.</description>
<picture>45081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16049" type="appears in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="23">5.50</rating>
<name>Lee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lee is a soldier of Athens who detests Krisna for their ruthless acts during the previous war, though she seems unaware of Athen`s own acts during it. Cleo and her went to the same Military School.</description>
<picture>45082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16050" type="appears in" update="2010-03-27">
<rating votes="7">2.45</rating>
<name>Elekt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elekt is a soldier of Athens.</description>
<picture>45083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19431" type="appears in" update="2010-07-09">
<rating votes="14">5.99</rating>
<name>Io</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19432" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-22">
<rating votes="48">8.21</rating>
<name>Jirugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19433" type="appears in" update="2010-07-09">
<rating votes="16">4.07</rating>
<name>Nike</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>50892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19434" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="21">3.59</rating>
<name>Borcuse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Athens most infamous Generals. To his subordinates he is seen as a loving father and a good friend, but in reality, he is a cold and calculating man who will not hesitate to commit heinous acts of barbarism to achieve his goals.</description>
<picture>50888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20399" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-22">
<rating votes="13">3.12</rating>
<name>True</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A hot-headed General of Krisna who always immediately runs into the battle without strategy much to the trouble of those under his command. Despite these flaws, he is well loved by the people of Krisna due to donating all of his money to the orphanages of Krisna and even taking care of the orphans himself with two of those orphans being Narvi and Nile.
He is killed at the end of Volume 4 due to his hot-headed impatience leading his forces right into an obvious ambush by the Athens Invasion Force.</description>
<picture>52648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20400" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-05">
<rating votes="20">6.84</rating>
<name>Baldr</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A calm General and brilliant strategist.He is one of Krisna`s most prized generals. He serves as a mentor to Rygart on becoming a soldier and is also his Commanding officer. He has a son named Girge but has since disowned him due to the latter killing one of his fellow cadets and severally injuring 8 others during a training exercise without reason. Baldr was away on border patrol when that incident occurred and has never been able to get the full story from his son or the reasons for his actions.</description>
<picture>52649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2730" picture="22755.jpg">Sugawara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20401" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="10">5.21</rating>
<name>Loggin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 28 year old male Upper First Class Heavy Knight from Krisna who serves as a mech sniper.</description>
<picture>52650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20830" picture="83147.jpg">Kawai Tomoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20402" type="appears in" update="2013-11-22">
<rating votes="7">3.91</rating>
<name>Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tall female military instructor for Krisna. She is an expert in close quarter melee combat</description>
<picture>52651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1659" picture="223004.jpg">Katsuragi Nanaho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20403" type="appears in" update="2013-11-22">
<rating votes="5">2.72</rating>
<name>Argath</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A soldier of Athens and a subordinate of Zess.</description>
<picture>52652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="169" picture="16976.jpg">Takahashi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20404" type="appears in" update="2011-04-15">
<rating votes="7">3.69</rating>
<name>Regats Arrow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The younger brother of Rygart and also an un-sorcerer.</description>
<picture>69741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31146" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Krisna Oukoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>69733.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31147" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="12">4.91</rating>
<name>Elza</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4217" picture="151698.jpg">Yanagisawa Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31150" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Athens Renpou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>69743.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31151" type="appears in" update="2011-08-21">
<rating votes="4">2.40</rating>
<name>Rokis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31152" type="appears in" update="2013-11-22">
<rating votes="6">2.03</rating>
<name>Bades</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6125" picture="223612.jpg">Hayashi Kazuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31154" type="appears in" update="2013-11-22">
<rating votes="6">2.15</rating>
<name>Ailes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31155" type="appears in" update="2013-11-22">
<rating votes="12">6.30</rating>
<name>Leto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31156" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="12">4.13</rating>
<name>Leda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31159" type="appears in" update="2011-04-13">
<rating votes="8">4.13</rating>
<name>Greta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35657" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="4">6.30</rating>
<name>Delfing</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45827.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35658" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="4">7.83</rating>
<name>Delfing</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Second form.</description>
<picture>45831.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35659" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Delfing</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Third form.</description>
<picture>45832.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35660" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Delfing</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Fourth form.</description>
<picture>45837.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35661" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Delfing</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Fifth form.</description>
<picture>45839.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35662" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45852.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35663" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45865.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35664" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45866.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35665" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45868.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35666" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45880.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35667" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45907.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35668" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45910.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35669" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45922.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35670" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45949.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35671" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Fabnir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45950.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35672" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="2">5.01</rating>
<name>Artemis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45958.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35673" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Artemis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45959.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35674" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="3">6.43</rating>
<name>Artemis Neos</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45960.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35675" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Hyukerion</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45963.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35676" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="3">6.43</rating>
<name>Toroia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45964.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35677" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Giratos</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45965.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35678" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Radun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45966.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35679" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Bersebone</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45978.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="35680" type="appears in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Doragia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>45986.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67871" type="appears in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Daphne Charibinsuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2339" picture="151715.jpg">Taketora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67872" type="appears in" update="2014-06-13">
<name>Terton Kizu Demuyato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="318" picture="69041.jpg">Iijima Hajime</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67873" type="appears in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Orleans Le Man Dubert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2145" picture="82117.jpg">Miyashita Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67874" type="appears in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39678" picture="224254.jpg">Komada Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="158731" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クロース・コンバット (近接戦闘)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Close combat – Affrontements rapprochés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Close Combat (Kinsetsu Sentou)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158732" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノット・バッド (停戦交渉)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Not bad – Cessez-le-feu et pourparlers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Not Bad (Teisen Koushou)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158733" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンダー・ゴゥレム (古代巨兵)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Protogolem – Le titan des Anciens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Undergolem (Kodai Kyohei)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158734" update="2014-03-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アン・ソーサラー (魔力無者)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sans-magie - Celui qui n`avais pas le don</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unsorcerer (Maryoku Musha)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159552" update="2014-04-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カウンター・アタック (逆撃強襲)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Counter-attack – La contre-offensive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Counter Attack (Gyakugeki Kyoushuu)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159603" update="2014-04-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウェイスト・ランド (死地凶変)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Wasteland – Terres de désastre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wasteland (Shichi Kyouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159604" update="2014-04-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナイト・ビフォア (出撃前夜)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Night before – La nuit d`avant l`attaque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Night Before (Shutsugeki Zenya)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159605" update="2014-04-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワール・ウィンド (疾風怒濤)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">War wind – Les vents déchaînés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">War Wind (Shippuudotou)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160015" update="2014-05-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンドレス・フェイト (永劫回帰)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endless Fight – L`éternel retour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Endless Fight (Eigou Kaiki)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160016" update="2014-05-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラスト・スタンド (要害堅固)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Last stand – La forteresse imprenable</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Stand (Yougai Kengo)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160017" update="2014-05-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライトニング・スピード (神速無双)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lightning speed – Vitesse inégalée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lightning Speed (Shinsoku Musou)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160018" update="2014-05-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ショウ・ダウン (竜虎宣戦)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Showdown – Provocation en duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Showdown (Ryuuko Sensen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161891" update="2017-03-04">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161892" update="2014-08-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163497" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2014-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命に抗おう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei ni Aragaou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163498" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜入! ボルキュス邸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sennyuu! Borukyusu Tei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163499" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミレニル部隊, 結成!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mireniru Butai, Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163500" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリシュナ9世, 御前試合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Krisna 9-sei, Gozen Shiai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163501" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2014-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イリオス連邦兵軍学校</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Irios Renpou Heigun Gakkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163502" update="2014-10-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大陸暦784年アッサム国立士官学校の某所にて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tairiku Reki 784-nen Assamu Kokuritsu Shikan Gakkou no Bousho nite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163503" update="2014-10-15">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2014-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Virgins War</title>
</episode>
<episode id="166869" update="2017-03-04">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="166870" update="2017-03-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170950" update="2015-08-23">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Extra 1 (1m 20s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170953" update="2015-08-23">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Extra 2 (1m 8s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170954" update="2015-08-23">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Extra 3 (1m 12s)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
