<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10453" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-03-27</startdate>
<enddate>2014-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun S: Daiji na Koto wa Zenbu Sentou ni Osowatta</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">とある科学の超電磁砲[レールガン]S OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">A Certain Scientific Railgun S OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun S OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun S: Everything Important We Learned in the Public Bathhouse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="short">어떤 과학의 초전자포 S OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Railgun S OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">とある科学の超電磁砲[レールガン]S 大事なことはぜんぶ銭湯に教わった</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">어떤 과학의 초전자포 S: 중요한 건 전부 대중탕에서 배웠다</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9484" type="Parent Story">Toaru Kagaku no Railgun S</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="478777">I actually enjoyed this! A nice, quick dose of fan-service! If you like the series then dig in!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20170719223534/http://www.project-railgun.net/contents/hp0013/index00590000.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Toaru Kagaku no Railgun manga written by http://anidb.net/cr6886 [Kamachi Kazuma] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr6888 [Fuyukawa Motoi], which in itself is a spin-off of the light novel, manga and anime series http://anidb.net/a5975 [Toaru Majutsu no Index].
As Misaka and the gang decide what to do for the day, they encounter Konori-senpai handing out pamphlets for her childhood public bathhouse; it is struggling with slow business and facing closure. Wanting to help out, the gang comes up with a unique idea to save the bathhouse...
— written by CDB-Man
Note: Bundled with the Toaru Kagaku no Railgun S official visual book.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="636">3.77</permanent>
<temporary count="640">6.08</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>233286.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22759</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20170719223534/http://www.project-railgun.net/contents/hp0013/index00590000.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>A_Certain_Scientific_Railgun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>とある科学の超電磁砲</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2469" type="main character in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="2418">8.60</rating>
<name>Misaka Mikoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misaka Mikoto is one of the series` main heroines, as well as the main protagonist of the side story, A Certain Scientific Railgun. Her parents are Tabigake and Misuzu Misaka, which her father is a prominent businessman and millionaire. Despite her rich background, she grew up in a normal typical childhood.
At a young age, she was discovered to be a Level 1 Electromaster, espers who have the ability to generate and control electricity. She enrolled into Academy City to train her powers and worked very hard until her powers were ranked Level 5, the highest esper ranking, with her being the third strongest of the seven espers with this rank. As an electromaster, she can generate and manipulate electricity which she can use to shock opponents, hack into electronics like computer networks and security systems, and use electromagnetism to cling to surfaces or manipulate iron particles into a chain-sword whip. Mikoto`s signature move is her ability to shoot metal projectiles such as coins at high destructive speeds, hence her nickname, The Railgun. If she is in a bad mood, she will sometimes let out bursts of electricity describing her emotional stress, usually resulting in power failures or even citywide blackouts.
Mikoto attends Tokiwadai Middle School, a famous girls` school for the rich and elite psychics and one of the five elite schools of Academy City. To most people, she is considered a proper lady, but in reality, she has a short-tempered, prideful, and improper attitude with some tomboyish tendencies and insecurities, a fact few other characters know. She is fond of cute, childish things, such as flowery pajamas and Gekota, the popular frog mascot franchise. Contrary to what she claims, she has a strong sense of morals and hates injustice. Mikoto has a one-sided rivalry with Touma, who nicknamed her Biri Biri (ビリビリ, relating to the sound of an electric shock), ever since their first meeting before the events of the first novel when he first dissipated her electricity after he unsuccessfully tried to rescue her. Since that incident, she is always trying to have a proper match with Touma and defeat him despite his many attempts to avoid conflict with her.
When Mikoto was young, she was tricked into giving the city`s scientist her DNA under the pretense of finding the cure for Duchenne muscular dystrophy; their actual goal to create military-grade combat clones of her. When it was discovered that the clones did not have the same power level as Mikoto, they were instead used in an Project called Level 6 Shift, intended to make Accelerator the first level 6 esper by having him kill 20,000 clones. The events of how Mikoto tried to stop the project are briefly mentioned in the third novel and expanded upon in the Railgun manga. When all of her attempts failed, she contemplates letting herself be killed by Accelerator, as an unexpected variable to destroy Tree Diagram`s calculations. However, it is not until Touma intervenes and beats Accelerator, proving him to be really weak, that the project is canceled and the remaining 9969 surviving Sisters are spared.
After those events, she eventually develops strong romantic feelings towards Touma but is unable to express them due to her insecurities and the fact other girls are also interested in him. Even though she and Touma tend to bicker and argue with each other, they share a somewhat friendly relationship.</description>
<picture>232410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2470" type="main character in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="973">6.22</rating>
<name>Shirai Kuroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirai Kuroko is a level 4 psychic, and member of Judgement, a special public committee group, whose duty it is to maintain peace and order in Academy City. She is in love with Misaka, who she calls "Onee-sama" (sister) and tends to get jealous if someone else gets her attention. This unfortunately happens to be Touma, since he has caught the attention of Misaka for various reasons. Her special power is instant teleportation, which allows her to teleport herself and anything in her possession - as long as it weighs around 130-137 kilograms - to anywhere in a radius of around 81-85 metres.</description>
<picture>232414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2473" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="194">5.78</rating>
<name>Tsukuyomi Komoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite her childish and very short (135 cm) appearance, she is actually an adult and one of Touma`s teachers. This is proven by her apartment being littered with beer cans and cigarettes. She also contradicts her age by acting childish to her students, having a child-like crush on Touma, and ending her sentences with desu, something a child usually does. This irony means that she is often regarded as one of the seven great mysteries of Academy City.</description>
<picture>232411.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10391" type="main character in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="479">7.25</rating>
<name>Saten Ruiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saten Ruiko is a Level 0, classmate and friend of Uiharu who is known for wearing a flower on the left side of her hair. She is a little shameless as she sometimes flips Uiharu`s skirt in public. When rumours of a special tool that increases psychic powers called the "Power Upper" spread, she considers obtaining it out of envy as she does not have any apparent powers. When she uses it, Ruiko consequently winds up in a coma and gradually recovers thanks to the help the creator of the Level Upper. She first appears in the To Aru Kagaku no Railgun manga and makes a cameo appearance in the To Aru Majutsu no Index light novel series and the opening of the anime and is set to appear in the animated Railgun spinoff.</description>
<picture>33388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10392" type="main character in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="321">4.79</rating>
<name>Uiharu Kazari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uiharu Kazari is Shirai`s friend and colleague in Judgment and another protagonist in To Aru Kagaku no Railgun. Shy and humble, she goes to a different middle school from Shirai and is known for wearing a headband made of flowers on her head, and sometimes a surgical mask as she constantly suffers the flu. Her powers are currently unknown. She makes a cameo appearance in the opening of the anime and is set to appear in the animated Railgun spinoff. She has enormous eyebrows.</description>
<picture>33387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12365" type="appears in" update="2011-04-26">
<rating votes="162">5.58</rating>
<name>Kongou Mitsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kongou Mitsuko is a Level 4, 2nd year transfer student of Tokiwadai Middle School. As Kuroko`s rival, she is confident, boastful, and desires to become a Level 5. Although she if often boastful about her abilities, she usually finds herself the victim of several attacks. Like all Tokidawai students, she lives in one of the school`s dormitories albeit her dormitory is located within the School Garden District.
Her ability is called "Aero Hand" (空力使い, Kuuriki Tsukai) which with any object she touches, a powerful gust of wind will take form, propelling it like a missile. She also owns a pet snake named Ekaterina. She originally appears in the eighth novel and makes her first animated appearance in the Toaru Kagaku no Railgun anime.</description>
<picture>37373.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12366" type="appears in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="35">4.31</rating>
<name>Tessou Tsuzuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tessou Tsuzuri is a grade school teacher who wears glasses with a rather panicky personality and also a member of the Anti-Skills, where she normally partners with Yomikawa. Her lack of confidence makes her prone to messing up on the field. She enjoys beat-em-up games.</description>
<picture>37374.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12957" type="appears in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="31">4.72</rating>
<name>Wannai Kinuho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wannai Kinuho is Kuroko`s classmate who resides in the same dorms as Mitsuko. She is best friends with Awatsuki Maaya and together they are members of the swim club with Kinuho having the ability of aquakinesis, which gives her control over water. Kinuho was once saved from some thugs by Mikoto and is thankful to Mikoto on what she did. They are often seen hanging around Mitsuko.</description>
<picture>38716.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12958" type="appears in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="34">5.23</rating>
<name>Awatsuki Maaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Awatsuki Maaya is Kuroko`s classmate who resides in the same dorms as Mitsuko. She is best friends with Wannai Kinuho and together they are members of the swim club. They are often seen hanging around Mitsuko.</description>
<picture>38717.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12959" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-03-15">
<rating votes="84">5.97</rating>
<name>Konori Mii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konori Mii is a high school student and Chief of the 177th Branch of Judgment where Kazari and Kuroko work. As their sempai before becoming chief, she tries to make sure both girls do their work at Judgment seriously and at the same time wants them to be safe. She is a Level 3 esper with a power called Clairvoyance (透視系能力 (クレアボイアンス), Toushi Kei Nouryoku) which gives her X-ray vision, allowing her to spot concealed weapons. In the past, she used to be a member of a Skill-Out gang called Big Spider to find a purpose in her life. It was there where she met and fell in love with Wataru Kurozuma, the leader of the Big Spider`s. But after his supposed death two years ago, the incident made her change her ways and become the Judgment member she is now.</description>
<picture>38718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12960" type="appears in" update="2009-11-13">
<rating votes="31">5.25</rating>
<name>Ryoukan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38719.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13691" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="165">5.61</rating>
<name>Yomikawa Aiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A teacher at Touma`s school and a friend of Komoe. She is beautiful, has glamorous proportions, and is always seen with a green jersey. She is a member of the Anti-Skills and cares deeply for her students, and is apparently an active peacekeeper within the Academic City. A favor to her old friend, Yomikawa is asked by Yoshikawa Kikyou to take care of Accelerator and Last Order after they are released from the hospital.</description>
<picture>232406.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14942" type="appears in" update="2010-03-02">
<rating votes="19">4.38</rating>
<name>Haruue Erii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruue marks her first appearance in episode 17 where she is helped in a search for her lost locket by Tsuzuri. Later she reappears as an out-of-season transfer student into Sakugawa Middle School`s 2nd year and becomes Uiharu`s roommate.
The locket actually contains a picture of Edasaki Banri. Haruue was raised at a child care institute as a child error. When she was young, she held a strong telepathic connection to Edasaki who stayed at the same institute for some time.</description>
<picture>42840.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="56196" type="appears in" update="2019-03-09">
<rating votes="52">6.75</rating>
<name>Frenda Seivelun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Frenda Seivelun is a member of ITEM. She makes use of a tape of explosive material and an electronic device to create a fuse that can cut through various objects. Usually the fuses are connected to dolls with explosives within them.</description>
<picture>65247.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="56197" type="appears in" update="2017-07-28">
<rating votes="33">6.14</rating>
<name>Takitsubo Rikou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takitsubo Rikou is a member of ITEM. Her ability is called AIM Stalker (能力追跡, Nouryoku Tsuiseki) which she uses to track down espers by memorizing their AIM fields. Her ability also allows her to steal other espers` abilities by memorizing their AIM, potentially allowing her to become the eighth Level 5 esper in Academy City.</description>
<picture>65246.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="56198" type="appears in" update="2019-04-11">
<rating votes="35">6.94</rating>
<name>Kinuhata Saiai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinuhata Saiai is a member of ITEM. Her ability is the Level 4 Offense Armour (窒素装甲, Chisso Soukou), which she uses to control the nitrogen in the atmosphere and create a few centimeters barrier of nitrogen that she can use to attack and defend.</description>
<picture>232495.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="56199" type="appears in" update="2017-07-28">
<rating votes="64">4.79</rating>
<name>Mugino Shizuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mugino Shizuri is one of the seven Level 5 espers, ranking fourth after Misaka Mikoto, she is the leader of ITEM, which is at odds with SCHOOL. She looks down upon lower-level espers and does not mind eliminating people who get in her way or go against her, regardless of whether they are enemies or allies.
Her power can create multiple beams that can sear through objects, or she can defend herself by creating a shield of energy. She can also use silicon cards to split her attacks into multiple blasts.</description>
<picture>65245.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="158135" update="2014-04-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2014-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OAD</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
