<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1046" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1992-03-07</startdate>
<enddate>1992-03-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dragon Ball Z: Gekitotsu!! 100-oku Power no Senshi-tachi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ドラゴンボールZ 激突!! 100億パワーの戦士たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Z: Attack!! 10.000.000.000 Power Warriors</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Z: Collision! 10 Billion Powered Warriors</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Z 06 - 100 000 guerriers de métal</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Z: Powrót Coolera</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">DBZ Movie 6</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">DRAGON BALL Z 激突!! 100億パワーの戦士たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dragon Ball Z: The Return of Cooler</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Dragonball Z - The Movie: Coolers Rückkehr</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Dragon Ball Z 06 - Cent mille guerriers de métal</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Dragon Ball Z: L`invasione di Neo Namek</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Dragon Ball Z 6 - O Poder Misterioso</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Dragon Ball Z: Ataque! 10 Bilhões de Guerreiros Poderosos</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Dragon Ball Z - Taistelu ylivoimaa vastaan</title>
<title xml:lang="gl" type="official">Combate contra cen millóns de poderosos guerreiros</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1045" type="Prequel">Dragon Ball Z: Tobikkiri no Saikyou tai Saikyou</anime>
<anime id="1530" type="Parent Story">Dragon Ball Z</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="1009" type="Unknown Relation">Toei Douga</name>
<name id="1902" type="Original Work">Toriyama Akira</name>
<name id="4539" type="Direction">Nishio Daisuke</name>
<name id="3962" type="Music">Kikuchi Shunsuke</name>
</creators>
<description>New Namek is besieged by an enormous evil entity - the Big Gete Star - a `living planet` of metal that sustains itself by devouring entire worlds.
Fearing for the existence of his people, Dende, the new guardian of Earth, turns to Goku and his friends for help. The Z-Fighters spring into action in an effort to save the new Namekian home world from this invading menace, but their fight won`t be easy! The Big Gete Star has an army of powerful Cyclopean Guards at its disposal, and what`s more, at the heart of this metal giant lurks an old enemy... Cooler!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1561">4.16</permanent>
<temporary count="1578">6.38</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>145590.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>995</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>899</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>563</identifier>
<identifier>rmtvot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dragon_Ball_Z:_The_World's_Strongest</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>151629</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2085" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="689">8.50</rating>
<name>Kame Sennin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kame Sennin is an ancient and wise martial arts master and the first Earthling to wield the Kamehameha. Though he seems frail, he is a mighty warrior, having trained Grandpa Gohan, Gyuumaou, Son Gokuu, and others.</description>
<picture>135368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3059" picture="203228.jpg">Miyauchi Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2103" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="2804">8.56</rating>
<name>Son Gokuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son Gokuu is a Saiyajin warrior who was sent to Earth when he was a child.</description>
<picture>135352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2105" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="1212">8.57</rating>
<name>Vegeta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vegeta is the prince of the Saiyajin race and http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu]`s most fearsome rival. He is a very prideful person and, as a full-blooded saiyajin, loves the prospect of a good battle.</description>
<picture>230630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="132" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6881" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="128">4.59</rating>
<name>Oolong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oolong is a shapeshifting, anthropomorphic pig that uses his abilities for his own greedy desires. He was expelled from shapeshifting training for stealing the teacher`s underwear, so he lacks the ability to change his form for more than five minutes at a time without a break. He joins with Goku to search for the Dragon Balls and eventually steal them, but he abandons his plans. In Dragon Ball Z, he is often in the company of Roshi.</description>
<picture>135369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11414" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="230">7.05</rating>
<name>Kuririn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuririn is introduced in Dragon Ball as a rival of the main character, http://anidb.net/ch2116 [Son Gokuu]. Later in the series, he develops a close relationship with him as well as his son, http://anidb.net/ch11419 [Gohan].</description>
<picture>66653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11416" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="557">7.67</rating>
<name>Piccolo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Piccolo, whose full name is Piccolo Jr., was first introduced as the reincarnation of the evil http://anidb.net/ch22168 [Piccolo Daimaou] in http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], making him a demon and arch-rival of the primary protagonist, http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Son Gokuu]. However, it is later revealed that he is from the race of alien beings called Namekians and he decides to team up with http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] and his friends in order to beat newer, more dangerous threats.</description>
<picture>135357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11417" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="67">6.16</rating>
<name>Mr. Popo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is an immortal genie who tends the grounds of Kami`s Lookout and is bound there eternally as the gardener and caretaker. He uses a magic carpet for Instant Transportation. Though he may not appear to physically age, Mr. Popo is very old; having served Kami, the Guardian of Earth for hundreds of years, he also served Kami`s predecessor, as well as every other guardian of the Earth in the past. Being the loyal and faithful servant that he is, his purpose consists mainly of tending to Kami`s Palace, keeping the Lookout clean, helping to reconstruct Shenron if needed, and most importantly, taking care of Kami. He also tends to the ancient butterfly garden that he planted thousands of years ago, and enjoys the more simple things in life.</description>
<picture>34072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9290">Nishio Toku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11419" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="262">5.01</rating>
<name>Son Gohan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gohan is introduced at the age of 4 as the first son of the primary protagonist, http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Son Gokuu], and his wife, http://anidb.net/ch11409 [Chichi].</description>
<picture>34074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11421" type="appears in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="85">5.16</rating>
<name>Yajirobe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yajirobe is an overweight samurai that Goku meets in Dragon Ball. He is often considered to be rude, unmannered, timid, lazy, and cowardly. He helps Goku prepare for the battle against Piccolo Daimao, and continues to support Goku and his companions, though often from the sideline</description>
<picture>34076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11591" type="appears in" update="2009-09-08">
<rating votes="35">2.75</rating>
<name>Dende</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dende is a Namekian child saved from Dodoria by Gohan and Kuririn. He has the ability to heal wounds.</description>
<picture>35012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3733" picture="203229.jpg">Suzuki Tomiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22130" type="main character in" update="2010-10-07">
<rating votes="3">4.17</rating>
<name>Meta Cooler</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meta-Cooler is essentially a reincarnation of Cooler. Cooler was blown into the sun by a kamehameha from Goku. Eventually the Big Gete Star stumbled upon and absorbed what was left of Cooler. His consciousness gained control of the Big Gete Star, allowing Cooler to recreate himself as a cybernetic being.</description>
<picture>56010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22131" type="appears in" update="2010-10-07">
<rating votes="2">4.30</rating>
<name>Big Gete Star</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Big Gete Star started as a single computer chip that achieved sentience. It drifted through space gathering debris into itself, becoming quite massive. Eventually it absorbs the remains of Cooler. This leads to Cooler`s consciousness taking control and creating Meta-Cooler.</description>
<picture>56012.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="11035" update="2017-04-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1992-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
