<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10486" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-05-16</startdate>
<enddate>2014-06-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Initial D Final Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">頭文字[イニシャル]D Final Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Initial D Final Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Initial D Final Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Инициал «ДИ» финальная стадия</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">头文字D Final Stage</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9344" type="Prequel">Initial D Fifth Stage</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="459461">Of course the end was predictable but it had some nice surprices along the way so the ending was satisfying. Shame there won`t be a continuation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="134143">A good closure for the best car racing series every made!

I honestly want to keep it going but all good things must come to an end...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.animax.co.jp/special/initial-d</url>
<creators>
<name id="1163" type="Animation Work">SynergySP</name>
<name id="4141" type="Character Design">Satou Masaki</name>
<name id="5476" type="Direction">Hashimoto Mitsuo</name>
</creators>
<description>Initial D Final Stage takes place right after the end of http://anidb.net/a9344 [Fifth Stage] and shows the long-awaited final fierce downhill battle between Takumi`s 86 and Shinji`s 86.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="694">7.27</permanent>
<temporary count="695">7.49</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>155726.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16073</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22507</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mv.avex.jp/initial/initial.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.animax.co.jp/special/initial-d</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Initial_D</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>頭文字D</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4669</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348582</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16989</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2762" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>golf</name>
<description>Golf is a game played in an open field where the player hits a small ball with a specifically prepared club to sink it into a hole of about the same size. This may appear as a very boring and pointless type of game to on-lookers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2766" parentid="2759" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>street racing</name>
<description>Seen The Fast and The Furious or played Need for Speed Underground series? This is it: people racing in illegal races on the streets with their own modified cars and maybe seeing the police chasing them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4258" parentid="2759" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>drifting</name>
<description>Drifting is a driving technique where the driver intentionally oversteers, causing loss of traction in the rear wheels, while maintaining control from entry to exit of a corner. A car is drifting when the rear slip angle is greater than the front slip angle, to such an extent that often the front wheels are pointing in the opposite direction to the turn (e.g. car is turning left, wheels are pointed right or vice versa).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5584" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>euro-beat</name>
<description>Euro-beat, as the name implies, is a music genre from Europe. It is a sub-genre of 80s Italo-disco (aka 80s Euro-disco). In Japan, this label is strongly tied to dance and para-para music.
A good example is the entire Initial D soundtrack.</description>
<picurl>169134.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5947" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-04-09">
<name>tuning</name>
<description>Pimp your ride to get better performance where it matters, slick paint jobs, or stupid things like TV displays in your exhaust pipe.
Placing a "PRO GT-R PERFORMANCE" bumper sticker in your ride is NOT tuning!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9199" type="main character in" update="2019-10-04">
<rating votes="168">8.59</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiwara Takumi is the main character in Initial D. Takumi has been driving up and down Akina mountain using a panda coloured Toyota Corolla Sprinter Trueno (AE86) since the age of 12, doing deliveries for his father`s tofu shop. Because of this, he has became a very skilled driver and after overtaking http://anidb.net/ch9257 [Takahashi Keisuke] he is thrown into the world of mountain pass racing.</description>
<picture>174502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9257" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-10">
<rating votes="61">7.86</rating>
<name>Takahashi Keisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takahashi Keisuke is the number two driver for the Red Suns. Keisuke drives a Mazda FD3S RX-7 and is a skilled driver, second only to his brother http://anidb.net/ch9258 [Ryousuke].
Keisuke is a rather hot-headed young man and does not like losing. Keisuke is also known to drive with his emotions, for example if he realises that he cannot win his driving suffers and if he is in the lead he is carefree and much relaxed.
Before Ryousuke got Keisuke involved in street racing he was the leader of a Bosozoku gang. He joins his brother`s new team and has a rivalry with http://anidb.net/ch9199 [Takumi]. Keisuke races the uphill (hillclimb) on most races, while Takumi races the downhill.</description>
<picture>174503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9258" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-10">
<rating votes="87">8.98</rating>
<name>Takahashi Ryousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takahashi Ryousuke is one of the most skilled drivers in the series (he is the Red Suns` fastest member as well as their leader); he and his younger brother http://anidb.net/ch9257 [Keisuke] (the Takahashi Brothers, also known as the Rotary Brothers because they both drive RX-7 versions) have been featured in racing magazines and are regarded highly by other drivers. Ryousuke drives a Mazda FC3S RX-7 and was previously undefeated until he met http://anidb.net/ch9199 [Fujiwara Takumi].
Ryousuke is very serious about racing; he pours over technical data just like any professional driver and he is one of the few drivers with skills as a mechanic to match those he possesses as a driver. He can usually be found in his room going over data on his laptop. He is known to be able to tell what kind of modifications have been made to a car just by hearing it, and what a driver is capable of just by watching the car drift. Ryousuke`s fame is so wide spread throughout Japan that he has been given the moniker, "Akagi`s White Comet".
Note: Takahashi Ryousuke is modeled after the "Drift King" Keiichi Tsuchiya`s mentor and retired race car driver, Takahashi Kunimitsu.</description>
<picture>174504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9259" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-10">
<rating votes="83">1.91</rating>
<name>Takeuchi Itsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Itsuki Takeuchi is http://anidb.net/ch9259 [Takumi]`s best friend; he provides the comic relief in the series, and is generally quite loud and obnoxious. Itsuki works part-time at a gas station with Takumi and http://anidb.net/ch9273 [Iketani]; Itsuki plans to use the money he earns to buy an AE86 Corolla Levin (to complement Takumi`s AE86 Trueno) but mistakenly buys an inferior (less power, poor brakes, less chassis breaking, and worse suspension) AE85.</description>
<picture>160190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9273" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-27">
<rating votes="37">6.43</rating>
<name>Iketani Kouichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iketani Kouichirou, one of http://anidb.net/ch9199 [Takumi]`s friends, works at a local gas station with both Takumi and http://anidb.net/ch9259 [Itsuki]. Itsuki admires him, as Iketani is leader of the local racing team, the Akina Speed Stars. Iketani drives a Nissan S13 Silvia. At first, Iketani thinks that the Speed Stars are the best drivers in Akina but later his boss Yuuichi tells Iketani of the mysterious driver of an AE86 who was the fastest driver in his time, and that he suspects that the driver is the owner of the local tofu shop.</description>
<picture>160189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32347" type="appears in" update="2015-06-10">
<rating votes="89">8.93</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Bunta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujiwara Bunta is the owner of a tofu shop in Akina, and the father of http://anidb.net/ch9199 [Takumi]. He used to be the No.1 downhill racer in Mt. Akina years ago, but he no longer races, preferring to guide Takumi`s racing development. He is the original driver of the mysterious "white ghost of Akina" AE86 Sprinter Trueno that holds the record of the fastest downhill time at Akina.</description>
<picture>160188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32348" type="appears in" update="2011-05-19">
<rating votes="16">2.73</rating>
<name>Nakamura Kenta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32349" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-27">
<rating votes="6">4.10</rating>
<name>Fumihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1929" picture="186242.jpg">Hosoi Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32350" type="appears in" update="2014-09-06">
<name>Matsumoto Shuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matsumoto Shuuichi is the personal mechanic for Takumi`s AE86 and the chief mechanic for Project D.</description>
<picture>160512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32351" type="appears in" update="2012-11-13">
<name>Miyaguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyaguchi is a main mechanic of Keisuke`s FD.</description>
<picture>128019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4764" picture="67960.jpg">Takahashi Ryoukichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32352" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-17">
<rating votes="24">7.28</rating>
<name>Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32366" type="appears in" update="2011-05-17">
<rating votes="11">7.04</rating>
<name>Tachibana Yuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32389" type="appears in" update="2015-06-10">
<rating votes="18">8.86</rating>
<name>Nakazato Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakazato Takeshi, also known as the Black Lightning, is the leader of the Myogi NightKids. He made his first appearance at the race in Akina where http://anidb.net/ch9257 [Takahashi Keisuke] of the RedSuns is to race against http://anidb.net/ch9199 [Takumi]. Surprised that Takumi could defeat Keisuke, Takeshi decides that he is going to be the one to challenge and defeat the "Akina downhill specialist", and that the RedSuns are next on his list.
He drives black Nissan Skyline GT-R V-Spec II (BNR32).</description>
<picture>160192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32410" type="appears in" update="2015-06-10">
<rating votes="10">4.66</rating>
<name>Shouji Shingo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32426" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-06">
<rating votes="16">8.18</rating>
<name>Satou Mako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satou Mako is the driver of the Usui combination which she forms with her co-driver http://anidb.net/ch32427 [Sayuki]. She drives blue Nissan Sileighty (RPS13).</description>
<picture>160509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32427" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-06">
<rating votes="24">4.13</rating>
<name>Sayuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sayuki is the co-driver of the Usui combination which she forms with the driver http://anidb.net/ch32426 [Satou Mako].</description>
<picture>160510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32592" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<rating votes="2">5.73</rating>
<name>Sudou Kyouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="284" picture="225436.jpg">Tanaka Masahiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32593" type="appears in" update="2011-05-21">
<rating votes="1">1.92</rating>
<name>Iwaki Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29951" picture="79209.jpg">Kawahara Kazuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32700" type="appears in" update="2011-05-24">
<rating votes="4">2.03</rating>
<name>Kogashiwa Kai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32793" type="appears in" update="2011-05-27">
<name>Ninomiya Daiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32794" type="appears in" update="2011-05-28">
<name>Tachi Tomoyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2672" picture="188511.jpg">Endou Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32798" type="appears in" update="2011-05-27">
<name>Smiley Sakai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>72374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2365" picture="211146.jpg">Takase Akimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50371" type="appears in" update="2012-11-12">
<rating votes="4">8.02</rating>
<name>Uehara Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uehara Mika is a girl who accused Takumi of hitting on and then forgetting a friend of hers.</description>
<picture>127766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50372" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-11-13">
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<name>Houjou Gou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Houjou Gou is a member and chief driver of Sidewinder. He drives Honda NA1 NSX.</description>
<picture>128015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50586" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-06">
<rating votes="2">1.21</rating>
<name>Kubo Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kubo Eiji is a chief mechanic and strategist of Kanagawa`s team Sidewinder.</description>
<picture>160511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50587" type="appears in" update="2014-09-05">
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<name>Oomiya Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oomiya Satoshi is a leader of Team 246. He drives Mazda NB8C Roadster RS.</description>
<picture>160497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50588" type="appears in" update="2012-11-13">
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<name>Kobayakawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kobayakawa is a member of Team 246. He drives Mitsubishi CT9A Lancer Evolution VII GSR.</description>
<picture>128021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50589" type="appears in" update="2014-09-01">
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<name>Ikeda Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikeda Ryuuji is a member and leader of Team Spiral. He drives Nissan Z33 Fairlady Z Version S.</description>
<picture>160314.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="50590" type="appears in" update="2012-11-13">
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<name>Minagawa Hideo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minagawa Hideo is a member of Racing Team Katagiri - Street version. He drives Toyota JZA80 Supra RZ.</description>
<picture>128014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50592" type="appears in" update="2012-11-13">
<name>Mika no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mika`s golf coach.</description>
<picture>128022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24404" picture="68958.jpg">Murakami Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52557" type="appears in" update="2014-09-01">
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<name>Okuyama Hiroya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Okuyama Hiroya is a member of Team Spiral. He drives blue Nissan S15 Silvia Spec-R.</description>
<picture>160315.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="65422" type="main character in" update="2014-09-06">
<rating votes="5">2.64</rating>
<name>Inui Shinji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inui Shinji is a member of Kanagawa`s team Sidewinder. He races downhill in his white Toyota AE86 Sprinter Trueno GT-APEX (Late Type).</description>
<picture>160513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69767" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-01">
<name>Shinji no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinji`s mother.</description>
<picture>160318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6012" picture="228332.jpg">Hirose Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69782" type="appears in" update="2014-09-05">
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<name>Houjou Rin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Houjou Rin known as Shinigami, is Houjou Gou`s older brother and a legendary driver of Kanagawa. He drives in the black Nissan Skyline GT-R V-Spec II (BNR32).</description>
<picture>160483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69813" type="appears in" update="2014-09-03">
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<name>Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaori was Houjou Rin`s arranged fiance.</description>
<picture>160388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="159708" update="2014-07-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2014-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危険な匂い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dangerous Smell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un parfum de danger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiken na Nioi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159709" update="2014-05-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2014-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナチュラル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Natural</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un talent inné</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natural</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159952" update="2014-05-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159953" update="2014-05-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-05-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160251" update="2014-06-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2014-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドリーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dream</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160252" update="2014-05-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2014-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強の敵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Enemy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le plus redoutable des adversaires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou no Teki</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
