<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10514" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-22</startdate>
<enddate>2014-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">M3: Sono Kuroki Hagane</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">M3 - Sono Kuroki Hagane</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">M3 ~ソノ黒キ鋼~</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">M3 the dark metal</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">M3~黑色钢铁~</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">ام 3: فلز تیره</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8480" approval="2" total="8">Guilty Crown</anime>
<anime id="1085" approval="1" total="5">Gilgamesh</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="31909">Mech designs are good.
Characters fair even though Akashi gets all the attention and the others sit on the side
Animation Fair CG doesnt fit to well with the animation some of the times
Story wise is isnt really any guessing it will show more story towards the end. Focus is mostly on the character development for Akashi and thats about it. If you liked guilty crown this might be for you but adding things that dont happen and making suggestions that aren`t answered this fails for me. This is like persona trinity soul/guilty crown/fafner combined nothing of value unless you like Akashi</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.m3-project.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="122" type="Series Composition">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="3611" type="Direction">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="9269" type="Character Design">Inoue Hideki</name>
<name id="1043" type="Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="39839" type="Music">Sakita Hajime</name>
<name id="13150" type="Animation Work">C2C</name>
<name id="18685" type="Chief Animation Direction">Imanishi Tooru</name>
<name id="36182" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Kie</name>
<name id="9269" type="Chief Animation Direction">Inoue Hideki</name>
<name id="1043" type="Original Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="1260" type="Original Work">Mag Garden</name>
<name id="3512" type="Original Work">Bandai Namco Games</name>
<name id="14662" type="Original Work">Sotsu</name>
<name id="122" type="Original Work">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="3611" type="Original Work">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>There is distorted, deep blackness everywhere. That place, in which blackness swallowed everything and took away everything, has become known as the Avidya Zone. Strange beings assume the very form of the despair and chaos of humanity. They are known by this name: Imashime.
An expedition surveys the Avidya Zone which consumes human spirits. So, in the intricate intersection between the present in impending crisis and the destiny of the past... can eight boys and girls, assembled to confront the Imashime, find the bright future that lies before the Avidya Zone?
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="568">3.51</permanent>
<temporary count="570">5.71</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>151816.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15897</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23133</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>25543</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.m3-project.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>M3_the_dark_metal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>M3〜ソノ黒キ鋼〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3365</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348818</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17069</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="65723" type="main character in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="5">2.10</rating>
<name>Isaku Heito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65724" type="main character in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="8">4.52</rating>
<name>Izuriha Sasame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32588" picture="87531.jpg">Koiwai Kotori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65725" type="main character in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="8">4.78</rating>
<name>Yuzuki Maamu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65726" type="main character in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="5">4.59</rating>
<name>Namito Iwato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65727" type="main character in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="5">1.44</rating>
<name>Maki Minashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65728" type="main character in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="7">5.05</rating>
<name>Hazaki Emiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65729" type="main character in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="7">6.09</rating>
<name>Kasumi Raika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65730" type="main character in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="5">5.41</rating>
<name>Saginuma Akashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66887" type="appears in" update="2014-04-30">
<name>Isaku Heito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66888" type="appears in" update="2014-04-30">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Yuzuki Maamu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66889" type="appears in" update="2014-04-30">
<name>Maki Minashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21823" picture="131326.jpg">Tsuda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66890" type="appears in" update="2014-04-30">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kasumi Raika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66891" type="appears in" update="2014-04-30">
<name>Namito Iwato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66892" type="appears in" update="2014-04-30">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Izuriha Sasame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32588" picture="87531.jpg">Koiwai Kotori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66893" type="appears in" update="2014-04-30">
<rating votes="3">5.72</rating>
<name>Hazaki Emiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66894" type="appears in" update="2014-04-30">
<name>Saginuma Akashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67114" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-30">
<rating votes="5">4.64</rating>
<name>Agura Kasane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67115" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-30">
<rating votes="3">4.65</rating>
<name>Natsuiri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67116" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-30">
<rating votes="2">4.40</rating>
<name>Saginuma Aoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68957" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<rating votes="5">5.85</rating>
<name>Suzaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68958" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-29">
<rating votes="7">5.58</rating>
<name>Tsugumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32588" picture="87531.jpg">Koiwai Kotori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="159359" update="2014-05-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">混ゼルナ危険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger, Do Not Mix</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Danger ! Ne pas mélanger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mazeruna Kiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159360" update="2014-04-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去ノ綻ビ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seam of the Past</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les déchirures du passé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako no Tanbi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159361" update="2014-04-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死神ニ抱カレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Embraced by the Reaper</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans les bras de la faucheuse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinigami ni Yokare</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159362" update="2014-04-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">降星ノ夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starry Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nuit étoilée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuhoshi no Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159403" update="2015-03-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159404" update="2014-04-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159849" update="2014-05-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キエ逝ク恐怖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Terror Fading into Death</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La peur qui s`en va</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieyuku Kyoufu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="159850" update="2014-05-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">己虚シク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Self in Vain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En vain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onore Kyoshiku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160163" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人ヲ繋グモノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Links Two People</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce qui les relie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari o Tsunagu Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160164" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤ノ慟刻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Lament of Cruelty</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tristes heures rouges</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aka no Doutoki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160165" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君ノ歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Song</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ta chanson</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Uta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160166" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼キ鋼心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Heart of Steel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Métal bleu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoki Hagane Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160167" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無謀禁域</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reckless Forbidden Realm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Zone d`interdiction d`imprudence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mubou Kiniki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160168" update="2014-05-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤独ノ采配</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Command of Solitude</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Solitude du commandant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodoku no Saihai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161197" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一緒ノ約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Promised Together</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Issho no Yakusoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161198" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未明ノ欠心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vacant Heart of Morning Gray</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mimei no Ketsu Kokoro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161199" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">思ヒ残シノオト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sounds of Regret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omohi Nokoshi no Oto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161200" update="2014-07-08">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">獣ノ咆哮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Roar of the Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kemono no Houkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161624" update="2014-07-28">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛ノ重音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overlapping Sound of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Juuon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161625" update="2014-07-28">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒キ入日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Sunset</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroki Irihi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161626" update="2014-07-28">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">読島ノ真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth of Yomijima</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomijima no Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161627" update="2014-07-28">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無明ノ光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light of the Lightless</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mumyou no Hikari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162412" update="2014-08-26">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">原罪, カコミライ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Original Sin, Past and Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genzai, Kako Mirai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162413" update="2014-08-26">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強ノ証</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Proof of the Strongest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou no Akashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162414" update="2014-08-26">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光, ソシテ光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Light, and Then Light</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikari, Soshite Hikari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162415" update="2014-08-26">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終焉ノ産声ニ君ハ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Will, to the Birth Cry of the End</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuen no Ubugoe ni Kimi wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167414" update="2015-03-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167415" update="2015-03-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212604" recap="true" update="2019-02-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第1部特別総集編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 Special Summary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 1 Tokubetsu Soushuuhen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
