<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10529" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>2015-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shinmai Maou no Testament</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shinmai Maou no Keiyakusha</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新妹魔王の契約者[テスタメント]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Testament of Sister New Devil</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">The Testament of Sister New Devil</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Shinmai Maô no Testament</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">새 여동생 마왕의 계약자</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">新妹魔王的契约者</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11142" type="Sequel">Shinmai Maou no Testament Burst</anime>
<anime id="11000" type="Side Story">Shinmai Maou no Testament: Toujou Basara no Hard Sweet na Nichijou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8660" approval="47" total="50">High School DxD</anime>
<anime id="9015" approval="32" total="36">Hagure Yuusha no Aesthetica</anime>
<anime id="6968" approval="23" total="29">Ichiban Ushiro no Daimaou</anime>
<anime id="11638" approval="16" total="17">Masou Gakuen HxH</anime>
<anime id="9659" approval="9" total="20">Yuusha ni Narenakatta Ore wa Shibushibu Shuushoku o Ketsui Shimashita.</anime>
<anime id="5625" approval="9" total="15">To Love-Ru: Trouble</anime>
<anime id="8879" approval="9" total="10">Dakara Boku wa, H ga Dekinai.</anime>
<anime id="27" approval="3" total="10">Aa! Megami-sama!</anime>
<anime id="9466" approval="1" total="14">Hataraku Maou-sama!</anime>
<anime id="10323" approval="1" total="7">Ore, Twintail ni Narimasu.</anime>
<anime id="7568" approval="1" total="6">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="515975">Holy.. no wonder this is heavily censored.  Some scenes from the BD were totally cut from the broadcast version! (they couldn`t even censor it!)

I was beginning to wonder if I was watching Hentai.  But other than that, a pretty decent shounen/harem with a really likeable cast.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://anime-shinmaimaou.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="38786" type="Animation Work">Production IMS</name>
<name id="15901" type="Character Design">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="30855" type="Original Work">Uesu Tetsuto</name>
<name id="6276" type="Direction">Saitou Hisashi</name>
<name id="3730" type="Series Composition">Yoshioka Takao</name>
<name id="17220" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shen Hong</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="15901" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Yoshihiro</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch70590 [Toujou Basara] is a high school student whose father has suddenly just remarried. His father then departs overseas leaving Basara with two new beautiful step-sisters. Little does he know, his new sisters, http://anidb.net/ch70589 [Mio] and http://anidb.net/ch70588 [Maria] are actually the new Demon Lord and a succubus!? Almost trapped into a life of servitude, Basara forms a reverse contract by accident and ends up becoming Mio`s master! Hijinks ensue as Basara finds himself in one ecchi situation after another. However, Mio`s life is in danger as she is pursued by demons and heroes!
Source: Crunchyroll
Note: Episode 01 premiered at a special event on 21.12.2014. The regular airing started on 08.01.2015.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2041">3.79</permanent>
<temporary count="2059">6.25</temporary>
<review count="3">4.22</review>
</ratings>
<picture>226480.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16252</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23233</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>30464</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anime-shinmaimaou.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Testament_of_Sister_New_Devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>新妹魔王の契約者</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3601</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349974</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17792</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B076FFCCW7</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2143" parentid="2646" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>succubus</name>
<description>A demon who takes the form of a woman to seduce men in dreams to have sexual intercourse. In modern times, a succubus is often depicted as highly attractive, while in the past succubi were depicted as frightening and demonic. Succubi draw energy from men to sustain themselves, often until the victim becomes exhausted or dies. The male counterpart is the incubus.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2725" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-20">
<name>ahegao</name>
<description>A term for the weird face occasionally seen in adult games/anime/manga. Canonically, ahegao has eyes rolled up, mouth open and tongue sticking out. Sometimes also referred to as "fucked silly".</description>
<picurl>175637.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2739" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>brother-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two siblings of opposite sex.</description>
<picurl>210881.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5406" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-02">
<name>submission</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="70588" type="main character in" update="2014-10-10">
<rating votes="128">7.24</rating>
<name>Naruse Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="425" picture="17296.jpg">Fukuhara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70589" type="main character in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="153">6.11</rating>
<name>Naruse Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38232" picture="140073.jpg">Asai Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70590" type="main character in" update="2014-10-10">
<rating votes="99">5.83</rating>
<name>Toujou Basara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70591" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-10">
<rating votes="32">5.58</rating>
<name>Toujou Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70592" type="main character in" update="2014-10-10">
<rating votes="129">6.55</rating>
<name>Nonaka Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34234" picture="228806.jpg">Bridcutt Sarah Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70593" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-12">
<rating votes="132">7.13</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Chisato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71447" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-04">
<rating votes="74">7.18</rating>
<name>Zest</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5641" picture="228630.jpg">Yoshida Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71448" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="4">2.85</rating>
<name>Sakasaki Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71449" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="8">5.89</rating>
<name>Shiba Kyouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71450" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="8">2.19</rating>
<name>Hayase Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71451" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-04">
<rating votes="39">5.94</rating>
<name>Takigawa Yahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71452" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-04">
<rating votes="60">5.18</rating>
<name>Nonaka Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74059" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="11">2.97</rating>
<name>Sakaki Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27341" picture="74876.jpg">Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74060" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="11">2.77</rating>
<name>Aikawa Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10391" picture="38277.jpg">Zougou Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74061" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="8">5.17</rating>
<name>Youshou Basara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9512" picture="35180.jpg">Togashi Misuzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74062" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="3">1.40</rating>
<name>Varga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74063" type="appears in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="2">2.14</rating>
<name>Youshou Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37301" picture="37436.jpg">Kitaoka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74072" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="14">1.59</rating>
<name>Zorugia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3805" picture="125128.jpg">Kazuki Hiroto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74073" type="appears in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="5">3.95</rating>
<name>Mio no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5889" picture="30436.jpg">Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74074" type="appears in" update="2015-03-26">
<rating votes="3">4.95</rating>
<name>Mio no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29964" picture="79254.jpg">Itatori Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74075" type="appears in" update="2015-03-27">
<rating votes="12">6.14</rating>
<name>Lars</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74076" type="appears in" update="2015-12-22">
<rating votes="32">5.57</rating>
<name>Shela</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3133" picture="25830.jpg">Nishihara Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74105" type="appears in" update="2015-03-27">
<rating votes="8">5.87</rating>
<name>Shiro Kamen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74106" type="appears in" update="2015-03-27">
<rating votes="20">5.56</rating>
<name>Leohart</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79030" type="appears in" update="2015-12-22">
<rating votes="5">3.54</rating>
<name>Donoue Shouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12413" picture="41795.jpg">Etou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79036" type="appears in" update="2015-12-22">
<rating votes="8">4.96</rating>
<name>Balfrea</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4270" picture="197671.jpg">Nakagawa Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="165033" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めての主従契約</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Contract Between Servant and Master</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Erster Meister-Diener-Pakt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le premier pacte d`allégeance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Shujuu Keiyaku</title>
<summary>As daughter of the former demon lord, Mio`s foster parents were slain by powerful demons after her life. Still seeking to slay her, Basara reveals himself as a member of the hero clan--an enemy of the demons--and vows to protect Mio as a member of his family.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668459</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165034" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹ができた日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day I Got a Little Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Tag, an dem ich kleine Schwestern bekam</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour où j`ai eu des petites sœurs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto ga Dekita Hi</title>
<summary>Thanks to his father`s sudden remarriage, Toujou Basara finds himself with two beautiful new step-sisters. Their names are Naruse Mio and Maria. Mio wakes him up in the morning, while Maria stands in the kitchen wearing a suggestive outfit...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668413</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165183" update="2017-02-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165184" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみがゼロになるまで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Until Sadness Reaches Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bis deine Traurigkeit gleich null ist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jusqu’à ce que le chagrin disparaisse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi ga Zero ni Naru made</title>
<summary>Basara suffers a deep wound in the battle against the white-masked man after Mio`s power.
Mio regrets getting Basara involved, and challenges the white-masked man to battle on her own. Meanwhile, in order to protect Mio, Basara resolves to use the "forbbiden art" he sealed away after the events of his past. What was the tragedy that visited the hero village and Basara?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668463</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165185" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会と信頼の狭間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion and a Gap in Trust</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zwischen Wiedersehen und Vertrauen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les retrouvailles et le fossé de la confiance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai to Shinrai no Hazama</title>
<summary>Basara`s childhood friend Nonaka Yuuki warns him not to get involved with Naruse Mio any longer. She is a fellow member of the hero clan, and the one charged with observing Mio. She claims that Mio will bring great disaster, but Basara proclaims that he will protect Mio as a girl on his own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668461</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165425" update="2017-02-01">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165671" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">朝の妹の魔王無双</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Little Sister`s Morning Demon Lording</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Unvergleichliche Dämonenschwester am Morgen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une petite sœur reine-démon sans pareille au réveil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asa no Imouto no Maou Musou</title>
<summary>With the battle against the white-masked man settled, they returned to their bawdy daily life. Basara wakes up with his hand groping Maria`s butt, he runs into a naked Mio when he enters the bathroom, and Yuki sneaks into the bath with him. The master-servant pact lying at the heart of everything. Accoring to Takigawa, his classmate and the white-masked man, the pact between Basara and Mio holds another secret. Meanwhile, Basara`s childhood friend Yuki invites him out on a date...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668465</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165761" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走のエロサキュバス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Erotic Succubus Out of Control</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Porno-Sukkubus außer Kontrolle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un succube pervers hors de contrôle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou no Ero Succubus</title>
<summary>Ten days pass since the battle with Takashi and others. Although the battle ended with reconciliation, Yuki returned to the hero`s village. ...or she was supposed to, but when Basara returns home, he finds Yuki in an apron!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668471</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165762" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恩讐の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Depths of Love and Hatred</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Am Ende von Liebe und Hass</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au-delà de l`amour et de la haine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onshuu no Hate ni</title>
<summary>Basara leads Mio to higher peaks as he pursues pleasure with the use of syrup.
With their master-servant pact reaching a new level, they both bring their full might to face the ones trying to eliminate Mio: Takashi and Kurumi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668469</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165763" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">募る思いを抱えて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bearing Growing Emotions</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mit heftiger werdenden Gefühlen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De puissants sentiments</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunoru Omoi o Kakaete</title>
<summary>Basara goes on a date with Yuki. Unaccostomed to the shopping center, When the two of them are overwhelmed by a clerk`s sales talk, Mio stops following to rescue them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668467</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166524" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この夜, このときのために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For This Night, This Moment</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Für jenen Abend, für jenen Moment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pour cette nuit, pour cet instant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Yoru, Kono Toki no Tame ni</title>
<summary>Everyone is trapped inside the body of the demon realm`s most dangerous creature, a beast capable of infinitely multiplying until it swallows the entire world. Dimensionally cut off, the only remaining option for Basara and the others is to completely eliminate this dangerous creature`s vital core.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677879</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166525" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">諜報者[エスピオナージ]...その先にあるもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Espionage... What Lies After</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Spionage... Was danach kommt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Espionnage... ce qui attend au bout de la route</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Espionage... Sono Saki ni Aru Mono</title>
<summary>Strength as a human, the power to rend evil--With the power inherited from his father, Toujou Jin, Basara faces off against Zolgia. Basara is driven by the desire to protect his precious family. That desire gives him strength, and even as Zolgia pushes him to the edge, he rises without breaking. However, even Basara eventually runs out of strength facting that all too powerful might.
His mind in despair, he`s unable to escape from Zolgia`s dominion...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668477</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166526" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀切なる背信</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plaintive Betrayal</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Herzergreifender Vertrauensbruch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une affligeante trahison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aisetsunaru Haishin</title>
<summary>Mio has been captured by Zolgia following Maria`s betrayal. Basara too is captured by Lars and brought to Zolgia`s mansion. Lars` goal is to exchange Basara for Mio. He explains that he`s only doing his duty as Mio`s observer, but negotiations fail, and Zest slays him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668475</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166527" update="2019-12-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">主従の功罪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Merits and Demerits of Master and Servant</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Verdienste und Vergehen von Meister und Diener</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mérites et défauts de l’allégeance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuujuu no Kouzai</title>
<summary>Basara and Yuki begin the ceremony to form their pact. Clad in a bustier and garter belt, Yuki was raring to go for it, but she refused to forge the pact normally, and suffered the same succubus curse as Mio.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668473</identifier>
<identifier>the-testament-of-sister-new-devil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167432" update="2015-05-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168300" update="2015-05-05">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169366" update="2015-09-12">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169367" update="2015-09-12">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171318" update="2015-09-11">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171319" update="2015-09-11">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175319" update="2017-02-03">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1l</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175320" update="2017-02-03">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175321" update="2017-02-03">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175322" update="2017-02-03">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175323" update="2017-02-03">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175324" update="2017-02-03">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175325" update="2016-07-01">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175326" update="2016-07-01">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175327" update="2016-07-01">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175328" update="2016-07-01">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175329" update="2016-07-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175330" update="2016-06-11">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ep 05 Alternative Ending BD Bonus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175331" update="2016-06-11">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ep 02 and 04 Alternative Ending BD Bonus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175332" update="2017-01-06">
<epno type="3">C23</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175334" update="2017-01-06">
<epno type="3">C21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175335" update="2016-04-28">
<epno type="3">C20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175336" update="2017-02-01">
<epno type="3">C19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175337" update="2016-02-17">
<epno type="3">C18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175338" update="2017-02-01">
<epno type="3">C17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175339" update="2016-02-17">
<epno type="3">C16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175340" update="2016-04-28">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175341" update="2016-04-28">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
