<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10537" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-07-11</startdate>
<enddate>2014-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Zankyou no Terror</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Terror in Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Резонанс Ужаса</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Эхо Террора</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Терористичен екот</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Ехото на терора</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">残響のテロル</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Terror in Resonance</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Terror in Tokio</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Terror in Resonance</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Резонансный террор</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Екот на терор</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">东京残响</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">ترور طنین انداز</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4563" approval="28" total="57">Death Note</anime>
<anime id="6238" approval="25" total="34">Higashi no Eden</anime>
<anime id="4472" approval="4" total="6">Night Head Genesis</anime>
<anime id="12653" approval="1" total="10">Inuyashiki</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="473211">In terms of motives, direction and storytelling it really reminded me of Cowboy Bebop. Some people could find it somehow boring and IMHO it would have looked better as a movie but overall — really great series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="499428">I would by far Recommend this, so far it does seem like the best show of the season, it is dark, interesting and has some very interesting characters. This is the only show this month where i so far, are really excited for the next episode. Definitely a Seinen show.
- This recommendation might change to a must see, if the future episodes are just as good as the first couple.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="715072">A linear and compelling story that parallels the current powers that be in a uniquely interpretive manner. The story is extremely symbolic, the animation is stellar and the music is top notch. An absolute must watch for those who prefer a story that is closer to reality than fantasy.  Those who seek fantasy and fanservice will not enjoy this series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="660321">Although I believe the execution to be not all that good and the plot to be rather disappointing, especially in the middle, the art is amazing and the soundtrack is without a doubt the best I`ve ever heard in anime, with my personal favorite being the hauntingly beautiful track [i]von[/i] by Icelandic singer Arnór Dan. I`ve also been a longtime fan of The Morning Benders/POP ETC and hearing them in anime sealed the deal on my love of the OST</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="449083">A unique style of anime, with a very interesting plot that never loses some sense of epicness.
Although very different, it somehow resembles Stein`s Gate.
Originality++</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://terror-in-tokyo.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="805" type="Work">Dentsu</name>
<name id="762" type="Work">Aniplex</name>
<name id="1522" type="Character Design">Nakazawa Kazuto</name>
<name id="129" type="Direction">Watanabe Shin`ichirou</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="31375" type="Animation Work">MAPPA</name>
<name id="129" type="Original Plan">Watanabe Shin`ichirou</name>
<name id="44905" type="Work">Kyouraku Sangyou Holdings</name>
</creators>
<description>In an alternate version of the present, Tokyo has been decimated by a shocking terrorist attack, and the only hint to the identity of the culprit is a bizarre video uploaded to the internet. The police, baffled by this cryptic clue, are powerless to stop the paranoia spreading across the population.
While the world searches for a criminal mastermind to blame for this tragedy, two mysterious children - children who shouldn`t even exist - masterfully carry out their heinous plan. Cursed to walk through this world with the names http://anidb.net/ch65792 [Nine] and http://anidb.net/ch65794 [Twelve], the two combine to form Sphinx, a clandestine entity determine to wake the people from their slumber - and pull the trigger on this world.
Source: Funimation
Note: First two episodes were pre-broadcasted at Japan Expo by the French simulcasting company Wakanim on July 5, 2014. The regular television broadcast started on July 11, 2014.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3688">6.97</permanent>
<temporary count="3703">7.43</temporary>
<review count="3">7.38</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224610.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15974</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23283</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://terror-in-tokyo.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Terror_in_Resonance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>残響のテロル</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3475</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349463</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17354</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>zankyono_terror/</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18512</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4217" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-11">
<name>nightmares</name>
<description>One or more characters in the anime are plagued by bad dreams.
Possible causes: A traumatic experience in the past or induced by an external "presence".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="65792" type="main character in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="28">8.10</rating>
<name>Nine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65793" type="main character in" update="2014-08-25">
<rating votes="31">2.54</rating>
<name>Mishima Lisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65794" type="main character in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="30">5.55</rating>
<name>Twelve</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67926" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-12">
<rating votes="27">1.45</rating>
<name>Five</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67927" type="main character in" update="2014-08-10">
<rating votes="22">8.20</rating>
<name>Shibazaki Kenjirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="144" picture="16904.jpg">Sakuya Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68750" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-21">
<rating votes="7">3.13</rating>
<name>Kurahashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11025" picture="43745.jpg">Tezuka Hideaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68751" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-21">
<rating votes="9">4.63</rating>
<name>Hamura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40589" picture="159114.jpg">Aigasa Keisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68752" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-21">
<rating votes="3">2.05</rating>
<name>Okano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158347.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11054" picture="39865.jpg">Sakamoto Kunpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68753" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-21">
<rating votes="5">3.09</rating>
<name>Kinoshita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158348.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26923" picture="73461.jpg">Kuwahata Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68754" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-21">
<rating votes="6">4.48</rating>
<name>Mukasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>158349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32782" picture="223624.jpg">Kanuka Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69519" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="8">1.32</rating>
<name>Clarence</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40647" picture="159504.jpg">Takahashi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70267" type="appears in" update="2014-09-26">
<rating votes="2">2.44</rating>
<name>Mamiya Shunzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29468" picture="78588.jpg">Moriyama Shuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70268" type="appears in" update="2014-09-26">
<rating votes="2">2.11</rating>
<name>Aoki Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70384" type="appears in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34984" picture="222849.jpg">Ueda Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70385" type="appears in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Fujikawa Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34774" picture="129969.jpg">Obana Kanji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70390" type="appears in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="2">1.84</rating>
<name>Kawai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70391" type="appears in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="2">2.51</rating>
<name>Mobuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162027.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23965" picture="146646.jpg">Satake Uki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70392" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Shimada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70393" type="appears in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="2">2.91</rating>
<name>Shibazaki Tsuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40929" picture="162042.jpg">Kaneta Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="160896" update="2017-10-31">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FALLING</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Falling</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chute</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Падане</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Falling</title>
<summary>In Aomori, Japan, plutonium was stolen from a nuclear fuel reprocessing facility during a snow storm. A perpetrator left the message "VON" at the scene of the crime in red paint. Six months after the event, a mysterious video is posted on social media. Referring to themselves as Sphinx 1 and 2, two masked teenagers claim "Tokyo will be enveloped by darkness after 3:00 p.m. and large sparks will fly, scattered around the Shinjuku area." Despite the video coming to the attention of former detective Shibazaki, he does not initially report it. Nine and Twelve interrupt Lisa Mishima`s classmates as they bully her, then take their place undercover in her school. Lisa withdraws further and begins showing signs of an eating disorder. While at the government office building, she wishes everyone would disappear in frustration. At that moment, the greater Tokyo prefecture loses power and citizens in the building are evacuated without Lisa. Assuming the government office building free of surveillance, Nine and Twelve place stuffed animals containing thermite-based explosives beneath the sprinkler systems of the main building. When Twelve is interrupted by Lisa, he gives her one of their stuffed animal bombs and flees the building. He asks Nine to decide whether they should kill her or keep her alive. Nine`s terse answer is that he will ask her directly. Lisa responds that she does not want to die, sending Twelve to extract her as the building crumbles down. Nine takes a photo of the destruction with his phone. Twelve and Lisa return unharmed, but Nine informs her as a result of her decision to live she has decided become their accomplice. Lisa is left speechless by this.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="160897" update="2017-10-31">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">CALL &amp; RESPONSE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call &amp; Response</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Question-réponse</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Зов и отзив</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Call &amp; Response</title>
<summary>It is revealed that the bombing and subsequent building collapse, despite the large scale of destruction involved, left several with minor injuries, and no fatalities. Lisa returns home from the incident shaken, but her mother (unaware of Lisa`s location during the bombings) breaks down and berates her for ignoring her text messages. During her tirade, she reveals that Lisa`s father has left the family. Nine and Twelve return without Lisa to their residence, to start work on a cellphone bomb. The police force gathers for a comprehensive briefing of the day`s events, where they become aware of the video on social media. Nine and Twelve, aware of this, release a second video with a riddle from Oedipus Rex referring to the location of their next bombsite. After finding what appears to be the answer to the riddle, police move on the suspected location, a DNA laboratory. Shibazaki phones the chief of police, Kurahashi, with alternate interpretation to the riddle, and suggests that the bomb will be in a police district office. After the bomb discharges in the district office instead of the lab, Kurahashi asks for Shibazaki to involve himself in the case. In privacy, Kurahashi reveals the theft of plutonium to Shibazaki, and his suspicion of the connection to the bombers. Lisa follows Twelve on the street, where he reminds her that if she reveals their secret, he will kill her.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161229" update="2014-10-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="20">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BREAK THROUGH</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Break Through</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Découverte capitale</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Пробив</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Break Through</title>
<summary>Nine successfully hacks into the Metropolitan Police Department database in search of something. Twelve goes out to follow Lisa, expressing his concern that her running away from home will jeopardize the mission. Nine sends a fourth video, titled "Time Shock Bomb", where he and Twelve give another riddle related to Oedipus Rex and then state their hopes that their game would be played "without cheating", otherwise a hidden bomb will explode. Using the riddle, Shibazaki finds a website created by Nine and Twelve, which asks for a password related to three maxims inscribed at the temple at Delphi. Realizing that time is running out, the police decide to search an apartment building where Nine was recorded dropping off a suspicious package, although Shibazaki is still intent on solving the riddle. Twelve finds Lisa and tells her to go home, but she refuses, then comments she was stupid for running away before fleeing. Police officers breach the apartment, only to find no bomb and a laptop instead. Time runs out, even though Shibazaki manages to solve the password (his surname). Seconds later, police investigation reports of the attacks are leaked online, drawing a shocked reaction from the public since the reports conclude the perpetrators are always one step ahead of them. Simultaneously, Twelve rescues Lisa from two police officers. While on their way to Nine`s location, Lisa asks Twelve if he is going to destroy the world, to which both laugh; Lisa then comments she hadn`t laughed like that in "a really long time". At Nine`s location, he disapproves of Lisa staying with them, just before she suddenly collapses.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161230" update="2014-10-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SEARCH &amp; DESTROY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Search &amp; Destroy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rechercher &amp; détruire</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Открий и обезвреди</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Search &amp; Destroy</title>
<summary>Shibazaki transfers to the police agency heading the investigation, much to the dissatisfaction of several employees. As he constructs another bomb, Nine deduces from the presence of counter-nuclear terrorism special forces that the police are aware of his and Twelve`s stealing of the plutonium from the Aomori nuclear facility, but intends to confirm his suspicions through another attack. Talking with Kurahashi, Shibazaki learns that one of the men who stole the plutonium worked at the nuclear facility for a short time, and had his identity erased after the incident occurred. Shibazaki then laments to Kurahashi that, as a Hiroshima native, he hated summer due to the fears held by the older townspeople who experienced the town`s atomic bombing during World War II. Nine and Twelve send a third video with another riddle related to Oedipus Rex. Finally unable to bear with her mentally-unstable mother, Lisa runs away from home. Solving the riddle, the police streams a live recording of Shibazaki all over Japan, in which he announces the location of the newest bomb. He then issues a direct challenge to Nine and Twelve before the police is forced to cut off the livestream. Viewing news and surveillance footage and realizing the officers were wearing hazmat suits, Nine realizes the police have definitely connected them to the stolen plutonium. Kurahashi reveals to other officers the reason behind Shibazaki`s demotion, as Shibazaki steps outside the building and comments, "Today`s another hot day."</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161231" update="2014-07-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161232" update="2014-07-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161509" update="2014-10-14">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">My Fair Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Fair Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">My Fair Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Моя прекрасна лейди</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">My Fair Lady</title>
<summary>In the wake of the attempted terminal bombing, the media believes the foiled attack to be the work of Sphinx. The officers who accompanied Shibazaki to Haneda Airport are reprimanded by their boss, who takes them off the case and gives them a three-month suspension, while Shibazaki himself is given a permanent suspension. Shibazaki goes to his daughter Haruka, who is studying physics at a university, and asks her if an average person could construct an atomic bomb from plutonium. She replies that with the right tools and knowledge, it is possible. Using Lisa`s stolen ID, Five tracks her down at Nine and Twelve`s hideout while they are away. She sends her a bomb, but Lisa escapes before it detonates, destroying the entire upper floor. Joined by Nine and Twelve, Lisa flees to an abandoned video arcade that Nine and Twelve arranged to use as an alternate refuge. There, Nine implies that it was Lisa`s fault their initial headquarters was destroyed, which she sadly confirms. Shibazaki investigates on his own, and while at the National Archives of Japan, he learns that a decade ago, the Rising Peace Academy implemented an operation called the "Athena Project", whose goal was to educate gifted children, but he is unable to find further details about it. He visits Ichiro Fujiwaka, a politician, and asks about it, then threatens to expose his son`s illegal activities after not receiving an honest answer. Fujiwaka informs Shibazaki that orphaned children were gathered, with the gifted ones singled out for the Athena Project. Eventually leaving, Shibazaki is joined by another suspended officer, Hamura, who helps him as he follows numerous leads. Lisa later overhears Nine and Twelve arguing about what to do with her and leaves, only to be captured by Five`s men. When she wakes up in Five`s office, Five initially acts friendly towards her by painting her nails, but quickly becomes hostile and tells her that she does not care for the lives of Nine and Twelve. Later, Twelve receives a threatening text message from Five, revealing that Lisa has been taken hostage. Refusing Nine`s pleas to remember their mission, Twelve sets off to try and rescue Lisa.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161510" update="2014-10-14">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DEUCE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deuce</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Égalité</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Реми</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deuce</title>
<summary>Nine and Twelve decide to play along with Five`s chess game. Arriving at the terminal, Shibazaki and the officers see messages being given to Nine and Twelve from Five in regards to the game and learn that the police ordered airport employees to transmit them. They realize that the latest Sphinx video was a fake created by the police, and that it is Sphinx they are communicating with. When they get closer to the bomb`s potential location, Twelve sends in Lisa to create a distraction; after some hesitation, she sets off flares that trigger a fire alarm. Twelve then hacks into the camera system and brings the recordings back by five minutes, allowing Nine to rush to Five`s location without being detected. He confronts Five and holds her at gunpoint with a pistol he brought, demanding to know why she is getting in the way of his and Twelve`s plans. She responds that she wants to settle something with him, then reveals her knowledge of Lisa being an accomplice and that she is being held captive at the bomb`s location. Airport police then arrive and fire at Nine, forcing him away. While fleeing, he briefly passes Shibazaki. Nine regroups with Twelve, who receives a phone call from Lisa describing her and the bomb`s whereabouts: a plane that is on autopilot and headed for a terminal filled with numerous commuters. Realizing there is a way to save both Lisa and the commuters, Nine contacts Shibazaki, convinces him that the latest bomb isn`t Sphinx`s, and instructs him to infiltrate the control tower and take control of the autopilot system. Nine and Twelve rescue Lisa from the plane, while Shibazaki enters the control room and forces one of the operators to divert the plane away from the terminal at gunpoint. The plane explodes without injuring anyone, and Shibazaki spots a masked Nine, who signals him in thanks before leaving. Five manages to escape, and it is revealed that she has Lisa`s school ID. Looking at it, she smiles and says, "I won`t let you get away again."</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161511" update="2014-10-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">READY OR NOT</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ready or Not</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tu es prêt ?</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Готов или не</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ready or Not</title>
<summary>During a comprehensive meeting, the chief announces the involvement of the Federal Bureau of Investigation in the investigation, surprising the other officers. After Nine has a nightmare involving Five, he and Twelve discuss about her, and Nine concludes that Five is continuing a "game" the three played together previously. When Lisa offers to help them, Nine shows her pictures of the aftermath of the subway train bombing and states that this is what they were doing, which shocks her. Kurahashi later recounts to Shibazaki his meeting with the FBI agents, which include Five, whose job is described as a researcher from an American organization called the Nuclear Emergency Support Team. Twelve tells Lisa that he suffers from synesthesia, a condition that allows him to see colors through sound, and describes her voice as being a "pale yellow". Five sends a text containing a riddle to the public, posing as Sphinx; the riddle can only be decoded via Caesar cipher. The answer turns out to be a set of coordinates leading to Haneda Airport`s International Terminal, one of the locations targeted by Nine and Twelve. The police try to respond to the scene, only to be told to stand by on orders from the superintendent general. Knowing that they will be caught by Five while trying to enter the terminal, Nine reluctantly decides to bring Lisa along with them, since she isn`t known to be associated with him and Twelve. Shibazaki and several officers decide to disobey orders and converge on the terminal as well. Upon arriving at the terminal, Nine realizes that Five plans to play a game of chess using the airport as the chessboard.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161512" update="2014-10-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HIDE &amp; SEEK</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hide &amp; Seek</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cache-cache</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">Криеница</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hide &amp; Seek</title>
<summary>Lisa wakes up in Nine and Twelve`s residence, while the two debate on giving her shelter. They then catch her playing around with their devices, and she faints again after learning she nearly blew up the building with one of their newly-made bombs. Nine and Twelve later place the same bomb inside a passenger train. Upon returning home, they find Lisa attempting to cook, and then criticize her food. Twelve later comments to Nine that the food had value despite its taste, since it reminded him of the food at the institution. Nine and Twelve then send another video with another riddle, also saying that an explosion will occur after 8:00 p.m. if the riddle isn`t solved before then. Using clues from the riddle, Shibazaki concludes the newest bomb is on the Shuto Shinjuku Line train. He then explains his discovery of a connection between all of the bombings: certain people connected to the bombsites participated in a seminar run by the Rising Peace Academy, a non-profit organization that promoted interaction between the Japanese government and the people. As the day goes by, there have been no reports of the bomb being recovered, and Nine and Twelve, not wishing to kill people, plan on deactivating it using a cellphone. However, cellphone reception goes out all over the area, preventing them from doing so, forcing them to try and remove it manually. Kurahashi later informs Shibazaki that higher-ranking agents have prevented them from removing the bomb. While trying to pinpoint the train`s location, Nine is horrified when his computer is hacked into, and realizes that he might know the hacker. He then manages to find the train using a second computer and rushes to the station, throwing a smoke bomb to force commuters off the train and cover his tracks. However, one woman still remains, and the bomb explodes as he enters the train to save her. Nine is unhurt, and as he drags the commuter out of the wreckage, he receives a text message saying, "I found you". Shibazaki confronts Kurahashi about the bombing, but he informs him that he had no knowledge of it. They then spot a mysterious woman sitting nearby, whom Nine identifies as Five.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162133" update="2014-10-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">VON</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Von</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Von</title>
<title xml:lang="bg">ВОН</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Von</title>
<summary>Japan goes into a state of panic from Nine`s declaration, and Tokyo`s entire population begins to evacuate. Lisa regroups with a severely injured Twelve, who greets her before collapsing. Citing that Sphinx had killed no one during all of the attacks, Shibazaki assumes the atomic bomb is just part of a message from them. He then calls Haruka and asks her of the existence of the possibility that an atomic bomb can explode without inflicting a single casualty; she replies that it would be possible if it explodes while in the stratosphere, otherwise known as a "high-altitude nuclear explosion". Hamura realizes that Sphinx would be using a balloon to lift the atomic bomb into the air. Finding a security video of a balloon carrying a box into the air, the police realize that Sphinx plans on disabling all of Japan`s electronic devices with an electromagnetic pulse that would result in the atomic explosion, essentially paralyzing the country. They then realize that aircraft would also be disabled, and there are hundreds of passenger flights currently in the air, carrying evacuated citizens. Fighter jets are dispatched to intercept the atomic bomb but are unable to succeed, while Nine goes up a skyscraper as he observes the countdown on his cellphone. Simultaneously, the passenger flights are all grounded, and Twelve regains consciousness. He is asked by Lisa if Nine really was going to destroy the whole world, to which he replies that he and Nine were always alone and were never needed by anyone before. He then thanks Lisa and proclaims that he is glad to have met her, which prompts her to smile seconds before the atomic bomb detonates. Everyone watches the explosion occur before the entire city is plunged into darkness, followed by an aurora, formed by the radiation from the atomic bomb, illuminating the sky.
The following day, Tokyo`s buildings and streets are completely abandoned. Nine heads to the Settlement, where he sets up makeshift grave markers for the children who died from the Athena Project`s experiments, including Five. He is then joined by Twelve and Lisa, and forgives the former for his actions. The three then spend the rest of the day playing around with a ball and listening to music. As night falls, they are approached by Shibazaki, who tells them that if they turn themselves in, then Project Athena will be exposed to the world and will not be ignored by anyone anymore. Minutes later, U.S. helicopters arrive and hold Nine and Twelve at gunpoint, but Nine pulls out a detonator, claiming that it is for another atomic bomb designed by the Japanese government, which is now in a nuclear power plant. Despite the threat, the soldiers shoot and kill Twelve under orders from their superior, who wants to keep the American government`s involvement in the investigation a secret. Shibazaki orders the soldiers to stand down, then negotiates with an outraged Nine, who eventually gives the detonator to him before abruptly experiencing the same headache Five suffered. Before dying, he tells Shibazaki to always remember Sphinx. One year later, it is revealed that Project Athena was exposed to the world, leaving the Japanese government under scrutiny. Lisa and Shibazaki visit the graves of Nine, Twelve, Five, and the other experimented children regularly, and are on a familiar basis with each other. While coming across Shibazaki one day, Lisa tells him what Nine had told her before his death: the meaning of "VON", which is Icelandic for "hope".</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162134" update="2014-10-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HELTER SKELTER</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Helter Skelter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Helter Skelter</title>
<summary>Nine goes to the police headquarters, dons his Sphinx mask, and turns himself in. He refuses to speak to anyone but Shibazaki, but later relents and issues a demand for a press conference at a specific location at 8:00 p.m., or he will activate the atomic bomb prototype. Shibazaki visits Shunzo Mamiya, who confesses that he created the Athena Project as part of a plan to revitalize Japanese national morale following the nation`s defeat at the end of World War II. Five, who has been hospitalized due to her deteriorating health as a consequence of the Athena Project experiments, learns of Nine`s surrender and desperately sets off to try and reach him. When Twelve hears from Lisa that Nine has surrendered, he attempts to forget about Sphinx in his shame for betraying Nine, but Lisa convinces him to help Nine like he helped her. Five`s men pursue the police convoy carrying Nine to the press conference through Shuto Expressway, only to find that the truck is a decoy. Enraged and desperate, Five leaves to pursue Nine herself. Twelve interferes, but Five disables his motorbike before stopping the truck carrying Nine. After killing her assistant for attempting to stop her, Five confronts Nine and confesses that she always wanted to beat him but never could. Knowing that she is dying, Five admits her love for Nine, begs him to live for them both, and gives him a brief kiss before committing suicide by detonating the spilled gasoline from her car. The Japanese airwaves are then hijacked by a prerecorded message from Nine: as his plans for the press conference were disrupted, the countdown for the atomic bomb`s detonation has begun. Declaring that this is the final message from Sphinx, Nine unmasks himself and bids the people of Japan farewell.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162135" update="2014-10-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HIGHS &amp; LOWS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Highs &amp; Lows</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des hauts &amp; des bas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Highs &amp; Lows</title>
<summary>Nine leaves their hideout and heads to retrieve the plutonium he and Twelve have hidden. Meanwhile, Shibazaki and Hamura visit Souta Aoki, the former welfare minister, to find out more about the Athena Project. To their surprise, Aoki tells them everything about it; its connection to the members of Rising Peace Academy; and that Five was the only child to have survived by the end of the experiments within the "Settlement", a location where the orphans were secretly taken to for the purpose of artificially producing Savant syndrome in humans. However, Aoki mentions that two children, Nine and Twelve, managed to escape, then tells Shibazaki that the mastermind behind the Athena Project was in fact Dr. Shunzo Mamiya, the politician who was the reason behind Shibazaki`s demotion. At the same time, while Nine is busy making the bomb, Twelve reaches the amusement park where Lisa is being held captive. As he comes onto the Ferris wheel, he finds Lisa, her body laced with several bombs that immediately activate when the ride begins to run. Twelve comforts her and begins disarming the bombs one by one. Though both seem to realize that he can`t possibly defuse them all in time, Twelve continues while revealing his feelings for Lisa. Moved to tears, she nevertheless tells Twelve to escape and save himself, reminding him that Nine needs him, but Twelve refuses, just before Five calls him and tells him to give her the location of the plutonium in exchange for disarming the bombs on Lisa. She reveals that she knows Nine and Twelve had actually stolen a prototype of an atomic bomb, rather than plutonium, from Aomori. Twelve becomes torn between saving Lisa and covering for Nine, but at the last few seconds, Twelve reluctantly discloses the prototype`s location. Five stops the timer, and along with it, cuts the power to the Ferris wheel, trapping Twelve and Lisa midair. Five immediately mobilizes the Metropolitan Police Department to the school, where Nine has just arrived to retrieve the bomb. Catching a glimpse of them in advance, he manages to take the prototype from the locker and tries to escape. However, he is spotted and Five, suffering from a seemingly worsening headache, immediately orders Nine to be taken down before abruptly fainting.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="174597" update="2016-01-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">メイキング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Making-of</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Making</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
