<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10549" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-09-27</startdate>
<enddate>2015-04-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Suisei no Gargantia: Meguru Kouro, Haruka</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">취성의 가르간티아: 순환하는 항로, 저 멀리</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Suisei no Gargantia OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Gargantia OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">翠星のガルガンティア~めぐる航路, 遥か~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gargantia on the Verdurous Planet: Far Beyond the Voyage</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9556" type="Prequel">Suisei no Gargantia</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://gargantia.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9870" type="Animation Character Design">Tashiro Masako</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="2442" type="Story Composition">Urobuchi Gen</name>
<name id="1496" type="Direction">Murata Kazuya</name>
<name id="9870" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tashiro Masako</name>
<name id="8344" type="Music">Iwashiro Tarou</name>
<name id="2442" type="Original Plan">Urobuchi Gen</name>
<name id="1496" type="Original Plan">Murata Kazuya</name>
</creators>
<description>Six months has passed since the battle with Kugel`s fleet. Fleet that has been released from the tyranny of the machine caliber Striker is about to join the Gargantia fleet, and new people are coming onboard. http://anidb.net/ch65956 [Ledo], while working with salvage team, is gathering information about the old civilization. He seeks answers to questions why the mankind had left the Earth and what were the reasons of strife between human race and Hideous. Ledo had deepened his interest in archeology and explores the history of mankind. Meanwhile, http://anidb.net/ch51233 [Amy] teaches her new messenger recruit, http://anidb.net/ch65957 [Reamer], about her work. Reamer is a member of the original Kugel`s fleet and after its dismantling, she had begun a new life on Gargantia.
Source: Official site</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="707">5.88</permanent>
<temporary count="710">6.94</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>231920.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16335</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23319</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>31113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://gargantia.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gargantia_on_the_Verdurous_Planet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>翠星のガルガンティア</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3725</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348783</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>348782</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17619</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gargantia-on-the-verdurous-planet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19565</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18831</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3097" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-29">
<name>underwater</name>
<description>Underwater is a term describing the realm below the surface of water where the water exists in a natural feature such as an ocean, sea, lake, pond, or river.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5284" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-22">
<name>ocean world</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="51227" type="appears in" update="2016-02-06">
<rating votes="59">7.58</rating>
<name>Ledo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ledo is a Second Lieutenant in the Galactic Alliance of Humankind. His combat skills are great, but he grew up knowing nothing other than war. As a result, he`s not very good at expressing his emotions, and often misunderstood. During combat he`s swallowed by a rift in space-time and castaway to the remote planet, Earth, where he`s rescued from cold sleep by Gargantia. In the midst of an unknown environment and a language he doesn`t understand, he starts communicating with the people of Gargantia in order to survive, and slowly he begins to have a change of heart. He`s 16.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>129289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51228" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-04">
<rating votes="67">5.67</rating>
<name>Bellows</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bellows runs a salvage operation focused on recovering artifacts of old civilization from the sea. She`s the one who discovered http://anidb.net/ch51227 [Led] and http://anidb.net/ch51232 [Chamber] at the bottom of the ocean and pulled them up. She excels at operating the heavy labor robot, Yunboro. She`s a caring older sister figure who`s strict when it comes to work, and her comrades all have great faith in her. She`s 18.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>129291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51229" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-09">
<rating votes="44">4.50</rating>
<name>Ridget</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ridget is Gargantia Fleet Commander http://anidb.net/ch52528 [Farelock]`s second-in-command. She`s calm, diligent, logical, and holds a strong sense of responsibility.
Following Farelock`s death, she takes over as Fleet Commander.</description>
<picture>129292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51230" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-10">
<rating votes="41">5.15</rating>
<name>Melty</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Melty`s another messenger like http://anidb.net/ch51233 [Amy] and http://anidb.net/ch51234 [Saya]. She`s younger than the other two, and she still looks young, so she`s trying to stretch herself. She likes handsome men and tales of romance, but she`s never been in love. Her mischievous grin is one of her notable traits. She`s 14.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>129294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51231" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-04">
<rating votes="30">2.39</rating>
<name>Pinion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pinion is a young man who handles maintenance and repairs on Gargantia. He gets carried away easily, but everyone trusts his knowledge and skills when it comes to machinery. He dreams of making it rich one day by dragging treasure up out of the sea. He`s 20.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>129295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51232" type="appears in" update="2014-11-07">
<rating votes="99">9.05</rating>
<name>Chamber</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Chamber is the Machine Caliber that http://anidb.net/ch51227 [Ledo] pilots. It comes equipped with a Pilot Support and Development Interface System, charged with training its pilots to become excellent soldiers via communication and capable of taking autonomous action, and is an important companion to Ledo.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>129296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51233" type="main character in" update="2013-05-25">
<rating votes="72">6.49</rating>
<name>Amy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amy is a young messenger aboard Gargantia. She`s active, filled with curiosity, and she always has a smile on her face. Once she meets http://anidb.net/ch51227 [Led] after he wakes from cold sleep, she grows very interested in him, and volunteers to be his guide on Gargantia. She treasures her younger brother http://anidb.net/ch52759 [Bevel]. She`s 15.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>129290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51234" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-10">
<rating votes="40">5.18</rating>
<name>Saaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saya is a messenger, just like http://anidb.net/ch51233 [Amy]. She`s friends with http://anidb.net/ch51230 [Melty], and the three are always together. She`s bit laid back, but tight when it comes to money. Both men and women admire her glamorous figure. She`s 15.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>129293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52366" type="appears in" update="2013-04-04">
<name>Sensui Yunboro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A Yunboro model used by salvage operations to haul materials up from the bottom of the sea. It`s design features many rounded edges to help withstand water pressure.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>131279.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="52526" type="appears in" update="2013-04-04">
<name>Chuugata Yunboro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>This Yunboro is often employed in battle due to its ease of use, and it`s possible to attach armor plating to the front of its frame. It comes equipped with small guns for Yunboro use and a needle gun that fires sharp metal rods.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>131641.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="52528" type="appears in" update="2013-04-04">
<rating votes="9">3.38</rating>
<name>Farelock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Farelock is the captain who commands the Gargantia Fleet. He`s well experienced, and always stays calm. He puts the safety of his fleet above all else.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>131633.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11025" picture="43745.jpg">Tezuka Hideaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52530" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-04">
<rating votes="3">6.03</rating>
<name>Joe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joe is a young welder who specializes in creating and severing the attachments that join the ships together. He`s a true craftsman who`s strict about his work.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>131635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5978" picture="170983.jpg">Hayashi Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52759" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="16">5.65</rating>
<name>Bebel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amy`s little brother with an illness that compromises his health, thus he is usually bedridden, and only moves by a wheelchair. He befriends Ledo, who treats him as a younger brother.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>132980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="25450.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53333" type="appears in" update="2013-03-02">
<rating votes="3">2.78</rating>
<name>Warm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53334" type="appears in" update="2013-03-02">
<rating votes="8">2.75</rating>
<name>Flange</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="562" picture="17888.jpg">Tsuda Eizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53335" type="appears in" update="2013-03-02">
<rating votes="12">4.91</rating>
<name>Mayta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53336" type="appears in" update="2013-03-02">
<rating votes="4">2.33</rating>
<name>Crown</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2067" picture="186243.jpg">Hoshino Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54560" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-01">
<rating votes="11">5.66</rating>
<name>Oldham</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54561" type="appears in" update="2013-04-01">
<rating votes="3">5.03</rating>
<name>Oldham no Joshu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134565.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54562" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-25">
<rating votes="15">7.11</rating>
<name>Rackage</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54563" type="appears in" update="2013-04-01">
<rating votes="6">4.65</rating>
<name>Paraem</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54564" type="appears in" update="2013-04-01">
<rating votes="6">5.09</rating>
<name>Parinuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54909" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-10">
<rating votes="14">4.77</rating>
<name>Grace</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135066.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54992" type="appears in" update="2013-04-14">
<name>Shuuri Fune Senshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20336" picture="212609.jpg">Machida Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55255" type="appears in" update="2013-04-22">
<name>Marocchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135668.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55443" type="appears in" update="2013-04-28">
<name>Oyakata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2339" picture="151715.jpg">Taketora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55621" type="appears in" update="2013-05-06">
<name>Okama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136294.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55746" type="appears in" update="2013-05-11">
<name>Rackage Yunboro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>136526.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55792" type="appears in" update="2013-05-13">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Ryoushi Guild Chou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57260" type="appears in" update="2013-06-17">
<rating votes="2">2.32</rating>
<name>Herick</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138654.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57609" type="appears in" update="2013-07-01">
<rating votes="2">4.85</rating>
<name>Isabella Artlyal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Crew member of Gargantia fleet.
Note: One of 12 winners of original character design pixiv contest. The character appeared in anime`s final episode. Author of the design: Ryuuzaki Ichi (竜崎いち).</description>
<picture>139360.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57942" type="appears in" update="2013-07-18">
<rating votes="4">5.04</rating>
<name>Kuraria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1961" picture="222838.jpg">Yonezawa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57943" type="appears in" update="2013-07-18">
<rating votes="4">5.04</rating>
<name>Onderia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65956" type="main character in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="6">8.60</rating>
<name>Ledo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65957" type="main character in" update="2014-06-19">
<rating votes="7">4.70</rating>
<name>Reamer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156895.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71293" type="appears in" update="2014-11-11">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Fleiss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saya`s older brother.</description>
<picture>163950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71294" type="appears in" update="2014-11-11">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Bellows no Nakama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bellows` colleague.</description>
<picture>163951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71295" type="appears in" update="2016-02-06">
<name>Muzzle</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>182291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77505" type="appears in" update="2015-09-21">
<name>Ryuuguujou Shunou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dragon`s Palace Leader.</description>
<picture>177682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12464" picture="42188.jpg">Miyazawa Kiyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="160553" update="2014-11-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2014-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792122</identifier>
<identifier>gargantia-on-the-verdurous-planet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161035" update="2015-03-31">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2015-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792123</identifier>
<identifier>gargantia-on-the-verdurous-planet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169207" recap="true" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2014-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぷちっとふりかえりんてぃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Li`l Recapantia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Petit Furikaerintia</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
