<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10548" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-25</startdate>
<enddate>2014-11-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kuroshitsuji: Book of Murder</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">黒執事 Book of Murder</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Black Butler: Book of Murder</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">خادم سیاه: کتاب قتل</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11696" type="Sequel">Kuroshitsuji: Book of the Atlantic</anime>
<anime id="10402" type="Prequel">Kuroshitsuji: Book of Circus</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="815148">A fun little OVA but don`t watch without watching the first season and Book of Circus as it contains spoilers for the latter in particular. It`s a murder-mystery in the Phantomhive manor and it`s just loads of fun watching all the regulars try and solve the mysteries with some eccentric house guests to make things even funner. It can be a bit cheesy but if you`re a fan of the series, you`ll probably love it even more for that.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kuroshitsuji.tv/bom/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2459" type="Character Design">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="4250" type="Series Composition">Yoshino Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="8740" type="Original Work">Toboso Yana</name>
<name id="4566" type="Direction">Abe Noriyuki</name>
<name id="2459" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="15228" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawaguchi Chisato</name>
<name id="20907" type="Music">Mitsuda Yasunori</name>
</creators>
<description>At the Queen`s behest, young master http://anidb.net/ch11141 [Ciel Phantomhive] hosts a lavish banquet to be attended by the crème-de-la-crème of London`s elite. However, what begins as a fabulous affair quickly takes a dark turn when guests begin turning up dead. Should http://anidb.net/ch11140 [Sebastian] and Ciel wish to once more see the light of day, they must join forces with their guests, including the legendary author Sir Arthur Conan Doyle, to unravel the mystery and apprehend the murderer before it`s too late.
Source: Funimation</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="474">7.57</permanent>
<temporary count="480">7.57</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224674.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16031</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23317</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kuroshitsuji.tv/bom/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Black_Butler</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>黒執事_Book_of_Murder</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>350526</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>349707</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17764</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kuroshitsuji2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19582</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>19431</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01FNAS094</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2686" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>Victorian period</name>
<description>The Victorian era of British history was the period of Queen Victoria`s reign from 20 June 1837 until her death on 22 January 1901. The Victorian Era style of clothing, however, ended in 1912. It was a long period of peace, prosperity, refined sensibilities and national self-confidence for Britain. Some scholars date the beginning of the period in terms of sensibilities and political concerns to the passage of the Reform Act 1832.
A famous era for old classic literature works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11140" type="main character in" update="2014-07-12">
<rating votes="267">8.08</rating>
<name>Sebastian Michaelis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sebastian appears to be a youthful male with red-orange eyes and dark brown hair (black in the anime). He is typically dressed in a distinguished outfit consisting of black trousers, tailcoat, vest, tie and shoes with a white botton-down shirt. He wears white gloves that cover up the sign of his Faustian contract with Ciel Phantomhive, which is on his left hand. When they are off, it is shown that he has black fingernails, although it is unknown if this is their natural colour. He frequently carries a pocket watch as well. When in tutor mode, he also wears glasses, although it`s unknown if he actually needs them or not. He slightly resembles Ciel`s father, and has had his attractiveness commented on before.
Sebastian`s demonic form has never fully been shown. Details including high-heeled boots, longer fingernails, slitted pupils and sharper, longer teeth are all that have been revealed. In the anime, he has the ability to transform into a crow, although this has never been said or implied in the manga.
Source: kuroshitsuji.wikia.com</description>
<picture>157980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11141" type="main character in" update="2017-12-31">
<rating votes="109">7.16</rating>
<name>Ciel Phantomhive</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ciel is a young male, whose age is from 12 to 13 throughout the series, with blue eyes and black hair. As the head of the noble Phantomhive family, he typically dresses in a way that suits his standing, including a long jacket, button-down shirt, tie, shorts, knee-high socks and boots. Occasionally, he carries other accessories such as a top hat, white or black gloves and a cane. He also has his ears pierced and frequently wears a one-of-a kind family ring that has been passed down through his family for generations. He nearly always wears an eye patch over his left eye, not because he is missing it, but because that`s where the sign of his Faustian contract with Sebastian Michaelis is hidden.
Occasionally, he wears other outfits, typically because he is undercover, investigating something at Queen Victoria`s request. These outfits have included a dress, when he invaded Aleister Chamber`s home, and pauper`s clothes, when he posed as a servant when joining the Noah`s Ark Circus.
Source: kuroshitsuji.wikia.com</description>
<picture>33143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11143" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="51">8.26</rating>
<name>Undertaker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Undertaker has long, grey hair with a few braids throughout, which is worn so as to hide his eyes. He has a noticeable scar across his face, although how he acquired it is unknown, and has long, black fingernails. He also wears all black, including an incredibly long, black top hat, and a he wears a long, grey scarf across his chest, with it knotted by his hips.
Source: kuroshitsuji.wikia.com</description>
<picture>198167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18402" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="28">5.44</rating>
<name>Baldroy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baldroy, usually referred to as Bard, is the household cook of American descent. Bard gruffly treats everything as though it`s a military exercise, often referring to troops, enemies, and weaponry when he goes off into one of his many long-winded speeches about what it truly means to appreciate the culinary arts. He rarely produces anything edible as he uses weaponry such as a series of flamethrowers, each more extravagant than the last to cook and believes cooking is an art requiring explosions. Sebastian believes anything he creates is made up of charcoal and carcinogens. It`s unknown if the food he produces is actually edible.</description>
<picture>168999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18403" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="17">4.75</rating>
<name>Finnian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Finnian, often called Finny, is the Phantomhive household gardener. However, it seems every time he tends to the garden, it is killed through an accident caused by his clumsiness and overenthusiastic pruning or not noticing that the pesticide container is leaking. In fact, if left to his own devices, he`s stated that he`d like to make the garden into the shape of a giant robot.</description>
<picture>168997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18404" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="40">6.94</rating>
<name>Mey Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maylene is a clumsy maid whose cracked glasses do nothing to improve her clumsiness. However, she refuses to purchase a new pair as they are the first thing Ciel bought for her. Sebastian believes her main problem is her intelligence and not her poor eyesight. She has a crush on Sebastian as blushes when ever she is in his presence and is even clumsier when Sebastian is watching. In the anime she fantasizes about being close to him in episode 1. She is rather superstitious but admits to having a soft spot for scary stories. Maylene used to be a sniper who did not use a scope, due to her sharp far-sighted vision caused by her ill-fitting glasses. She is also physically fit as she can use a sniper rifle like a hand gun and keeps hundreds loaded at once to decrease reload time. At the anime`s conclusion, it is unknown whether she is alive or dead, although it is noted she was breathing before she collapsed.</description>
<picture>168998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18405" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-03">
<rating votes="13">7.50</rating>
<name>Tanaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tanaka is the house steward who has served under the former Master Phantomhive. He was present when Ciel`s parents were killed and was stabbed in the back during the incident and as a result, rarely does any work or even talking. Sebastian seems to respect him the most out of all the staff. He is usually seen drinking from a Japanese tea cup. Despite his appearance, Tanaka is capable of killing intruders. Prior to Sebastian`s appointment as Ciel`s butler, Tanaka served as the head butler of the Phantomhive household, for both Ciel`s father and Ciel; when Sebastian is apparently murdered, Ciel appoints Tanaka as the head butler again. In the anime, he is commonly in a super deformed form. When he is not, he is as capable a servant as Sebastian. As the series progresses, he is seen less often in a super deformed form.</description>
<picture>49018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18661" picture="49054.jpg">Fujimura Shunji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18408" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-16">
<rating votes="21">4.95</rating>
<name>Lau</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lau is a Chinese noble, President of the British Branch of a Chinese trading company, and friend to the Phantomhive family. He is also part of the Shanghai Mafia and runs an opium den. He is always smiling and his eyes are always closed except for brief moments in episodes fifteen and twenty. Lau often agrees to things before learning what is happening and jumps into conversations with helpful information only to later state he has no idea. He is also unaware his antics appear strange to others. However, he can be very coldblooded and cryptic and is willing to go further than Ciel would, such as having Lord West and his wife killed because he knew they`d try to cheat again. He is often seen with his personal assassin Ran-Mao, a Chinese, doll-like girl referred to as his sister, although not by blood. Although she very rarely speaks and is portrayed as emotionless, she is very loyal to him. In the anime adaption, Lau and Ran-mao are defeated by Ciel and Sebastian after they use the Earl`s company to store and sell Lady Blanc opium in the guise of candy. Lau and Ran-mao then throw themselves into the River Thames.</description>
<picture>49022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18409" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="12">8.31</rating>
<name>Soma Asman Kadar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Prince Soma Asman Kadar is a sixteen-year-old Indian prince. Unlike Ciel, he is spoiled and uses his parent`s fortune for his personal needs and blames all of his problems on others. He bestowed his affections on Meena, a beautiful maidservant who had served at his palace in India since his birth. He saw her as an older sister. However, she came to hate him due to his arrogance and ran away to England with Lord Harold West, a trader in Indian goods, wanting to be a rich wife, rather than an ordinary cook bound to her social class. During the course of his time in England, Soma begins to see things in a different perspective, realizing that he is blaming problems he caused on others. After learning Meena hated him for his ignorance, Prince Soma decided to stay with Ciel and learn how to act as a gentleman and even proclaims to be Ciel`s best friend. He does not know that Meena and Lord West were both killed by Ranmao on Lau`s orders after they lost the curry contest and were planning to try again. Shortly after, Ciel has him and Agni manage his property in London, in order to keep them out of his way.</description>
<picture>63632.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18410" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="13">6.33</rating>
<name>Agni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Agni is the servant of Prince Soma, whom he sees and worships as a god. Agni was once a nobleman named Arshad (in Indonesia: Arsyad) who used his powers and wealth for his own desires to the point that he was to be hanged for his crimes. Before he was to die, Prince Soma offered him a new life with the death of his old self. He is able to fight on a par with Sebastian while using a fencing foil, a feat which briefly makes Ciel wonder if he is a demon until Sebastian confirms he is a human. The source of his martial prowess comes from his devotion to Prince Soma. Unlike Sebastian, however, he is able to see the good in the Phantomhive manor staff and assign them tasks where their skills will be of use. He is known as the "Right Hand of God" for his god-like skill at making curry. He betrays Prince Soma and becomes the chef for a curry contest for Lord West to keep him from revealing to Soma that Meena ran away from and hated the prince. Later, Agni reconciles with the prince. He is staying in the Phantomhive manor to learn to become a better servant from Sebastian`s example, and even calls Sebastian his friend, something that surprises Sebastian as no one has ever referred to him as such before. Sebastian also takes Agni`s advice on taking care of Ciel, much to the younger boy`s annoyance.</description>
<picture>63631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18411" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-31">
<rating votes="48">5.44</rating>
<name>Elizabeth Midford</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elizabeth Midford is the daughter of Marchioness Frances Midford and is both Ciel`s cousin and fiancée. She is a very happy and upbeat girl. She has known Ciel for a long time and cares deeply for him, trying her best to see him smile again. Elizabeth would always tell Ciel to call her "Lizzy". She also loves cute things. Ciel sees her as an important friend and a girl that he needs to protect because he says that he does not want to lose anything important again. It has been shown a few times on how much Ciel cares for her, such as throwing himself in front of her to protect her from a bear in the manga, how he tried his best to save Elizabeth from Drocell, and also drying her tears after she broke his ring despite how upset he had been.</description>
<picture>198166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18421" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-17">
<rating votes="27">7.52</rating>
<name>Ran-Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Lau`s girls from his opium den. He introduces her to Ciel and company as "his little sister, though not by blood." Ranmao almost never speaks and seems entirely unflappable. But she`s not as harmless as she looks...</description>
<picture>49035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65844" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-12">
<rating votes="3">7.36</rating>
<name>Snake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67237" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="7">6.09</rating>
<name>Charles Grey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67238" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="5">6.16</rating>
<name>Charles Phips</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67239" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-11">
<name>Peter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="84" picture="16692.jpg">Tai Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68602" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="2">7.04</rating>
<name>Arthur</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="161263" update="2015-02-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2014-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161264" update="2015-03-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>2014-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
