<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1055" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>1991-11-22</startdate>
<enddate>1993-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Koko wa Green Wood</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Here Is Green Wood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kokowa Greenwood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Koko wa Greenwood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kokowa Green Wood</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Green Wood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Greenwood</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ここはグリーン・ウッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Here Is Greenwood</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8367" approval="5" total="9">Kimi to Boku.</anime>
<anime id="10288" approval="3" total="4">Bokura wa Minna Kawai-sou</anime>
<anime id="9153" approval="2" total="3">Sakura-sou no Pet na Kanojo</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.jvcmusic.co.jp/m-serve/ova/greenwood/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1906" type="Financial Production">Victor Ongaku Kangyou</name>
<name id="988" type="Financial Production">Hakusensha</name>
<name id="8234" type="Music">Nagata Shigeru</name>
<name id="5091" type="Character Design">Gotou Masako</name>
<name id="500" type="Direction">Mochizuki Tomomi</name>
<name id="8204" type="Original Work">Nasu Yukie</name>
<name id="724" type="Animation Work">Studio Pierrot</name>
</creators>
<description>Meet http://anidb.net/ch10097 [Hasukawa Kazuya] - he`s just a regular teenager who wants to live a normal, peaceful life. But when his first love marries his older brother and moves into their house, Kazuya decides that he has to move out to preserve his sanity! Things go from bad to worse when he discovers he`s been assigned to the strangest dorm on campus - an asylum called Greenwood - where all the weirdos, outcasts and lunatics at the prestigous Ryokuto Academy reside. Experience life at Greenwood, where nothing is ever as it seems, especially the people. Can Kazuya and his classmates survive the insanity?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="469">5.95</permanent>
<temporary count="473">6.97</temporary>
<review count="2">7.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>90538.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>504</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1804</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>205</identifier>
<identifier>cdmghg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jvcmusic.co.jp/m-serve/ova/greenwood/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Here_is_Greenwood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ここはグリーン・ウッド</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88541</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2040</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/799</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1894" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-04">
<name>shota</name>
<description>Shotacon, sometimes shortened to shota, is a Japanese slang portmanteau of the phrase Shoutarou complex and describes an attraction to young boys, or an individual with such an attraction. Outside Japan, the term is less common and most often refers to a genre of manga and anime wherein pre-pubescent or pubescent male characters are depicted in a suggestive or erotic manner.
In a general sense, this is the same as http://anidb.net/t2566 [loli], just replace young girls with young boys.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>35399.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2671" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>school dormitory</name>
<description>A school dormitory or residence hall is the student living quarters at an elite academy, boarding school, or military school. The main characters may live or work at the dormitory, and it often becomes the backdrop for a reoccurring part of the story.</description>
<picurl>223167.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5872" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>bad luck</name>
<description>You are living a blessed life far from any troubles. Your sister is a famous reporter, you have a good looking girlfriend and you excel in your studies aiming to be a scientist. Your future is looking bright. But reality is, fate hates you. Your sister is killed, your girlfriend breaks up with you after being crippled in a terrorist attack and finally you end up as a pizza delivery boy.
And just when you thought it can`t get worse, it does. Your former girlfriend turns into a Darth Vader knock-off, tries to impose her world view on others by force and is out there to kill you. Yes, your life does truly suck.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10097" type="main character in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<name>Hasukawa Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hasukawa is an orphan. He was raised by his older brother, Kazuhiro, who also attended Ryokuto Gakuen. As a child, Hasukawa idolized his brother and wanted to enroll at Ryokuto to be more like him.
At the start of the series, we see him enrolling into the school, realizing his dream, but he is very late due to a series of freak accidents.
Sadly, all of the personality traits Kazuya prized in his brother (drive, determination, and ambition) have seemingly disappeared. To make matters worse, Hiro has just married Kazuya`s first love, Sumire-chan!
Unable to live in the same house as the now-frivolous Hiro and his bride, Kazuya moves into the dorms. Little does he know what terrors await him there!</description>
<picture>30398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10098" type="main character in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shun is Kazuya`s easygoing roommate. Although Kisaragi resembles a cute, tomboyish girl, he`s actually a guy. Shun is the oldest son of the Kisaragi family, who run a chain of traditional Japanese inns. The females in the Kisaragi family inherit the company, but it has no connection with Shun`s girlish figure. In fact, Shun is heterosexual; he likes girls, and when he was a junior high school student, he went together with a girl. Shun is very self-confident and proud of his beautiful long hair, and he knows he is so cute. Because he thinks it is the best way to be cool, he does not hesitate to dress like a girl. He can makes sound decisions and is a man of action, and no character believes that Shun is actually feminine.
Shun has a younger brother named Reina and an infant sister named Yui. ~From Wikipedia</description>
<picture>30399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10099" type="main character in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<name>Ikeda Mitsuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mitsuru is the eldest son of the Ikeda family and heir to the Kouryu Temple in Uguisudani. He is also adopted, having been found abandoned outside the temple on the day his brother, Masato, was born.
Although he lives close enough to Ryokuto Academy to easily commute, Mitsuru has chosen to live in the dorms to distance himself from his family.
There are rumors that Mitsuru was a member of a gang in junior high, but they are unconfirmed.
Mitsuru is the dorm head of Greenwood in his second year.</description>
<picture>30400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10100" type="main character in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<name>Tezuka Shinobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinobu is the youngest child of a wealthy samurai family from Nagano. His oldest brother, Akira, has been missing for 3 years, and his sister, Nagisa, is psychotic. Shinobu`s parents are distant, at best.
Needless to say, Shinobu is not close to his family and he entered the dorms with the primary goal of getting away.
Shinobu is Student Council President in his second year and roommate to Ikeda Mitsuru.
He is friends with Noriko, a morose painter who was once in love with his brother -- and who may have transferred her affections to Shinobu.</description>
<picture>30401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10101" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<name>Otoko A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nameless men in dark suits and sunglasses who do the dirty work of She-who-must-be-obeyed. They aren`t terribly good at whatever it is they do.</description>
<picture>30403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3291" picture="24306.jpg">Takemura Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10103" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-01">
<name>Tezuka Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The middle child of the Tezuka family, Nagisa has been ignored a little too long. She is, in a word, psychotic.
A beautiful woman with wavy black hair and blue eyes, Nagisa dresses and behaves like a rich gangster. She even employs nameless henchmen, dresses them in in black suits and sunglasses, and drives around in a Mercedes.
Nagisa is consumed by the desire for revenge on Shinobu for injustices perpetrated on her as a child. Unfortunately, this revenge seems to inconvenience Shinobu`s friends far more than it does him.</description>
<picture>30406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10105" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<name>Otoko D</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nameless men in dark suits and sunglasses who do the dirty work of She-who-must-be-obeyed. They aren`t terribly good at whatever it is they do.</description>
<picture>30410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10106" type="appears in" update="2009-07-04">
<name>Otoko C</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nameless men in dark suits and sunglasses who do the dirty work of She-who-must-be-obeyed. They aren`t terribly good at whatever it is they do.</description>
<picture>30555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10107" type="appears in" update="2009-07-01">
<name>Otoko B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nameless men in dark suits and sunglasses who do the dirty work of She-who-must-be-obeyed. They aren`t terribly good at whatever it is they do.</description>
<picture>30408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10108" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Hasukawa Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiro`s wife and Kazuya`s sister-in-law, Sumire is a violet-haired beauty with a happy personality.
Sumire is blissfully unaware that Kazuya is in love with her, which makes her attempts to mother him all the more horrifying for the poor guy. She often embraces Kazuya, which either causes him to have a nosebleed or renders him catatonic.
Sumire and Hiro met each other in college, where he was her sempai. (Hiro was in third year when she entered college). Sumire was Kazuya`s English tutor during his third year of middle school (At the time she was in her fourth year in college, majoring in English culture).
Her tutoring helped Kazuya pass the Ryokuto entrance examination. Sumire played the Queen in the "Here is Devilwood" movie.</description>
<picture>30412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10133" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-02">
<name>Hasukawa Kazuhiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Blond and grey-eyed, Kazuhiro resembles Mitsuru more than he does his younger brother, Kazuya.
Orphaned while still in high school, Kazuhiro was forced to raise Kazuya by himself. At the time, he took this responsibility very seriously, but now that Kazuya is grown, Hiro has allowed himself to return to his former easy-going personality (much to his brother`s chagrin).
To add insult to injury, Hiro has married Kazuya`s first love, Sumire-chan. He also takes perverse pleasure in teasing the heck out of his brother because "His reactions are so cute!".
Kazuhiro works at Ryokuto Academy as the school nurse. As such he has to deal with the disappointment of the various boys who come through the infirmary expecting a female nurse.
Kazuhiro also graduated from Ryokuto Academy. He has a fairly friendly relationship with Mitsuru and Shinobu which dates back to their first year. (Both of them wound up unconscious in the infirmary within the first four weeks of their arrival! Not at the same time, though).
Although Hiro gives Kazuya a hard time, he really does love his brother.</description>
<picture>30471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10134" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-02">
<name>Koizumi Tenma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tenma lives across from Igarashi Miya. He has looked after her since they were children, as her mother is often away on business. He is indirectly responsible for Igarashi`s delinquent tendencies.
Tenma seems nice on the outside, but is actually quite possessive of Miya.</description>
<picture>30473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10135" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-02">
<rating votes="2">6.33</rating>
<name>Igarashi Miya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A second year from Suminohana Girl`s School, Igarashi is Mitsuru`s kouhai from his junior high school days.
Igarashi cultivates a "tough" exterior, referring to herself as "ore." ("Ore," meaning "I/me," is a pronoun properly used only by men and usually only in the company of other men! Shinobu uses the less rough pronoun "boku" in mixed company and Shun uses "boku" all the time).
Igarashi`s quirk gets her into trouble and only the gang of four can help her.</description>
<picture>30474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10136" type="appears in" update="2009-07-02">
<name>Tochizawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tochizawa dreams of becoming a movie director, and both wrote and directed the school festival video "Here is Devilwood" in OAV 3.</description>
<picture>30475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10138" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Misako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sixteen year old Misako died before ever receiving her first kiss. Unable to move on to her next existence without resolving her past loves and regrets, she decides to haunt Mitsuru.
Her final wish is to possess Shinobu`s body and use it to kiss Mitsuru!
Her sobs are about a 7.0 on the Richter scale, luckily her range is fairly short.</description>
<picture>30477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10145" type="appears in" update="2009-07-02">
<name>Furusawa Shin`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Furusawa is a muscular giant. He lives with his motorcycle in his room, which means that when he wants to ride it, he has to carry it down (and later up) the stairs. This often leads to him putting his foot through the floor.
Furusawa was the Dorm Head the year Mitsuru and Shinobu were first years.
He has a girlfriend, Kawasumiya Yuuko, for whom he works part time.</description>
<picture>30484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10147" type="appears in" update="2009-07-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kawasumi Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Furusawa`s love interest. He has a part time job at at her family`s market.
Yuuko has a cameo in "Here is Devilwood" as the "ferryman`s wife" opposite Furusawa in OAV 3.
Mitsuru`s advice helped them get together, so he has to tease Furusawa about her in the anime. Yuuko`s birthday is Valentine`s Day.</description>
<picture>30486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10148" type="appears in" update="2009-07-02">
<name>Watanabe Yoshiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Watanabe is a small, delicate boy with brown hair and green eyes and he is shy and retiring.
When he first met his roommate, Fujikake, on a Tokyo train, Fujikake mistook him for a cute girl! Unlike Shun, Watanabe is unhappy with his girlish looks and hopes to become more manly.
He`s the boy who goes to the infirmary for "a small cut". Watanabe is from Hokkaido.</description>
<picture>30489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8" picture="171393.jpg">Ikura Kazue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10149" type="appears in" update="2009-07-02">
<name>Ryokurin Ryou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Greenwood, or Ryokurin Ryou, is an all-boys dorm at the prestigious private high school, Ryokuto Academy.</description>
</character>
<character id="10150" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-02">
<name>Kisaragi Reina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shun`s 13-year old brother. Reina has pale lavender hair and pink eyes. He also looks like a girl. Reina idolizes Shun.</description>
<picture>30492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2792" picture="26717.jpg">Kawata Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10151" type="appears in" update="2009-07-02">
<name>Ikeda Masato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Black haired and blue eyed like his mother, Sho is younger than Mitsuru by approximately two weeks. Although technically the "true Ikeda," Sho is content to be the second son and cede inheritance of Kouryu Temple to Mitsuru.
He obviously loves his brother and is hurt by Mitsuru`s choice to move out of the house. He appears in both the anime (OAV 6) and manga. In manga volume 10, Sho`s grandfather asks him: "Do you really hate the idea of becoming a monk that much?" to which he replies "I don`t hate it.".
We also find out that Sho failed the Ryokuto entrance exam.</description>
<picture>30494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10176" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-04">
<name>Ryoubo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A solidly built, forty to fifty-something year old woman who acts as the dorm manager and chaperon. She is adamant about keeping girls out of the dorm and can cuss like a sailor. Has a son who lives away from home.</description>
<picture>30557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5073" picture="33047.jpg">Sasaki Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="13943" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汝の日常を愛せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Here is Greenwood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanji no Nichijou o Ai seyo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13944" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園祭出品作"ここは魔王の森"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Here is Devilwood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuensai Shuppin Saku "Koko wa Maou no Mori"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13945" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1993-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君を好きでよかった (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suka-chan`s Second Love: I`m So Glad That I Fell in Love with You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi o Suki de Yokatta (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13946" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1992-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渚狂走曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nagisa Strikes Back!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagisa Kyousoukyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13947" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1992-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光流とゴースト~緑林寮の幻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Phantom of Greenwood</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsuru to Ghost: Ryokurin Ryou no Maboroshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13948" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>1993-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君を好きでよかった (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suka-chan`s Second Love, Part II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi o Suki de Yokatta (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
