<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10553" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-07-06</startdate>
<enddate>2014-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Space Dandy 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Космический Денди 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">스페이스 댄디 2</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Космическото конте 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">宇宙浪子 第二季</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スペース☆ダンディ 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Space Dandy Season 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10027" type="Prequel">Space Dandy</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="23" approval="4" total="10">Cowboy Bebop</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="354949">Like `impressive` said, easy going and smooth... its dandy baby. Enjoy</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://space-dandy.com/top.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="755" type="Original Work">Bones</name>
<name id="7788" type="Character Design">Itou Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="9862" type="Direction">Natsume Shingo</name>
<name id="129" type="Chief Direction">Watanabe Shin`ichirou</name>
<name id="7788" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="4567" type="Music">Nanba Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="21590" type="Music">Taku Takahashi</name>
<name id="38993" type="Music">Space Dandy Band</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch59014 [Dandy] is a space hunter, someone who is paid to search for new, undiscovered alien species. It`s an industry where the prize goes to the person who finds aliens the fastest. Dandy searches unknown planets for strange beings with his companions, http://anidb.net/ch59015 [QT] the worn-out robot and http://anidb.net/ch59016 [Meow] from Betelgeuse. Meanwhile, they`re being chased by minions of the Gogol Empire, for reasons that are still a mystery.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1109">7.60</permanent>
<temporary count="1114">7.53</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>157140.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16029</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30246</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>23327</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://space-dandy.com/top.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3443</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349540</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16580</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00NAKH08W</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="12068" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="45">9.32</rating>
<name>Yamato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>After the defeat of the Earth`s space fleet by the Gamilas Empire in the year 2199, the inhabitants of Earth secretly convert the ruins of the Japanese battleship Yamato into a massive spaceship, the Space Battleship Yamato. Using blueprints they attain from Queen Starsha of the planet Iscandar, they equip their new ship with a space warp drive, called the "wave motion engine", and a new, incredibly powerful weapon called the "wave motion gun" which fires from the bow.</description>
<picture>36555.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="59014" type="main character in" update="2014-01-11">
<rating votes="45">7.62</rating>
<name>Dandy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character who is an easygoing man working as an alien hunter whose job is to locate and apprehend rare specimens of creatures across the galaxy. He is the captain of the Aloha Oe, his personal spaceship. His life mission is to visit all the intergalactic locations of a restaurant known as ``Boobies`` and indulge in his posterior fetish as well as someday buying out the chain.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>146484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59015" type="main character in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="24">7.20</rating>
<name>QT</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dandy`s other partner and a proud robot that resembles (and also works as) a vacuum cleaner. QT`s software is out of date, just like most of the other devices on Dandy`s ship. As such, QT is prone to memory shorts and battery outages.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>141668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23965" picture="146646.jpg">Satake Uki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59016" type="main character in" update="2014-01-11">
<rating votes="26">6.12</rating>
<name>Meow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Dandy`s partners, he is a dimwit cat-like alien from the Betelgeuse star, whose alien breed is named after the star. Like Dandy, he enjoys ogling the girls at "Boobies" and is never seen without his touch screen phone. His name, "Meow", was given to him by Dandy since neither he nor QT could understand his real name.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>141669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60754" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-15">
<rating votes="8">1.78</rating>
<name>Perry Teitoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The ruler of the Gogol Empire, which is currently at war with the Jaicro Empire for control of the universe. He has sent Dr. Gel to capture Dandy, claiming he is the key to the future of the universe.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>159728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60755" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-11">
<rating votes="11">5.14</rating>
<name>Gel Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brilliant scientist, working for the Gogol Empire, that pursues Dandy for yet unknown reasons. His face and overall design makes him appear more like a gorilla than a human. However, he could be a primate-like alien. He wears an eye piece over his left eye, shaped like a "G".
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144770.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60756" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-11">
<rating votes="9">3.16</rating>
<name>Bee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Gel`s right handed assistant. He is very diminutive compared to Dr. Gel.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21734" picture="63348.jpg">Hatakeyama Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60757" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-11">
<rating votes="30">8.21</rating>
<name>Honey</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A beautiful blonde haired and blockhead waitress who works at the "Boobies" restaurant that Dandy usually frequents.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10129" picture="37440.jpg">Yurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60758" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-11">
<rating votes="28">7.65</rating>
<name>Scarlett</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A beautiful inspector at the space alien registration center who oversees Dandy`s work.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>144778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69496" type="appears in" update="2014-08-17">
<rating votes="3">4.58</rating>
<name>Johnny</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Commander-in-Chief of the Jaicro Empire, and aspiring rock star.</description>
<picture>62098.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95573" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Pine-Pine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95574" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Rose Reginald</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95575" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Professor Duran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2143" picture="178043.jpg">Kayumi Iemasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95576" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="2">2.84</rating>
<name>Erssime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54088" picture="239586.jpg">Kobayashi Seiran</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95577" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Dolph</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95578" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>L`Delise</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>[b][/b]</description>
<picture>217616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95579" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Sofia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="83" picture="38901.jpg">Nanri Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95580" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Poe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95581" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ferdinand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95582" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Freckles</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="161022" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">転校生はダンディじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Transfer Student Is Dandy, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le nouvel élève, c`est Dandy, baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkousei wa Dandy Jan yo</title>
<summary>In order to capture a rare alien species, Dandy goes undercover at a glamorous high school where popularity is determined by your ability to sing and dance!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161023" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">急がば回るのがオレじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Slow and Steady Wins the Race, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rien ne sert de courir, il faut partir à point, baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isogabamawaru no ga Ore Jan yo</title>
<summary>Thanks to a nifty, handheld teleportation device, Dandy and Meow get mixed up with a fishy little alien whose planet is teetering on the brink of obliteration!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161024" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇には闇の音色があるじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s Music in the Darkness, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Il y a de la musique dans les ténèbres, baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami ni wa Yami no Neiro ga Aru Jan yo</title>
<summary>After a big fight with QT and Meow, Dandy is lured to the distant planet of an extremely rare, ukulele-playing alien that wants to turn him into a statue – and steal his smile forever!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161025" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オンリーワンになれないじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Be the Only One, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne peux pas être le seul, baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Only One ni Narenai Jan yo</title>
<summary>There’s a Dandy in every universe, and Space Dandy is about to meet them all! He just needs to pull the nearest Cosmic String, and he’ll find himself face-to-face with himself. Talk about trippy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161421" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しみのない世界じゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A World with No Sadness, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi no Nai Sekai Jan yo</title>
<summary>When an unfortunate encounter with a dark nebula maroons Dandy on a mysterious planet populated by bizarre beings, the legendary bounty hunter scrambles to find his ticket out of limbo!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161422" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロックンロール★ダンディじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rock `n` Roll Dandy, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rock `n` Roll Dandy Jan yo</title>
<summary>Dandy and a new friend decide to start a legendary rock group, but it’s hard to write a hit song when you can`t stop arguing over band names and t-shirt designs!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161423" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の紳士はジェントルマンじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gallant Space Gentleman, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Shinshi wa Gentleman Jan yo</title>
<summary>When Dr. Gel kidnaps his favorite Boobies girl, Dandy joins forces with a suave and sophisticated alien in a dashing attempt to save the day and collect a big bounty!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="161424" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビッグフィッシュはでっかいじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Big Fish Is Huge, Baby!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le big fish est énorme, baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Big Fish wa Dekkai Jan yo</title>
<summary>Dandy and the gang take up fishing in the hopes of capturing an extremely rare alien fish with a massive bounty, but to land this prized catch, they`re gonna need a  bigger boat!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162117" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裁かれるのはダンディじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dandy`s Day in Court, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabakareru no wa Dandy Jan yo</title>
<summary>A seemingly-harmless trip to Boobies ends with Dandy on trial for the murder of a very rare alien. When his friends are called to testify, the situation goes from bad – to worse!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162118" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">次元の違う話じゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Other-Dimensional Tale, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigen no Chigau Hanashi Jan yo</title>
<summary>Dandy must confront a painful memory from his past when a four-dimensional ex-girlfriend shows up looking for help avoiding the bounty hunter’s two-dimensional former rival!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162119" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋人たちはトレンディじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lovers Are Trendy, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koibito-tachi wa Trendy Jan yo</title>
<summary>Dandy’s dead broke, so he agrees to pose as Scarlett’s boyfriend in exchange for some cold hard cash. Does true love stand a chance when you’re paying your date?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162120" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">同じバカなら踊らにゃ損じゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re All Fools, So Let`s All Dance, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onaji Baka nara Odoranya Son Jan yo</title>
<summary>Dandy and his crew head to Planet Grease for a legendary party, only to find themselves walking the streets of a ghost town. Luckily, Dandy’s got the booty that launched a thousand dance parties!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162601" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネバーエンディングダンディじゃんよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Never-ending Dandy, Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Never-ending Dandy Jan yo</title>
<summary>Dr. Gel finally captures Dandy, which sparks an ultra-destructive space war that could end the universe. Meanwhile, Honey and Scarlet team up with QT and Meow to save their favorite bounty hunter!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="168163" update="2015-04-24">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-01-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Space Dandy 2nd Season Picture Drama 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168164" update="2015-04-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Space Dandy 2nd Season Picture Drama 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168165" update="2015-04-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2014-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Space Dandy 2nd Season Picture Drama 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
