<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10565" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-26</startdate>
<enddate>2014-04-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Minami no Shima no Dera-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dera-chan of the Southern Island</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">南の島のデラちゃん</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10326" type="Other">Tamako Love Story</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tamakolovestory.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="736" type="Animation Work">Kyoto Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>After talking bird http://anidb.net/ch51224 [Dera Mochimazzi]`s extended stay in the Usagiyama Shopping District, eating way too much mochi (rice cake), the day came when he had to return to southern islands, for a more gentle daily live with Prince http://anidb.net/ch51674 [Mecha] and http://anidb.net/ch51675 [Choi].
Note: Double-billed in the cinemas with http://anidb.net/a10326 [Tamako Love Story] movie.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="325">3.32</permanent>
<temporary count="326">5.58</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>228790.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23399</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tamakolovestory.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tamako_Market</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>たまこまーけっと#.E5.8A.87.E5.A0.B4.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348728</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/5232</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19255</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2406" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-13">
<name>talking animal</name>
<description>Talking animals are a common theme in mythology and folk tales, as well as children`s literature. Fictional talking creatures often are anthropomorphic, possessing human-like qualities but appearing as a creature. An animal that only knows how to say its name (for example, 99.9% of all http://anidb.net/t2493 [Pokemon]), are not talking animals.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3968" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>animal protagonist</name>
<description>The anime revolves around an animal, usually only communicating with typical onomatopoeia. The animal mostly lives in a human family and has adventures on a regular base. This can be the discovery of a new room, or being lost by having taken a wrong turn in the outside world.
Typical example: http://anidb.net/a5801 [Chii`s Sweet Home].
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t4259 [animal world], where the whole world is composed of animals.</description>
<picurl>10255.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="50996" type="appears in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="78">7.13</rating>
<name>Kitashirakawa Tamako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129117.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51111" type="appears in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="56">7.32</rating>
<name>Makino Kanna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129116.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51112" type="appears in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="48">4.66</rating>
<name>Tokiwa Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129115.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51137" type="appears in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="36">7.20</rating>
<name>Kitashirakawa Anko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129280.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51139" type="appears in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="41">6.02</rating>
<name>Asagiri Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129282.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51224" type="main character in" update="2013-01-09">
<rating votes="55">5.05</rating>
<name>Dera Mochimazzi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51278" type="appears in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="15">6.36</rating>
<name>Kitashirakawa Mamedai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129369.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51279" type="appears in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="10">4.88</rating>
<name>Kitashirakawa Fuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129368.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51482" type="appears in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Shiraki Tadanao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129804.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51483" type="appears in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Shimizu Tomio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129803.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51484" type="appears in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="3">6.80</rating>
<name>Uotani Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129806.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51485" type="appears in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Uotani Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129807.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51487" type="appears in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Mitsumura Fumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129802.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51488" type="appears in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Yumoto Chouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129809.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51490" type="appears in" update="2012-12-22">
<rating votes="5">6.57</rating>
<name>Hanase Kaoru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>129801.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51674" type="main character in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="17">1.86</rating>
<name>Mecha Mochimazzi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Trivia: His name sounds like something along the lines of "the Mochi taste very bad" to the ears of the Japanese around him. Especially Tamako`s father http://anidb.net/ch51278 [Mamedai] is visibly shaken whenever he hears the full name.</description>
<picture>130010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51675" type="main character in" update="2014-11-24">
<rating votes="35">3.87</rating>
<name>Choi Mochimazzi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Trivia: Her name sounds like something along the lines of "the Mochi taste a little bad" to the ears of the Japanese around her. Especially Tamako`s father http://anidb.net/ch51278 [Mamedai] is visibly shaken whenever he hears the full name.</description>
<picture>130009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9405" picture="228517.jpg">Yamaoka Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="158609" update="2017-12-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2014-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
