<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10589" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2014-12-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ookami Shoujo to Kuro Ouji</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">オオカミ少女と黒王子</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Wolf Girl &amp; Black Prince</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">狼少女与黑王子</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10919" type="Sequel">Ookami Shoujo to Kuro Ouji: Gishin`anki - Happiness Kiss</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9903" approval="6" total="16">Nisekoi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="413731">I was really surprised at this series, I was not expecting much of it. As I watched it I was dragged into it and ended up finishing it in one sitting. The characters were in perfect balance with each other and the story progressed very well. I have to say this is a must see for people who enjoy romantic comedies.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="348650">A run of the mill romance comedy. The animation is WAY below average, with barely any animation movement going on. Most of the time it`s mouth moving only, bodies never showing feet as they walk, or simple sliding of images together to make the viewer think there`s "animation". Also, there`s lots of talking in still pictures. Nice!

The story is below average, but I am a sucker for this kind so I was stuck watching it till the end.

The comedy was really strong, but at least the romance wasn`t over the top.

If you like a show where a woman lowers herself to the floor for a guy, then go for this, you`ll enjoy it.

If looking for a better romance comedy watch Tonari no kaibutsu kun</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ookamishojo-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="23325" type="Music">Sakabe Gou</name>
<name id="7768" type="Character Design">Fujioka Maki</name>
<name id="19716" type="Series Composition">Hirabayashi Sawako</name>
<name id="654" type="Direction">Kasai Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="7768" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujioka Maki</name>
<name id="19268" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yasuda Takahiro</name>
<name id="9212" type="Animation Work">TYO Animations</name>
<name id="47872" type="Original Work">Hatta Ayuko</name>
</creators>
<description>The story centers around http://anidb.net/ch66317 [Shinohara Erika], a vain 16-year-old girl who tells her friends about her romantic exploits, but she actually has no boyfriend. She claims that a handsome boy in a candid photo is her boyfriend, but it turns out that boy is a schoolmate named http://anidb.net/ch66312 [Sata Kyouya]. She has no choice but to make him her fake boyfriend. Unfortunately, Sata may look like a sweet person, but he is actually an ultra-black-hearted sadist. Sata takes advantage of Erika`s weakness and treats her like his dog.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1175">4.93</permanent>
<temporary count="1177">6.60</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>160610.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16158</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>29129</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>23673</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://vap.co.jp/ookamishojo-anime/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ōkami_Shōjo_to_Kuro_Ōji</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>オオカミ少女と黒王子</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3531</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349706</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17563</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3129" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-13">
<name>fake relationship</name>
<description>A relationship where characters just play the boyfriend and girlfriend roles.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="66311" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<rating votes="10">7.07</rating>
<name>Sanda Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66312" type="main character in" update="2015-10-06">
<rating votes="12">3.87</rating>
<name>Sata Kyouya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="42" picture="155105.jpg">Hayamizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66313" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<rating votes="7">4.15</rating>
<name>Tezuka Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66314" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<rating votes="6">4.72</rating>
<name>Hibiya Takeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66315" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="6">2.65</rating>
<name>Kamiya Nozomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66316" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<rating votes="5">3.84</rating>
<name>Tachibana Marin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66317" type="main character in" update="2014-12-08">
<rating votes="23">4.57</rating>
<name>Shinohara Erika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66318" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="4">3.68</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66319" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="4">2.45</rating>
<name>Kimura Yoshito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69887" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-22">
<rating votes="3">8.46</rating>
<name>Sata Reika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sata Reika is Kyouya`s older sister.</description>
<picture>166308.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69888" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-22">
<rating votes="3">6.42</rating>
<name>Sata Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyouya`s mother.</description>
<picture>166307.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70829" type="appears in" update="2014-11-04">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Erika Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Erika`s mother.</description>
<picture>163642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70830" type="appears in" update="2014-10-22">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kenta no Kainushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The owner of Kenta.</description>
<picture>163090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39685" picture="152297.jpg">Komatsu Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71137" type="appears in" update="2014-11-04">
<rating votes="2">2.51</rating>
<name>Erika Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Erika`s father.</description>
<picture>163643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34608" picture="171027.jpg">Date Tadanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71656" type="appears in" update="2014-11-26">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kitamura-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71657" type="appears in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Yajima Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41766" picture="242448.jpg">Kitou Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71826" type="appears in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="578" picture="193571.jpg">Tatsumi Yuiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71827" type="appears in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="2">2.51</rating>
<name>Kojima Atsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38324" picture="140893.jpg">Nakata Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71828" type="appears in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165286.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71829" type="appears in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Takii Yuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10130" picture="151714.jpg">Takumi Yasuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71830" type="appears in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Miho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71831" type="appears in" update="2014-12-01">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38903" picture="239362.jpg">Uchimura Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72148" type="appears in" update="2014-12-22">
<rating votes="2">2.51</rating>
<name>Chii Mama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2488" picture="186147.jpg">Matsuda Ken`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="163008" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">日々悶々 -Love attack-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Daily Anguish: Love Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jours tourmentés, Love Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hibi Monmon: Love Attack</title>
<summary>Dismayed when Kyoya refuses to respond to her confession of love, Erika goes to all kinds of strange lengths to change her image to appeal to him more.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662127</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163009" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">急転直下 -Fall in-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Precipitous Drop: Fall In</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Changement de situation, Fall In</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuutenchokka: Fall In</title>
<summary>Unhappy with her sadistic fake boyfriend, Erika sets out to find a real one.  But when she finds the perfect man, he might be just too good to be true.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662125</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163010" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">軽挙妄動 -First love-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Rash and Blind Act: First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Comportement spontané, premier amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keikyomoudou: First Love</title>
<summary>Unhappy with her sadistic fake boyfriend, Erika sets out to find a real one.  But when she finds the perfect man, he might be just too good to be true.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662123</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163011" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自縄自縛 -liar-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Caught in Her Own Trap: Liar</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La menteuse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jijoujibaku: Liar</title>
<summary>Erika is so obsessed with appearances that she lies to her friends and pretends she has a boyfriend.  She even goes so far as to take a picture of a stranger to claim that`s him!  Unfortunately, he`s a student in her school . . . and he has a nasty sense of humor.  If she doesn`t want him to spill the beans, the "girl who cried wolf" now has to pretend to be his dog.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662121</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163106" update="2014-10-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163107" update="2014-10-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163684" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二律背反 -Spring storm-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Self-Contradiction: Spring Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Antinomie, Spring Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niritsuhaihan: Spring Storm</title>
<summary>Erika and Kyoya go out on their first proper date, and she wants to do all of the typical couple things.  He thinks they`re stupid, and refuses.  But perhaps he might be showing his first hints of compromising...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662135</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163685" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">落花流水 -White day-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mutual Love: White Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rupture, White Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakkaryuusui: White Day</title>
<summary>Erika tries as hard as she can to fall in love with Kusakabe.  But her heart belongs to Kyoya, no matter what.  If only the two can have mutual feelings.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662133</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163686" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">臨戦態勢 -Valentine day-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preparing for Battle: Valentine Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Prêt à combattre, Valentine Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rinsentaisei: Valentine Day</title>
<summary>Erika decides to make chocolate for Kyoya for Valentine`s Day.  A quiet boy in their class, Kusakabe, starts to fall for Erika, but she just can`t think of anyone but Kyoya.  Meanwhile, Kyoya`s jealousy brings out his nastiest side yet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662131</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163687" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">難攻不落 -Christmas eve-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Impregnable Defense: Christmas Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Forteresse imprenable, Christmas Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nankoufuraku: Christmas Eve</title>
<summary>In this episode, Erika wants to spend Christmas with Kyoya to keep up her image, but she really wants it to be romantic, too.  He hates Christmas, so he plays a nasty trick on her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662129</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164179" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛及屋鳥 -I love you-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Pressing Appeal: I Love You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un amour infini, I Love You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aikyuu Okuu: I Love You</title>
<summary>Erika and Kyoya have gone off to Kobe to visit Kyoya`s mother.  He claims he has no abandonment issues, but she`s beginning to suspect he might be lying.  Can she get him and his mother back together again?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662143</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164180" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一触即発 -Judgement-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Critical Situation: Judgement</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Situation explosive, le jugement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isshokusokuhatsu: Judgement</title>
<summary>Kyoya`s older sister comes to visit, and she`s just like Kyoya -- only worse!  When she decides to challenge Erika, can Erika hold up to her scrutiny?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662141</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164181" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">掉棒打星 -Happy birthday-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wasted Effort: Happy Birthday</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Peine perdue, Happy Birthday</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touboudasei: Happy Birthday</title>
<summary>The new boy in their class, Kamiya, is determined to make Kyoya abandon monogamy.  He thinks the only path to happiness is having loads of girlfriends and cheating on them all.  As you might expect, Kyoya is unresponsive about this.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662139</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164182" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">手練手管 -Wake up-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Honeyed Words: Wake Up</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Manipulation, Wake Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Terentekuda: Wake Up</title>
<summary>The new boy in their class, Kamiya, is determined to make Kyoya abandon monogamy.  He thinks the only path to happiness is having loads of girlfriends and cheating on them all.  As you might expect, Kyoya is unresponsive about this.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>662137</identifier>
<identifier>wolf-girl-and-black-prince</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200231" recap="true" update="2018-05-23">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">総集編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushuuhen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
