<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10594" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-06-27</startdate>
<enddate>2014-11-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Konna ni Yasashiku Sareta no</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">I Have Been Treated Nicely</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">이렇게 부드럽게 풀어져 버렸...</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">こんなに優しくされたの</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.mediabank.co.jp/mediabank/product?page=product&amp;model=QNB-M001</url>
<creators>
<name id="40111" type="Original Work">Kishizuka Kenji</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="143">3.15</permanent>
<temporary count="145">5.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>160643.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.mediabank.co.jp/product.php?model=QNB-M001</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.mediabank.co.jp/product.php?model=QNB-M003</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.mediabank.co.jp/product.php?model=QNB-M005</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2491" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-09">
<name>nurse</name>
<description>For hentai shows, it`s enough if a http://anidb.net/t884 [nurse costume] is worn without the female character actually working as a nurse.
For ecchi shows, the nurse profession must play a big enough part in the overall setting.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
<picurl>160445.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2696" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-13">
<name>threesome</name>
<description>Tag for any scene where sexual acts take place with three people of any gender. Should not be used if more than three.</description>
<picurl>150774.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2705" parentid="2848" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>creampie</name>
<description>The act of a man ejaculating inside a girl`s vagina, leaving the semen oozing out of her.</description>
<picurl>160720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2707" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-20">
<name>internal shots</name>
<description>Internal shots are pictures that display the interior of the body of a living being, either through the skin, kind of as an "x-ray" of sorts, or from the inside, as if the camera was also inside. This is generally used during sex scenes to display the inside of any area being penetrated. Those shots may happen either by making an area of the body transparent or by displaying the same area again, but from the inside; the latter method is shown in the picture.</description>
<picurl>213307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2709" parentid="4656" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-30">
<name>netorare</name>
<description>Netorare is what happens when the protagonist gets his wife/girlfriend stolen from him by someone else. It is a sexual fetish designed to cause sexual jealousy by way of having the heroine indulge in sexual activity with someone other than the protagonist.
The intent or reason causing the scenario does not have any bearing as to whether the scenario is netorare or netori; perspective is the only differentiating factor.
Netorare is generally caused by, but not limited to: the stealing party has malicious intent to harm the protagonist, or the wife/girlfriend hopes to improve their relationship by causing the protagonist to be jealous.
Netorare Type A
The heroine is willingly cheating on the protagonist with another guy, and enjoys every second of it. No rape, blackmail, drugs etc. involved; it`s consensual sex from the very beginning.
Netorare Type B
Initially, the heroine is raped, blackmailed, drugged, or otherwise tricked to have sex with someone other than the protagonist. However, she eventually starts enjoying it, and the sex becomes fully consensual in the end.
Netorare Type C
The heroine is raped in front of the protagonist, and he can only helplessly watch it. It`s non-consensual from start to finish.
Note: Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2716 [Netori].</description>
<picurl>150946.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2722" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>doggy style</name>
<description>Bang her from behind and use her boobies as a steering wheel!</description>
<picurl>161394.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2724" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>double penetration</name>
<description>Double penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by two penises or strap-ons.</description>
<picurl>172771.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2731" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>sex while on the phone</name>
<description>Girl gets banged while talking to another person on the phone (usually her boyfriend or husband in a NTR scenario).</description>
<picurl>161353.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2739" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>brother-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two siblings of opposite sex.</description>
<picurl>210881.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2890" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>foot fetish</name>
<description>Anime contains scenes which revolve around foot-fetishism.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2892" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>housewives</name>
<description>A housewife is a mature woman (should be out of high school age) who doesn`t necessarily have to be married in our context, but typically is. A housewife doesn`t work (depending on context, she would be an Office Lady instead), however, since we`re not as much down to technical details as we are of visuals, that restriction can be discarded if the character in question is shown mostly in home environment wearing leisure time clothing or a kimono and an apron can also be safely added to the bunch.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2911" parentid="2890" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>footjob</name>
<description>A foot is used to invoke sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3027" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-10">
<name>sex tape</name>
<description>A sex tape is a camera recording of sexual acts, regardless of the actual storage medium. Such recordings are sometimes made against the will or even knowledge of the depicted persons.
While most of them are made solely for personal use, a sex tape may be released (or threatened to be released) to damage the reputation of the depicted, to blackmail them or merely to make a profit.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4656" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-06">
<name>infidelity</name>
<description>Infidelity is a violation of a couple`s assumed or stated contract regarding emotional and/or sexual exclusivity, sometimes according to the subjective feeling that one`s partner has violated a set of rules or relationship norms; this violation results in feelings of sexual jealousy and rivalry. What constitutes an act of infidelity is dependent upon the exclusivity expectations within the relationship. In marital relationships, exclusivity expectations are commonly assumed although they are not always met. When they are not met, research has found that psychological damage can occur, including feelings of rage and betrayal, lowering of sexual and personal confidence, and damage to self-image.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5750" parentid="2724" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>triple penetration</name>
<description>Triple penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by a minimum of three penises or strap-ons. Usually, this means one oral penetration, one vaginal penetration, and one anal penetration. Triple penetration happens most often during http://anidb.net/t2719 [gang bang] and particularly http://anidb.net/t4492 [gang rape] scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6573" parentid="2696" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-13">
<name>MMF threesome</name>
<description>A threesome with two male and one female partner.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="68005" type="main character in" update="2014-06-17">
<rating votes="4">6.51</rating>
<name>Yoshino Ayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16797" picture="156378.jpg">Ueda Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68006" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-17">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Hiromi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40379" picture="230207.jpg">Yumeno Botan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68007" type="main character in" update="2014-06-17">
<rating votes="4">7.09</rating>
<name>Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37114" picture="93006.jpg">Suzune Kagetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70913" type="appears in" update="2015-10-26">
<name>Nakai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178886.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40379" picture="230207.jpg">Yumeno Botan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70914" type="appears in" update="2015-10-26">
<name>Kyaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41148" picture="228600.jpg">Kojirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70915" type="appears in" update="2015-10-26">
<name>Yamaguchi-senpai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41149">Ibukijima Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70916" type="appears in" update="2015-10-26">
<name>Oyakata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41148" picture="228600.jpg">Kojirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75958" type="main character in" update="2015-10-26">
<rating votes="2">2.69</rating>
<name>Fujita Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16006" picture="75317.jpg">Kasuga An</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75959" type="appears in" update="2015-10-26">
<name>Isha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4825" picture="216007.jpg">Kojirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75960" type="appears in" update="2015-10-26">
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<name>Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16006" picture="75317.jpg">Kasuga An</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75961" type="main character in" update="2015-10-26">
<rating votes="2">3.44</rating>
<name>Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34882" picture="156285.jpg">Yukimura Toa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75962" type="main character in" update="2019-08-23">
<rating votes="1">2.27</rating>
<name>Ishii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178884.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41149">Ibukijima Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78029" type="main character in" update="2015-10-26">
<rating votes="2">3.44</rating>
<name>Kurata Chie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16111" picture="47259.jpg">Sugihara Matsuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78036" type="main character in" update="2015-10-26">
<rating votes="2">3.44</rating>
<name>Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29462" picture="188133.jpg">Haruna Ren</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="159205" update="2014-04-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2014-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スイート・ドリームス / 女将さん妄想中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Pour My Heart Into This / The Chief Hostess` Fantasy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sweet Dreams / Okami-san Mousou Chuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160382" update="2014-06-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2014-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">由衣の社 / Hospital is happy</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui`s Shrine / Hospital Is Happy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yui no Yashiro / Hospital Is Happy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162542" update="2014-09-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2014-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Adoration / 僕の知らない母</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adoration / The Mother I`ve Never Known</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Adoration / Boku no Shiranai Haha</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
