<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10619" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2014-12-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Denki-gai no Hon`ya-san</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Denki-Gai no Honya-san</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">デンキ街の本屋さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Denki-Gai</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">전자상가의 서점 아가씨</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">电器街的漫画店</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5071" approval="9" total="10">Doujin Work</anime>
<anime id="10542" approval="2" total="8">Gekkan Shoujo Nozaki-kun</anime>
<anime id="6780" approval="2" total="5">Working!!</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://umanohone.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3724" type="Series Composition">Fudeyasu Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="11552" type="Character Design">Kuniyuki Yurie</name>
<name id="11552" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kuniyuki Yurie</name>
<name id="2336" type="Music">Takaki Hiroshi</name>
<name id="38902" type="Original Work">Mizu Asato</name>
<name id="1284" type="Animation Work">Shin-Ei Animation</name>
<name id="15769" type="Direction">Satou Masafumi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch68403 [Umio] works part-time at BOOKS Umanohone, a manga shop deep in a certain denki-gai neighbourhood, along with his senior at work (but not in age) http://anidb.net/ch68398 [Hiotan]. As many dedicated manga fans visit the store, there is always something going on.
Source: ANN
Note: Denki-gai or "Electric Town" is a popular name for shopping areas that specialize or used to specialize in electric and electronic items, like Tokyo`s Akihabara.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1114">5.13</permanent>
<temporary count="1118">6.57</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>159793.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16137</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>24031</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://umanohone.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://umanohone.us/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Denkigai_no_Honya-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>デンキ街の本屋さん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3511</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349180</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17565</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="389" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>crybaby</name>
<description>Someone whose feelings are very easily hurt, often by trivial matters.</description>
<picurl>162105.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2520" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>school swimsuit</name>
<description>A school swimsuit (also known as sukumizu, shorthand for school mizugi) is a standardised navy blue one-piece swimsuit worn by schoolgirls. Typically they also have a name tag on the front. Sukumizu can also be black or white.
Normally worn at schools though sometimes also worn at beaches when the character feels this to be easier, forgot to buy a normal swimsuit of their own or wants to give some fan service to those that like school swimsuits better than regular swimsuits.
In http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] anime, a swimsuit of this type sometimes serves censoring purposes when characters take a bath. If there is a group of female characters donning swimsuits, you can expect the youngest or youngest-looking girl to wear one of these.</description>
<picurl>52174.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2978" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-28">
<name>aim for the top</name>
<description>This can be a positive or negative plot device. A character may strive to become the best in an altruistic way (e.g. best healer, most widely learned master), or it can be quite banal and primitive (e.g. challenged delinquents wanting to be the strongest fighters).
Alas in fighting anime the latter usually prevails.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="68396" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="9">6.33</rating>
<name>G Men</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68397" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="5">5.37</rating>
<name>Tsumorin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68398" type="main character in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="14">5.41</rating>
<name>Hiotan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159821.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68399" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="8">7.25</rating>
<name>Kameko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68400" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="6">4.21</rating>
<name>Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68401" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="7">5.46</rating>
<name>Sommelier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37069" picture="157013.jpg">Tomita Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68402" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="15">6.96</rating>
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21823" picture="131326.jpg">Tsuda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68403" type="main character in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="6">3.71</rating>
<name>Umio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68404" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-21">
<rating votes="9">4.24</rating>
<name>Fu Girl</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70633" type="appears in" update="2014-12-20">
<name>SSDko-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166220.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="327" picture="17472.jpg">Momoi Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72120" type="appears in" update="2014-12-20">
<name>Umanami-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10222.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34875" picture="157016.jpg">Iizuka Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="162981" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キングオブPOP / chocolate panic</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King of POP / Chocolate Panic</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le roi de la pop / Panique chocolatée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">King of POP / Chocolate Panic</title>
<summary>Valentine`s Day! Also known as "National Standardized Girl Power Exam Final Answer Finals!" There aren`t any girls at Umanohone so low in girl power that they can`t participate! Or are there? With the huge girls` event right around the corner, the girls of Umanohone are feeling lofty and restless and head-achey. Maximum girls power! Go! Super-cute red-faced combo!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661393</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162982" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Party Hard / ひおたんよ家に帰れ / エンドレス・カルナバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Party Hard / Hio-tan, Go Home / Endless Carnival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Super fête / Hio, rentre chez toi ! / Un Carnaval sans fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Party Hard / Hio-tan yo Ie ni Kaere / Endless Carnival</title>
<summary>Is it the Christmas Party Episode? No! The Cosplay episode! Miniskirt Santa, a dream come true! And rather pecuilar costumes are on demand, too! But Umanohone`s selling Moe-style games!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661391</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162983" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Deep Deep Night / デンキ街は燃えているか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deep Deep Night / Is the Denki-gai Pumped?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En pleine nuit / Le quartier de l’électronique brûle-t-il ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deep Deep Night / Denki Machi wa Moete Iru ka</title>
<summary>Denki-gai has a ton of weird events. The Umanohone staff are pumped to win the cash prize at the most infamous event, the Late-Summer Greetings Festival. Hurry up, who are you nyan-nyan-ing with, you bitches! You have no one to nyan-nyan with? Shut up, you have your 2D wives! The swimsuit episode comes early! Let`s go get that prize money!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661389</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162984" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラブ&amp;エロス フォー オール / ナイトメア ビフォア カルナバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love &amp; Eros for All / The Nightmare Before Carnaval</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Amour et érotisme pour tous / Cauchemars, conseil clients, carnaval</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love &amp; Eros for All / Nightmare Before Carnaval</title>
<summary>The job of a book store, naturally, is to sell books. In Denki-gai, a gathering place for people who are true to themselves, even erotic literature is valued merchandise! At Umanohone, a store that sells everything from famous works to doujinshi, an "ero book lover" checks through all the erotic books at incredible speed... No, it`s actually what they call an "Ero Books G-man"! Love and eros for all! There is no human who doesn`t need eros!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661387</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163006" update="2014-10-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163007" update="2014-10-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163835" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿はなし / Secret Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homeless / Secret Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sans refuge / Jardin secret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yado wa Nashi / Secret Paradise</title>
<summary>Sensei hasn`t changed her trademark tracksuit in days... that`s because she`s been sleeping at Umanohone in order to draw a manga for the Rookie of the Year Award! 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661397</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163836" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">春にパンチラ / I am Rain / ざわめき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Panties in the Spring / I Am Rain / Rustling</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le printemps des plans-culottes / Je suis la pluie / Se démener</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru ni Panchira / I Am Rain / Zawameki</title>
<summary>There`s no man on Earth who doesn`t like panties! (Wise saying) - Of course Umio loves panties, too! (Let`s make it clear.) Sensei tells him bashfully "Do you want to see them?" 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661395</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163951" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ワンダフル・チョコレート / chocolate philosophy / 飴色の部屋 / 眠れぬ夜につかまえた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wonderful Chocolate / Chocolate Philosophy / Tan-Colored Room / Caught You on a Sleepless Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Merveilleux chocolat / Philosophie chocolatée / Une chambre couleur d`ambre / Rattrapés par la nuit blanche</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wonderful Chocolate / Chocolate Philosophy / Ameiro no Heya / Nemurenu Yoru ni Tsukamaeta</title>
<summary>Valentine`s Day! I said the same thing in Episode 4, didn`t I? Handmade chocolate is a dangerous mission, but Sensei-chan attempts it for the sake of redemption. Not surprisingly, she fails. The fool! She`ll need Tsumorin`s help. Bring us Tsumorin!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661405</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163952" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Koijanaino / やあ, 調子はどうだい / 雪の降る夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Not Love / Hey, How`re You Feeling? / Snowy Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Si ce n’est pas de l’amour / Salut, comment te sens-tu ? / Une nuit où la neige tombe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi ja Nai no / Yaa, Choushi wa Doudai / Yuki no Furu Yoru</title>
<summary>Hio-tan`s has the flu?! She takes the day off, and Kantoku pays her a visit. Things get a little awkward when he shows a more caring side of himself. But whatever happened to the com in this romcom: things get serious when Hio-tan collapses!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661403</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163953" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眠る人 / ラフさりげなく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sleeping One / Subtly Rough</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`endormie / Subtile grossièreté</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemuru Hito / Rough Sarigenaku</title>
<summary>Ugh, first date! Stop, Sensei`s down to zero health! Sensei-chan accidentally (seriously, accidentally) asks Umio out on a date, and she has no idea what to wear.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661401</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163954" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いざ銭湯へ... / 胸がいっぱい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Bath House... / A Full Chest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tous aux bains / Le plein de poitrines</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iza Sentou e... / Mune ga Ippai</title>
<summary>Summer Comika, an event so hot that you can see clouds forming inside the venue! S here`s he onsen - Japanese hot springs- episode! When you have to sweat, you need an onsen. Umaophone supports Oedo Onsen Monogatari! 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661399</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164626" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">隠者の書庫 / 桜が咲いたら / Welcoming morning</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hermit`s Library / When the Cherry Blossoms Bloom / Welcoming Morning</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les archives de l`ermite / Quand les cerisiers fleuriront / Salutations matinales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inja no Shoko / Sakura ga Saitara / Welcoming Morning</title>
<summary>The cherry blossoms are blooming, so we`re going on a picnic. The wind blows through flowers and hearts alike... and it`s a cosplay cherry blossom picnic!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661409</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164627" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな頃から / 暴かれた生活 / 唇のソレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starting Young / Life, Exposed / The Lips</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Depuis l`enfance / Le quotidien révélé / Sur tes lèvres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Koro kara / Abakareta Seikatsu / Kuchibiru no Sore</title>
<summary>Childhood memories. They`re beautiful, fleeting, sour and eternal. Even if they`re about ero-books! Who would have thought we`d have an episode about G-men`s childhood?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661407</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182121" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661191</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182122" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>661189</identifier>
<identifier>denki-gai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
