<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10638" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2015-04-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nisekoi OAD</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ニセコイ OAD</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">니세코이 OAD</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10859" type="Parent Story">Nisekoi:</anime>
<anime id="11551" type="Other">Nisekoi: (2016)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="59" type="Chief Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="7770" type="Character Design">Sugiyama Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="26229" type="Series Composition">Tou Fuyashi</name>
<name id="59" type="Series Composition">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="37305" type="Original Work">Komi Naoshi</name>
<name id="3537" type="Direction">Tatsuwa Naoyuki</name>
<name id="11940" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shiotsuki Kazuya</name>
<name id="14204" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishizawa Shin`ya</name>
<name id="7770" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugiyama Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="3399" type="Music">Kikuya Tomoki</name>
</creators>
<description>Recap: The high school student http://anidb.net/ch57797 [Ichijou Raku] is the son of a leader in the yakuza faction Shuei-Gumi, and http://anidb.net/ch57798 [Kirisaki Chitoge] is the daughter of a boss in a rival gang known as Beehive. Upon returning home, Raku learns that the Shuei-Gumi and Beehive gangs have agreed to settle their feud by pairing their leaders` children, and that his girlfriend-to-be is none other than Chitoge. For the next three years, they must pretend to be in a relationship to maintain peace between the gangs...
Loss — http://anidb.net/ch57906 [Miyamoto Ruri] loses her glasses at school, but even without them she clearly sees what Raku and http://anidb.net/ch57799 [Onodera Kosaki] mean to each other.
Shrine Maiden — Ruku`s father asks the gang to help out at a friend`s shrine on New Year`s Day. As it turns out something very bad is haunting Raku or so the girls are led to believe.
Work — Lately http://anidb.net/ch60162 [Tachibana Marika] leaves school early, making Raku wonder. When he and Chitoge visit the local fast food restaurant they find out why.
Change — On New Year`s Day the whole gang unexpectedly visits Raku`s mansion. After a feast Chitoge craves some non-Japanese sweets, that unbeknownst to them happen to contain alcohol.
Bath House — The bath at Raku`s mansion is not working properly, so he visits the local public bath, where Chitoge also happens to turn up, along with Marika, her maid http://anidb.net/ch67775 [Honda], Kosaki, and her sister http://anidb.net/ch72125 [Haru].
Service — The girls visit the hot springs up in the mountains. Their tied-together clothes get catapulted into the mens` hot spring where Raku is trying to relax for once.
— written by foo2
Note: Bundled with the 14th, 16th and 17th Nisekoi manga volumes. The OVA adapts from the manga: chapter 58 Funshitsu and chapter 64 Mikosan (first episode), chapter 65 Henbou and chapter 71 Oshigoto (second episode), chapter 81 Sentou (third episode).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1056">5.60</permanent>
<temporary count="1062">6.87</temporary>
<review count="1">7.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>162451.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16607</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>24227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nisekoi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ニセコイ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>371606</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>371607</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>371608</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="57797" type="main character in" update="2014-06-07">
<rating votes="101">4.13</rating>
<name>Ichijou Raku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raku is the son of a Yakuza family leader. He refuses to take over the family`s duties as the next leader, and prefers to pursue a normal career when he graduates. In the story, he is placed in a fake relationship with Chitoge to prevent a war from starting between their families. The relationship often leads to misunderstandings and difficulties for him as he pursues his crush, Kosaki Onodera. Raku is shown to be very kind and caring even to the people he is supposed to hate, as shown when he helps Chitoge numerous times in the series. As the story progresses, he grows closer to Chitoge, and he even stated that he no longer hates her, although he has yet to sort out his true feelings.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>142256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57798" type="main character in" update="2015-12-02">
<rating votes="303">5.76</rating>
<name>Kirisaki Chitoge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of the leader of the Bee Hive Gangsters, Chitoge transfers from America to Raku`s high school at the start of the series. She and Raku pretend to be in a relationship in order to prevent their families` factions from feuding. She is half-Japanese with long blonde hair that is tied with a ribbon. She is good at sports and academics, but clueless when it comes to cooking. Despite not getting along with Raku from the start, she makes an effort to find his lost pendant. Ten years before, Chitoge makes a promise with a boy; when she looks through her diary from that time, she stumbles upon a key that could potentially unlock Raku`s locket. Later she develops feelings for Raku without realizing it, and tends to get jealous whenever other girls such as Marika try to get close to him. During their Romeo and Juliet class play, she eventually realizes that she is genuinely in love with him. Her mother, Hana, is a powerful CEO in America.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>142255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57799" type="main character in" update="2014-06-07">
<rating votes="290">7.13</rating>
<name>Onodera Kosaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Onodera Kosaki is a kind and sweet classmate of Raku. She has a shoulder length dark brown hair and chestnut brown eyes. Although Raku has a major crush on her, she does not reveal that she has a similar crush on him. When Raku mentions his lost locket of his first love, she shows some interest as she secretly carries a potential key, however, when confronted about the key or being the first love, she lies and denies it in embarrassment. Although she works with her mother at a dessert shop, she turns out to be a terrible cook on her own. Surprisingly, whatever food she fashions looks good on the outside.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>142254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57905" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-28">
<rating votes="118">6.89</rating>
<name>Tsugumi Seishirou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsugumi is a hitwoman who was raised and trained by Claude of the Beehive Gangsters. Tsugumi is originally introduced as a guy who transfers to Chitoge`s class, and has orders to protect her from Raku, whom she thinks forced Chitoge into the relationship. She and Chitoge are childhood friends; she tries to keep a ten year old promise of becoming strong to protect Chitoge. However, after Raku treats her nicely, she begins to develop feelings for him, even though she is too stubborn and embarrassed to admit it. In America, her assassin code name is "Black Tiger", who had a rivalry with "White Fang" Paula McCoy. She does well academically, having ranked next to Chitoge on a yearly exam. Raku has occasionally confided with her as a good friend and also for romance advice.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>146655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57906" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-02">
<rating votes="101">7.54</rating>
<name>Miyamoto Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruri is Kosaki`s best friend. She is never afraid of speaking what is on her mind and she is very aggressive when giving punishment especially to Shu. She is always pushing Kosaki to get closer to Raku, and is doing the bold things which Kosaki often cannot. She regularly beats up Shu for his perverted comments, although Shuu sometimes has pearls of wisdom that she can respect.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>146653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58637" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-31">
<rating votes="59">5.50</rating>
<name>Maiko Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shuu is Raku`s best friend; they have known each other since pre-school. He is the kind of person that would do anything for a laugh, and often makes perverted passes or comments without shame to his friends. He is also very perceptive, knowing immediately that Raku was not really dating Chitoge, that Raku and Onodera have secret crushes on each other, and that Tsugumi develops feelings for Raku. He uses this knowledge for his enjoyment. On academic rankings, he places next to his "glasses buddy" Ruri, much to the latter`s chagrin. He has not expressed romantic interest in Raku`s friends, but has expressed interest in their homeroom teacher Kyouko.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>177029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58638" type="appears in" update="2014-01-19">
<rating votes="32">1.94</rating>
<name>Claude</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Claude is one of the leaders of the Bee Hive Gangsters, and one of the few characters who suspects the relationship between Raku and Chitoge is fake. He stalks Chitoge regularly to make sure Raku does not take advantage of her. Chitoge stated that when she was young, she was unable to make friends because of Claude`s overprotectiveness and background checks. He raises Tsugumi as a hitman, and appears to be clueless as to her gender, having given her a boy`s name, Seishirou.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>148755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60162" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-02">
<rating votes="128">6.30</rating>
<name>Tachibana Marika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marika transfers to Raku`s class and is introduced as his fiancée; she bears a key that she thinks will unlock Raku`s pendant, and is the most vocal about expressing her love to Raku. She is the daughter of the police chief, and has been in love with Raku for the past ten years. She does not get along with Chitoge; she states she hates girls with long hair despite the fact that she also has long hair. She has a frail constitution; ten years prior, she was frequently visited by a young Raku, who brought her gifts and sparked a friendship with her. She used to speak in a rather vulgar manner, but has attempted to correct her language after Raku had told her that he likes a girly girl with long hair. However, when flustered, she reverts to her old speaking habits.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>146654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62996" type="appears in" update="2014-01-12">
<rating votes="10">5.50</rating>
<name>Raku (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>148411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39068" picture="204958.jpg">Sekine Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62998" type="appears in" update="2014-07-03">
<rating votes="11">5.11</rating>
<name>Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67775" type="appears in" update="2015-12-02">
<rating votes="15">3.15</rating>
<name>Honda Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67820" type="appears in" update="2015-12-02">
<rating votes="7">4.35</rating>
<name>Tachibana Marika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Marika.</description>
<picture>156355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72125" type="appears in" update="2014-12-22">
<rating votes="48">5.51</rating>
<name>Onodera Haru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73489" type="appears in" update="2015-04-03">
<rating votes="17">4.55</rating>
<name>Fuu-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>171338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32588" picture="87531.jpg">Koiwai Kotori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73674" type="appears in" update="2015-04-29">
<rating votes="22">5.15</rating>
<name>Paula McCoy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73917" type="appears in" update="2015-03-19">
<rating votes="3">4.51</rating>
<name>Kannushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="598" picture="45415.jpg">Sadaoka Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74021" type="appears in" update="2015-03-23">
<rating votes="3">3.40</rating>
<name>Migisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74022" type="appears in" update="2015-03-23">
<rating votes="2">4.36</rating>
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74276" type="appears in" update="2015-04-03">
<rating votes="2">5.11</rating>
<name>Bandai no Obaa-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>171339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12464" picture="42188.jpg">Miyazawa Kiyoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="159851" update="2014-05-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フンシツ / ミコサン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Loss / Shrine Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">분실 / 무녀</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funshitsu / Miko-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162686" update="2014-10-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オシゴト / ヘンボウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Work / Change</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아르바이트 / 변모</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshigoto / Henbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163642" update="2014-10-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163643" update="2014-10-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164628" update="2015-04-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">セントウ / サービス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bath House / Service</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">대중목욕탕 / 서비스</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentou / Service</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
