<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10641" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>5</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-05-13</startdate>
<enddate>2013-06-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shin Seikimatsu: Yatsuto no Souguu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">新世紀末 奴との遭遇</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.cwfilms.jp/yatsutonosogu/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10345" type="Work">CoMix Wave Films</name>
</creators>
<description>In the corner of the universe, there was a small planet where creatures called men flourished. Doomsday finally looms near to this planet where destruction and creation have occurred repeatedly. The great king of terror appears from the sky and the mankind faces the end.
Source: Anime Bancho</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="13">3.88</permanent>
<temporary count="13">4.53</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>155684.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22657</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.cwfilms.jp/yatsutonosogu/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>playlist?list=PL8Vd-cvqk4GuGfSLQSanC5QtFNixuhnQ2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3206" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-06">
<name>stop motion</name>
<description>Stop motion (also known as stop-action or frame-by-frame) is an animation technique to make a physically manipulated object appear to move on its own. The object is moved in small increments between individually photographed frames, creating the illusion of movement when the series of frames is played as a continuous sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5939" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-09">
<name>CAST MISSING</name>
<description>Important characters are missing, either in-part or entirely. This includes basic entry info (name, gender, picture), appear episode range, seiyuu and/or tags.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="160087" update="2014-05-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2013-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴かれた 惑星の真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Divulged Truth of the Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abakareta Wakusei no Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160088" update="2014-05-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2013-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅の大地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crimson Land</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurenai no Daichi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160089" update="2014-05-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄の大海</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ocean of Shudders</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senritsu no Taikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160090" update="2014-05-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2013-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突の時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu no Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160091" update="2014-05-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">終末の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuumatsu no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161496" update="2014-07-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
