<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10648" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-03-10</startdate>
<enddate>2015-03-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hitsugi no Chaika: Nerawareta Hitsugi / Yomigaeru Iseki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Chaika: The Coffin Princess - The Coffin Hunt / The Ruins Reborn</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">관희 챠이카 OAD - 표적이 된 관/되살아난 유적</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hitsugi no Chaika OAD</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">棺姫のチャイカ ねらわれた棺 / 蘇る遺跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Chaika: The Coffin Princess - The Targeted Coffin / Ruins Resurrected</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">棺姬嘉依卡 Ova</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9973" type="Parent Story">Hitsugi no Chaika</anime>
</relatedanime>
<description>While escaping from the Gillette Corps, http://anidb.net/ch62587 [Tooru] and http://anidb.net/ch62586 [Chaika] hide inside a theater. After a couple of mishaps, they end up taking part in a stage performance along with http://anidb.net/ch62588 [Akari] and http://anidb.net/ch63807 [Fredrika].
Later, the Saboteurs, the Gillette Corps and the http://anidb.net/ch67359 [Red Chaika]`s group go to the ancient ruins rumoured to contain http://anidb.net/ch71993 [Emperor Gaz]`s remains. A three-way battle ensues as each party tries to obtain the remains first.
— written by Singan
Note: the OVA contains two side-stories for the first season. The first one takes place somewhere between episode 4 and 6, and the second one takes place somewhere between episode 6 and 10. The OVA was bundled with the 12th Hitsugi no Chaika novel volume.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="621">4.95</permanent>
<temporary count="623">6.60</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>170479.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>24261</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Chaika_-_The_Coffin_Princess</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>棺姫のチャイカ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3611" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-12-06">
<name>evil empire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4149" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>non-blood-related siblings -- DO NOT USE -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be deleted. Please add char-char relations of the "is family of" type with the http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Content:Characters#is_family_of [appropriate relation comment] to the relevant characters and remove the tag from the corresponding anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4178" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-06">
<name>manipulated memories</name>
<description>The protagonist finds out that his/her cherished memories are actually fake and have been implanted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="62586" type="main character in" update="2014-03-31">
<rating votes="107">7.98</rating>
<name>Chaika Trabant</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A silver-haired girl wizard with big purple eyes. She always carries a huge coffin on her back, one that is larger than her height, which has a magical sniper rifle (Gundo) carefully stashed inside. Her speech is imperfect, and she seems to be running from someone for some particular reason. She says she is wandering the continent collecting something...
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10759" picture="38748.jpg">Anzai Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62587" type="main character in" update="2015-05-31">
<rating votes="53">6.13</rating>
<name>Tooru Acura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tooru Acura has been wasting away his days with the motto Working is losing, but encounters http://anidb.net/ch62586 [Chaika] and decides to set out on a journey with her. He never seems to be able to say no to his younger sister http://anidb.net/ch62588 [Akari]. He is actually a survivor of saboteurs who were active during the recent war and is able to use the art of Iron Blood Transformation, which temporarily enhances his physical abilities.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150137.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62588" type="main character in" update="2015-05-31">
<rating votes="82">7.60</rating>
<name>Akari Acura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akari Acura is a beautiful green-haired girl with blue eyes, who is also a saboteur like her older brother http://anidb.net/ch62587 [Tooru]. She is a girl of strong character and has a job to support their living, as her brother will not work. She worships her brother fervently, to the extent that one day she wants to make him a stuffed specimen. She tags along her brother who has decided to venture on a journey with http://anidb.net/ch62586 [Chaika].
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>150135.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39277" picture="150138.jpg">Hara Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63807" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="83">8.20</rating>
<name>Fredrika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65353" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-04">
<rating votes="29">4.68</rating>
<name>Alberic Gillette</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65354" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-04">
<rating votes="30">3.21</rating>
<name>Zita Brusasco</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38704" picture="145173.jpg">Kouda Yumeha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65355" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-04">
<rating votes="13">3.68</rating>
<name>Nikolai Avtotor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11087" picture="39958.jpg">Satou Kensuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65356" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-04">
<rating votes="13">3.66</rating>
<name>Mateus Callaway</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23574" picture="64846.jpg">Morishima Shuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65357" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-04">
<rating votes="17">3.28</rating>
<name>Leonardo Stora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10380" picture="38227.jpg">Yamamoto Kazutomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65358" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-04">
<rating votes="45">3.24</rating>
<name>Vivi Holopainen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67359" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="58">6.19</rating>
<name>Chaika Bogdan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10391" picture="38277.jpg">Zougou Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67385" type="appears in" update="2014-05-11">
<rating votes="4">4.75</rating>
<name>Fredrika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67386" type="appears in" update="2014-05-11">
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<name>Fredrika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="164709" update="2016-11-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OAD</title>
</episode>
<episode id="185365" update="2017-03-06">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「棺姫のチャイカXⅡ」Blu-ray付き限定版CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Hitsugi-hime no Chaika X II" Blu-Ray Tsuki Genteiban CM</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
