<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10685" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-04-24</startdate>
<enddate>2014-07-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">World Fool News (2014)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ワールド フールニュース (2014)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13071" type="Sequel">World Fool News Part II</anime>
<anime id="10633" type="Alternative Setting">World Fool News</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.gtv.co.jp/program/animation/wfn/</url>
<creators>
<name id="40085" type="Direction">Mashimo Yuu</name>
<name id="44581" type="Music">Yuma Yumaguchi</name>
</creators>
<description>Takahashi is transferred to a main anchor of a news program, which is known for being a little...weird. This is a comedy about somewhat ridiculous happenings occurring at a broadcasting station.
Note: A TV Remake of the World Fool News ONA</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="49">3.93</permanent>
<temporary count="49">5.28</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>155371.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16146</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18205</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gtv.co.jp/program/animation/wfn/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ワールドフールニュース</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3555</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3149" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-15">
<name>journalism</name>
<description>Journalism is the work and distribution of reports on the interaction of events, facts, ideas, and people that are the "news of the day" and that informs society to at least some degree. The word applies to the occupation (professional or not), the methods of gathering information, and the organizing literary styles. Journalistic media include: print, television, radio, Internet and, in the past, newsreels.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="88572" type="main character in" update="2017-04-02">
<rating votes="3">8.57</rating>
<name>Shimohira Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49484" picture="200524.jpg">Hagiwara Rin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88573" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-02">
<rating votes="2">8.50</rating>
<name>Maruyama Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49485" picture="200525.jpg">Murayama J Sarshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88574" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-02">
<rating votes="2">8.50</rating>
<name>Honjou Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49486" picture="200526.jpg">Satou Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88575" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-02">
<rating votes="2">7.99</rating>
<name>Usui Takahito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49487" picture="200527.jpg">Love Morinaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88576" type="main character in" update="2017-04-02">
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<name>Takahashi Ichitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43073" picture="172512.jpg">Noda Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="160602" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新キャスターの憂鬱!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of a New Newscaster!?</title>
<summary>A big promotion to a nightly news program is not what it seems to be.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653943</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160603" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">草津温泉湯けむり事件!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Steamy Incident at the Kusatsu Hot Springs!?</title>
<summary>While on location at a hot spring, Miki tries to keep it together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653949</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160604" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">下平さんの休日!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shimohira-san`s Day Off!?</title>
<summary>Takahashi is a stalker?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653947</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160605" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">本番スタート!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Show Begins!?</title>
<summary>Takahashi first show introduces a new set of weirdness.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653945</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160606" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐竜の里へようこそ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Dinosaur Village!?</title>
<summary>Tonight on World Fool News: A water pipe burst, a dinosaur fossil is discovered, and a super baby.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653961</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160607" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">JOYnt!がやってきた!? 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">JOYnt! Is Here!? Part 2</title>
<summary>JOYnt host are continuing to annoy the crew of World Fool News.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653959</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160608" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">JOYnt!がやってきた!? 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">JOYnt! Is Here!? Part 1</title>
<summary>Isn’t it Naigayara Falls?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653957</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160609" recap="true" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">一人きりの休日!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day Off All by Myself!?</title>
<summary>A request to buy noodles causes Takahashi to have flashbacks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653955</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160610" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋に落ちた薄井さん!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Usui-san in Love!?</title>
<summary>Usui complicated love triangle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653953</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160611" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トロッコ列車で行こう!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Take the Trolley!?</title>
<summary>Tonight, a report about the Rose Garden in Shikishima, a crushing injury to a promising athlete, and “Let’s keep News Upbeat”
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>653951</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160612" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会,気になる同級生!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion! That Classmate You Like!?</title>
<summary>Takahashi runs into an old classmate who asks about his life as a newscaster.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>655963</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160820" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2014-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">変わり者でいこう!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s All Be Weird!?</title>
<summary>Do you get along with weirdos?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656421</identifier>
<identifier>world-fool-news</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
