<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1068" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1993-12-23</startdate>
<enddate>1993-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Battle Spirits: Ryuuko no Ken</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Battle Spirits: Dragon Tiger Fist</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">バトルスピリッツ 龍虎の拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Art of Fighting</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3564" type="Same Setting">The King of Fighters: Another Day</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="1225" type="Original Work">SNK Playmore</name>
<name id="4806" type="Direction">Fukutomi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="6152" type="Music">Miyake Kazunori</name>
<name id="2175" type="Character Design">Iwakura Kazunori</name>
<name id="2175" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iwakura Kazunori</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
</creators>
<description>The only witnesses to a mob hit, Ryou and Robert were in the wrong place at the wrong time. Since then, they`ve been shot at, run off the road, and nearly blown to pieces-but now it`s getting personal. Based on the Hit Video Game!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="204">2.19</permanent>
<temporary count="209">4.86</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>42588.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>516</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>51</identifier>
<identifier>xzwvrt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>バトルスピリッツ_龍虎の拳</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>235502</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2802" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-14">
<name>action game</name>
<description>Any game where reflexes are the key to the gameplay, violence is optional.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29245" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-07">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Toudou Ryuuhaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31098" type="appears in" update="2012-01-02">
<name>Mr. Big</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2143" picture="178043.jpg">Kayumi Iemasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31099" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="3">6.12</rating>
<name>King</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31100" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-25">
<name>Jack Turner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2201" picture="34284.jpg">Matsuo Ginzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31101" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-25">
<name>John Crawley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31102" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="4">3.37</rating>
<name>Yuri Sakazaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuri Sakazaki is a video game character from SNK Playmore`s (formerly known as SNK) Art of Fighting series. She first appears in the original Art of Fighting being kidnapped by Mr. Big, a criminal from the fictional city of Southtown. The players, Yuri`s brother Ryo and his friend Robert Garcia spend the game searching for her. In the second Art of Fighting, Yuri appears for the first time as a playable character, having been trained by her father Takuma in the art of the Kyokugenryu Karate. She has also appeared in most games from The King of Fighters series, with the notable exception of the non-canon The King of Fighters XII, participating in the annual tournaments from each title. She initially starts in the Women Fighters Team (composed exclusively by women), but she later moves to the Art of Fighting Team along with her family. She was also featured in the SNK vs. Capcom crossover series as well as in SNK Gals` Fighters.
Yuri has also starred in the anime adaptation from Art of Fighting, in which she reprises her role from the first game. Her character has been well-received by gamers, having ranking high in several popularity polls developed by journals. Video games publications have commented on Yuri`s character; Yuri`s addition to Art of Fighting 2 as a playable character has been praised by several reviewers, and some have also complained on her absence in the following title.</description>
<picture>69644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33973">Horie Kaori</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="7004" picture="31991.jpg">Hamasaki Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31103" type="main character in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<name>Ryou Sakazaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryo Sakazaki is a video game character developed for the fighting game Art of Fighting from SNK Playmore (formerly SNK). His name is most often written in kana, however, in some games kanji is used to write parts of his name. In the series, Ryo is a martial artist that practices his family`s fighting style, the Kyokugenryu Karate. He and his best friend Robert Garcia enter the Southtown city to rescue Ryo`s sister, Yuri Sakazaki. In their fights, Ryo and Robert learn that the Sakazaki became the target from the criminal Geese Howard, and decide to face him. Ryo is also a regular character in the crossover series The King of Fighters, in which he participates in fighting tournament in a team composed of his friends and family. He would also make appearance in other SNK games under the name of Mr. Karate II (二代目Mr.カラテ). Additionally, he stars in manhua adaptations of the several series, and appeared in the anime film from Art of Fighting.
Ryo has been well-received by gamers; his character has ranked high in several popularity polls from journals. Video game publications have provided praise and criticism on Ryo`s character. While Ryo has been criticized for its similarities with the Street Fighter video games` characters, several reviewers have praised his development in several games from SNK such as his introduction in The King of Fighters.</description>
<picture>69642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33747" picture="92670.jpg">Bessho Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31104" type="main character in" update="2011-04-12">
<rating votes="1">7.77</rating>
<name>Robert Garcia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Robert Garcia is a video game character created by SNK Playmore, formerly known as SNK. Robert stars in the fighting video game Art of Fighting as the lead character along his best friend Ryo Sakazaki. The game features both of them as practitioners of the Kyokugenryu Karate fighting who search for Ryo`s younger sister, Yuri Sakazaki, who was kidnapped by a criminal named Mr. Big. He is additionally featured in most of The King of Fighters crossover games, in which starts into the King of Fighters tournament in teams composed of three members. Thus far, he has been a playable character in every edition of KOF except The King of Fighters XI; however, he has recently been added back in for the PlayStation 2 version of the game.
Robert has additionally appeared in the film adaptation of Art of Fighting, and the manhua from The King of Fighters. He received mixed critics from video games publication, which praised his design, but some also noted him similar to the Street Fighter main characters. He has also been well-received by gamers, appearing in several popularity polls developed by journals and websites.</description>
<picture>69643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5776" picture="30241.jpg">Ikeda Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="19217" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1993-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
