<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10729" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2015-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ore ga Ojou-sama Gakkou ni "Shomin Sample" Toshite Gets-sareta Ken</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Shomin Sample</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">I Was Kidnapped As a "Sample Commoner" for a Princess School</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Syomin Sample</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">I Was Abducted by an Elite All-Girls School as a Sample Commoner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ore ga Ojousama Gakkou ni "Shomin Sample" Toshite Gets♥Sareta Ken</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">俺がお嬢様学校に「庶民サンプル」としてゲッツされた件</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Shomin Sample</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Shomin Sample</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我被绑架到贵族女校当“庶民样本”</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4148" approval="2" total="5">Ouran Koukou Host Club</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="242627">Not sure about this one. Plot and characters initially seem dull and generic, but after a few episodes, "Shomin Sample" grew on me. Unfortunately, it has one of the worst ending episodes I`ve ever seen. Tl;dr: recommended only if you can let yourself avoid ep 12 completely. Otherwise, for fans and completionists.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://syominsample-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2900" type="Animation Work">Silver Link</name>
<name id="11842" type="Chief Animation Direction">Furukawa Hideki</name>
<name id="11748" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirata Kazuya</name>
<name id="40366" type="Original Work">Nanatsuki Takafumi</name>
<name id="9744" type="Character Design">Sano Takao</name>
<name id="2753" type="Music">Mizutani Hiromi</name>
<name id="19607" type="Series Composition">Shimoyama Kento</name>
<name id="2900" type="Work">Silver Link</name>
<name id="11181" type="Direction">Jinbou Masato</name>
<name id="9744" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sano Takao</name>
</creators>
<description>One day, a completely average high school boy named http://anidb.net/ch76043 [Kagurazaka Kimito] is kidnapped to attend an elite young lady`s academy, the Seikain Girls` School, to be a sample of a commoner.
Due to a misunderstanding, the school`s president is under the impression that Kimito is only interested in men. When Kimito tries to inform her that the opposite is true, he quickly is made aware of the dire consequences such an admission would lead to. And since Kimito`s parents apparently OK`ed the matter of changing schools, he has no choice but to play along, feigning disinterest in girls. Kimito soon learns that the overly protected life of these female students from wealthy families has led them to develop quite bizarre misconceptions of how commoners live.
Together with the energetic, yet naive http://anidb.net/ch72725 [Tenkuubashi Aika] he founds the Commoner Club that steadily gains new and unlikely members: be it the shy genius http://anidb.net/ch74018 [Shiodome Hakua], the katana-swinging http://anidb.net/t2455 [tsundere] http://anidb.net/ch74019 [Jinryou Karen], or the polite http://anidb.net/t815 [ojou] http://anidb.net/ch74017 [Arisugawa Reiko].
Thus Kimito`s normal life ends, as he henceforth studies at this elite school, where the female students have never met a male student, let alone a commoner, before...
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1183">4.02</permanent>
<temporary count="1188">6.29</temporary>
<review count="1">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>239899.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16726</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31797</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>25099</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://syominsample-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Syomin_Sample</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>俺がお嬢様学校に「庶民サンプル」として拉致られた件</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3886</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349665</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18474</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2671" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>school dormitory</name>
<description>A school dormitory or residence hall is the student living quarters at an elite academy, boarding school, or military school. The main characters may live or work at the dormitory, and it often becomes the backdrop for a reoccurring part of the story.</description>
<picurl>223167.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3508" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-09-26">
<name>school for the rich elite</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3872" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>formerly one-gender school</name>
<description>This anime takes place at a school that was formerly one-gender, but has recently begun to admit the opposite sex. This can be a set-up for harem situations stemming from a still-skewed gender ratio.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4090" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-08">
<name>cardiopulmonary resuscitation</name>
<description>Cardiopulmonary resuscitation, commonly known as CPR, is an emergency procedure that combines chest compression often with artificial ventilation in an effort to manually preserve intact brain function until further measures are taken to restore spontaneous blood circulation and breathing in a person who is in cardiac arrest. It is indicated in those who are unresponsive with no breathing or abnormal breathing. CPR involves chest compressions at a rate of at least 100 to 120 per minute. The rescuer may also provide artificial ventilation by either exhaling air into the subject`s mouth or nose (mouth-to-mouth resuscitation) or using a device that pushes air into the subject`s lungs (mechanical ventilation).
CPR alone is unlikely to restart the heart; its main purpose is to restore partial flow of oxygenated blood to the brain and heart. The objective is to delay tissue death and to extend the brief window of opportunity for a successful resuscitation without permanent brain damage. Administration of an electric shock to the subject`s heart, termed defibrillation, is usually needed in order to restore a viable heart rhythm. In general, CPR is continued until the person has a return of spontaneous circulation or is declared dead.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>68242.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5463" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-25">
<name>boarding school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="72725" type="main character in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="30">6.09</rating>
<name>Tenkuubashi Aika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36230" picture="242785.jpg">Serizawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74017" type="main character in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="33">6.79</rating>
<name>Arisugawa Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42286" picture="167754.jpg">Tachibana Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74018" type="main character in" update="2019-11-21">
<rating votes="28">7.56</rating>
<name>Shiodome Hakua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74019" type="main character in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="34">8.00</rating>
<name>Jinryou Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40739" picture="186144.jpg">Morinaga Chitose</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74020" type="main character in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="34">8.08</rating>
<name>Kujou Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76043" type="main character in" update="2015-10-12">
<rating votes="12">4.42</rating>
<name>Kagurazaka Kimito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24946" picture="200733.jpg">Tamaru Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76044" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-08-26">
<rating votes="14">5.74</rating>
<name>Hanae Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>176862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79271" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="3">4.63</rating>
<name>Taiiku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27064" picture="228527.jpg">Kashiyama Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79272" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Uranaishi Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79273" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="8">4.24</rating>
<name>Mibu Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41504" picture="178543.jpg">Matsuda Risae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79274" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="11">5.37</rating>
<name>Kimachi Sayuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79275" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Yamada Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38294" picture="150942.jpg">Okuno Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79276" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="12">5.81</rating>
<name>Sakimori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79277" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="4">4.18</rating>
<name>Shinjin Maid</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27064" picture="228527.jpg">Kashiyama Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79278" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="5">4.24</rating>
<name>Arisugawa Masaomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181027.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79279" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="11">5.41</rating>
<name>Arisugawa Houko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79280" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="9">3.82</rating>
<name>Suehiro Mizuho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44370" picture="181010.jpg">Sugiura Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79281" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="9">5.35</rating>
<name>Toujou Kae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38613" picture="200781.jpg">Aisaka Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79282" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Takemiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79283" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="4">4.98</rating>
<name>Marika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79284" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="4">4.18</rating>
<name>Eigo Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33692" picture="216159.jpg">Komaki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79285" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Konoe no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29852">Asashina Junpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79286" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="8">4.95</rating>
<name>Kiryuu Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34696" picture="202613.jpg">Kaneko Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79287" type="appears in" update="2015-12-29">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Reiko no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="172245" update="2015-10-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お茶会事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tea Party Incident</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ochakai Jiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172246" update="2015-10-02">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エデンの園ってカンジだった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Was Like the Garden of Eden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eden no Sonotte Kanji Datta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172247" update="2015-10-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">麗子様は私たちの憧れですわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reiko Is Who We Wish to Be Like</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reiko-sama wa Watashitachi no Akogare Desu wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172248" update="2015-10-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ庶民</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome, Commoner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso Shomin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172451" update="2017-12-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172452" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172777" update="2015-10-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛佳様は友達が多い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aika-sama Has a Lot of Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aika-sama wa Tomodachi ga Ooi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172778" update="2015-10-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツンピュアさんの本領</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tsun-Pure in Her Element</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunpyua-san no Honryou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172779" update="2015-10-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">表に出ろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Step Outside</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omote ni Shutsuru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172780" update="2015-10-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友達だけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Just Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi Dake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173377" update="2015-11-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不束者ですが, 末永くお願い致します.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inexperienced Though I Am, Please Accept Me Forever</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futsutsukamono Desu ga, Suenagaku Onegai Itashimasu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173378" update="2015-11-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">公人様が見ていた空はこうではありませんの?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is This Not the Sky That Kimito-sama Was Looking At?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimito-sama ga Mite Ita Sora wa Koude wa Arimasen no?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173379" update="2015-11-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">前から気になっていたんだけど, ゲッツってなんなの?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ve Been Curious About This for a While, but What Is Gets?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mae kara Ki ni Natte Itanda kedo, Gettsutte Nan na no?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173380" update="2015-11-18">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神楽坂様が来てるのよっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kagurazaka-sama Is Here</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagurazaka-sama ga Kiteru no yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174494" update="2016-10-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">九条さんのドS相談室アニメ版</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kujou-san no do S Soudanshitsu Anime-ban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175900" update="2016-10-15">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">庶民魔法って知ってるか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shomin Mahou tte Shitteru ka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175901" update="2016-10-15">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">無理しない程度に大食い大会致しましょう♪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Murishinaiteido ni Oukui Taikai Itashimashou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175902" update="2016-10-15">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねえ, 何でこの靴下こんなにゆるいの?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nee, Nande Kono Kutsushita Konnani Yurui no?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181070" update="2016-10-15">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イチズレシピ 庶民部Ver.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichizureshipi Shomin-bu Ver.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181071" update="2016-10-15">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">私ぎゅうどんいっぱいに興味がありますわ♪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi Gyuudon Ippai ni Kyoumi ga Arimasu wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193895" update="2017-12-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
