<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10720" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-06-13</startdate>
<enddate>2015-06-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Love Live! The School Idol Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ラブライブ! The School Idol Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Love Live! The School Idol Movie</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9927" type="Prequel">Love Live! School Idol Project (2014)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="179476">It`s an ending.  The concert/music performances were generally lacking and uninspired in presentation (didn`t live up to the billing).  At times it showed hints of the TV charm, only to fall flat in the next scene.  The storyline was average at best.  

Recommended only for completionist fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="315386">If you love the love live anime project, love live project as a whole, the real life concerts were amazing(to you)(i know some of you won`t like this project , therefore it`s for fans.)

Feel more of a musical then a movie and continue to the anime tv series.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.lovelive-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4246" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishida Asako</name>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="4246" type="Character Design">Nishida Asako</name>
<name id="15999" type="Character Design">Murota Yuuhei</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="6996" type="Original Plan">Kimino Sakurako</name>
<name id="21152" type="Direction">Kyougoku Takahiko</name>
<name id="31562" type="Music">Fujisawa Yoshiaki</name>
</creators>
<description>Hot on the heels of the third year students` graduation, μ`s is invited to New York in hopes of spreading the joy of school idols to other parts of the world. Due to the events of the recent Love Live!, μ`s has reached eminent stardom which results in crowds swarming them whenever they appear in public. With the increased attention, however, comes a difficult choice.
Having yet to publicly announce the decision they came to regarding their future, the young members of μ`s are pushed to continue performing by rival group A-RISE, Otonokizaka High School, and even Love Live! itself. As leader, http://anidb.net/ch21496 [Kousaka Honoka] is left wondering if the path they have chosen is truly for the best, as μ`s must re-evaluate their choices and come to a final decision on what they want for the future.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="517">7.03</permanent>
<temporary count="521">7.25</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>168228.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16742</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>24997</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>32476</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.lovelive-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4073</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>351663</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18382</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01GPQMMTE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2684" parentid="2812" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>New York</name>
<description>The City of New York, often called New York City or simply New York, is the most populous city in the United States. New York City is also the most densely populated major city in the United States. Located at the southern tip of the state of New York, the city is the center of the New York metropolitan area, one of the most populous urban agglomerations in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214276.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2927" parentid="2676" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Akihabara</name>
<description>Akihabara is a common name for the area around Akihabara Station in the Chiyoda ward of Tokyo, Japan. It gained the nickname Akihabara Electric Town shortly after World War II for being a major shopping center for household electronic goods and the post-war black market. Nowadays, Akihabara is considered by many to be an otaku cultural center and a shopping district for video games, anime, manga, and computer goods.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214314.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="21496" type="main character in" update="2013-06-12">
<rating votes="268">6.50</rating>
<name>Kousaka Honoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54758.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22170" picture="226837.jpg">Nitta Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21497" type="main character in" update="2014-04-22">
<rating votes="284">5.94</rating>
<name>Ayase Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21498" type="main character in" update="2011-12-13">
<rating votes="317">7.15</rating>
<name>Minami Kotori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21499" type="main character in" update="2013-06-12">
<rating votes="348">7.07</rating>
<name>Sonoda Umi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21500" type="main character in" update="2013-06-12">
<rating votes="248">6.07</rating>
<name>Hoshizora Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22171" picture="173757.jpg">Iida Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21501" type="main character in" update="2013-02-04">
<rating votes="417">7.39</rating>
<name>Nishikino Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22173" picture="207914.jpg">Pile</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21502" type="main character in" update="2013-06-12">
<rating votes="317">6.48</rating>
<name>Toujou Nozomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22169" picture="58225.jpg">Kusuda Aina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21503" type="main character in" update="2013-06-12">
<rating votes="215">5.37</rating>
<name>Koizumi Hanayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21504" type="main character in" update="2013-06-12">
<rating votes="468">7.65</rating>
<name>Yazawa Niko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41710" type="appears in" update="2012-02-24">
<rating votes="34">8.69</rating>
<name>Muse</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>79013.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51958" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-10">
<rating votes="9">5.64</rating>
<name>Yuuki Anju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3622" picture="214935.jpg">Oohashi Ayuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51959" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-09">
<rating votes="20">6.34</rating>
<name>Rijichou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51960" type="appears in" update="2013-01-09">
<rating votes="13">4.84</rating>
<name>Honoka no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51961" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-10">
<rating votes="11">5.44</rating>
<name>Toudou Erina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17070" picture="46274.jpg">Matsunaga Maho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51962" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-10">
<rating votes="11">6.43</rating>
<name>Kira Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133439.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29669" picture="228702.jpg">Sakuragawa Megu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51963" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-09">
<rating votes="32">5.24</rating>
<name>Kousaka Yukiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51964" type="appears in" update="2013-01-09">
<rating votes="8">4.89</rating>
<name>A-Rise</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>130510.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51965" type="appears in" update="2013-01-09">
<rating votes="4">7.45</rating>
<name>Kokuritsu Otonokisaka Gakuin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>130516.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51966" type="appears in" update="2013-01-09">
<name>UTX Gakuen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>130515.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="51967" type="appears in" update="2013-06-12">
<rating votes="3">5.03</rating>
<name>Kousaka Honoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22170" picture="226837.jpg">Nitta Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51968" type="appears in" update="2013-01-09">
<rating votes="4">5.60</rating>
<name>Minami Kotori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51969" type="appears in" update="2013-06-12">
<rating votes="8">7.07</rating>
<name>Sonoda Umi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>130513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52454" type="appears in" update="2013-01-29">
<rating votes="10">5.10</rating>
<name>Maki no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>131481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32701" picture="88087.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53027" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-20">
<rating votes="26">6.12</rating>
<name>Ayase Arisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67074" type="appears in" update="2014-04-28">
<rating votes="4">6.46</rating>
<name>Yazawa Kokoa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67075" type="appears in" update="2014-04-28">
<rating votes="5">6.37</rating>
<name>Yazawa Kokoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67076" type="appears in" update="2014-04-28">
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<name>Yazawa Kotarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67403" type="appears in" update="2014-05-12">
<rating votes="5">6.75</rating>
<name>Akiba Reporter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68438" type="appears in" update="2014-07-05">
<rating votes="6">6.12</rating>
<name>Nico no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79437" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-02">
<rating votes="2">8.12</rating>
<name>Josei Singer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A street performer, whom http://anidb.net/ch21496 [Honoka] meets when she gets lost in New York.</description>
<picture>181346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="165699" update="2015-06-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>105</length>
<airdate>2015-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168190" update="2015-04-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場本予告(90秒ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (90 sec ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijou Hon Yokoku (90-byou Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173896" update="2015-12-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-06-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213427" update="2019-03-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou Manner CM: BiBi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213428" update="2019-03-09">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou Manner CM: Lily White</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213429" update="2019-03-09">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou Manner CM: Printemps</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213430" update="2019-03-09">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou Manner CM: Special Stage</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
