<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10742" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-04-18</startdate>
<enddate>2015-04-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dragon Ball Z: Fukkatsu no "F"</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Z: Resurrection of "F"</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Z: Revival of "F"</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">DBZ Movie 15</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドラゴンボールZ 復活の「F」</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dragon Ball Z: Resurrection "F"</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Dragon Ball Z : La Résurrection de `F`</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Dragon Ball Z: O Renascimento de F</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9314" type="Prequel">Dragon Ball Z: Kami to Kami</anime>
<anime id="11210" type="Alternative Setting">Dragon Ball Super</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.dragonball2015.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2099" type="Animation Character Design">Yamamuro Tadayoshi</name>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="1902" type="Character Design">Toriyama Akira</name>
<name id="1902" type="Original Work">Toriyama Akira</name>
<name id="2099" type="Direction">Yamamuro Tadayoshi</name>
<name id="15540" type="Music">Sumitomo Norihito</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr5372 [Weekly Shounen Jump].
One year after http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Goku]`s battle with http://anidb.net/ch53774 [Beerus], remnants of http://anidb.net/ch9009 [Frieza]`s army attempt to revive their long-dead master. After learning that Goku has far surpassed the power he showed in their battle on Namek, Frieza spends 4 months training.
Goku &amp; http://anidb.net/ch2105 [Vegeta] are not on Earth and are training under http://anidb.net/ch53770 [Whis], so http://anidb.net/ch10070 [Bulma] gathers the rest of the gang to fight against the revived Frieza and protect the universe that is once again under grave threat.
Note: Pre-screened via lottery on March 30 in Japan and on April 11 in Los Angeles. Regular cinematic release in Japan on April 18.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="713">5.27</permanent>
<temporary count="721">6.49</temporary>
<review count="1">3.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>164388.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16549</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>25389</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dragonball2015.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dragon_Ball_Z:_Resurrection_'F'</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドラゴンボールZ_復活の「F」</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1062</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17947</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0146DO50W</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3870" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>resurrection</name>
<description>At least one character in this anime is brought back from the dead or from a near-death experience. This is achieved by either very advanced technology or simply magic.</description>
<picurl>191152.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2085" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="689">8.50</rating>
<name>Kame Sennin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kame Sennin is an ancient and wise martial arts master and the first Earthling to wield the Kamehameha. Though he seems frail, he is a mighty warrior, having trained Grandpa Gohan, Gyuumaou, Son Gokuu, and others.</description>
<picture>135368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2103" type="main character in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="2804">8.56</rating>
<name>Son Gokuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son Gokuu is a Saiyajin warrior who was sent to Earth when he was a child.</description>
<picture>135352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2105" type="main character in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="1212">8.57</rating>
<name>Vegeta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vegeta is the prince of the Saiyajin race and http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu]`s most fearsome rival. He is a very prideful person and, as a full-blooded saiyajin, loves the prospect of a good battle.</description>
<picture>230630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="132" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9009" type="main character in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="176">5.16</rating>
<name>Freezer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Freezer was the main antagonist in the Freezer Saga of http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z]. He`s an alien tyrant with plans of universal domination. He`s cunning, charismatic, arrogant, imperative and, of course, powerful. He possesses different abilities such as ki manipulation and transformation. He also has high survivability, as he could live on even when wounded and thrown away into outer space.</description>
<picture>133698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9915" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="187">5.58</rating>
<name>Son Gohan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gohan is introduced as the first son of the primary protagonist, Son Goku, and his wife, Chi Chi, in volume #17 of the original manga, or the premiere episode of its animated adaptation, Dragon Ball Z. Gohan is the first Saiyan/Human hybrid in the series.
As opposed to full-blooded Saiyans, whose hair stays the same from birth, Gohan`s is drawn at varying lengths, and changes markedly in style. Many of Yamcha`s hairstyles are used by Gohan at various points in his life.
Initially, Gohan is illustrated garbed in a Hanfu-like surcoat with the Chinese character 孫, fixed on the front and the four-star Dragon Ball fitted on top of his hat. Piccolo later supplies him with a keikogi fashioned after Goku`s, but substitutes it with the demon character "魔" as a sign of his admission into the Demon Tribe. Normally thereafter, Gohan is drawn with a keikogi modeled after Piccolo`s own, with the anime recoloring his wristbands from blue to red and, during the Cell Games tournament, his obi from red to blue, despite reverting to the original colors for the former. On Namek, Gohan is portrayed in battle armor worn by Frieza`s henchmen, having been given it by Vegeta in preparation for their encounter with Frieza. Prior to his second fight with Majin Buu, Gohan asks Kibito for an outfit resembling his father`s, and is then drawn in a keikogi identical to Goku`s.</description>
<picture>135354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11416" type="appears in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="557">7.67</rating>
<name>Piccolo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Piccolo, whose full name is Piccolo Jr., was first introduced as the reincarnation of the evil http://anidb.net/ch22168 [Piccolo Daimaou] in http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], making him a demon and arch-rival of the primary protagonist, http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Son Gokuu]. However, it is later revealed that he is from the race of alien beings called Namekians and he decides to team up with http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] and his friends in order to beat newer, more dangerous threats.</description>
<picture>135357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11420" type="appears in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="85">5.23</rating>
<name>Tenshinhan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially an enemy of Goku who was trained by Kame Sennin`s rival Tsuru Sennin, Tenshinhan soon makes peace with Goku and becomes a Z Fighter along with his friend Chaozu.</description>
<picture>135362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19619" type="appears in" update="2016-09-22">
<rating votes="219">7.16</rating>
<name>Jinzouningen 18 Gou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jinzouningen 18 Gou (Android #18 in the English adaptations) is a fictional character who first appears in the Dragon Ball manga created by http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira], followed by the shows http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z] and http://anidb.net/a233 [Dragon Ball GT]. She is a mass murderer in http://anidb.net/ch13302 [Future Trunks]` timeline.
Originally a human, she and her brother were modified into cyborgs by http://anidb.net/ch18381 [Dr. Gero].
On a Q&amp;A with mangaka http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira] published May 2nd, 2014 it was revealed that her human name was Lazuli.
After http://anidb.net/ch20915 [Cell] is defeated, http://anidb.net/ch11414 [Kuririn] uses the Dragon Balls to wish for her and her brother to be turned into humans; http://anidb.net/ch7015 [Shenron] is unable to perform this task because of the unfathomable differences in power between him and the duo, so he wishes instead for their self destruct devices to be removed. Kuririn pursues her and, at some point, they marry and have a daughter named http://anidb.net/ch30874 [Marron].
To clear up the heavily espoused misconception that she is a pure android and therefore could not have a child, Kuririn went on to explain to http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Son Gokuu] during the Tenkaichi Budoukai Saga that she was originally human but that Dr. Gero just "remodeled her a little bit."</description>
<picture>135365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53770" type="appears in" update="2019-10-19">
<rating votes="11">5.20</rating>
<name>Whis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Whis is the caretaker as well as trainer of http://anidb.net/ch53774 [Beerus], the god of destruction of Universe 7.
He and his siblings are one of the strongest beings in all of creation, only admitting that his father http://anidb.net/ch84322 [Daishinkan] and http://anidb.net/ch82121 [King of All] are stronger.</description>
<picture>60037.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53771" type="appears in" update="2015-08-09">
<rating votes="6">2.15</rating>
<name>Yogen-gyo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yogen-gyo is a blue fish which has prophetic powers, which http://anidb.net/ch53774 [Beerus] keeps as a pet.
Source: Dragon Ball Wikia</description>
<picture>135381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3929" picture="25678.jpg">Nakagawa Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53774" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="31">5.08</rating>
<name>Beerus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Beerus is the God of Destruction, an individual that`s been around for centuries having destroyed several planets, solar systems and races. Even the mighty saiyajin king Vegeta once bowed in terror infront of him. Beerus even sees Freezer as little more than a nuisance that was too far away to deal with.
Beerus spends most of his time either sleeping for decades at a time or traveling around the universe destroying planets, eating whatever people offer him or in general doing whatever he feels like doing.
Beerus might have a short temperament and with his title God of Destruction may sound quite evil but despite all this, he is not a bad guy in general but rather more of in the gray area, always honoring his words and not doing things unnecessarily.
He is currently the second strongest individual in the Dragonball world. http://anidb.net/ch9004 [Super Saiyajin 3 Gokuu] was nothing but a toy for him. Even after http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] ascended to Super Saiyajin God and came back with an increased power, he still did not manage to push Beerus to fight at more than 60% of his full power.
Note: As is the case with most of the main cast from Dragonball, Beerus`s name is a pun. In this case, it`s two puns meshed into one. The original pun was on the word `virus` as scriptwriter, Watanabe Yuusuke, stated in an interview with DVD &amp; Blu-ray Magazine that he had written a scenario in which the God of Destruction was actually the one responsible for originally infecting the Saiyajins with evil. However, when Toriyama Akira stepped in and changed a great deal of the movie`s backstory, he thought Beerus`s name was a pun on the English word `beer` and then followed suit by naming http://anidb.net/ch53770 [Whis] (ウイス or uisu) after `whiskey`, another alcoholic beverage.</description>
<picture>169214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55083" type="appears in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="14">3.08</rating>
<name>Kuririn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55084" type="appears in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="20">5.15</rating>
<name>Videl</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55085" type="appears in" update="2016-09-22">
<rating votes="143">6.68</rating>
<name>Bulma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55092" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="7">5.71</rating>
<name>Pilaf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55093" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="9">3.50</rating>
<name>Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55094" type="appears in" update="2013-11-20">
<rating votes="14">3.92</rating>
<name>Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1811" picture="222844.jpg">Yamada Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72561" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-05">
<rating votes="3">1.64</rating>
<name>Sorbet</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4731" picture="27599.jpg">Saitou Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72562" type="appears in" update="2015-01-05">
<rating votes="4">1.60</rating>
<name>Tagoma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79026" type="appears in" update="2015-12-22">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Jaco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82955" type="appears in" update="2016-07-13">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Pan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188352.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="83562" type="appears in" update="2016-08-04">
<rating votes="25">6.93</rating>
<name>Freezer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Freezer`s true form.</description>
<picture>64037.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105588" type="appears in" update="2019-09-26">
<name>Freezer Gun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Freezer Gun is the organisation controlled a majority of Universe 7 at the peak of its power and serves as the primary antagonistic force of the first half of the Dragon Ball Z series. Freezer`s father, Cold Daio was the leader of the organisation prior to passing control over to his son.
The organisation employs and enslaves powerful races, such as the Saiyans, to take over suitable planets so that they can be sold to the highest bidders, or alternatively to destroy planets which are determined to be not financially viable. Freezer`s forces are equipped with scouters, portable computers mainly used to measure power levels, and wear standard-issue battle armor which usually have dual shoulder guards, matching gloves and Buuts, and some form of skirt armor or crotch guard.
Freezer himself does not really consider his soldiers as an army, looking at them more as a convenient group of followers. In reality, the soldiers follow him and his relatives out of fear, though some soldiers are known to be fiercely loyal to Freezer such as the Ginyu Force.
Source: Wikipedia
When Freezer took over the business from his father in 732, most of the soldiers came from Planet Vegeta. However, Freezer became fearful of the power of the saiyajin and worked to make the army less saiyajin reliant. In five years from his accession, he destroyed Planet Vegeta, and cutting the size of the army in half.
In 762, the army took heavy losses while fighting on Planet Namek for the Dragon Balls, but was ultimately defeated.
In 764, the army attempt to invade Planet Earth, which proved even more fatal, as Freezer and Cold Daio were slain. Hence the army has reduced to a rump under http://anidb.net/ch72561 [Sorbet].
In 779, the army had become a shadow of its former self, as many words had liberated themselves. Thus Sorbet made a desperate attempt to fix the empire by resurrecting Freezer with the help of the Dragon Balls. However, Freezer was disinterested in fixing his empire and instead set on wasting the remaining resources of the army in order to pursue vengeance; a decision which ended in his, Sorbet`s and the bulk of the army`s soldiers` deaths.
In 780, when Freezer was resurrected for the second time, with the guidance of http://anidb.net/ch105587 [Beriblu] and http://anidb.net/ch105586 [Kikono], he decided to rebuild the army.</description>
<picture>67928.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="164029" update="2015-04-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2015-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169557" update="2015-07-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode T1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178512" update="2016-07-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">"Z" no Chikai Music Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178513" update="2016-07-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Voices of Dragon Ball Z</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178514" update="2016-07-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Return of Dragon Ball Z</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178515" update="2016-07-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178516" update="2016-07-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">US Blu-ray trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198030" update="2018-04-15">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">映画「ドラゴンボールZ 復活の「F」」"未来"トランクス特別編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Future Trunks Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eiga "Dragon Ball Z: Fukkatsu no "F"" "Mirai" Trunks Tokubetsu Hen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
