<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10744" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2014-12-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Madan no Ou to Vanadis</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">마탄의 왕과 바나디스</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔弾の王と戦姫[ヴァナディース]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Lord Marksman and Vanadis</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Владыка волшебных стрел и девы войны</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">魔弹之王与战姫</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11679" approval="20" total="30">Nejimaki Seirei Senki: Tenkyou no Alderamin</anime>
<anime id="12496" approval="19" total="22">Grancrest Senki</anime>
<anime id="9287" approval="4" total="12">Maoyuu Maou Yuusha</anime>
<anime id="9973" approval="1" total="6">Hitsugi no Chaika</anime>
<anime id="6331" approval="1" total="4">Guin Saga</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="31909">Light novels are much better. The tv series wasnt bad but felt rushed and very short while the books had more to offer.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="616779">Meh - alright not everything is bad in this show - it has some quite interesting characters, a fair but cliché plot with an ok world and an adventurous taste to it --but yea -- i cant help to be Objective and point out how AVERAGE this show is OVERALL: it feels like it has been written by a 3rd rate author , it has no depth, characters are mostly introduced by boobs shots, relationship are simplified to the extreme (like most LN stories) with a  too good to be true MC... action sequence  are cut by poor choice of editing and music , and a lot of slow and fan service all over the show make for a mediocre result --- so , i guess its ok if u have nothing to watch it would be fairly entertaining..... but i would think most people have better anime or things to do instead of watching this --</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="366878">Not bad. It has an interesting story which makes me watch it consistently from the start to the end. The only weakness in my opinion is its forced ending. However, it is open-ended I would not be surprised if there is a continuation to this story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="780947">decent pass time imo easily could have been better but I enjoyed the music</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.madan-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3613" type="Direction">Satou Tatsuo</name>
<name id="1043" type="Animation Work">Satelight</name>
<name id="1766" type="Character Design">Kabashima Yousuke</name>
<name id="3613" type="Series Composition">Satou Tatsuo</name>
<name id="40440" type="Original Work">Kawaguchi Tsukasa</name>
<name id="1766" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kabashima Yousuke</name>
<name id="3326" type="Music">Yokoyama Masaru</name>
<name id="40986" type="Music">Nobusawa Nobuaki</name>
</creators>
<description>In times of war, set in Western Europe, http://anidb.net/ch68735 [Eleonora Viltaria], one of the seven Vanadis of Zhcted, leads the war into Brune. There are actually seven Vanadis, named like this because they each received a powerful weapon from the dragon, to reign over seven territories, each possessing their own. The power of the Vanadis causes dread and fear toward their enemies. An Earl in the service of the country of Brune, a young archer called http://anidb.net/ch68734 [Tigre], got a taste of it after he was defeated on the battlefield by Ellen (Eleonora). However, Ellen decided to spare his life after seeing his skills. In exchange, he is asked to serve her.
Source: Baka-Tsuki</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1820">4.48</permanent>
<temporary count="1830">6.47</temporary>
<review count="2">3.91</review>
</ratings>
<picture>158459.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16170</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>27857</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>24455</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madan-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Madan_no_Ō_to_Vanadis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔弾の王と戦姫</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3509</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349819</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17582</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>lord-marksman-and-vanadis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00TYBAH3G</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1664" parentid="2881" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-20">
<name>horse riding</name>
<description>Equestrianism (from Latin equester, equestr-, horseman, horse) more often known as riding, horseback riding (American English) or horse riding (British English) refers to the skill of riding, driving, or vaulting with horses. This broad description includes the use of horses for practical working purposes, transportation, recreational activities, artistic or cultural exercises, and competitive sport.</description>
<picurl>47385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3481" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-04-19">
<name>recruiting teammates</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3581" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>tactics</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4274" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>hidden agenda</name>
<description>Someone or some organization/government/etc. is misrepresenting themselves by doing/saying one thing while hoping/striving for something else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="68734" type="main character in" update="2014-09-02">
<rating votes="31">6.09</rating>
<name>Tigrevurmud Vorn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68735" type="main character in" update="2014-09-02">
<rating votes="43">7.53</rating>
<name>Eleonora Viltaria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69461" type="appears in" update="2014-10-01">
<rating votes="14">6.24</rating>
<name>Alexandra Alshavin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69462" type="appears in" update="2014-10-01">
<rating votes="12">6.14</rating>
<name>Elizaveta Fomina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69463" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-02">
<rating votes="20">6.14</rating>
<name>Sofya Obertas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69464" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-02">
<rating votes="26">5.56</rating>
<name>Titta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69465" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-02">
<rating votes="31">7.14</rating>
<name>Limalisha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69466" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-02">
<rating votes="31">7.26</rating>
<name>Ludmila Lourie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69467" type="appears in" update="2014-10-01">
<rating votes="8">6.29</rating>
<name>Valentina Glinka Estes</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69785" type="appears in" update="2014-10-20">
<rating votes="2">1.12</rating>
<name>Zion Thenardier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69786" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-02">
<rating votes="7">4.33</rating>
<name>Bertrand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69787" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-03">
<rating votes="6">1.99</rating>
<name>Felix Aaron Thenardier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162221.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69788" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-02">
<rating votes="7">4.18</rating>
<name>Mashas Rodant</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="318" picture="69041.jpg">Iijima Hajime</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69789" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-05">
<rating votes="8">3.77</rating>
<name>Rurick</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69790" type="appears in" update="2014-11-07">
<rating votes="3">6.75</rating>
<name>Roland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70309" type="appears in" update="2014-10-01">
<rating votes="5">3.64</rating>
<name>Olga Tamm</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162128.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70449" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-03">
<rating votes="5">1.32</rating>
<name>Maximilian Bennusa Ganelon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162220.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70736" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Steed</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70737" type="appears in" update="2014-10-18">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Dorekavak</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37281" picture="151721.jpg">Nemoto Akihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70738" type="appears in" update="2014-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Urs Vorn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162910.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70739" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kodomo Tigre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70740" type="appears in" update="2014-10-18">
<rating votes="2">9.76</rating>
<name>Kodomo Titta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70813" type="appears in" update="2014-10-20">
<rating votes="2">7.48</rating>
<name>Lunie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163035.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70815" type="appears in" update="2014-10-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kuro Yumi no Koe</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>It`s a bow. A black bow. It speaks.</description>
<picture>163038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71221" type="appears in" update="2014-11-07">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Viktor Kokuou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3102" picture="24178.jpg">Chou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71222" type="appears in" update="2014-11-29">
<rating votes="1">9.13</rating>
<name>Hugues Auger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3239" picture="225574.jpg">Ito Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71777" type="appears in" update="2014-11-29">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Olivier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10130" picture="151714.jpg">Takumi Yasuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71778" type="appears in" update="2014-11-29">
<rating votes="2">2.25</rating>
<name>Pierre Baudouin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165177.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71786" type="appears in" update="2014-11-29">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Qasim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71787" type="appears in" update="2014-11-29">
<rating votes="3">5.95</rating>
<name>Gerald Auger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71788" type="appears in" update="2014-11-29">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Fallon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71789" type="appears in" update="2014-11-29">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Dorei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71790" type="appears in" update="2014-11-29">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71791" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="3">5.57</rating>
<name>Tabi no Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12783" picture="225340.jpg">Fujii Yukiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72484" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Kureys Shahin Balamir</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2230" picture="21782.jpg">Iwasaki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72487" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Emile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72488" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="1">6.80</rating>
<name>Auguste</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42036" picture="186168.jpg">Takashina Toshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72489" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Scheie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72493" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="7">6.68</rating>
<name>Regin Estelle Loire Bastien de Charles</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12783" picture="225340.jpg">Fujii Yukiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72494" type="appears in" update="2015-01-02">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kodomo Regnas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12783" picture="225340.jpg">Fujii Yukiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="162791" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">凍漣の雪姫[ミーチェリア]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow Princess of the Frozen Ripple</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Princesse de la neige et de la glace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michelia</title>
<summary>Elen returns to Zhcted, and answers to the king for invading Brune without his permission, while Tigre tries to muster more help. Ludmilla, one of the other war maidens, may prove to be an obstacle in Tigre and Elen`s war against Thenardier.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162792" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">甦る魔弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return of the Magic Marksman</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Résurrection de l`arc magique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Madan</title>
<summary>With the town safe, Elen and Tigre make plans to drive Zion`s army out of Alsace. They are still outnumbered three-to-one, however, and must come up with some brilliant strategies if they are to succeed in defending Tigre`s homeland.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162793" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Return Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan</title>
<summary>Duke Thenardier sends his son Zion to raze Tigre`s fiefdom of Alsace. Tigre prepares to return and defend his home, but as her prisoner, Elen imposes conditions on letting him go. Titta defends the Vorn estate while she awaits Tigre`s return.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="162794" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦場の風姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wind Princess of the Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Princesse du vent sur le champ de bataille</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senjou no Kazehime</title>
<summary>Count Tigrevurmud Vorn of the Brunish territory of Alsace is taken prisoner by Eleonora Viltaria, a war maiden of the neighboring kingdom of Zhcted. She will return him to Brune if his ransom is paid, but she has another reason for keeping him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163085" update="2014-10-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163086" update="2014-10-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163238" update="2018-05-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ 第0話「戦姫とのそーぐー」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 0</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tigre-kun to Vanadi-chu Dai 0 Wa "Senki to no Souguu"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163401" update="2014-10-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ はげしく突け!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Hageshiku Tsuke!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163554" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二千対二万</title>
<title xml:lang="en">2,000 vs. 20,000</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">2 000 contre 20 000</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nisen Tai Niman</title>
<summary>Elen is called back to Zhcted on urgent business, leaving Tigre and Rurick in charge of 1000 of her men. Roland heads to the royal capital to plead Tigre`s case before the king. A massive invasion force from Muozinel threatens all of Brune.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163555" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">守るために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Protect</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pour le protéger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamoru Tame ni</title>
<summary>With Tigre seriously injured, Elen takes command of his men and prepares to fight Roland`s forces the next day. Mashas returns from the capital with news of the king. Tigre and Titta follow the black bow`s guidance in search of greater power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163556" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chevalier noir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro Kishi</title>
<summary>Mila and Tigre reach an understanding. A united army of men from both Brune and Zhcted is formed, led by Tigre and Elen, but it is not without its difficulties. Sofy reaches Elen with bad news, while Roland, the Black Knight, is sent to deal with Tigre.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163557" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タトラ山攻略戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Storming of the Tatra Mountains</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`attaque de Tatras</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatrasan Kouryakusen</title>
<summary>When Mila abruptly leaves Rodnik, Elen fears that it spells hostilities between their two lands. Their two armies meet on a snowy battlefield, but when Mila`s forces retreat to a safe haven, Elen must figure out how she is going to claim victory.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="163616" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ 買い食いの戦姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Kaigui no Senki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163917" update="2018-05-13">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ 覚醒めるくまたん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Mezameru Kuma-tan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163924" update="2014-11-03">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ 天然の耀姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Tennen no Presuvet</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163925" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ あたたかな何かときれいな何かと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Atatakana Nanika to Kirei na Nanika to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163926" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ 可愛いくまとやわらかい何かと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Kawaii Kuma to Yawarakai Nanika to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163927" update="2014-11-03">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ くま好き一人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Kumazuki Hitori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164098" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">広がる世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Widening World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde s`agrandit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hirogaru Sekai</title>
<summary>Devastated by his surrogate father`s loss, Tigre is comforted by Elen. Badouin shows up, and invites Regin back to see the king, who has regained his senses. However, Thenardier stands in their way, and a final showdown between him and Tigre awaits!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164099" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖窟宮[サングロエル]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Holy Grotto (Saint-Groel)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Grotte sacrée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saint Groel</title>
<summary>After resting up briefly from the battle with Thenardier`s army, Tigre and the others plan to make their way into the Holy Grotto beneath Artesium, to establish Regin`s royal identity. However, Thenardier has other plans for them once they arrive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164100" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦姫二人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two War Maidens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux Vanadis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senki Futari</title>
<summary>The battle against Muozinel behind them, the Silver Meteor Storm camps in Perche, where Regin makes a surprise announcement to Tigre and the others. With his dragons now mature, Thenardier sends his army to attack the Silver Meteor Storm.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164101" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オルメア会戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ormea Campaign</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille d`Ormea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ormea Kaisen</title>
<summary>With overwhelming numbers, the Muozinellan army lays seige to the makeshift hilltop fortress, as Tigre and Mila`s forces strike back. But with such a long battle ahead of them, will they be able to last long enough to achieve victory?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164102" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷渦と煌炎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thunder Swirl and Luminous Flame</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tonnerre et flamme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raika to Kouen</title>
<summary>Elen visits Sasha, and learns that Elizaveta, one of the other war maidens, is attacking her lands over a perceived slight. Meanwhile, Mila and Tigre negotiate the terms of her assistance in driving the invading Muozinel army out of the land.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="164322" update="2014-11-20">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ 幕間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Makuai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164323" update="2014-11-20">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ 明かされてしまった真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Akasareteshimatta Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164324" update="2014-11-20">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ 明かされかける真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Akasarekakeru Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164325" update="2014-11-20">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ こっそり集結</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Kossori Shuuketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164326" update="2014-11-20">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ 皮肉 対 禿頭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Hiniku tai Tokutou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164855" update="2014-12-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165095" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165096" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165097" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165098" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165099" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165100" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165101" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165102" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165103" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165104" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165105" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165106" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165107" update="2015-01-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode Previews 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165399" update="2018-11-11">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ティグルくんとヴァナディーちゅ もう一つのエピローグ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tigre-kun and Vanadi-chu 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tiger-kun to Vanadi-chu: Mouhitotsu no Epilogue</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
