<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10785" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-22</startdate>
<enddate>2015-02-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Wake Up, Girl Zoo!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">わぐZOO!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">wug zoo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">うぇいくあっぷがーるZOO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Wake Up, Girl Zoo!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13554" type="Sequel">Wake Up, Girl Zoo! Miyagi PR de Go!</anime>
<anime id="9417" type="Alternative Setting">Wake Up, Girls!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2824" approval="1" total="1">Damekko Doubutsu</anime>
<anime id="14223" approval="1" total="1">Youkoso Japari Park</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="460944">I think that the tongue-in-cheek recreation of the WUG story as we know it in the boundaries of a zoo setting is actually kind of clever and it`s just oh so cute. I, for one, want more of this. It`s the epitome of lightheartedness, short and fun. Not a "must see" per se, but for those who enjoyed the main WUG story highly recommended.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://wug-zoo.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1560" type="Work">Ordet</name>
<name id="29349" type="Direction">Morii Kenshirou</name>
<name id="40631" type="Work">Studio Moriken</name>
<name id="40633" type="Character Design">Miyajima Seiya</name>
</creators>
<description>A small zoo, at the outskirts of Sendai in north-eastern Japan is facing the imminent demise, about to be absorbed by the I-1 Park. The curator Tange orders zookeeper Matsuda to scout for new animals, after even their last animal, an elephant, died.
Matsuda advertises: "Become an idol! Comes with three meals and a nap."
And so seven girls in animal costumes decide to help out and join the zoo: the tiger http://anidb.net/ch69355 [Minami] is interested in the free food, the bear http://anidb.net/ch69357 [Yoshino] just wants to help out, then there is the attention-hungry eagle http://anidb.net/ch69356 [Miyu], the shark http://anidb.net/ch69351 [Airi] looking to become an idol, the career-focused wolf http://anidb.net/ch69353 [Nanami], the crocodile http://anidb.net/ch69352 [Kaya] wanting to change herself, and finally the lion http://anidb.net/ch69354 [Mayu] set on getting fed while napping the rest of the time.
But can the actions of these assembled seven creatures bring back the Wake Up Girl Zoo from the brink?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="149">3.23</permanent>
<temporary count="150">5.30</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>159464.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16315</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>25875</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://wug-zoo.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Wake_Up,_Girls!#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Wake_Up,_Girls!#Web.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>351248</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17663</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="69351" type="main character in" update="2014-08-10">
<name>Airi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38298" picture="222818.jpg">Eino Airi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69352" type="main character in" update="2014-08-10">
<name>Kaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38294" picture="150942.jpg">Okuno Kaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69353" type="main character in" update="2014-08-10">
<name>Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38295" picture="222841.jpg">Yamashita Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69354" type="main character in" update="2014-08-10">
<name>Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159471.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38299" picture="222837.jpg">Yoshioka Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69355" type="main character in" update="2014-08-10">
<name>Minami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38297" picture="150939.jpg">Tanaka Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69356" type="main character in" update="2014-08-10">
<name>Miyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38293" picture="150943.jpg">Takagi Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69357" type="main character in" update="2014-08-10">
<name>Yoshino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38296" picture="228671.jpg">Aoyama Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92097" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-02">
<name>Tange-enchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209135.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92098" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-02">
<name>Matsuda-shiikuin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="162541" update="2014-10-13">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第1話・お試し版</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 1 Wa Otameshi Han</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163399" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水族館でGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aquarium Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suizokukan de Go!</title>
<summary>Nanami and her friends exchange ideas to get "Wake Up, Girls ZOO" back on its feet. The girls come up with a plan to create an aquarium, a popular and typical date destination, to bring in the money.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>666409</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163400" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">動物園でGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wake Up, Girls! ZOO</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doubutsuen de Go!</title>
<summary>"Wake Up, Girls ZOO" is a small zoo on the outskirts of Sendai. Due to the careless management of Curator Tange and the advancement of national theme park "I-1 Park", the zoo is in danger of disappearing. Curator Tange decides to take the next step by forming an animal unit.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>666407</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164007" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怪談でGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scary Story Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaidan de Go!</title>
<summary>The girls gather in a single room due to leaks and power outages in the zoo. At first the girls enjoy the sleepover-like experience, but Minami and the girls don`t return after leaving for the bathroom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>666411</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164384" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲームでGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Game Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Game de Go!</title>
<summary>"Is there any meaning to an eagle who cannot fly?" I met a young girl named Miyu in the zoo at dusk.
From October 22nd, 2014, to February 25, 2015, I shall exchange countless words with Miyu and come to understand her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>666413</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164618" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フィギュアでGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Figures Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Figure de Go!</title>
<summary>Thank you for your phone call. This is Zoonet Shimada. You`re calling to place an order? Thank you! You`d like the product that appeared on the previous broadcast? Very well. Please give me a moment to confirm your order. Excuse me. (Hold Music) Thank you for waiting. Would you like to purchase the "Polar Bear with a Shark in its Mouth figurine" introduced on Zoonet TV for 7,980 yen? Okay, thank you.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>666415</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164657" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロレスでGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Absolute Champion vs the True Leader</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pro Wres de Go!</title>
<summary>In order to save the zoo, the members of WUG ZOO formed WUG, a new pro wrestling organization.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668351</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164658" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一点豪華主義でGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Single Grand Attraction Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itten Gouka Shugi de Go!</title>
<summary>If the zoo is short on funds, why don`t we bring in guests with a single grand attraction?" At Nanami`s suggestion, the animals work to create a single grand attraction, but perhaps they should have gone for a swimsuit episode instead. What does the future have in store for the Wake Up, Girls ZOO?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668349</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="164659" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2014-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チラシ配りでGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distributing Fliers Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chirashi Kubari de Go!</title>
<summary>While handing out fliers, I sometimes wonder if I`m invisible to everyone. One day I was shocked and amazed by the sight that unfolded before me. Since then I`ve started thinking maybe I can do anything if I put my mind to it! That`s right! I`m not just a farm animal! Let`s get busy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>666417</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165710" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終回でGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Episode Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saishuukai de Go!</title>
<summary>The members of WUG ZOO decide to participate in the Animal Festival! Will everyone be able to make it to the very end?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668355</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165711" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦隊ヒーローでGO!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">WUG Zoo Ranger Show</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentai Hero de Go!</title>
<summary>Suddenly, a band of righteous heroes known as the WUG Zoo Rangers appears!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>668353</identifier>
<identifier>wake-up-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194532" update="2017-12-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2015-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Blu-ray Special Feature</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
