<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10782" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2015-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Re-Kan!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">レーカン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Re-Kan!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">灵感少女</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8245" approval="4" total="5">Honto ni Atta! Reibai-sensei</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="318511">Orochimaru reborn as erocat.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="20352">Lovely and entertaining. Has some good funny moments. And some good emotional moments as well. Recommended for light viewing.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/re-kan/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6017" type="Music">Kouzu Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="17096" type="Character Design">Yamamoto Midori</name>
<name id="6742" type="Series Composition">Aoshima Takashi</name>
<name id="5806" type="Direction">Kudou Masashi</name>
<name id="41563" type="Original Work">Seta Hinako</name>
<name id="17916" type="Animation Work">Pierrot Plus</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="17096" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamoto Midori</name>
<name id="3068" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishibashi Yukiko</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch71985 [Amami Hibiki] is a girl who can see ghosts and other supernatural phenomena in her surroundings. The stories follow her daily life with both her friends and the otherworldly.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="729">4.18</permanent>
<temporary count="731">6.13</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>169954.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16597</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>25859</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/re-kan/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Re-Kan!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>レーカン!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3697</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>349940</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17975</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="71983" type="main character in" update="2014-12-12">
<rating votes="9">6.22</rating>
<name>Uehara Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22171" picture="173757.jpg">Iida Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71984" type="main character in" update="2014-12-12">
<rating votes="14">6.68</rating>
<name>Inoue Narumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37283" picture="238137.jpg">Itou Miku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71985" type="main character in" update="2014-12-12">
<rating votes="14">7.03</rating>
<name>Amami Hibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71986" type="main character in" update="2014-12-12">
<rating votes="10">6.14</rating>
<name>Ogawa Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37227" picture="195131.jpg">Yamazaki Erii</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71987" type="main character in" update="2014-12-12">
<rating votes="11">6.83</rating>
<name>Esumi Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73187" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-10">
<rating votes="1">2.29</rating>
<name>Ero Neko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73188" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-10">
<rating votes="4">8.05</rating>
<name>Kogyaru Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73189" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-10">
<rating votes="4">8.64</rating>
<name>Merry-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73190" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-10">
<rating votes="1">3.62</rating>
<name>Daihen Zamurai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5040" picture="88977.jpg">Kawahara Yoshihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73191" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-10">
<rating votes="5">5.55</rating>
<name>Hanako-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39921" picture="225566.jpg">Izawa Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73192" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-10">
<rating votes="3">4.86</rating>
<name>Kaonashi Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36907" picture="135730.jpg">Kino Futaba</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74295" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-03">
<rating votes="5">1.61</rating>
<name>Yamada Kenta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>171377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36495" picture="176250.jpg">Yamaya Yoshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74296" type="appears in" update="2015-07-06">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Amami Yuuhi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74297" type="appears in" update="2015-07-06">
<name>Amami Asahi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76248" type="appears in" update="2015-07-06">
<name>Yamada Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="25068" picture="70119.jpg">Kajikawa Shouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="167326" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏といえば, 海です.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Means the Beach.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Toieba, Umi Desu.</title>
<summary>Amami and her friends join their classmate Yamada Kenta on a trip to the coast. 
For some reason the beach is almost empty and the kids couldn`t be happier...except for Esumi Kyouko. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678277</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167327" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美味しい, 卵焼きです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Delicious Fried Eggs.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oishii, Tamagoyaki Desu.</title>
<summary>Inoue`s bratty little cousin Yuuki is visiting. She`s trying to cater to him 
by cooking his favorite breakfast (fried eggs) every morning, but he complains about the 
awful taste every time! Amami vows to help Inoue cook the best eggs ever, but after 
consulting with a nearby ghost, she learns that maybe Yuuki wants something more than 
just better flavor?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678275</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167328" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしの, お友達です.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">They`re My Friends.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no, Otomodachi Desu.</title>
<summary>Nightmares about the lecherous neighborhood stray cat have been keeping 
Amami up at night, so a few nearby spirits have taken to answering the morning 
roll-call in her stead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678273</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167329" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたし, 視[み]えるんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can See Them.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi, Mierun Desu.</title>
<summary>Amami Hibiki has been able see ghosts and spirits since she was a young child. 
Rather than fear the otherworldly spirits, the kind young lady quickly befriends them. 
After transferring to a new school her classmates quickly adjust to Amami’s tendency to 
talk to empty space and walk around invisible obstacles...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678271</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167514" update="2015-04-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167515" update="2015-04-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167924" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなで, 一緒に遊ぶんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s All Play Together.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna de, Issho ni Asobun Desu.</title>
<summary>Amami meets the ghost of a young girl who keeps repeating a
mysterious nonsense word: "Morya." No longer able to recall her life
or how she died, the roll-call samurai and Amami worry she may simply
fade away.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678285</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167925" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にぎやかな, 年明けです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Busy New Year.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nigiyaka na, Nen`ake Desu.</title>
<summary>When the gang sees a sleep-deprived Amami stumbling down the
street, they worry her inability to ignore her spectral friends is
putting her heath at risk. They decide to speak with her father Asahi,
who digs up a special pair glasses capable of blocking Amami`s sixth
sense.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678283</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167926" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チョベリグな, 聖夜です.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Super Awesome Holy Night.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choberigu na, Seiya Desu.</title>
<summary>Amami`s classmates are dumbfounded when she suddenly starts
acting like a total brat, until Uehara Kana snaps a picture that
reveals the truth: she`s been possessed by "gal ghost!"
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678281</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167927" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の, 文化祭です.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Culture Festival.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no, Bunkasai Desu.</title>
<summary>It`s time for the school culture festival! Under Amami`s supervision and the help of a few ghosts, her class decides to make a haunted house. The whole class (except Inoue) wants the result to be nothing short of legendary! 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678279</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168404" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんな, つながっているんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Are All Connected.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna, Tsunagatteirundesu.</title>
<summary>After her sixth sense suddenly vanishes, Amami wanders aimlessly searching for her spectral friends. Their voices, their faces, even their presence is nowhere to be found. Amami quickly falls into a deep depression over the loss of the friendships she`d formed
with the ghosts over the years, and Inoue and the rest of her living friends are at a loss for how to cheer her up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678293</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168405" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私の, お願いです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Wish.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no, Onegai Desu.</title>
<summary>Amami invites her friends over to her house for the Star Festival, and they`re excited for the visit when they learn about her late mother`s handmade decorations. According to Amami, they`re packed with mysterious powers that are all but guaranteed to make wishes come true...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678291</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168406" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いよいよ, 2年生です.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`ve Entered Our Second Year.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iyoiyo, 2 Nensei Desu.</title>
<summary>A new school year begins, and Amami and her friends are
pretty excited about having younger students around. Wanting to be a
model student, Amami tries to help the new freshman class...and so do
her spectral friends. The otherworldly assistance scares off the new
kids and leaves Amami feeling crushed, so Inoue and the others take it
upon themselves to make her more appealing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678289</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168407" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密の, バレンタインです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret Valentine.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu no, Valentine Desu.</title>
<summary>Valentine`s Day is getting closer and all the boys and girls
are getting restless. And when the gang finds out Amami wants to try
her hand at home-made chocolate, they can`t help but wonder who it`s
for! Tune in for a sweet, emotional Valentine`s Day episode. You`ll
never believe who Amami`s heart really belongs to!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678287</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169045" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の, 思い出です.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Memories.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no, Omoide Desu.</title>
<summary>Amami heads to a theme park with all her friends, living and otherwise (and Yamada`s older brother, for some reason)! According to her father, this particular theme park is the site of some fond memories for Amami, but now that she`s older the memories have begun
to fade...until a mysterious girl appears before her. Join the whole Re-Kan! gang as they make the most of a beautiful summer day, capped off with a sleepover at the Amami residence!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678295</identifier>
<identifier>re-kan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
