<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10800" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-08-01</startdate>
<enddate>2016-08-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Under the Dog</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">UNDER THE DOG</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11596" approval="1" total="2">Gravity Daze the Animation: Ouverture</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://under-the-dog.com/ja/</url>
<creators>
<name id="141" type="Direction">Andou Masahiro</name>
<name id="2950" type="Animation Work">Kinema Citrus</name>
<name id="44157" type="Original Work">Ishii Jirou</name>
<name id="6427" type="Character Design">Satou Masahiro</name>
<name id="16800" type="Animation Work">Orange</name>
<name id="16368" type="Series Composition">Koyanagi Keigo</name>
<name id="43167" type="Music">Kevin Penkin</name>
</creators>
<description>The story takes place in 2025 in Neo Tokyo, five years after a devastating terrorist attack at the Tokyo Olympics. In the wake of the tragedy, the U.N. formed a covert ops unit dedicated to seeking out and eliminating those responsible for the attack. http://anidb.net/ch69895 [Anthea Kallenberg], a girl of Swedish descent is a member of this elite group who has honed her combat abilities and has become a deadly assassin, but must come to terms as to who she really is.
Source: Creative Intelligence Arts via ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="637">4.07</permanent>
<temporary count="640">5.95</temporary>
<review count="1">5.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>159764.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18675</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>27387</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>32467</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://under-the-dog.com/jumbled/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://under-the-dog.com/ja/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1300298569/under-the-dog</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://under-the-dog.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Under_the_Dog</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Under_the_Dog</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>364001</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21336</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6358" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-18">
<name>crowdfunded</name>
<description>This anime was funded, at least partially, through a campaign on a crowdfunding website (e.g. Kickstarter, Makuake).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7086" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>soft science fiction</name>
<description>Soft science fiction is a type of science fiction in which the science presented is scientifically inaccurate or unimportant to the story, in contrast to http://anidb.net/t4667 [hard science fiction]. Its elements generally present themselves via artistic licence.
This is not to be confused with social science fiction, confusingly also called "soft science fiction", which is science fiction concerned with the "soft sciences" (social sciences), as opposed to the "hard sciences" (natural sciences).</description>
<picurl>222752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="69895" type="main character in" update="2016-08-04">
<rating votes="4">4.96</rating>
<name>Anthea Kallenberg</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anthea Kallenberg, a Swedish girl, is the team`s infiltrator and assassin who was personally raised by Colonel Amagata. She prides herself in her abilities in combat and for good reason. Because of her skill, Anthea is often given point on special operations, usually to get the other agents out of a jam.
Source: official site</description>
<picture>64032.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69896" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-04">
<rating votes="3">2.42</rating>
<name>Hyuuga Sayuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sayuri is a Japanese girl from Sapporo who was forced into service during middle school. As a young, intelligent girl, the art of espionage is her specialty. She is frequently paired together with Estella for missions to lure out otherwise hard to acquire targets.
Source: official site</description>
<picture>64035.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="45751" picture="186293.jpg">Takahashi Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69897" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-04">
<rating votes="3">2.83</rating>
<name>Estella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Estella is the veteran of the team having been recruited at age eight. She is a Spanish American girl skilled in long range combat, especially the sniper rifle. On missions, she is often paired with Sayuri. Although typically sarcastic, she can surprise with her warm hearted whims.
Source: official site</description>
<picture>64033.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="37280" picture="136935.jpg">Oozora Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69898" type="main character in" update="2016-08-04">
<rating votes="4">4.46</rating>
<name>Tougetsu Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hana is the main character of episode 1. Although not remarkably skilled in combat, her stereotypical Japanese high schooler exterior belies her unique gift to shift people`s` moods and mental states. Using her talent, she often gives much needed stability and catharsis to the team, helping shield them from their tremendous burdens. An all around nice girl with strong family ties, she lives with her family and brother.
Source: official site</description>
<picture>64034.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69899" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Amagata Jun`ichi Taisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amagata came to command the covert branch of the UN shortly after his discovery and subsequent rescue of Anthea from a human trafficking cell during a top secret mission in Scandinavia. A now former NATO soldier, Amagata poses as staff for the international school while he dictates and supervises the various missions and objectives for the team.
Source: official site</description>
</character>
<character id="69900" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Robert Raymonds</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="81928" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-29">
<rating votes="3">6.42</rating>
<name>Nanase Shun`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanase Shun`ichi is a 16-year-old student at a public school on Enoshima Island. Shun`ichi is quiet and withdrawn in class, and yet Hana appears to have taken a special interest in him.
Source: official site</description>
<picture>186275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83463" type="appears in" update="2016-08-01">
<name>Flowers</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="172953" update="2015-10-30">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Dog Trailer (SEP 2015) (1 min 6 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177326" update="2016-08-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2016-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-other">Under the Dog: Episode 0</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179539" update="2016-08-09">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Dog Trailer (APR 2016) (45 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179772" update="2019-01-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Dog Update Message: Anthea-chan</title>
<summary>Anthea-chan tries to order various weapon online but ends up getting sent the wrong package.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182131" update="2016-11-16">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197992" update="2018-04-14">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2018-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Anthea-chan Theater Edition</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197993" update="2018-04-14">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2018-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Dog: Jumbled</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
