<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10835" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2015-06-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Stardust Crusaders (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ジョジョの奇妙な冒険 スターダストクルセイダース エジプト編</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Stardust Crusaders Egypt Arc</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Stardust Crusaders (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">JoJo Part III: Stardust Crusaders (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Невероятните приключения на Джо-Джо и звездните кръстоносци: Египет</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Stardust Crusaders - Egypt Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">JJBASC2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">jojo3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">JJBA 2015</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">JoJo 2015</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">jojosc2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ジョジョの奇妙な冒険 スターダストクルセイダース (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Stardust Crusaders - Battle in Egypt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Stardust Crusaders - Battle in Egypt</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">JoJo的奇妙冒險 星塵鬥士 (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">JoJo的奇妙冒险 星尘斗士 (2015)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11734" type="Sequel">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Diamond wa Kudakenai</anime>
<anime id="10206" type="Prequel">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Stardust Crusaders</anime>
<anime id="788" type="Alternative Setting">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2"/>
<url>http://jojo-animation.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2887" type="Animation Work">David Production</name>
<name id="12357" type="Direction">Suzuki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="2702" type="Series Composition">Kobayashi Yasuko</name>
<name id="981" type="Original Work">Araki Hirohiko</name>
<name id="6306" type="Music">Kanno Yuugo</name>
</creators>
<description>Continuation of the http://anidb.net/a10206 [first half] of Stardust Crusaders.
http://anidb.net/ch894 [Joutarou], http://anidb.net/ch1742 [Joseph], http://anidb.net/ch1722 [Avdol], http://anidb.net/ch1732 [Kakyouin] &amp; http://anidb.net/ch1725 [Polnareff] have finally made it to Egypt in their quest to find and vanquish their sworn enemy, http://anidb.net/ch895 [DIO]. On their arrival to Egypt, they are joined by a new but unwilling ally, http://anidb.net/ch1739 [Iggy], who possesses the http://anidb.net/t133 [Stand], http://anidb.net/ch1741 [The Fool]. The crusaders are then informed that after they defeated all fourteen of DIO`s minions of the Tarot, nine more minions of the Egyptian Tarot have been dispatched by DIO to eliminate them. The crusaders continue their journey in Egypt to find DIO and confront the almighty Stand, http://anidb.net/ch1721 [The World].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1620">8.28</permanent>
<temporary count="1626">7.92</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>226411.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16303</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>26055</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://jojo-animation.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>JoJo's_Bizarre_Adventure:_Stardust_Crusaders</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ジョジョの奇妙な冒険</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3629</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>351064</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17002</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_jojo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2833" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Middle East</name>
<description>The Middle East is a transcontinental region centered on Western Asia, Turkey (both Asian and European), and Egypt (which is mostly in North Africa). The corresponding adjective is Middle Eastern and the derived noun is Middle Easterner. The term has come into wider usage as a replacement of the term Near East (as opposed to the Far East) beginning in the early 20th century.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192047.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2835" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Africa</name>
<description>The world`s second-largest continent and the birthplace of the human species, Africa is a place of a huge diversity, with deserts and savannas, with famine and precious stones, with cultural and economical riches of all kinds. Throughout history, Africa has been the cradle of empires and has been ruled by foreign powers, and as of the early 21st century sees swift changes and economic boom going side by side with inhuman levels of poverty.</description>
<picurl>126530.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3327" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-08">
<name>manly</name>
<description>Masculinity is possessing qualities or characteristics considered typical of or appropriate to a man.
Typical characteristics associated with masculinity are: courage, a strong physique, competitive, strong willed, and a sense of honor.
Very important for being considered masculine however is the ability to inspire respect from your fellow brethren and/or being perceived as a virile man by the opposite sex.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3568" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-07">
<name>gambling</name>
<description>Gambling is the wagering of money or something of value (referred to as "the stakes") on an event with an uncertain outcome with the primary intent of winning additional money and/or material goods. Gambling thus requires three elements be present: consideration, chance and prize. The outcome of the wager is often immediate, such as a single roll of dice or a spin of a roulette wheel, but longer time frames are also common, allowing wagers on the outcome of a future sports contest or even an entire sports season.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5405" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-24">
<name>Egyptian mythology</name>
<description>The anime holds elements of Egyptian mythology featuring egyptian gods, mummies, sphinxes, trips through an old pharaos pyramid or similar things.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7081" parentid="2835" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Egypt</name>
<description>Egypt, officially the Arab Republic of Egypt, is a transcontinental country spanning the northeast corner of Africa and southwest corner of Asia by a land bridge formed by the Sinai Peninsula. Egypt is a Mediterranean country bordered by the Gaza Strip and Israel to the northeast, the Gulf of Aqaba to the east, the Red Sea to the east and south, Sudan to the south, and Libya to the west.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214387.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="894" type="main character in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="170">8.36</rating>
<name>Kuujou Joutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuujou Joutarou has a very tough exterior, and is even rather rough and delinquent, but he also is very dedicated, intense, and loyal. He is intelligent, but usually lets his (or Star Platinum`s) fists do the talking with the enemy, even though he often has to rely on his wits to deal with stand users` attacks. Joutarou has a perpetual cooler-than-thou, slightly disinterested attitude, although he loves his mother and respects his grandfather. It is not that he is unaware of his own love and/or respect; rather, he thinks anyone can tell his emotions just by looking at him, and probably thinks further effort in portraying how he feels to be a waste of time. In the manga, he`s constantly chased by adoring girls, whom he ignores or tries to drive away. He is the main target of http://anidb.net/ch895 [Dio], who realises that Joutarou is his greatest threat.</description>
<picture>147627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1720" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="18">7.38</rating>
<name>Star Platinum</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the strongest stands in the JoJo universe; Star Platinum possesses super human senses, strength, stamina, accuracy and speed. It can see for great distances and at great magnifications. As an added bonus, it has a "Star Finger" attack in which it extends its finger to attack.
It is similar to Dio`s The World stand, and, it turns out, can likewise be used to stop time, but that ability is only revealed in Jotaro`s epic battle with Dio Brando when Dio was about to drop a lorry on him.
The Star card symbolises, above all, hope. This is very appropriate, since Jotaro is very much the young new hope of the series. Like other physically powerful stands, Star Platinum suffers from a narrow range of activity. It can only be active within a 2-3 metre radius from Jotaro.</description>
<picture>153555.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1721" type="appears in" update="2015-06-02">
<rating votes="7">8.40</rating>
<name>The World</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Very similar to Jotaro`s Star Platinum, The World is a stand with phenomenal strength, senses and stamina - but is also faster and more accurate.
It can also stop time (for a longer duration as well). He also has at least a measure of Joseph`s psychic abilities (specifically, the ability to create a vision on a photograph).</description>
<picture>173993.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1722" type="main character in" update="2016-08-14">
<rating votes="41">8.11</rating>
<name>Mohammed Avdol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Avdol is a fortune teller, born in Cairo, Egypt. He was also one of the first to meet Dio after the vampire`s resurrection, barely escaping with his life and sanity. Before the events in the anime, he had met and barely tamed the Stand-wielding dog Iggy.</description>
<picture>147623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1724" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-06">
<rating votes="10">4.45</rating>
<name>Magician`s Red</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Magician`s Red appears as a red humanoid figure with the head of a great eagle and fur-covered legs. Its abilities all involve the manipulation of fire. Abdul was born with this Stand and learned to control its power.
This fiery stand can also be remotely controlled and generates intense flames capable of melting steel within moments. The fire is hot enough to have evaporated including but not limited to metal projectiles in mid-air and sliced through railroad tracks. It also has more nuanced uses, such as suffocating foes by placing flame in front of their mouth (Red Bind), or using floating balls of psychic flame which flicker in response to enemy presence. Magician`s Red can also produce a "heat radar", a cruciform mass of flame that indicates the location of heat sources.</description>
<picture>152747.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1725" type="main character in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="72">8.48</rating>
<name>Jean Pierre Polnareff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Polnareff is the stereotypical "good natured klutz": he is heroic and protective of those he loves, but is not very bright (although he has shown lots of cunning and strategy throughout the series). He is very impulsive and loud, and is quick to jump into action without considering the risk, character traits that have landed him in lots of trouble. However, he is sincerely dedicated to doing good, and is a good man to watch your back. He also fancies himself as a ladies man, but this is probably him overestimating his actual prowess (he probably has horrible luck with the ladies).
Out of all the characters in the series, Polnareff is the one that has the least problems showing his feelings, and he adds a lot of humour and warmth to what would otherwise be a pretty cold team (Kakyoin and Jotaro in particular are very cold characters). Indeed, while he may sometimes be seen as the comic relief of the series, Polnareff`s companions appreciate his good nature and trust him to help them win when a tough battle arrives.</description>
<picture>147625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="6976" picture="158591.jpg">Komatsu Fuminori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1727" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-02">
<rating votes="9">6.95</rating>
<name>Silver Chariot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very powerful, battle-dedicated Stand: all its powers are destructive in nature or assist him in battle. In appearance, it looks like a thin, robotic humanoid clad in medieval armour, armed with a rapier. Silver Chariot is an incredibly agile Stand, able to attack enemies with barrages of sword slashes and thrusts before the opponent can react. It can also use this agility, along with its sword, to defend and deflect attacks aimed at it (he has been able to slash fire attacks from Abdul away from him without any harm). If necessary, Polnareff can also shed Silver Chariot`s armour away, exposing its robotic form. In this form, Silver Chariot is even faster, to the point it can actually move fast enough to create doubles of itself. These doubles are not illusory: the Stand is moving at faster-than-the-eye-can-see speed between different positions. As such, were all the doubles to attack at once, it`d mean that the Stand is attacking from all those positions simultaneously, giving it incredible destructive power. Similarly, because of this same speed, attacking the doubles would be futile, as the Stand can easily move away before being harmed. Polnareff`s `secret attack` is called `shooting the sword`, in which the blade of his sword detaches at high speed. He uses this only when it is certain it will it strike, because the blade has to be reattached before Silver Chariot can be fight effectively again.</description>
<picture>155121.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1732" type="main character in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="50">7.78</rating>
<name>Kakyouin Noriaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially a student who has travelled to Egypt, Dio Brando sensed his Stand powers and asked him for a demonstration, which turned out to be a fight.
Afterwards, Kakyoin is brainwashed by Dio using buds from his own cells into following his will, which is to kill Jotaro Kujo.
In the anime, he attacks Jotaro by possessing the body of a female student with his Stand. He is defeated by Jotaro either way. Jotaro soon discovers that Kakyoin was under the influence of Dio. Jotaro then used his own Stand, Star Platinum, to remove Dio`s implant buds from Kakyoin`s head in spite of the risk that it may openly attack both of them. Kakyoin is freed from Dio`s slavery afterwards to which he joins the heroes as thanks for helping them.</description>
<picture>147624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1737" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-12">
<rating votes="11">5.40</rating>
<name>Hierophant Green</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hierophant Green is an elastic and remote Stand, capable of `scouting` and performing actions from far distances. Kakyoin has wielded this Stand since birth. His Stand looks humanoid but robotic with yellow eyes, no distinguishable mouth, and green-coloured appendages that resembles a watermelon in texture. The exterior features of the Stand sports a cream-white or beige colour. The composition of this Stand isn`t solid; instead, it is a compact winding coils of itself that can unravel at a moment`s notice. The Stand is approximately as tall as Kakyoin himself. Whenever the green appendages glow, the Stand is priming for an attack, such as Emerald Splash.</description>
<picture>153549.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1739" type="main character in" update="2015-01-10">
<rating votes="26">8.46</rating>
<name>Iggy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iggy, who possessed the powers of a Stand, was found by Muhammad Abdul in the street slums of New York. Only Abdul is able to come close to him.
Iggy came to the scene aboard a Speedwagon-sponsored helicopter in the middle of the desert. Polnareff, being cocky and intrigued about their new partner, becomes the target of the ferocity that Iggy is famous for, after disturbing his slumber. The pilots and Abdul were only able to control him because of one unlikely treat; a coffee-flavoured chewing gum.</description>
<picture>167358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1741" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-01-10">
<rating votes="3">3.65</rating>
<name>The Fool</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Fool is a very unorthodox Stand. Unlike more traditional Stands, it does not have an actual psychic manifestation (i.e. it is not normally visible), but instead takes its form by manipulating sand and dust particles in the environment. As such, it is one of the few Stands that is visible to everyone, not only to Stand users. Also, since it does not have a psychic form, it cannot be harmed in any way (attacking it would just mean you are attacking a pile of dirt), and as such, Iggy can not be harmed by attacking it. Iggy, through The Fool, can manipulate sand in any way he can think of; indeed, he even fooled Vanilla Ice momentarily by using The Fool to masquerade as Dio. Iggy has been able to glide through the air with it, and can attack opponents by bombarding them with waves of sand. The preferred form Iggy gives it is that of a dog-like being with an Aztec-like stone mask face and wheels for hind legs.</description>
<picture>167363.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1742" type="main character in" update="2016-12-18">
<rating votes="114">8.53</rating>
<name>Joseph Joestar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joseph comes to the aid of his daughter Holly, and his grandson Joutarou. He teaches his grandson about the Stand, and for the most, has done his share of directing the group towards their goal, through fatherly advices and tactics and analysis. He deciphered Kakyouin Noriaki`s message despite cryptic depictions in regards to Dio`s power.</description>
<picture>147622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1743" type="appears in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="7">3.51</rating>
<name>Vanilla Ice</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dio Brando`s most loyal henchman. He uses the Cream Stand, which is capable of creating an invisible, spherical void by devouring itself and Vanilla, much like an ouroboros. Vanilla can control the sphere, which is capable of free flight. If any part of an object or being touches the sphere, that part is irrevocably gone, sucked into the void, vaporised. Unfortunately he is unable to see or hear anything inside the void, so he has to at least partially come out to check the exterior. He proves his loyalty to Dio by cutting his own head off, so Dio would drink his blood. Dio repays him by resurrecting him into a vampire using his own blood.</description>
<picture>16316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1744" type="appears in" update="2008-12-30">
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<name>Cream</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Capable of creating an invisible, spherical void after devouring itself and Vanilla Ice (much like an ouroboros). Vanilla can control the sphere, which is capable of free flight. If any part of an object or being touches the sphere, that part is irrevocably gone, sucked into the void and vaporized. Unfortunately he is unable to see or hear anything inside the void, so he has to at least partially come out to check the exterior.</description>
<picture>16317.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1745" type="appears in" update="2015-01-18">
<rating votes="6">4.06</rating>
<name>N`doul</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Stand user named after Youssou N`Dour, a Senegalese artist. He appears as a blind man leaning on a cane and uses his sensitive hearing to track his opponent. His Stand is Geb, an extremely fast stand of water.
After his defeat he committed suicide, shooting himself through the head with a high-pressure water jet, lest he "slip" any secret of Dio to protagonists.</description>
<picture>167602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1746" type="appears in" update="2015-05-14">
<rating votes="6">4.69</rating>
<name>Daniel J. D`Arby</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A compulsive gambler, a proficient poker player, and excels at cheating. His Stand is Osiris, which transforms the soul of D`Arby`s defeated opponent into a poker chip, and gives D`Arby himself an almost superhuman sense of touch.
He plays Jotaro in a Poker game after beating Polnareff and Joseph. Jotaro bluffs him into a nervous breakdown, causing him to forfeit the game in the process.</description>
<picture>16320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2782" picture="23189.jpg">Ginga Banjou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1747" type="appears in" update="2015-05-09">
<rating votes="3">2.64</rating>
<name>Osiris</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A stand that transforms the souls of D`Arby`s defeated gambling opponents into poker chips, and gives D`Arby himself an almost superhuman sense of touch.</description>
<picture>16321.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1748" type="appears in" update="2016-12-18">
<rating votes="23">5.39</rating>
<name>Kuujou Holly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Holly is the daughter of Joseph and Suzie Joestar, and mother of Kuujou Joutarou. Her sweet charm is known by all. She believes in her son deeply, proud of the compassion that he has shown to others. A woman who loves her family, she will deliberately lie about her illness so as to lessen their worry. Her ailing condition becomes the catalyst for Joutarou and company`s quest to Egypt.
Her Japanese name is "Seiko".</description>
<picture>152746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1436" picture="18822.jpg">Takagi Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1749" type="appears in" update="2014-09-07">
<rating votes="8">3.68</rating>
<name>Suzie Q Joestar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Married to Joseph Joestar, with daughter Holly Joestar.</description>
<picture>160552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1801" type="appears in" update="2014-06-14">
<rating votes="12">6.38</rating>
<name>Hol Horse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An arrogant cowboy and the wielder of the Emperor Stand, which takes the form of a revolver. Upon being fired, the Emperor can control the bullet`s flight path, allowing it to turn in mid-air. He, however, prefers to operate with a partner, as his Stand is fairly weak and not effective without backup. While originally seen working with J. Geil, he later becomes partners with Boingo. Despite his arrogance, Hol Horse prefers to see himself as a "No.2 kind of guy" rather than a "No.1 kind of guy". He is named after the hip-hop group Full Force.</description>
<picture>156666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="280" picture="170840.jpg">Kiuchi Hidenobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67039" type="appears in" update="2014-04-26">
<rating votes="6">2.69</rating>
<name>Enya Geil</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154945.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67133" type="appears in" update="2014-05-02">
<rating votes="5">8.00</rating>
<name>Pet Shop</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155119.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69868" type="appears in" update="2014-09-07">
<rating votes="4">5.57</rating>
<name>Roses</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69932" type="appears in" update="2015-01-17">
<rating votes="3">3.70</rating>
<name>Geb Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167605.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="72640" type="appears in" update="2015-01-09">
<rating votes="2">3.33</rating>
<name>Emperor</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167359.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="72675" type="appears in" update="2015-01-17">
<rating votes="4">3.66</rating>
<name>Boingo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72676" type="appears in" update="2015-06-20">
<rating votes="2">8.52</rating>
<name>Thoth Shin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174779.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="72677" type="appears in" update="2015-01-17">
<rating votes="4">2.40</rating>
<name>Oingo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72962" type="appears in" update="2015-02-01">
<rating votes="2">6.67</rating>
<name>Anubis Shin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62493.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72963" type="appears in" update="2015-02-01">
<rating votes="2">5.98</rating>
<name>Chaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>62494.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2002" picture="21307.jpg">Katsu Anri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75048" type="appears in" update="2015-05-29">
<rating votes="3">2.52</rating>
<name>Telence T. D`Arby</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75049" type="appears in" update="2015-05-29">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Atum</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173934.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="75409" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-27">
<rating votes="75">8.63</rating>
<name>Dio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76001" type="appears in" update="2015-06-20">
<rating votes="2">2.80</rating>
<name>Khan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="36733.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76002" type="appears in" update="2015-06-20">
<rating votes="4">6.60</rating>
<name>Mariah</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76003" type="appears in" update="2015-06-20">
<rating votes="2">6.90</rating>
<name>Bastet</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174776.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="76004" type="appears in" update="2017-05-02">
<rating votes="3">4.32</rating>
<name>Alessi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76005" type="appears in" update="2015-06-20">
<rating votes="2">9.08</rating>
<name>Set</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174778.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84403" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<name>Horus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64139.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="84437" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="2">1.61</rating>
<name>Kenny G.</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10906" picture="200861.jpg">Yanagita Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84438" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="2">1.09</rating>
<name>Nukesaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64141.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="17149" picture="174125.jpg">Yamamura Hibiku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84508" type="appears in" update="2016-09-03">
<rating votes="4">1.68</rating>
<name>Wilson Phillips</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89118" type="appears in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="2">1.43</rating>
<name>Roujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5026" picture="151676.jpg">Sawada Toshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89125" type="appears in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="3">7.98</rating>
<name>Malena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201908.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89142" type="appears in" update="2017-05-02">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Josei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38677" picture="145133.jpg">Kimura Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="165271" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「愚者[ザ・フール]」のイギーと「ゲブ神」のンドゥール その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Iggy the Fool and Geb`s N`doul, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Iggy (The Fool) et N`Doul (Geb), Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"The Fool" no Iggy to "Geb-shin" no N`doul: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Jojo and the others land in Egypt where DIO awaits, and are currently cutting through the desert, when a helicopter approaches them. The helicopter belonged to the Speedwagon Foundation that had been helping them on their journey so far, and brought them something that Joseph had asked for.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667921</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165272" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「アヌビス神」その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anubis, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Anubis, Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Anubis-shin": Sono 1</title>
<summary>Jojo and the others look for a boat to take to Cairo where DIO awaits. Meanwhile, Chaka was walking along a nearby beach where he finds a sword. The men he`s with all try to draw the sword with no luck, but then Chaka tries and is easily able to draw the sword. The sword glows eerily and Chaka suddenly hears a mysterious voice, changing his usually calm demeanor. What is the true identity of this sword?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667927</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165273" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「クヌム神」のオインゴと「トト神」のボインゴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Khnum`s Zenyatta and Thoth`s Mondatta</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Oingo (Khnum) et Boingo (Thoth)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Khnum-shin" no Oingo to "Thoth-shin" no Boingo</title>
<summary>After their battle with N`doul, Kakyoin and Avdol are badly hurt, so they take them to a hospital in Aswan. While being careful of possible enemies around them, Polnareff picks a cafe for the rest of the crew to go into. However, that cafe had already been taken over by the Stand user brothers, Khnum`s Zenyatta and Thoth`s Mondatta. Zenyatta disguises himself as the manager of the cafe and tries to serve Jojo and the others poisoned black tea, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667925</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165274" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「愚者[ザ・フール]」のイギーと「ゲブ神」のンドゥール その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Iggy the Fool and Geb`s N`doul, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Iggy (The Fool) et N`Doul (Geb), Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"The Fool" no Iggy to "Geb-shin" no N`doul: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Jotaro and crew acquire the help of Iggy, but due to a surprise attack from a water Stand, Kakyoin is injured. Avdol tries out a strategy against the unseen enemy, but the enemy quickly sees through it. Despite everything going on, Iggy is napping.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667923</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165276" update="2015-01-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165277" update="2016-04-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165681" update="2015-01-29">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165750" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「セト伸」のアレッシー その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Set`s Alessi, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alessi (Sethan), Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Set-shin" no Alessi: Sono 1</title>
<summary>While Joseph and Avdol were fighting with Mariah, Jotaro gets concerned that they haven`t shown up yet, and goes to look for them around Luxor. Then, Polnareff senses someone following them and confronts the man.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667935</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165751" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「バステト女神」のマライア その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bast`s Mariah, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mariah (Bast), Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Bastet-joshin" no Mariah: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Due to the powers of an enemy Stand, Joseph`s body becomes magnetised. While chasing after the woman that seemed to be the Stand user, Avdol also touches the electrical outlet and becomes magnetised as well.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667933</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165752" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「バステト女神」のマライア その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bast`s Mariah, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mariah (Bast), Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Bastet-joshin" no Mariah: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Jotaro and the others arrive in Luxor. While heading there, Joseph notices an electrical outlet in a rock. Obviously fascinated by the electrical outlet in the rock, Joseph gets closer, and get gets shocked.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667931</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="165753" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「アヌビス神」その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anubis, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Anubis, Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Anubis-shin": Sono 2</title>
<summary>Polnareff had defeated the Anubis Stand user, Chaka, however the barber he had visited suddenly starts talking about Anubis and attacks him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667929</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166843" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホル・ホースとボインゴ その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hol Horse and Mondatta, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hol Horse et Boingo, Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hol Horse to Boingo: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Hol Horse arrives at Cairo in order to pursue Jotaro and the others. He has joined forces with another partner and is after the lives of Jotaro and crew once more. That partner, is none other than Mondatta.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667943</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166844" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="13">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダービー・ザ・ギャンブラー その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">D`Arby the Gambler, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">D`Arby the Gambler, Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">D`Arby The Gambler: Sono 2</title>
<summary>After losing to D`Arby, Joseph and Polnareff have their souls taken. In order to have their souls returned, Jotaro shows off Star Platinum`s powers before going into a match with D`Arby, warning him that cheating won`t work.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667941</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166845" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダービー・ザ・ギャンブラー その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">D`Arby the Gambler, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">D`Arby the Gambler, Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">D`Arby The Gambler: Sono 1</title>
<summary>After a long journey, Jotaro and the others finally reach Cairo. They go to a cafe and ask if anyone knows where DIO`s mansion is located by showing the picture around. Then, someone says that they have seen the building before.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667939</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="166846" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「セト伸」のアレッシー その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Set`s Alessi, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alessi (Sethan), Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Set-shin" no Alessi: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Because of the power of Alessi`s Stand, Set, Polnareff is turned back into a child. The one who came to his aid amidst his confusion was a woman named Marena. However, Alessi`s evil hands followed Polnareff into her house.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667937</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167219" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホル・ホースとボインゴ その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hol Horse and Mondatta, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hol Horse et Boingo, Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hol Horse to Boingo: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Hol Horse and Mondatta followed Jotaro and the others to Cairo and as Mondatta`s book said, Hol Horse stuck his fingers into Polnareff`s nose... but he didn`t know what to do from there. Then Jotaro and the others, who were looking for Polnareff, show up, but things seem to be going the opposite way of the premonition.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667945</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167824" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の門番ペット・ショップ その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Guardian of Hell, Pet Shop, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pet Shop, le gardien des enfers, Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku no Monban Pet Shop: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Jojo and the others continue to look for DIO`s mansion in Cairo. Following Avdol`s advice, they have a beggar look for the mansion and wait. Meanwhile, Iggy, who is wandering the city alone, gets confronted by two large dogs. The dogs are freaked out by Iggy`s power, and decide to go after a bird that`s at a nearby mansion instead. However, as soon as the dogs go into the mansion, they are impaled by a giant icicle. Iggy is shocked by the occurrence, and sees a falcon appear...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667947</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167947" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄の門番ペット・ショップ その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Guardian of Hell, Pet Shop, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pet Shop, le gardien des enfers, Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigoku no Monban Pet Shop: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Iggy ends up in a battle to the death in the sewers against the falcon that guards DIO`s mansion, Pet Shop. Pet Shop shows no mercy, and goes after Iggy at a frightening speed. Iggy, despite being injured, runs into the river, making a dome made out of dirt to shield him. However, he underestimates Pet Shop`s abilities, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667949</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167961" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダービー・ザ・プレイヤー その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">D`Arby the Player, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">D`Arby the Player, Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">D`Arby The Player: Sono 2</title>
<summary>The battle for souls with D`Arby continues. Kakyoin challenged D`Arby to a race game, but ends up losing and D`Arby steals his soul. Before Joseph really has time to react, Jotaro picks the next game.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667953</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167962" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダービー・ザ・プレイヤー その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">D`Arby the Player, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">D`Arby the Player, Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">D`Arby The Player: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Despite Iggy`s injuries, Jojo and company finally make it to DIO`s mansion. Once they entered, a butler named D`Arby Younger was awaiting their arrival. The younger brother of the defeated D`Arby Elder, he immediately shows off his Stand, Atum`s power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667951</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168073" update="2015-04-20">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168250" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜空の瘴気 ヴァニラ・アイス その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miasma of the Void, Cool Ice, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vanilla Ice, Miasmes d`outre-espace, Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuu no Shouki Vanilla Ice: Sono 1</title>
<summary>The baseball match with D`Arby continues within DIO`s mansion. For some reason, Jotaro starts declaring his pitches to D`Arby. D`Arby finds Jotaro`s actions strange, but still believes he has the upper hand because of his Stand`s abilities.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667955</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168318" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜空の瘴気 ヴァニラ・アイス その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miasma of the Void, Cool Ice, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vanilla Ice, Miasmes d`outre-espace, Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuu no Shouki Vanilla Ice: Sono 2</title>
<summary>After a long, hard journey, they are faced with a sudden goodbye of a friend. Because it`s so sudden, Polnareff can`t control his emotions. He starts brandishing his sword toward the unseen enemy with very little success.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667957</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168598" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DIOの世界 その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dio`s World, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde de Dio, Partie 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dio no Sekai: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Polnareff finally comes face to face with DIO. Despite the hostility towards him, DIO tells him that he`d forgive him and will allow him to join him again. Polnareff refuses the offer, but for some reason, cannot get any closer to DIO. He unleashes Silver Chariot to at least try to reveal the identity of DIO`s Stand. Right when it was about to clash with DIO`s Stand, The World, the wall breaks behind them and the ones who appeared were...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667961</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168599" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜空の瘴気 ヴァニラ・アイス その3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miasma of the Void, Cool Ice, Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vanilla Ice, Miasmes d`outre-espace, Partie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuu no Shouki Vanilla Ice: Sono 3</title>
<summary>Polnareff is pushed to his limits with Cool Ice`s merciless attacks. He finally awaits death, but is saved at the last minute by the dying Iggy. Iggy uses the last bit of his energy, but his Stand is obviously losing power. Polnareff then stabs Cool Ice in the head. Despite showing resilience to the attacks so far, Cool Ice is finally destroyed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667959</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168607" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遥かなる旅 さらば友よ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Long Travels, Goodbye My Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un long périple, adieu les amis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harukanaru Tabiji Saraba Tomo Yo</title>
<summary>Because of Polnareff`s miraculous, life-risking trick, Jotaro is finally able to land a blow onto DIO. The injured DIO tries to escape within the stopped time. Jotaro tries to finish him with a rush attack, but that was the escape route that DIO was looking for. Before DIO lies the shriveled body of Joseph Joestar. Jotaro is enraged by DIO, who has now healed, and wages his final battle with DIO within stopped time!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667967</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168608" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DIOの世界 その3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dio`s World, Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde de Dio, Partie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dio no Sekai: Sono 3</title>
<summary>Joseph is able to figure out The World`s power because of the message Kakyoin left, but is quickly knocked out by a cruel attack by DIO. Jotaro then attacks The World with Star Platinum, but is no match for DIO`s power. DIO stopped time and goes in for the final blow, but he sees that Jotaro`s fingers are moving in the stopped time, and strengthens his defense. Jotaro telling DIO that their Stands are the same type lingers in his mind...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667965</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168609" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DIOの世界 その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dio`s World, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde de Dio, Partie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dio no Sekai: Sono 2</title>
<summary>The battle is taking place in the city of Cairo at night. Joseph and Kakyoin are running from DIO as they fight, and Jotaro and Polnareff chase after DIO as they fight. Amidst all of that, Kakyoin says he has a way to figure out what DIO`s Stand actually is. DIO, who was chasing after Kakyoin when he falls into Hierophant Green`s trap, and then...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>667963</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175951" update="2016-04-23">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175952" update="2016-04-23">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
