<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10833" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-07-25</startdate>
<enddate>2015-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya Zwei Herz!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">Fate/Kaleid Liner 프리즈마☆이리야 2wei Herz!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">F/K 2.5</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">F/K 2 Herz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Prillya Zwei Herz</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Fate/kaleid liner プリズマ☆イリヤ 2wei Herz!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya 2wei Herz!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">Fate/kaleid liner 魔法少女☆依莉雅 2wei! Herz!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11639" type="Sequel">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya Drei!!</anime>
<anime id="10804" type="Prequel">Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya Zwei! (2015)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://anime.prisma-illya.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2900" type="Animation Work">Silver Link</name>
<name id="11820" type="Character Design">Ushijima Nozomi</name>
<name id="7052" type="Series Composition">Inoue Kenji</name>
<name id="11181" type="Direction">Jinbou Masato</name>
<name id="1564" type="Chief Direction">Oonuma Shin</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
<name id="927" type="Original Work">Type-Moon</name>
<name id="31124" type="Original Work">Hiroyama Hiroshi</name>
<name id="11692" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamayoshi Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="11748" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirata Kazuya</name>
<name id="27370" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sawairi Yuuki</name>
<name id="14025" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takahashi Ken</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya Zwei! manga by http://anidb.net/cr31124 [Hiroyama Hiroshi], itself a spin-off of the http://anidb.net/a3348 [Fate/Stay Night] erotic visual novel by http://anidb.net/cr927 [Type-Moon].
Illya (Illyasviel von Einzbern) is a typical young girl attending Homurabara Academy who just happens to have a slight crush on her brother-in-law. Then, one night, a magic wand called Magical Ruby falls from the sky into her bath and tricks her into signing a contract...
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1018">5.80</permanent>
<temporary count="1029">6.87</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>170469.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16275</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>27525</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>31056</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anime.prisma-illya.jp/2weihelz/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fate/kaleid_liner_Prisma_Illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fate/kaleid_liner_プリズマ☆イリヤ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3835</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352101</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2827" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>sudden naked guy appearance</name>
<description>A male specimen previously unknown to the viewer and not dressed in any clothes suddenly appears out of nowhere.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5888" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>power gives you wings</name>
<description>It is not Red Bull that gives you wings, but power, most often even the power of love.
Whether it`s an android, a mecha, mons, a mahou shoujo, or basically any super powered individual, once they start powering up and become REALLY powerful, it will be indicated by them getting a pair of wings.
Specifically, feathery white angelic wings, sometimes also wings made of Hard Light or Pure Energy. These wings will of course allow the character to fly, float, and glow, all without needing to flap them!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5915" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>French kiss</name>
<description>A kiss in which the tongue enters the partner`s mouth.</description>
<picurl>238326.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="241" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-20">
<rating votes="2756">8.36</rating>
<name>Toosaka Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toosaka Rin is a model student and idol of Shirou`s school, Rin is secretly a sorceress and Master in the Holy Grail War. She is descended from a long line of sorcerers, and though lacking a formal magic education, is extremely powerful in her own right. Her father was killed in the 4th Holy Grail War, and she has trained since his death to succeed him. She is perceptive, resourceful and avidly competitive. Although she tried to summon a Saber-class Servant, she accidentally called Archer instead.
Rin excels in transformation of energy, which includes storage of Mana in objects. She stores all of her mana in jewels that she charges daily to bypass her body`s natural limitations on releasing energy. She can detonate her jewels on contact with an object, resulting in a release of energy equivalent to an attack rank of "A". Her most common offensive spell is "Gandr", which fires concentrated mana in the form of a black orb from her finger. On contact, the spell amplifies physical conditions -- a person who is already sick, for example, becomes far sicker upon being hit. Rin is also proficient with reinforcement sorcery, which she uses on her legs to give herself more speed.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>172322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1904" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-20">
<rating votes="1261">2.88</rating>
<name>Emiya Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emiya Shirou is the main character of http://anidb.net/a3348 [Fate/Stay Night], a serious and honest teenager as well as a hard worker who enjoys helping others. He is in his second year of High School, and his hobbies include fixing a variety of broken things, from VCRs to stoves, as well as cooking and cleaning. He has some slight proficiency with reinforcement sorcery, though his foster father http://anidb.net/ch1919 [Emiya Kiritsugu] did not encourage him to improve it. Initially, he is confused about the Holy Grail War and irrationally attempts to shield others, even his own servant Saber, from danger.</description>
<picture>172321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1921" type="appears in" update="2015-04-20">
<rating votes="380">6.17</rating>
<name>Fujimura Taiga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taiga is an English teacher at Shirou`s school, homeroom instructor of Shirou`s class and the supervising teacher for the Archery Dojo. She is widely called "Tiger", a nickname she dislikes ("Taiga" and "Tiger" sound similar in Japanese), though Shirou refers to her as "Fuji-nee" (older sister Fuji). After Kiritsugu died, Taiga became Shirou`s guardian and has been living with him for several years. Taiga and Shirou are very close, and she regards him as a younger brother.
Taiga is largely a comic relief character; she is irresponsible, clumsy, and prone to sporadic bouts of extreme lethargy or zest. She lives with Shirou under the pretences of being his caretaker, although she cannot cook and lacks many other domestic skills, relying on Shirou to maintain her welfare. Shirou, however, appreciates Taiga`s company, and is more than happy to care for her. When Shirou is in any need of advice, Taiga can be depended on to be a confidante for his worries.</description>
<picture>172325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1924" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="58">3.65</rating>
<name>Ryuudou Issei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Issei is the Student Body President of Shirou`s school, and another close friend of Shirou. Issei often asks Shirou to fix broken equipment for the Student Body to try and reduce save money on the school`s bill. Issei and Shirou often have lunch together in the Student Body`s office where they talk about what ever comes to mind. His father is the head priest of Ryuudouji Temple, and his brother was a classmate of Taiga and Neko-san. He dislikes Rin and seems to have some sort of fear of females, although he seems to be unusually at ease around Saber.
Issei unknowingly tells Shirou that Caster is at the Temple.</description>
<picture>49451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1934" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="69">4.17</rating>
<name>Sella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sella and Leysritt are Ilya`s maids, but they act as her caretakers and instruct her in the secrets of sorcery. Like Ilya, they both have silky blonde hair and deep crimson eyes. Sella is rather fickle and insecure (especially regarding her body), and is very suspicious of Emiya Shirou.</description>
<picture>137030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40833" picture="198636.jpg">Nanao Haruhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1939" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="89">5.77</rating>
<name>Leysritt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sella and Leysritt are Ilya`s maids, but they act as her caretakers and instruct her in the secrets of sorcery. Like Ilya, they both have silky blonde hair and deep crimson eyes. Leysritt is casual, and has affection for Shirou because his presence makes Ilya happy. Leysritt is skilled in combat, particularly with halberds.</description>
<picture>137031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="249" picture="46910.jpg">Miyagawa Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1951" type="appears in" update="2014-02-11">
<rating votes="7">4.69</rating>
<name>Majutsu Kyoukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A trans-national, self-preservative organisation created by western magi for the purpose of controlling, concealing and developing Magecraft. Founded around the Middle Ages by those who foresaw the decline of Magecraft, they decided that in order to preserve their power Thaumaturgy should drift apart from society and become a secret known only by a necessary minimum number of people.
It has many laboratories and research bodies that seek to advance the progress of Thaumaturgy, as well as institutions that transmit their secrets to the next generation. Although the emphasis lies on the pursuit of knowledge, the Association also seeks to increase its own military strength so it can defend itself against those that might threaten it, such as the Holy Church, other mystic organizations and supernatural forces seeking punish mankind for meddling with areas that should not be touched.
The Mage`s Association is currently headquartered at the Clock Tower in London.</description>
<picture>150073.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1952" type="appears in" update="2014-02-15">
<rating votes="14">5.27</rating>
<name>Seidou Kyoukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Holy Church, also referred simply as "the Church", is a worldwide religious organisation, apparently styled after the real Roman Catholic Church. It is a powerful faction in the Nasuverse, with several important characters in the `verse works being its active or former members. On the surface, they coexist rather peacefully with the http://anidb.net/ch1951 [Mage`s Association], but that is only out of necessity, and neither group will waste an opportunity to backstab the other. They sometimes act as arbiters in the Association`s internal disputes; one such example are the Holy Grail Wars. Aside their regular duties as a normal religious group, they have a few special agencies dedicated to supernatural events.
The Assembly of the Eighth Sacrament, the lowest among the Church`s special agencies, is charged with researching, recovering and managing Holy Relics, items considered to have the holy attribute, scattered around the world. Their name comes from the seven Sacraments of the Catholic Church. As the Holy Grail is a Holy Relic, they`re in charge of managing every Holy Grail that appears; as such, in order to watch over the Holy Grail War, the priest stationed at Fuyuki City is always a member of this agency and is the one who acts as the war`s Supervisor.
The Church is also very active and relentless in the pursue and elimination of heretics, beings acting in disagreement with the Holy Scriptures. The members of the Church in that line of work are called Executors, and their specialties include magus hunting, demon killing, and vampire slaying. Among them, the most powerful ones are members of the Burial Agency, a group always composed of eight Executors, one of whom is the leader and another of whom is not an acting member, but a backup. Members of the Burial Agency work alone, and they will act without orders if they deem necessary, even going as far as skewering bishops, which earned them the reputation of the most heretic group inside the Church.
Among the items the Holy Church uses for its purposes, one can find the many types of Keys of Providence, Conceptual Weapons used for purification, and the Holy Scriptures, very powerful Conceptual Weapons used only by a few select Executors. Examples of Keys of Providence are http://anidb.net/ch1916 [Kotomine Kirei]`s most used weapons, the Black Keys, sword-shaped items that can be thrown at an opponent in order to pierce them and that do not have a blade when inside the priest`s frock. An example of a Holy Scripture is the Seventh Holy Scripture, used by http://anidb.net/ch1941 [Ciel], a massive metal weapon which can kill a vampire through physical power alone, shoots Bible pages, has an unicorn horn for a bayonet, and has a http://anidb.net/ch31725 [residing spirit].</description>
<picture>150288.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="25939" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-16">
<rating votes="388">6.84</rating>
<name>Irisviel von Einzbern</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Irisviel von Einzbern is the heroine of the Fate/Zero story, the mother of Illyasviel von Einzbern and Kiritsugu`s wife. A homunculus prototype created by the Einzbern family with the idea to give birth to an ultimate homunculus. Like many of the Einzberns, she is skilled in alchemy. Irisviel serves as Saber`s proxy Master, since Kiritsugu believes that he and Saber are incompatible.</description>
<picture>126277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31686" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-21">
<rating votes="35">4.99</rating>
<name>Caren Hortensia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caren is a member of the Church and Burial Agency, and she works as a priestess.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>6189.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37942" type="appears in" update="2016-12-20">
<rating votes="38">7.97</rating>
<name>Gilgamesh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38211" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-10-14">
<rating votes="17">8.00</rating>
<name>Saber Lion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74873.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38853" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-22">
<rating votes="53">5.82</rating>
<name>Bazett Fraga McRemitz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bazett Fraga McRemitz is a magus sent from the http://anidb.net/ch1951 [Mage`s Association] to fight the 5th Holy Grail War. She was born in Ireland as a descendant of an old family of magi that had detached itself from the Association, but she chose to join the Association regardless. Despite her rare lineage, she was dismissed, and decided to employ her abilities as a hunter of those that had been given a Sealing Designation.
She is mentioned very briefly in the http://anidb.net/a3348 [Fate/Stay Night] visual novel. She was the original Master of http://anidb.net/ch1908 [Lancer], but http://anidb.net/ch1916 [Kotomine Kirei] betrayed her and stole her command spells, fatally injuring her in the process. In Fate/Hollow Ataraxia, she is saved by the servant http://anidb.net/ch40363 [Avenger] and acts as his Master.</description>
<picture>77327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42302" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-22">
<rating votes="132">8.76</rating>
<name>Prisma Illya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch83473 [Illyasviel von Einzbern], turned http://anidb.net/t2503 [magical girl].</description>
<picture>157694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15655" picture="44791.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42327" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-27">
<rating votes="116">7.23</rating>
<name>Luviagelita Edelfelt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Luviagelita or simply Luvia is a wealthy and proud young woman and mage.
In Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya she is assigned to work together with Rin to capture the Class Cards. After Sapphire abandons her, Luvia immediately adopts Sapphire`s new master, Miyu, and guides her to capture the Class Cards. She is indiscriminate in using her wealth, erecting a mansion across the street from Einzbern house in a single day, where she and Miyu are currently living. Her rivalry with Rin stems from their mutual crush on Shirou, who fails to notice their attraction to him
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>137014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49571" type="main character in" update="2015-09-05">
<rating votes="168">5.83</rating>
<name>Miyu Edelfelt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious girl who is chosen by Sapphire to become its new master and then adopted by Luvia. She takes her duties as a Magical Girl very seriously and is initially dismissive of Illya`s abilities, but gradually warms up to Illya. She comes to value Illya`s friendship greatly and is highly protective of her.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>177119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54376" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-14">
<rating votes="43">5.60</rating>
<name>Magical Ruby</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="488" picture="138714.jpg">Takano Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54377" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-14">
<rating votes="42">5.79</rating>
<name>Magical Sapphire</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Kaleidostick, the younger sister of Magical Ruby, that enables Miyu to become a Magical Girl. Sapphire was originally assigned to Luvia, but, as with Ruby, Sapphire abandoned Luvia after becoming tired of how she was constantly quarreling with Rin.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>137016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56113" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-14">
<rating votes="21">3.30</rating>
<name>Moriyama Nanaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56114" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-14">
<rating votes="44">5.63</rating>
<name>Gakumazawa Tatsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56115" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-14">
<rating votes="40">2.73</rating>
<name>Kurihara Suzuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56116" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-14">
<rating votes="25">2.99</rating>
<name>Katsura Mimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65744" type="main character in" update="2016-06-17">
<rating votes="164">8.73</rating>
<name>Chloe von Einzbern</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69249" type="appears in" update="2014-08-11">
<rating votes="3">3.14</rating>
<name>Auguste</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71988" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-22">
<rating votes="53">7.38</rating>
<name>Prisma Miyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch49571 [Miyu Edelfelt], turned http://anidb.net/t2503 [magical girl].</description>
<picture>157695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76639" type="appears in" update="2015-08-04">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Gakumazawa Stella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuko`s mother.</description>
<picture>175948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38704" picture="145173.jpg">Kouda Yumeha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76640" type="appears in" update="2015-08-04">
<name>Gakumazawa Gouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuko`s father.</description>
<picture>175949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76641" type="appears in" update="2015-08-04">
<name>Gakumazawa Reiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuko`s older brother.</description>
<picture>175950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76642" type="appears in" update="2015-08-04">
<name>Gakumazawa Gaisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tatsuko`s older brother.</description>
<picture>175951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25023" picture="70106.jpg">Kimura Subaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76643" type="appears in" update="2015-08-04">
<rating votes="2">5.55</rating>
<name>Moriyama Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nanaki`s older sister.</description>
<picture>175952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="216" picture="171983.jpg">Takahashi Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76798" type="appears in" update="2015-08-12">
<rating votes="3">3.20</rating>
<name>Kurihara Hibari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzuka`s older sister.</description>
<picture>176231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77224" type="appears in" update="2015-09-14">
<rating votes="1">6.93</rating>
<name>Kuroi Eirei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82606" type="appears in" update="2017-08-09">
<rating votes="10">6.83</rating>
<name>Emiya Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emiya Shirou from alternate parallel word, from which http://anidb.net/ch49571 [Miyu] came from. This Shirou is Miyu`s brother.</description>
<picture>205946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83466" type="appears in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="3">8.91</rating>
<name>Prisma Illya Zwei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch83473 [Illyasviel von Einzbern], turned http://anidb.net/ch42302 [Magical Girl], Zwei Form. Illya enters this form using the combined power of http://anidb.net/ch54376 [Ruby] and http://anidb.net/ch54377 [Sapphire].
</description>
<picture>189558.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="83473" type="main character in" update="2016-08-22">
<rating votes="236">8.47</rating>
<name>Illyasviel von Einzbern</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In contrast with her http://anidb.net/ch1913 [Fate/stay night counterpart], Illya has had a normal childhood, growing up with no knowledge of magic or the Holy Grail War. She lives with her brother http://anidb.net/ch1904 [Shirou] and is looked after by her maids http://anidb.net/ch1939 [Leysritt] and http://anidb.net/ch1934 [Sella] when her parents http://anidb.net/ch1919 [Kiritsugu] and http://anidb.net/ch25939 [Irisviel] are away.
She is a fan of http://anidb.net/t2503 [magical girl] anime, and daydreams about becoming one. When she encounters a magic wand named http://anidb.net/ch54376 [Magical Ruby], Illya is tricked into signing a contract and http://anidb.net/ch42302 [becoming a magical girl].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>189556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15655" picture="44791.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83474" type="appears in" update="2016-08-02">
<rating votes="2">6.09</rating>
<name>Vimana Ou no Mikura</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>189560.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="170224" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鏡にしてるみたいでイヤなんだけど</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Like Looking in a Mirror, and I Don`t Like It</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J’aime pas avoir l’impression de le faire avec un miroir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagami ni Shiteru Mitai de Iyanandakedo</title>
<summary>The grand event for elementary schoolers is finally here--Summer Break! In preparation for the long-awaited trip to the beach, Illya and the others go with their classmates to pick out new swimsuits and carry on in front of the skimpy clothing♪ While they`re out, Kuro runs out of mana and calls Illya away to an empty stairway platform. But Mimi catches sight of them in the act?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682399</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170225" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">てーまぱーく・ぱにっく!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Theme Park Panic</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Panique au parc d`attractions !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Theme Park Panic!</title>
<summary>After Illya recieves tickets from Luvia, she heads to a theme park with all her friends! As they play to their hearts content, they end up separated from their guardian, Iri. While looking for Iri, they encounter the nurse, Caren-sensei?! Meanwhile, Illya realizes she`s lost her precious bracelet charm...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682405</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170226" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">命短し腐れよ乙女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls, Life Is Short, so Rot Away</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vie est courte, gâte-toi, jeune fille</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inochi Mijikashi Kusare yo Otome</title>
<summary>When they were buying swimsuits in the shopping mall, Mimi caught sight of Illya "resupplying" Kuro. Ever since that day though, she`s been unable to stop herself from imagining naughty things. Then, after a few words from Suzuka, Mimi awakens! Illya and Kuro are forced to face the new rose-colored tone Mimi`s mind has taken.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682403</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170227" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリコロール・バースデー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tricolore Birthday</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un anniversaire tricolore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tricolore Birthday</title>
<summary>Summer! Swimsuits! The beach! Illya and the others enjoy the beach to fullest, playing along the shore and celebrating their birthday in a beach hut♪ But the popsicle seller they encounter there turns out to be the fierce foe they fought a hard pressed battle against... And to make matters worse, Ruby adds a Love Potion that makes Shirou go crazy! Will Illya`s desires come to fruition in an unexpected way?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682401</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170247" update="2015-07-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170248" update="2015-07-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170430" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blue glass moon</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Glass Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Blue Glass Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blue Glass Moon</title>
<summary>Iri and Liz enjoy playing with water in a vinyl pool in their yard. Then the two of them send Illya and Kuro for a dip too! While they enjoy the approaching end of summer, they recieve notice that Luvia`s holding a party to celebrate the reconstruction of her mansion. That was also the signal for them to begin the operation to retrieve the eighth card. The plan will be carried out tonight at midnight!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682409</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170431" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">浴衣と花火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukatas and Fireworks</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yukata et feux d`artifice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukata to Hanabi</title>
<summary>Illya`s enjoyable summer isn`t over! After changing into a yukata, she joins the usual gang and heads to a local festival. As Illya enjoys yo-yo fishing and lottery drawings at the festival, she realizes something dire--she was supposed to wear underwear beneath her yukata! A great tragedy befalls upon her!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682407</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170835" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界の片隅で君の名を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calling Your Name from a Corner of the World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">D`un recoin du monde, j`appelle ton nom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai no Katasumi de Kimi no Na o</title>
<summary>With Miyu swallowed by the Heroic Spirit, Illya seizes Ruby and Sapphire in each hand, transforming into her Zwei Form to draw Miyu out and slap her. She faces the greatest Heroic Spirit of all, who bears a sword that can rend the world. Prepared to sacrifice everything she has, Illya fights to save her precious friend, Miyu. What fate will her feelings lead to?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682417</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170836" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金色の少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Golden Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le garçon doré</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kin`iro no Shounen</title>
<summary>When Illya tries to stop the ritual to activate the Holy Grail, a young boy brimming with confidence appears before her, acting like he sees through everything. He calls Miyu "Miss Princess From A Parallel World"! Who is the eight Class Card?! Where did Miyu even come from?! With the appearance of this young boy, the viel covering the truth is torn off.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682415</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170837" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">監視者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le superviseur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanshisha</title>
<summary>The power dwelling within the heroic spirit of the eigth card rivaled the gods of myth... Sensing the hopeless difference in their power, Illya and the others escape from the Mirror World. But before they have a chance to breathe, a shock assails their whole party. The Mirror World rends apart, and the heroic spirit appears forth. As if mocking the bewildered group, the heroic spirit begins circling around in the air before finally acting--his goal: the great cavern where the Holy Grail sleeps.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682413</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170838" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">執行者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enforcer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`exécuteur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikkousha</title>
<summary>Illya, Miyu, Kuro, Luvia, Rin, and Bazett all head to the mirror world underground in order to face the Heroic Spirit of the eigth card. Centered in the ley line and stocking up a vast amount of mana, the only strategy they have is to through all of their might against him and take him down with their first blow. They unleash all the firepower they possess against that Heroic Spirit, but--?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682411</identifier>
<identifier>fatekaleid-liner-prisma-illya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="171613" update="2015-09-14">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172416" update="2015-11-17">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビースト, 再び!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Beast, Futatabi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173350" update="2016-01-12">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女よ闘志を抱け (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome yo Toushi o Idake (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173351" update="2015-11-17">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無限の服製</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mugen no Fukusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174265" update="2016-02-23">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女よ闘志を抱け (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome yo Toushi o Idake (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175960" update="2016-03-06">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2016-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バゼットはじめてのアルバイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bazett Hajimete no Arubaito</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179317" update="2016-08-01">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第三弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 03 (56 sec)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 3-dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179318" update="2016-08-01">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第2弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1 min 23 sec)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 2-dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179319" update="2016-08-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (40 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179320" update="2016-08-01">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">番宣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM (15 sec)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bansen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
