<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10860" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-08-22</startdate>
<enddate>2000-08-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Di Gi Charat Summer Special 2000</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Di Gi Charat サマースペシャル2000</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Di Gi Charat Summer Special</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="553" type="Parent Story">Di Gi Charat</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.broccoli.co.jp/dejiko/</url>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch6427 [Pyocola Analogue III] a.k.a. Pyoko, the leader of the Black Gema Gema Group that tried to invade planet Di Gi Charat, comes to Earth to kidnap http://anidb.net/ch6421 [Dejiko] and hold her for ransom. After a failed attempt to kidnap Dejiko, Pyoko decides to cause trouble for the gang and their store Gamers. If things were not bad enough, a http://anidb.net/ch70383 [slug-man] appears throughout the shenanigans to add to the problems.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="106">4.65</permanent>
<temporary count="106">5.97</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>162134.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2932</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1754</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.broccoli.co.jp/dejiko/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Di_Gi_Charat_(ワンダフル版)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>108</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>161600</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4056</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2927" parentid="2676" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Akihabara</name>
<description>Akihabara is a common name for the area around Akihabara Station in the Chiyoda ward of Tokyo, Japan. It gained the nickname Akihabara Electric Town shortly after World War II for being a major shopping center for household electronic goods and the post-war black market. Nowadays, Akihabara is considered by many to be an otaku cultural center and a shopping district for video games, anime, manga, and computer goods.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214314.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6421" type="main character in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="42">8.07</rating>
<name>Di Gi Charat</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character of the story. She is also known as Chocola but despite this alternate name implying she likes chocolate, she prefers broccoli. Dejiko has a Type A personality and can be aggressive at times.
Dejiko dresses up as a catgirl and is the princess of Planet Di Gi Charat. She is ten years old when she comes to Earth with hopes of becoming an idol singer. She has green eyes and green hair and her maid-like uniform consists of a white and navy blue dress with big cat bells tied to her hair with navy blue ribbons. On the very top of her head are her cat ears, which are white with pink inside and have a set of large, non-functional yellow cat eyes. She always wears white gloves and boots (with the exception of her sleeping outfit) and she has a white tail.
She has the ability to use her eye-beam weapon called the Me kara BEAM!. She ends each sentence with nyo.</description>
<picture>23835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6422" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="26">8.15</rating>
<name>Puchi Charat</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dejiko`s five year old sidekick and a catgirl. Puchiko is quiet and has a Type B personality. She has the ability to use an eye-beam similar to Dejiko`s but is often too docile to conjure the aggression required to perform such a feat. This has caused many things to come out of her eyes, including sludge, when she attempts to use it.
Puchiko has brown hair and dark brown eyes. She wears a schoolgirl-type uniform plus cat bells in her hair, though they are much smaller than Dejiko`s. She wears orange boots, cat ears and tail. She ends each sentence with nyu.</description>
<picture>23836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6423" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="8">7.12</rating>
<name>Rabi-en-Rose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dejiko`s rival. Seen as a normal girl who uses dice to transform into her bunnygirl outfit: a pink, white and red dress with large white rabbit ears and a large round cotton tail. Her parents left her to live on her own in an attempt to help her become an idol.</description>
<picture>23837.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6424" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="1">4.91</rating>
<name>Gema</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The guardian of Dejiko and Puchiko. Essentially he is a floating yellow balloon that is always upside-down with very small eyes and mouth. He ends his sentences with gema. He can shoot darts out of bamboo sticks; but they have little effect on anyone.</description>
<picture>23838.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3028" picture="228622.jpg">Kamei Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6425" type="appears in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="1">9.38</rating>
<name>Hokke Mirin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A cat who is Puchiko`s sidekick. It can walk sideways and has five kittens; Sa, Shi, Su, Se, and So.</description>
<picture>23839.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6426" type="appears in" update="2009-04-23">
<name>Majin Gappa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A small green creature likened to a kappa, is Rabi-en-Rose`s sidekick.</description>
<picture>23840.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6427" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="7">5.40</rating>
<name>Pyocola Analogue III</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Princess of planet Analogue and leader of the Black Gema Gema Gang. Her parents left her in Rik, Ky, and Coo`s care until she is thirteen because they are embarrassed to show their faces when their attempt to take over planet Di Gi Charat failed. She had to flee to earth because she blew up a city and couldn`t pay for repairs. Piyoko`s dresses similar to that of a nurse`s uniform, but in black and white colors like a panda. She ends her sentences with "pyo". She has an attack similar to Dejiko`s Laser Eye Beam called Upchuck Bazooka which is a beam that comes from her mouth, but whenever she attempts to attack Dejiko with it, she more often than not gets attacked herself.</description>
<picture>23841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6428" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="5">4.92</rating>
<name>Rik Heisenberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The General of the Black Gema Gema Gang. He plays the role of the veterinarian of the doctor trio. He takes pride in his profession and loves animals. As a result, Rik has many animals around him. The animals include Bun Bun and Amaenbou. As the gang considers themselves a "family", Rik considers himself as the "Daddy".</description>
<picture>23842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6429" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="5">4.92</rating>
<name>Ky Schweitzer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Lieutenant General of the Black Gema Gema Gang. He is a dentist and always worries after Piyoko. Ky makes sure that Piyoko practices proper dental hygiene. As the gang considers themselves a "family", Ky considers himself as the "Mummy", even though he is a male. He seems embarrassed by the title.</description>
<picture>23843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6430" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-23">
<rating votes="5">4.92</rating>
<name>Coo Erhard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Major of the Black Gema Gema Gang. He is the physician of the group. He is Piyoko`s childhood friend and is closest to her. Sometimes if food flies through the air he will jump up and catch it in his mouth in a dog-like manner. As the gang considers themselves a "family", Coo is considered the "brother". However, Piyoko thinks she is older than him, although she is only 8 while he is 13.</description>
<picture>23844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3062" picture="170303.jpg">Saeki Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6431" type="appears in" update="2009-04-23">
<name>Nazo Gema</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gema`s counterpart in the Black Gema Gema Gang. Like Gema, it is round and floats in the air, but instead of being yellow, it is black. It also has large spooky eyes and red lips. It ends its sentences with "Geba".</description>
<picture>23845.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70332" type="appears in" update="2014-09-30">
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70335" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="3">4.92</rating>
<name>Minagawa Takurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minagawa Takurou is a boy from neighborhood. He is a drama club member.</description>
<picture>161991.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="186" picture="16999.jpg">Minami Omi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70340" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-30">
<name>Kimura Takurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kimura Takurou is a student who lives in a mansion near Gamers shop.</description>
<picture>161950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70342" type="appears in" update="2014-09-30">
<name>Yoshimi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshimi is a customer of Gamers and Dejiko`s fan.</description>
<picture>161953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3140" picture="24125.jpg">Mori Norihisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70343" type="appears in" update="2014-09-30">
<name>Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takeshi is a customer of Gamers and Dejiko`s fan.</description>
<picture>161952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="272" picture="233512.jpg">Naitou Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70383" type="appears in" update="2014-10-03">
<rating votes="3">9.18</rating>
<name>Abarenbou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70405" type="appears in" update="2014-09-30">
<name>Nanda Koitsu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A bear-like something which Dejiko met near the mountain that says Paoon. It followed her to Gamers where it stays in the cardboard. You can`t tell whether it is smiling, depressed, crying or angry.</description>
<picture>162040.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70409" type="appears in" update="2014-10-01">
<name>Black GemaGema Dan`in</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Worker from Analogue planet. They end their sentences with "Geba".</description>
<picture>162091.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70448" type="appears in" update="2014-10-03">
<name>Payapaya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="8002" update="2014-10-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぴよこが来たにょ / ブラックゲーマーズだにょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Here Comes Pyoko-nyo! / It`s the Black Gamers-nyo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Piyoko ga Kita-nyo / Black Gamers Da-nyo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8004" update="2014-10-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰ってきた暴れん坊 / 夏の虫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Return of Abarenbou / Summer Bug</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaette Kita Abarenbou / Natsu no Mushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163001" update="2014-10-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2000-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163002" update="2014-10-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2000-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
