<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10905" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2015-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Death Parade</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Парад смерти</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Парад на смъртта</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Парад смерті</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">デス・パレード</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Death Parade</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Death Parade</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">死亡游行</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9253" type="Side Story">Death Billiards</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3291" approval="19" total="24">Jigoku Shoujo</anime>
<anime id="9555" approval="2" total="9">Danganronpa: Kibou no Gakuen to Zetsubou no Koukousei - The Animation</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="834921">Watch Death Billiards first.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="386453">It really is a nice and somehow unique anime, that i enjoyed watching, but as Wildblood already mentioned since there are some side plots and questions unanswered the anime feels unfinished and leaves this bad feeling you get when a promising plot ends while still in the middle...

Nevertheless: The anime is still pretty good and lets you think about one or two things about life and death ^^

tl;dr: Good anime, you won`t really regret watching, but be aware of some major question left unanswered</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="241634">I have not seen such a nice anime in a while. I can`t connect it with another one even if it reminds me of some. If I would compare this anime with any that would be Mushishi. Not because they have to do anything with each other but because they are such great anime and yet they do not fit in a specific category, at least for me. 

The stories are calm and brutal at the same time, at least in most cases. It involves death and the people slowly recollect their past and last moments. It plays with psychology and makes you wonder and guess what will happen on the next step. 

The anime has a single negative thing like most anime that I like; It ends too fast!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="371767">This series is not a lighthearted one, nor is it a fast one with tons of action, or even a tons of shocking developments. So be careful with your expectations: the summary can unintentionally give a completely wrong idea of what the series may be about. It is more about the `bar` than it is about the `games`.

Regardless, with expectations held in check I do not believe it can disappoint. It has wonderful music, art and animation. Additionally, it has patience, subtlety and maturity: all of which are quite rare to see in anime these days.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="492628">10/10
Maturity, well written plot, good and believable characters, amazing animation. It has an episodic progression with an overall story going around that concludes in the most stunning way. Calling this epic is not enough, one of the best animes of 2015.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://vap.co.jp/deathparade/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="8263" type="Original Work">Tachikawa Yuzuru</name>
<name id="8263" type="Direction">Tachikawa Yuzuru</name>
<name id="9394" type="Character Design">Kurita Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="8263" type="Series Composition">Tachikawa Yuzuru</name>
<name id="731" type="Original Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="9394" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kurita Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="27786" type="Music">Hayashi Yuuki</name>
</creators>
<description>After death, humans go to either heaven or hell. But for some, at the instant of their death, they arrive at the Quindecim, a bar attended by the mysterious white-haired http://anidb.net/ch52162 [Decim]. He challenges them to the Death Game, wherein they wager their lives and reveal their true natures.
— adapted from ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3640">7.47</permanent>
<temporary count="3660">7.66</temporary>
<review count="1">4.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>240112.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16375</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>28223</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://vap.co.jp/deathparade/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ntv.co.jp/deathparade/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Death_Parade</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>デス・ビリヤード</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3633</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>350690</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17852</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/5304</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19387</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B00XVPBKLY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3568" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-07">
<name>gambling</name>
<description>Gambling is the wagering of money or something of value (referred to as "the stakes") on an event with an uncertain outcome with the primary intent of winning additional money and/or material goods. Gambling thus requires three elements be present: consideration, chance and prize. The outcome of the wager is often immediate, such as a single roll of dice or a spin of a roulette wheel, but longer time frames are also common, allowing wagers on the outcome of a future sports contest or even an entire sports season.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4281" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>mind games</name>
<description>An act or series of acts of calculated psychological manipulation, especially in order to confuse or intimidate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5494" parentid="3568" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-14">
<name>roulette</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5914" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-05">
<name>afterlife</name>
<description>The afterlife is the continued existence of an essential part of an individual`s identity or consciousness after the death of the body. When people continue existing beyond the death of their physical bodies, they may or may not keep interacting with the realm of the living and/or retain their memories. It is possible for them to start a new life without a physical body in a spirit realm, and they may or may not be able to understand that they`re already dead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="301" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-04-01">
<rating votes="1761">8.42</rating>
<name>Yagami Light</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character of Death Note, Light is an extremely intelligent but bored 17-year old student. When he finds the Death Note, dropped in the human world by the shinigami Ryuk, he decides to use it to kill all criminals and earns the title Kira. His ultimate goal is to cleanse the world of evil to create a world without criminals and then reign over this new world as its "god."</description>
<picture>231916.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="52159" type="main character in" update="2014-11-22">
<rating votes="49">7.72</rating>
<name>Kurokami no Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52162" type="main character in" update="2014-11-22">
<rating votes="49">7.16</rating>
<name>Decim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71456" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-22">
<rating votes="19">4.78</rating>
<name>Ginti</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71457" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-22">
<rating votes="30">7.65</rating>
<name>Nona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72097" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-17">
<rating votes="9">3.90</rating>
<name>Clavis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72098" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-17">
<rating votes="7">2.93</rating>
<name>Quin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72099" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-17">
<rating votes="6">3.29</rating>
<name>Castra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72100" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-17">
<rating votes="11">2.79</rating>
<name>Oculus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72654" type="appears in" update="2015-01-11">
<rating votes="5">2.10</rating>
<name>Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72655" type="appears in" update="2015-01-11">
<rating votes="5">3.66</rating>
<name>Machiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72664" type="appears in" update="2015-02-27">
<rating votes="9">5.29</rating>
<name>Arita Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72665" type="appears in" update="2015-01-16">
<rating votes="5">3.66</rating>
<name>Miyazaki Chisato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72666" type="appears in" update="2015-01-16">
<rating votes="5">4.55</rating>
<name>Miura Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72844" type="appears in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="4">2.04</rating>
<name>Tateishi Yousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72845" type="appears in" update="2015-01-26">
<rating votes="3">4.36</rating>
<name>Tachibana Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73048" type="appears in" update="2015-06-25">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38071" picture="188447.jpg">Matsumoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73049" type="appears in" update="2015-02-04">
<rating votes="2">2.51</rating>
<name>Fujii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73244" type="appears in" update="2015-02-27">
<rating votes="2">1.86</rating>
<name>Harada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73509" type="appears in" update="2015-02-27">
<rating votes="3">3.76</rating>
<name>Shimada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73510" type="appears in" update="2015-02-27">
<rating votes="5">5.01</rating>
<name>Tatsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74238" type="appears in" update="2015-04-01">
<rating votes="2">5.10</rating>
<name>Uemura Sachiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>171225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5352" picture="134103.jpg">Tani Ikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85453" type="appears in" update="2016-10-11">
<rating votes="3">3.51</rating>
<name>Memine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40735" picture="228067.jpg">Chiba Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85454" type="appears in" update="2016-10-11">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Novem</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21337" picture="207958.jpg">Yamamoto Shouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85455" type="appears in" update="2016-10-11">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Tria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40735" picture="228067.jpg">Chiba Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="165162" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デス・アーケード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death Arcade</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jeu d`arcade mortel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Death: Arcade</title>
<summary>TV personality Misaki Tachibana is convinced that she is in Quindecim as part of a hidden-camera TV show, and enlists her counterpart, Yousuke Tateishi, to help her liven the show up. Decim takes measures to ensure extreme conditions for the contestants.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="165163" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="22">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ローリング・バラード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rolling Ballade</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Balade roulante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rolling Ballad</title>
<summary>College student Shigeru Miura wakes up in Quindecim, and falls in love at first sight with the woman at the bar. Unable to remember even her own name, the woman asks him to play a game with her, after being assured that it will jog her memory.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="165164" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="22">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デス・リバース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death: Reverse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mort, vue de l`autre côté</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Death: Reverse</title>
<summary>A black-haired woman awakens in an unfamiliar place, unable to remember even her own name. She is taken by a girl named Nona to Quindecim, where she is told that she will be an assistant, and  is instructed as to the purpose of the bar`s existence.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="165165" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="27">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デス・セブンダーツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death: Seven Darts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sept fléchettes mortelles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Death: Seven Darts</title>
<summary>A young couple, Takashi and Machiko, arrive in the bar Quindecim without any recollection of how they got there. The bartender tells them they cannot leave until they first finish playing a game, one in which their lives will be at stake.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="165310" update="2019-12-31">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165311" update="2015-01-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165588" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デス・ラリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death Rally</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Échanges mortels</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Death Rally</title>
<summary>Prior to the arrival of a pair of guests--a police detective and young man raising his sister--Decim wonders if there has been a mistake, since the memories he has received are those of a killer. But despite his protestations, Nona prods him to continue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="165589" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルコール・ポイズン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alcohol Poison</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Poison alcoolique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alcohol Poison</title>
<summary>When the black-haired woman stumbles upon a picture book, she asks Decim about it, and he tells her that it might belong to Quin, Quindecim`s previous bartender. Decim reveals the reasons why he spends so much time putting together mannequins.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="165590" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クロス・ハート・アタック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cross Heart Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cross Heart Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cross Heart Attack</title>
<summary>A high-school girl named Mayu arrives at a Japanese-style bar being tended by Ginti. He demands that she play a game against the man in the bar, who she instantly recognizes as Harada, of the boy idol band C.H.A, and she eagerly accepts.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="165591" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デス・マーチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death March</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Marche de la mort</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Death: March</title>
<summary>Two more people--a young boy and an older man--arrive at Quindecim, but this time, Decim senses something out of place. Before Decim can explain the game to the pair, the older man reveals that he remembers having seen Decim and the bar before!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="166585" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スーサイド・ツアー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suicide Tour</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tournée suicide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suicide Tour</title>
<summary>Oculus confronts Nona concerning Decim, demanding to know what she has done to him. Chiyuki awakens in her house the living world again to find that Decim has brought her there to offer her the chance to reclaim her life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="166586" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メメント・モリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memento Mori</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Memento Mori</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Memento Mori</title>
<summary>Mayu is given a chance to spare Harada`s soul from the void, for a price. With Chiyuki`s judgment pending, she revisits her love of ice skating, with the hope that the memories she recovers will help her to come to terms with her passing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="166587" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ストーリー・テラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Story Teller</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Conteur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Story Teller</title>
<summary>Decim visits Nona and tells her that he believes that their way of passing judgment is flawed. Nona sends him another customer, whose case may unravel the mystery of the black-haired woman, and whom Decim chooses to judge without the aid of any memories.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="166588" update="2017-05-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="22">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デス・カウンター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Death Counter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Contre mortel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Death Counter</title>
<summary>As the two contestants continue their game, Shimada is surprised to learn that Detective Tatsumi is sympathetic to his desire for revenge against his sister`s attacker. The black-haired woman is troubled by how far Decim is willing to go.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="223416" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223417" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223418" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223419" update="2019-10-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223764" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 (1:05)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223765" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (2:01)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223766" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223767" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD/DVD CM (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223768" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223769" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223770" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223771" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223772" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223773" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223774" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223775" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223776" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223777" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223778" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 Preview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
