<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10941" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-03-14</startdate>
<enddate>2015-03-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Eiga Precure All Stars: Haru no Carnival</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Precure All Stars Movie: Spring`s Carnival</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">映画プリキュアオールスターズ 春のカーニバル♪</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11797" type="Sequel">Eiga Precure All Stars: Minna de Utau - Kiseki no Mahou!</anime>
<anime id="10227" type="Prequel">Eiga Precure All Stars New Stage 3: Eien no Tomodachi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.precure-allstars.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2804" type="Direction">Shimizu Junji</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="5707" type="Character Design">Aoyama Mitsuru</name>
<name id="2808" type="Original Work">Toudou Izumi</name>
</creators>
<description>A spring carnival held in the country of dance and song, Harmonia, is beginning. http://anidb.net/ch72231 [Haruno Haruka] and her friends join the festival to learn dance and song from their senior Precure warriors. However, the fairies go missing and the carnival is thrown into confusion. Even worse, the announcers Odoren and Utaen seem extremely suspicious and the guardian dragon of Harmonia has started a rampage, angry at the chaos at the carnival. In order to protect the peace of Harmonia, the 40 Precure warriors work together to create a miracle through dance and song filled with hope.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="46">4.33</permanent>
<temporary count="46">5.96</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>164389.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16727</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>28511</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>30103</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.precure-allstars.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>映画_プリキュアオールスターズ_春のカーニバル♪</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3682</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>350897</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18071</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="164336" update="2015-03-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>75</length>
<airdate>2015-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170104" update="2015-07-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">映画プリキュアオールスターズ 春のカーニバル♪ 「イマココカラ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Precure All Stars Movie: Haru no Carnival: Feature Dance Presentation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Precure All Stars Movie: Haru no Carnival: Ima Koko Kara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189196" update="2017-07-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Precure All Stars Haru no Carnival Preview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
