<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10958" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2015-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Houkago no Pleiades (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">放課後のプレアデス (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Wish Upon the Pleiades (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">방과후의 플레이아데스</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">放学后的昴星团</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8076" type="Other">Houkago no Pleiades</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://sbr-gx.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="718" type="Animation Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="4255" type="Character Design">Ootsuka Mai</name>
<name id="718" type="Original Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="4255" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ootsuka Mai</name>
<name id="2019" type="Music">Hamaguchi Shirou</name>
<name id="3592" type="Direction">Saeki Shouji</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch24673 [Subaru] is a young girl who discovers that her best friend http://anidb.net/ch24672 [Aoi] is part of magical group trying to gather engine fragments so that a little being from Pleiades star system can return to his home. Subaru considers joining them as she was chosen by the Pleiadian, president of this afterschool club.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="395">4.15</permanent>
<temporary count="395">5.82</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>171719.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16641</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17919</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sbr-gx.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Wish_Upon_the_Pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>放課後のプレアデス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3714</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>351833</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18136</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3097" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-29">
<name>underwater</name>
<description>Underwater is a term describing the realm below the surface of water where the water exists in a natural feature such as an ocean, sea, lake, pond, or river.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4446" parentid="2639" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-12">
<name>faster-than-light travel</name>
<description>Faster-than-light travel is taken for grated in this anime. This is achieved by travelling via hyperspace, nullspace, or wormholes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4706" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-14">
<name>astronomy</name>
<description>Astronomy is the study of celestial objects (such as stars, galaxies, planets, moons, asteroids, comets and nebulae) and processes (such as supernovae explosions, gamma ray bursts, and cosmic microwave background radiation), the physics, chemistry, and evolution of such objects and processes, and more generally all phenomena that originate outside the atmosphere of Earth.
Astronomy is the oldest of the natural sciences. The early civilizations in recorded history, such as the Babylonians, Greeks, Indians, Egyptians, Nubians, Iranians, Chinese, and Maya performed methodical observations of the night sky. Historically, astronomy has included disciplines as diverse as astrometry, celestial navigation, observational astronomy and the making of calendars, but professional astronomy is nowadays often considered to be synonymous with astrophysics.
During the 20th century, the field of professional astronomy split into observational and theoretical branches. Observational astronomy is focused on acquiring data from observations of astronomical objects, which is then analyzed using basic principles of physics. Theoretical astronomy is oriented toward the development of computer or analytical models to describe astronomical objects and phenomena. The two fields complement each other, with theoretical astronomy seeking to explain the observational results and observations being used to confirm theoretical results.
Astronomy is one of the few sciences where amateurs can still play an active role, especially in the discovery and observation of transient phenomena. Amateur astronomers have made and contributed to many important astronomical discoveries, such as finding new comets.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5787" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>time dilation</name>
<description>Time dilation is a scientific phenomena related to relativity, basically stating that for an observer onboard a spaceship travelling at a certain speed, time passes more slowly than it would for an observer on Earth. 
When near-lightspeed travel becomes involved, the effects become quite drastic: a person might go on a space journey that seems to him to last one year and, on returning, find that 10 years have passed on Earth. This is sometimes extrapolated by sci-fi authors to apply to faster-than-light travel as well, though this would not necessarily be the case. 
Note that this effect occurs at considerably lower velocities as well, as an atomic clock on Earth and one in orbit around Earth will be ever so slightly desynced.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5871" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-19">
<name>breathing in space</name>
<description>Find yourself in space without an oxygen tank? Not a problem! Breathing in the vacuum of space is just as easy as breathing on Earth, especially if you are a superhero or somehow able to leave the atmosphere under your own power.</description>
<picurl>166122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="24671" type="main character in" update="2010-11-01">
<rating votes="9">5.53</rating>
<name>Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24672" type="main character in" update="2010-11-01">
<rating votes="10">4.52</rating>
<name>Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3622" picture="214935.jpg">Oohashi Ayuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24673" type="main character in" update="2010-11-01">
<rating votes="9">6.16</rating>
<name>Subaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24674" type="main character in" update="2010-11-01">
<rating votes="9">5.64</rating>
<name>Itsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4923" picture="51991.jpg">Tateno Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24675" type="main character in" update="2010-11-01">
<rating votes="8">4.59</rating>
<name>Hikaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28072" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-31">
<rating votes="3">1.76</rating>
<name>Minato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28074" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-31">
<rating votes="3">1.62</rating>
<name>Pleiades Seijin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64820.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76421" type="appears in" update="2015-07-19">
<name>Erunato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76422" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-19">
<name>Nazo no Shounen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="167220" update="2015-03-22">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Anime Japan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167221" update="2015-03-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167222" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソの夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dream of Sol</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rêve en sol</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">솔의 꿈</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">So no Yume</title>
<summary>Subaru are the others are able to go to the stratosphere now, but the next fragment appears in the moon`s planetary orbit! After a word from Hikaru, Subaru and the others begin training to travel to the moon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678471</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167223" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">5人のシンデレラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Five Cinderellas</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cinq Cendrillons</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">5명의 신데렐라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gonin no Cinderella</title>
<summary>Subaru and the others continue to gather engine fragments while publically becoming the Cosplay Club. However, the president calls all five of them ordinary junk in a roundabout way, leading Subaru to feel bad about her imperfect self.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678469</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167224" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星めぐりの歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Song of the Traveling Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La chanson des étoiles</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">별을 도는 노래</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi Meguri no Uta</title>
<summary>The following day after collecting their first engine fragment, Subaru goes to school only to find the other four girls are now her classmates. With Nanako interpreting for him, their President, a pleiadian, explains to Subaru that the five of them were gathered from different timelines that usually wouldn`t intersect.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678467</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167225" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流星予報: 雨時々流れ星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meteor Shower Forecast: Rain with Occasional Shooting Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bulletin météore : Alternance entre pluie et étoiles filantes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">유성 예보: 비 때때로 별똥별</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuusei Yohou: Ame Tokidoki Nagareboshi</title>
<summary>Subaru was a middle school girl who loved stargazing, but she was the only member of the astronomy club. Her childhood friend, Aoi, was now commuting to a different school, and their relationship had grown distant.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678465</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167885" update="2015-04-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168110" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ななこ13</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nanako 13</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nanako 13</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">나나코 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanako 13</title>
<summary>A fragment appears on the outer edge of the solar system, 0.25 light years away from Earth. Not only will it take 3 months at the speed of light to reach it, someone has to go on ahead of the others to pinpoint its location. The one who volunteers for that solitary journey is Nanako.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678479</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168111" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タカラモノフタツ 或いは イチゴノカオリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Treasures or the Smell of Strawberries</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les deux trésors, ou le parfum de la fraise</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">보물 두 개 혹은 딸기 향기</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takaramono Futatsu Aruiwa Ichigo no Kaori</title>
<summary>Subaru became depressed after losing sight of Minato. She tried to raise the flower remained from the greenhouse, so she joined the Gardening Club in caring for the flower beds. Meanwhile, Aoi worried about Subaru after seeing her like that and started growing frustrated with herself for being unable to do anything.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678477</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168112" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">目覚めの花</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flower of Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fleur de l`éveil</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">각성의 꽃</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezame no Hana</title>
<summary>The pleadian spaceship that had been invisibly floating in orbit around Earth begins to materialize. It becomes a grave task as they have to gather the fragments and stop the spaceship from materializing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678475</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168113" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帽子と氷とお姫様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Hat, Ice, and a Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chapeau, glace et princesse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">모자와 얼음과 공주님</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boushi to Koori to Ohime-sama</title>
<summary>The school`s theater festival draws near and Subaru`s class begins to decide the casting for their play. Itsuki is chosen to play the lead princess, and everyone agreed with that casting, but... Meanwhile, their meteor shower forecast detects the appearance of another fragment.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678473</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168572" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">渚にて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the Water`s Edge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sur la plage</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">물가로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagisa nite</title>
<summary>After going through several jumps to chase the final fragment that appeared beyond their galaxy, they reach the edge of the universe where even light distorts, and find a black hole waiting before their eyes. According to the President, the final fragment lies within that black hole, and at the current rate, the fragment will escape their universe before they can collect it! In order to stop its escape, they`ll need to draw the fragment back out of the black hole. Will they manage to retrieve the final fragment and safely repair the space ship`s engine before it`s all over?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678487</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168573" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の光と彼の名前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Light and His Name</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La dernière lueur et son nom</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">최후의 빛과 그의 이름</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Hikari to Kare no Namae</title>
<summary>Though Subaru managed to reclaim the fragments, her magic was lost in exchange. Subaru was shocked and bewildered, and while the five of them worried over it, they decided to work hard and enjoy the culture festival for now since there was nothing they could do.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678485</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168574" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キラキラな夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining Night</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nuit étincelante</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">반짝반짝한 밤</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirakira na Yoru</title>
<summary>The boy in black clothing steals all the fragments being stored in the Astronomy club for safekeeping during preparations for the culture festival. Then he goes further, drawing a brand new fragment towards him in the stratosphere
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678483</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168575" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プラネタリウムランデブー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planetarium Rendezvous</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rendez-vous au planétarium</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">플라네타리움 랑데부</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Planetarium Rendezvous</title>
<summary>The Culture Festival draws near. While the cosplay club decides to showcase outfits, Subaru decides to create a simple planetarium for the Astronomy club. Subaru was the only member of the club, but with Minato helping her out, things were proceeding smoothly. Seeing the nice atmosphere between Subaru and Minato, Hikaru and the others secretly plot to enter the two of them into the Culture Festival`s Couple Contest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678481</identifier>
<identifier>wish-upon-the-pleiades</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170120" update="2015-07-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
