<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10953" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-04-18</startdate>
<enddate>2015-04-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Meitantei Conan: Gouka no Himawari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Detective Conan Movie 19</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Detective Conan: Sunflowers of Inferno</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Detective Conan - Gouka no Himawari</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Detektiv Conan - 19. Film: Die Sonnenblumen der Hölle</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">名探偵コナン・業火の向日葵</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">名偵探柯南 業火的向日葵</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Detective Conan 19 - Los girasoles del fuego infernal</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="266" type="Parent Story">Meitantei Conan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.conan-movie.jp/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="917" type="Animation Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="474" type="Original Work">Aoyama Goushou</name>
<name id="14495" type="Direction">Shizuno Koubun</name>
<name id="4325" type="Music">Oono Katsuo</name>
<name id="49260" type="Animation Work">V1 Studio</name>
<name id="3743" type="Character Design">Sudou Masatomo</name>
<name id="3743" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sudou Masatomo</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch2260 [Conan] tries to track down http://anidb.net/ch8219 [Kaitou Kid], who supposedly steals a replica of one of Van Gogh`s Sunflowers paintings during an auction.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="216">6.64</permanent>
<temporary count="218">7.13</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>179638.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16837</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>28479</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.conan-movie.jp/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Detective_Conan:_Sunflowers_of_Inferno</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>名探偵コナン_業火の向日葵</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4182</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>350825</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18150</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="165" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>painting</name>
<description>Painting is the practice of applying paint, pigment, color or other medium[1] to a surface (support base). The medium is commonly applied to the base with a brush but other implements, such as knives, sponges, and airbrushes, can be used.
In art, the term painting describes both the act and the result of the action. Paintings may have for their support such surfaces as walls, paper, canvas, wood, glass, lacquer, clay, leaf, copper or concrete, and may incorporate multiple other materials including sand, clay, paper, gold leaf as well as objects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2684" parentid="2812" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>New York</name>
<description>The City of New York, often called New York City or simply New York, is the most populous city in the United States. New York City is also the most densely populated major city in the United States. Located at the southern tip of the state of New York, the city is the center of the New York metropolitan area, one of the most populous urban agglomerations in the world.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214276.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3797" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-13">
<name>trapped in the body of a child</name>
<description>For some reason, a character in this anime who is a late-teenager or an adult, has their mind trapped in the body of a child. E.g. a former late teenager or an adult is transformed into a child. This can be the result of magic, science, or otherwise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5838" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-26">
<name>fire</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2260" type="main character in" update="2012-02-12">
<rating votes="1562">7.54</rating>
<name>Edogawa Conan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2263" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-07-05">
<rating votes="724">7.91</rating>
<name>Kudou Shin`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2343" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-03">
<rating votes="1032">7.69</rating>
<name>Mouri Ran</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mouri Ran is one of the main characters in Detective Conan. She is the daughter of Mouri Kogoro, a famous but lazy detective. She is also friends with Kudo Shinichi, another famous detective, who is still in high school. She is the captain of the high school karate team, and is very strong willed.</description>
<picture>65742.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="321" picture="17158.jpg">Yamazaki Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8163" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="513">6.60</rating>
<name>Mouri Kogorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kogorou was once with the police, but due to an incident that involved his wife Eri as well, he quit. Due to the same incident, he and Eri split up.
He`s got custody of his daughter Ran who lives with him in an apartment that is at the same time his detective agency, on top of a café named Coffee Poirot. Despite of having been a good policeman, he`s a bad detective - but still very famous. That only comes due to the fact that Conan is "abusing" this adult`s sedated body to deduct his theories for the sake of outing the high amount of murderers whose crimes he solved.
Kogorou might be a smoking, drinking, good-for-nothing loudmouth with a high affection to idol Okino Youko, but he still is a good guy when it comes to handling his daughter or wife.
Due to Conan having made him famous as the Sleeping Kogorou, he sometimes gets over his head and just believes he`s the big shot everybody else thinks he is.
Kogorou finally accepts Conan as a "lodger", when Conan`s "mother" gave him access to an account filled with 10.000.000 Yen (about 90.000€/122.500$).
His voice is Number 59 on Conan`s bowtie.</description>
<picture>54062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8164" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-15">
<rating votes="255">3.94</rating>
<name>Agasa Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Agasa Hiroshi  is a good friend of Shin`ichi / Conan who invents several devices to help him out, such as the voice changing bowtie or the watch with which Conan can tranquilize people.
Note: His name Hiroshi is written with the kanji 博士, which can also be read `Hakase` (Professor)</description>
<picture>27247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8165" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-03">
<rating votes="987">8.25</rating>
<name>Haibara Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8167" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-23">
<rating votes="352">5.85</rating>
<name>Yoshida Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1623" picture="171605.jpg">Iwai Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8168" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-23">
<rating votes="138">2.86</rating>
<name>Tsuburaya Mitsuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8169" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-23">
<rating votes="106">4.41</rating>
<name>Kojima Genta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8170" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="388">5.35</rating>
<name>Suzuki Sonoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sonoko is Mouri Ran`s best friend and is the girlfriend of http://anidb.net/ch8180 [Kyougoku Makoto].
Source: detectiveconanworld.com</description>
<picture>28515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="291" picture="17122.jpg">Matsui Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8183" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-10">
<rating votes="62">3.55</rating>
<name>Megure Juuzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inspector Juuzou is a veteran police officer who has been working with http://anidb.net/ch2263 [Kudou Shin`ichi], http://anidb.net/ch8175 [Kudou Yuusaku] and http://anidb.net/ch8163 [Mouri Kogoro]. He always wears his hat to hide an old scar which reminds him of a special case from 20 years ago, during his early police days which involved his wife, http://anidb.net/ch16583 [Midori].</description>
<picture>27267.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8190" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-16">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Nakamori Ginzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Inspector of the Police Headquarter`s Criminal Investigation Squad 2.</description>
<picture>30853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8219" type="main character in" update="2009-06-03">
<rating votes="218">8.44</rating>
<name>Kaitou Kid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9190" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<name>Suzuki Jirokichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3301" picture="24327.jpg">Tomita Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16589" type="appears in" update="2014-10-24">
<name>Jii Kounosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jii Kounosuke is http://anidb.net/ch8218 [Kuroba Kaitou]`s assistant.</description>
<picture>46103.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="399" picture="17244.jpg">Suyama Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="23561" type="appears in" update="2010-10-28">
<name>Lupin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58150.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="80756" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Keiko Anderson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="571" picture="172734.jpg">Sakakibara Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80757" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Miyadai Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183956.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="80758" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Azuma Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5243" picture="29266.jpg">Isobe Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80759" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Kishi Kumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80760" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Ishimine Taizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80761" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Charlie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="144" picture="16904.jpg">Sakuya Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80762" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Umeno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5026" picture="151676.jpg">Sawada Toshiko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80763" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Haraguchi Hideo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80764" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Azuma Kiyosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80765" type="appears in" update="2016-03-09">
<name>Gotou Zengo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="164612" update="2015-04-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2015-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168315" update="2015-05-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Short Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171271" update="2015-09-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 5 of 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171272" update="2015-09-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 4 of 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171273" update="2015-09-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171274" update="2015-09-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171275" update="2015-09-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 5</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
