<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10962" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-07-10</startdate>
<enddate>2016-09-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ange Vierge</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">アンジュ・ヴィエルジュ "Progress": Girls facing destiny against Worlds` Ending</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アンジュ・ヴィエルジュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ange Vierge</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">圣洁天使</title>
</titles>
<url>http://ange-vierge-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2900" type="Animation Work">Silver Link</name>
<name id="9728" type="Character Design">Tamura Masafumi</name>
<name id="2836" type="Series Composition">Takayama Katsuhiko</name>
<name id="1178" type="Original Work">Sega</name>
<name id="38970" type="Original Work">Kadokawa</name>
<name id="9728" type="Direction">Tamura Masafumi</name>
<name id="11391" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takimoto Shouko</name>
<name id="37485" type="Animation Work">Connect</name>
<name id="39598" type="Music">Wakabayashi Takatsugu</name>
</creators>
<description>One day, out of the blue, the five worlds were linked together. Our blue world, Earth. The black world, ruled by night and magic, Darknes Embrace. The red world, protected by prayer and by the gods: Tera Rubily Aurora. The white world, managed by science and computers: System White Egma. The green world, governed by weapons and armies: Glynnesert. Meanwhile, in each of the worlds, there was an emergence of girls possessing special "Exceed" abilities. The girls would come to be known as the Progress. There, the girls would meet. The world is on the verge of doom. Only the Progress can save it.
Source: Crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="353">2.59</permanent>
<temporary count="356">5.10</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>187768.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18170</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32171</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ange-vierge-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ange_Vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アンジュ・ヴィエルジュ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4214</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354559</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19241</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ange_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07B6B948P</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2968" parentid="4831" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-05">
<name>faceless alien invasion</name>
<description>Uncommunicative, faceless aliens suddenly invade Earth from outer space or a parallel world thus causing a war with humans.
If the humans are lucky, the invasion may go off without a war that would cause untold destruction and death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3771" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>recycled animation -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag overlaps recaps, http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks], and http://anidb.net/t3671 [footage reuse]. For that reason, it is set to be split. If you can, please apply the correct tag to the anime that have it, and remove this one from them; guidance on how to use each of those tags can be found in their description. If what the anime contains is a mere recap, please don`t apply any tag at all, and remove this tag from it instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4352" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-11">
<name>censored uncensored version</name>
<description>Even the DVD and Blu-ray releases do not let you see everything you were expecting to, and you will have to live with censorship in the show. That normally applies to fan service, but may also apply to gore and violence. A very common example is characters without nipples, as in http://anidb.net/a6083 [KissXSis]; in other cases, something such as steam or foam stays in the camera`s way, like in http://anidb.net/a6531 [Kanamemo]. In some shows, the censorship in the disk releases is even stronger than in the TV version, while others may use creative censorship as a replacement for the removed fan service or even as a joke.
This does not apply to censorship of what Japanese pornography laws still require to be censored.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-02">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your month and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="81150" type="main character in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="7">7.23</rating>
<name>Almaria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81151" type="main character in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">6.28</rating>
<name>Elel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81152" type="main character in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="4">4.58</rating>
<name>Code Omega 77 Stella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42286" picture="167754.jpg">Tachibana Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81153" type="main character in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="6">6.22</rating>
<name>Nya Lapucea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34234" picture="228806.jpg">Bridcutt Sarah Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81154" type="main character in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="6">4.79</rating>
<name>Sougetsu Saya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81202" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">6.87</rating>
<name>Code Omega 00 Euphiria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81203" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">5.04</rating>
<name>Sofina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34195" picture="187736.jpg">Ishihara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81204" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">4.72</rating>
<name>Mayuka Sanagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81205" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<name>Ruby</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12666" picture="42833.jpg">Ikuta Yoshiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81206" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">2.78</rating>
<name>Hinata Miumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38613" picture="200781.jpg">Aisaka Yuuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82077" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="7">5.36</rating>
<name>Ayashiro Amane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188536.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82998" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">4.72</rating>
<name>Mikage Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82999" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Ramiel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83000" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">5.32</rating>
<name>Code Omega 33 Carene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83001" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Code Omega 46 Xenia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83002" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">2.21</rating>
<name>Eins Exaura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83003" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">4.72</rating>
<name>Ageha Sanagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83004" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="3">8.58</rating>
<name>Aurora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83005" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="5">6.60</rating>
<name>Dr. Michael</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83006" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-16">
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<name>Clara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46311" picture="188558.jpg">Satou Saya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="178400" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇を灼く炎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Flame That Burns Through Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les ténèbres à l`épreuve du feu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami o Yaku Honoo</title>
<summary>Saya and the others are to make their way to Darkness Embrace, the Black World. They have confirmed that the energy “Extra,” important to the worlds, is being lowered there. They are ordered to investigate, but someone’s there waiting for them…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715711</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178401" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">絆の代償</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Price of Bonds</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Renouer les liens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuna no Daishou</title>
<summary>The girls have to deal with the aftermath of the Ouroboros attack. Their fighting power has been greatly reduced, and they soon find out that things are worse than they had feared when some of the members are corrupted by the darkness...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715709</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178402" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憧れの背中</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One I Admire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Courir après ses rêves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akogare no Senaka</title>
<summary>The blooming battle between Saya and the other Progress comes to an end, and the result drives a wedge between Saya and Amane.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715707</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178403" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじまりの可能性</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starting Potential</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La naissance d`un potentiel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Kanousei</title>
<summary>Girl that have been dubbed the "Progress" are those which have awakened to the superpower "Exceed". These girls, from the five different worlds that exist, are kept safe and trained at Seiran Academy. They train day and night with their alpha drivers, a person who has the ability to enhance their powers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715705</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178673" update="2016-07-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178674" update="2016-07-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179116" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛しさの理由</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reason for Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce qui fait la beauté</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itoshisa no Riyuu</title>
<summary>The team receives a distress signal from Code Omega 46 Xenia in the White World, System White Eguma. Saya and the others immediately head to rescue her, but Code Omega 33 Carene stands in their way, and has a dangerous virus that threatens to destroy the White World.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715719</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179117" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当のともだち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Real Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une véritable amie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hontou no Tomodachi</title>
<summary>Elel feels down after being told off by Ramiel, who has turned to the dark side. Saya tries to make her feel better, but Ramiel makes another attack, and this time the Red World`s world crystal is in her sights. Elel and the others set out to try to win Ramiel back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715717</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179118" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘘の笑顔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Lying Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sourire mensonger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uso no Egao</title>
<summary>Saya and the others are heading to the Red World, Terra Rubiri Aurora, to check on the Ouroboros, but Elel`s best friend, Ramiel, is waiting for them. Ramiel asks Elel if they`re really friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715715</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179119" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅蓮の脈動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crimson Pulse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pulsations pourpres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guren no Myakudou</title>
<summary>Almaria is a vampire with a complex that stops her from sucking blood because she`s too embarrassed, and Sofina keeps inviting Almaria to suck her blood. Almaria is faced with a dilemma. On one hand, she respects Sofina, but on the other...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715713</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179840" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">私は, あなたと進化する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Will Evolve with You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je grandis avec toi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi wa, Anata to Shinka Suru</title>
<summary>At last, Saya and the others stand in the face of the ultimate enemy.  Will they be able to defeat the massive ouroboros and save the five worlds and their alpha drivers?  The chosen Progress prepare for the last battle to retake their bonds with Amane.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715727</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179841" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">残された可能性</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Remaining Possibility</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un potentiel préservé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokosareta Kanousei</title>
<summary>Saya goes to visit the frozen Amane and is met by a fallen Aoi.  Saya and the others are helpless before Aoi`s overwhelming power.  At the same time, the massive ouroboros descends upon Seiran Island.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715725</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179842" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">零れた想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emotions Spilled Over</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Débordante d`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koboreta Omoi</title>
<summary>Nya figures she has to move after seeing Saya and the others deepen their bonds, and heads off to the Green World on her own. But an army of Ouroboros stands in her way.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715723</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179843" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰よりも速く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Faster Than Anyone</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La plus rapide de toutes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dare yori mo Hayaku</title>
<summary>In order to destroy the White World`s world crystal by injecting a virus into it, Carene must fly at an incredibly fast speed. The only one who can stop her now is Stella and her Exceed with the power of super-speed. With the help of Saya and the others, Stella chases after Carene.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715721</identifier>
<identifier>ange-vierge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
