<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10970" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-07-02</startdate>
<enddate>2015-09-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Okusama ga Seitokaichou!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">おくさまが生徒会長!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">My Wife Is the Student Council President</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我老婆是学生会长</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11901" type="Sequel">Okusama ga Seitokaichou! Plus!</anime>
<anime id="11743" type="Other">Okusama ga Seitokaichou! Seitokaichou to Ofuro Asobi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3360" approval="8" total="10">Okusama wa Joshikousei (2005)</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="430272">This is really funny. Yes like the other comments mention it does sometimes get borderline hentai. But I also like how he reacts like a normal guy not always that denying his interest!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="315386">Recommeded for prevy anime.

1st off the tv is from At-x so it`s uncensored,
Secondly it;s borderline and (they alway stop just in time)= a good tease (which is good for u)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="687054">this series just know how to tease &amp; tempt the audience + some silly comedy. like it.
want another season please.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.dreamcreation.co.jp/okusama/</url>
<creators>
<name id="27343" type="Animation Work">Seven</name>
<name id="12155" type="Direction">Furukawa Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="31384" type="Work">Dream Creation</name>
<name id="12155" type="Character Design">Furukawa Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="10229" type="Original Work">Nakata Yumi</name>
<name id="36772" type="Music">Hatori Fuuga</name>
<name id="12155" type="Chief Animation Direction">Furukawa Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="47055" type="Series Composition">Takada Makoto</name>
</creators>
<description>"Seifuu High School, the newly opened school I am attending, has a new student council president like none we have ever seen." — Izumi Hayato
http://anidb.net/ch75357 [Izumi Hayato], as member of the student council strongly opposes the president http://anidb.net/ch75361 [Wakana Ui]`s "strong push for the liberation of love" at their school. But her charm reaches her fellow students and also the other student council members: treasurer http://anidb.net/ch75362 [Fujisaki Karen] and secretary http://anidb.net/ch75358 [Niikura Ayane].
When Ui makes an appointment with Hayato late in the evening, little does he know what is in store for him: Ui`s irresponsible mother in Canada OK`ed not only that Ui take up residence in Hayato`s apartment, but also live there as his wife. This came about because Hayato`s father apparently asked Ui`s parents many years ago to have their daughter marry Hayato.
And so Hayato`s bizarre life with the student council president and self-appointed wife begins...
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1549">3.87</permanent>
<temporary count="1557">6.12</temporary>
<review count="1">6.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>223874.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16812</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>28819</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>32634</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dreamcreation.co.jp/okusama/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Okusama_ga_Seitokaichō!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>おくさまが生徒会長!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3793</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352847</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18284</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19165</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2698" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>pantyjob</name>
<description>Stimulation done by rubbing through the panties. This involves no penetration.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="75356" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-30">
<rating votes="68">7.39</rating>
<name>Misumi Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misumi Rin is the head of the disciplinary committee, who dislikes http://anidb.net/ch75361 [Ui]`s love campaign. She`s somewhat hostile towards http://anidb.net/ch75357 [Hayato] as well, but later on she develops feelings for him after he treats her nicely and helps her on various occasions.
She explains that she joined the committee because she wanted to disclaim a rumor that she was seducing guys with her large chest by emphasizing her morally pure side.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>196333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21823" picture="131326.jpg">Tsuda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75357" type="main character in" update="2016-12-30">
<rating votes="32">5.18</rating>
<name>Izumi Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Izumi Hayato is a fairly serious individual who is the vice-president of the student council. He is set up with http://anidb.net/ch75361 [Wakana Ui] in an arranged marriage and must live with her in his apartment. Despite his ever-growing respect for Ui throughout the series, he often gets caught in her romantic advances which make him uncomfortable yet aroused. Hayato is notably self-sufficient, having cooked and cleaned for himself prior to Ui`s arrival.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>196334.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75358" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-30">
<rating votes="30">5.71</rating>
<name>Niikura Ayane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Niikura Ayane is the student council secretary. She likes to dress up in frilly outfits and cat ears. She is a bit spacey and absent-minded.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>196335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39062" picture="148642.jpg">Fujimoto Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75359" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-03">
<rating votes="41">6.88</rating>
<name>Sawatari Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sawatari Makoto is a member of the disciplinary committee, working under http://anidb.net/ch75356 [Misumi Rin]. She looks after Rin like http://anidb.net/ch75362 [Karen] does with http://anidb.net/ch75361 [Ui].
Makoto also has a collection of pictures of Rin in embarrassing situations.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>196319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22625" picture="59506.jpg">Nagatsuma Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75360" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-30">
<rating votes="20">6.40</rating>
<name>Wakana Misato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wakana Misato is http://anidb.net/ch75361 [Ui]`s energetic and playful mother. Her petite stature makes everyone think she is Ui`s little sister.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>196336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75361" type="main character in" update="2015-09-13">
<rating votes="65">7.64</rating>
<name>Wakana Ui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The newly-elected student council president, elected on a platform of "liberalising love" in the school. Her parents and Izumi Hayato`s parents arranged their marriage.</description>
<picture>175296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75362" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-30">
<rating votes="31">5.95</rating>
<name>Fujisaki Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fujisaki Karen is the student council treasurer. She is petite and is extremely devoted to http://anidb.net/ch75362 [Ui], harboring a perverted interest in her. She dislikes http://anidb.net/ch75357 [Hayato] and often comes in conflict with him.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>196320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43251" picture="190511.jpg">Sugiyama Yoshie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76280" type="appears in" update="2016-12-30">
<rating votes="2">2.13</rating>
<name>Kurihara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurihara is http://anidb.net/ch75357 [Hayato]`s classmate.</description>
<picture>196337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43348" picture="175073.jpg">Tan Takafumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76281" type="appears in" update="2015-07-12">
<rating votes="3">2.19</rating>
<name>Hayato no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46596" picture="189825.jpg">Yamaguchi Kazumichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76923" type="appears in" update="2016-12-30">
<rating votes="46">7.72</rating>
<name>Misumi Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Misumi Kei is http://anidb.net/ch75356 [Rin]`s elder sister, and the school nurse. She likes to wear sexy clothing, much to Rin`s annoyance. She lives in the unit next to http://anidb.net/ch75361 [Ui] and http://anidb.net/ch75357 [Hayato]`s.</description>
<picture>196338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77449" type="appears in" update="2016-12-30">
<rating votes="9">2.66</rating>
<name>Wakana Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wakana Ryou is http://anidb.net/ch75361 [Ui]`s father whose youthful appearance makes him look more like her little brother. He is severe and strict, although when he is pensive, little rats appear atop his head much like his daughter with the baby chicks.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>196339.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="169408" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会長がいないところで雨宿り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shelter from the Rain Without the President</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">S’abriter de la pluie sans la présidente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitokaichou ga Inai Tokoro de Amayadori</title>
<summary>Rin is once again attempting to prevent students from hand-holding, but Ui sees her this time and stops her. After school, Rin follows Ui and Hayato as they go home, but it suddenly starts to rain heavily. They run, trying to seek shelter, but Rin is distracted by a couple passing by sharing an umbrella. She trips into Hayato and they stumble into a love hotel and are forced into a room. Hayato has her change into a white swimsuit the hotel made available while he dries her clothes, and she tells about how she knew the couple and was somewhat close to the boy, and how a rumour started spreading about how she supposedly seduced him with her chest. She joined the Morals Committee and became such a zealot to prove her moral character despite her large breasts.
Rin finds a small vibrator and wonders what it is, much to Hayato`s alarm, but she refuses to give it to him, and puts it between her breasts. It turns on and migrates down her body between her legs. Startled and enraged she throws it against the wall. As they leave the hotel they run into Ui, who suddenly realises where they had gone.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682737</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169409" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会長と手つなぎ実験</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Student Council President and the Hand-Holding Experiment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tenir la main de la présidente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitokaichou to Te Tsunagi Jikken</title>
<summary>Misumi Rin admonishes a couple in the hall holding hands, she is seen by Karen who reports the incident to the Student Council. This prompts a discussion among them about it, and they all admit that none of them have actually even dated a guy to begin with. Hayato says that their policy of liberalising love amounts to a direct challenge to Rin`s Morals Committee, and then Rin and Makoto arrive themselves. There is a bit of an argument, Hayato saying that she is overreacting about hand-holding, and then takes her hand to illustrate. This flusters her greatly and she leaves.
Later that night in Hayato`s home, Ui tries to experiment with hand-holding. He eventually gets deeply flustered himself as she goes on to licking his fingers, eventually escalating to dry humping. She later concludes that hand-holding does indeed lead to indecent feelings, but she still refuses to accept Rin`s position, saying that if not taken too far such physical contact strengthens a couple`s feelings for each other and enables them to accept each others` imperfections.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682735</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169410" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会長とおうちごはん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Student Council President and Dinner at Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Repas à la maison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitokaichou to Ouchi Gohan</title>
<summary>Hayato left his "wife" Ui to sleep in his bed, setting up a futon for himself in the living room. He wakes up the next morning to find that Ui migrated to his futon in confusion after using the toilet that evening. He finds that she is not quite the same person in private as the "perfect superwoman" she appears to be in school. He makes her breakfast. His efforts to get her to "go home" to her own house are unavailing.
It appears that not everyone in the school is pleased with Ui`s platform of liberalising romance, most notably the school morals committee, led by Misumi Rin. Hayato attends cram school and is shocked to go home and find Ui apparently wearing nothing but an apron (she actually has a swimsuit underneath). She is trying to cook dinner but is hopelessly inadequate, so he helps her out. She has an accident, slipping and splashing hot water on herself, once again exposing her breasts.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682733</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169411" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会長の嫁ぎ先</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Student Council President Marries into a Family</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mariage de la présidente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitokaichou no Totsugisaki</title>
<summary>Izumi Hayato is griping after having lost the student council presidency election to Wakana Ui who ran under a platform of liberalising romance in the school, even giving away free condoms. Hayato is left as vice president. Ui later asks Hayato when he will be home that evening, believing that she only plans to call him at that time. He is shocked that she suddenly appears at his house at that time, wearing a bride`s veil, carrying all of her things, and calling him her husband, saying that their parents arranged their marriage. Hayato refuses to accept the ridiculous situation, but cannot just turn Ui out as it is much too late. After he finds Ui his bed, saying that married couples should sleep with each other, his lustful side awakens, and he begins to fondle and suck her breasts, but he is interrupted in this escalation by a sudden international call from his father, at which point Ui has fallen asleep again.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682619</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169480" update="2015-07-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169764" update="2015-07-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169859" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">副会長と保健室の悪魔2匹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vice President and the Two Infirmary Devils</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le vice-président et les deux démons de l’infirmerie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukukaichou to Hokenshitsu no Akuma 2-hiki</title>
<summary>Hayato has hardly slept from studying so he can beat Ui in the upcoming tests. They need to leave the apartment separately so that the Misumi sisters don`t realise they are living together. They see him at the entrance to their building and Kei notices how he seems a bit out of it, and so she brings him to the school clinic. Rin has told her about his supposed cross-dressing, despite Hayato`s admonitions to keep it a secret, and they believe that he is stressed from being unable to satisfy his urges to do so. He wants to correct this misunderstanding but remembers that if he does that he will expose his cohabitation with Ui. He falls asleep while the sisters dress him in girls` clothes and make him wear makeup, and Kei takes off her panties intending to put them on him, but Rin objects and she is made to do that instead. Kei however, finds Hayato rather handsome and she mounts him, intending to have sex with him as he sleeps, but Rin tries to stop her, and the commotion wakes him up, while Rin`s bare bottom is to his face.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682745</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169860" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こそこそ生徒会長</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sneaky Student Council President</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente cachottière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kosokoso Seitokaichou</title>
<summary>Misumi Kei, Rin`s elder sister, has just moved into the apartment next to Hayato`s. Rin is helping her adjust to her new neighbourhood and is going to be living there for the next few days. They have to keep Ui`s presence in his home a secret, so she has to hide every time Rin comes by to borrow some household items she needs. Distracted by Rin, he burns the fish he is cooking for dinner, and she enters his home uninvited. She discovers Ui`s panties lying on the floor, which he tries to explain away as being an aunt`s who recently visited. He tackles Ui into the toilet, where they hide while Rin uses the bathroom sink, and they rub against each other. Rin discovers Ui`s lip balm at the sink, which Hayato again tries to explain as his aunt`s, but this time Rin doesn`t believe him. He then says that the panties and the lip balm are his.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682743</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169861" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会長と身内ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Student Council President`s Family</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente et sa mère</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitokaichou to Miuchi-chan</title>
<summary>Hayato initially thought the apparent little girl might be Ui`s little sister and is thunderstruck to learn that she is actually Wakana Misato, Ui`s mother. After they go to Hayato`s home Misato has had movers bring over the last of Ui`s remaining effects, saying "a married couple needs only one house." Hayato then takes a bath, when Misato enters and talks to him. Hayato tries to get her to call off his engagement to Ui, when she reminds him of how Ui had been so close to him when they were younger. As Misato leaves she slips and lands on top of Hayato in a compromising position as Ui checks on them. He makes dinner with his "mother-in-law", both of them aware of Ui`s inadequacy in that department.
Later that night Ui gives him a massage, and this becomes a more intimate moment, as they tickle each other and kiss deeply, until Misato, who seems to have been peeking in on them, stumbles into the room.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682741</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169862" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会長と仲直りのアレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Making Up with the President</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Réconciliation avec la présidente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitokaichou to Nakanaori no Are</title>
<summary>Ui runs off after the incident with Rin, and has gone home to her parents. Hayato, despite originally wishing she would do so is troubled, and having gotten so used to Ui he makes two servings of breakfast before remembering she isn`t there.
At the Student Council the next day, Ui is visibly upset, and Ayane tries to console her. Later, the meeting comes to order, the student council has received an email from a girl whose case is very similar to Ui and Hayato. Rin, who was eavesdropping at the door, is invited to join the discussion, and there is a debate, with Karen advocating harsh measures and Hayato and Rin advocating understanding. The girl sent a second message telling the council that she had kissed and made up with her boyfriend.
After everyone else leaves, Ui and Hayato are left alone, and he tries to reconcile with her. She tells him to kiss her as a sign of their making up, and initially he gives her just a light kiss on the forehead, but this rapidly escalates into heavy, torrid kissing. They are interrupted by a little girl who seems to be a relation of Ui`s.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682739</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170535" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">会長の身内くん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">More of the President`s Family</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La famille de la présidente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaichou no Miuchi-kun</title>
<summary>While Ui and Hayato have gone out to buy ice pops she receives a telephone call from her mother, saying that she is right at their door. As usual, they go in separately, but he runs into Kei, who tells him to give her regards to his guests and that she will learn the truth from him. He sees Wakana Ryou, Ui`s father along with Misato, who like his wife looks incredibly young for 41. Ryou does not accept Hayato to be his daughter`s husband, and says that he has to prove himself, but Hayato considers that if he doesn`t prove himself than the farce will end. In the meantime, Ryou behaves abusively towards him.
They go out for a bit to buy dinner and when they head back Misato says that she explained to Kei exactly what their situation was. Ui apologises to Hayato about her father`s behaviour, and says she understands that he doesn`t feel the same way about her as she does about him, but she will wait as long as needed for him to return her feelings, and overcome by a sudden rush of feeling he calls her by her name for the first time.
Later that evening Ryou has already fallen asleep in Ui`s room, so Hayato has to sleep with Ui in his room. Ui is already asleep, and while he lies down next to her he remembers how they were as children, and apologises for how slowly he is moving. In her sleep she pushes him against her breasts and gets him to stimulate her between her legs, but suddenly she realises how it is so cold and without waking up she turns off the air conditioning.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682753</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170536" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会長16歳になる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The President Turns 16</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente fête ses 16 ans</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitokaichou 16-sai ni Naru</title>
<summary>It is Ui`s sixteenth birthday, and Hayato just suddenly hears about it from her mother, and he thinks of a gift to buy her. Just then, Sawatari visits, returning the panties she borrowed, and a gift-wrapped parcel containing a see-through nightie, saying that she heard about his cross-dressing fetish from Rin. He leaves the packages at the entrance to their apartment as he goes to do the laundry. Ui opens the package believes the nightie to be his gift for her birthday, and immediately wears it, much to Hayato`s shock, and he orders her to change out of it as it`s only lunch time, and Ui realises just how revealing the nightie really is. However she remembers her mother saying that if a man gives a woman clothes it`s so that he can take them off. Later, Hayato takes an afternoon nap, and wakes up to find Ui sleeping next to him. She then pounces on him, and they have a torrid kiss, and he ends up using his fingers to stimulate her to the point of orgasm. She later says that she was just happy to have spent the entire day with him.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682751</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170537" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">猿渡さんの真夏のプレゼン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sawatari-san`s Midsummer Presentation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`été de Sawatari</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sawatari-san no Manatsu no Presentation</title>
<summary>It is summer vacation and Hayato accompanies Ui for various meetings at school. While waiting for her, he sees Makoto carrying a huge bag full of books, clearly much too heavy for her, and watches as she falls over. He brings her to the infirmary and returns the books to the library. Thinking Makoto asleep Hayato reads aloud a somewhat intimate text message from Ui, leading Makoto to suspect him of having an illicit relationship. Afterwards, she sneaks behind him as he walks home, which irritates him, and he shouts at her, startling her enough that she urinates a little. Hayato thus brings Makoto to his home and lets her take a shower to clean herself up. She notices signs that Ui is living with him, and his excuses are unavailing, so he admits that he is living with Ui, but denies that they are in a relationship. She tries to get Hayato to consider Rin as well as a candidate, and is on the point of seducing him when Ui comes home. Makoto asks Ui what she likes about Hayato, and she gushes about him, clearly deeply in love.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682749</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170538" update="2017-03-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会長と賄賂と暴露</title>
<title xml:lang="en">President, Bribe, and Exposure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente et la divulgation des dessous de table</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitokaichou to Wairo to Bakuro</title>
<summary>Rin meets Hayato at the school rooftop and gives him a paper bag with panties inside, for his supposed cross-dressing fetish. Karen and Makoto see them, and when the former goes to the student council she tells them that Rin and Hayato seem suspiciously close, and she thinks the paper bag was something like a bribe for information or influence on the student council. Ui defends Hayato, giving him the benefit of the doubt, which upsets Karen even more as she noticed how Ui seems to be so close to him. Ui thus comforts her, embracing her and stroking her hair.
Later, as Hayato and Ui are walking home together, she tells him of how she also revealed to Karen and Ayame their relationship, though not that they were living together. Distracted, Hayato bumps into a lamppost and the bag with Rin`s panties falls out. Ui thus believes that her "husband" has a panties fetish, and that Rin tried to bribe him by giving her panties, so Ui has him go into an alley and take off her panties there. They wind up in compromising positions as they are distracted by a stray cat. When they get home Hayato considers how so many people have misconceptions about him.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682747</identifier>
<identifier>my-wife-is-the-student-council-president</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172431" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172432" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172433" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172434" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172435" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172436" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 09</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172437" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 08</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172438" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 07</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172439" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 06</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172440" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 05</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172441" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172442" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172443" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172444" update="2015-10-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Gekijou 01</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
