<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10984" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-10-10</startdate>
<enddate>2015-12-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Owari no Seraph: Nagoya Kessen Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-unk" type="synonym">Seraph of the End S2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Seraph of the End 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Owari no Seraph 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">終わりのセラフ Seraph of the end 名古屋決戦編</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Seraph of the End: Battle in Nagoya</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Seraph of the End Arc 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="official">终结的炽天使 名古屋决战篇</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10813" type="Prequel">Owari no Seraph</anime>
<anime id="11809" type="Other">Owari no Seraph (2016)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="531146">If you likedthe first season, then this one is a must! Sawano Hiroyuki`s soundtrack is outstanding. I highly recommend it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="633825">Episode 10 "Yu and Mika" is a Must See!!! This is the just about the climax of the entire series, and the episode with highest artistic value in the portrayal of mixture of both dark and bright side of human nature, and it is just touching my soul.

I shall repeat this again, Owari no Seraph is categorized in the genre of "Dark Fantasy" for a reason. It is just badassly good in portraying the ugliness of humanity, and therefore this never-ending dark world makes the love between characters so sensationally touching.

Although I do admit that it lacks quite many important explanations, but it doesn`t hinder my overall enjoyment. Besides, its original manga is still on-going, so I don`t blame the anime because not even the original manga had explained any details about the experiment of "Owari no Seraph", leaving a major cliffhanger for audience to hope for more.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://owarino-seraph.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="34645" type="Animation Work">Wit Studio</name>
<name id="522" type="Character Design">Kadowaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="37817" type="Series Composition">Seko Hiroshi</name>
<name id="17906" type="Original Work">Kagami Takaya</name>
<name id="27909" type="Manga Composition">Furuya Daisuke</name>
<name id="18269" type="Direction">Tokudo Daisuke</name>
<name id="18250" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamada Ayumi</name>
<name id="522" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kadowaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="18474" type="Music">Wada Takafumi</name>
<name id="42794" type="Music">Shiraishi Megumi</name>
<name id="34207" type="Music">Tachibana Asami</name>
<name id="6722" type="Music">Sawano Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch70947 [Yuuichirou] has reunited with http://anidb.net/ch70946 [Mikaela] at the Shinjuku Battle, but Mikaela was turned into a vampire. To save the "family," and to protect his fellow members, Yuuichirou needed to gain knowledge and power. He searched for ways to bring back vampire to human beings, and at the same time, trained hard working on the Cursed Gear. Meanwhile, http://anidb.net/ch72885 [Kureto] calls http://anidb.net/ch70945 [Guren] and tells him a shocking truth: in one month, the main unit of the vampire will start attacking Tokyo. To get a head start against vampires, Kureto orders Guren to go to Nagoya. The noble extermination mission is about to open fire.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1813">5.52</permanent>
<temporary count="1822">6.93</temporary>
<review count="2">4.91</review>
</ratings>
<picture>177225.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17482</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>28927</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>31918</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://owarino-seraph.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.funimation.com/shows/seraph-of-the-end-vampire-reign/home</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3922</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354061</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17964</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01DCO1ARM</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3167" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-16">
<name>Tokyo destroyed</name>
<description>Tokyo is depicted as being or having been destroyed, either partially or completely, by some sort of disaster, such as a nuclear blast, a very large-scale fire, or rising sea levels. Should the situation be dire enough, Tokyo may be destroyed again after a recovery, or a new Tokyo may be built and subsequently destroyed, by a new disaster.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="70945" type="main character in" update="2015-09-22">
<rating votes="47">4.85</rating>
<name>Ichinose Guren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guren is Lieutenant Colonel of the "The Moon Demon Company", Vampire Extermination Unit of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army. He has led Yuuichiro to join the Japanese Imperial Demon Army after he escaped the city of vampire. He is secretly attempting something to reform the Imperial Demon Army governed by the Hiiragi Family.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>166233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70946" type="main character in" update="2015-09-22">
<rating votes="90">5.04</rating>
<name>Hyakuya Mikaela</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikaela is the 2nd remaining survivor of the Hyakuya Orphanage, and best friend of Yuuichiro. He was thought to have died when escaping from the city of vampire, but was alive and turned into a vampire. He fights to rescue Yuuichiro who is been used by humans.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>166231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70947" type="main character in" update="2016-02-23">
<rating votes="99">4.75</rating>
<name>Hyakuya Yuuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hyakuya Yuuichirou is a boy who escaped from the vampire city. He holds intense hatred against the vampires who killed his family, and enlisted in the Japanese Imperial Demon Army for vampire extermination. He is not always a good team player, but deep inside he is kind and caring.
Source: Official Website</description>
<picture>166232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71716" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-23">
<rating votes="31">2.24</rating>
<name>Ferid Bathory</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ferid Bathory is the man who killed http://anidb.net/ch70947 [Hyakuya Yuuichirou]`s family when they tried to escape the vampire city. As a Seventh Progenitor vampire, he has much power, but he often speaks nonsense. He seems to be plotting something with the humans behind everyone`s back.
Source: Official Website</description>
<picture>166234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71717" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="160">8.03</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Shinoa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinoa is the Squad Leader of "The Moon Demon Company". Her origin is Hiiragi Family who takes control of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army, and is the real sister of Hiiragi Mahiru who developed the Cursed Gear. Is a subordinate of Lieutenant Colonel Guren, and was appointed to supervise Hyakuya Yuuichiro.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>166235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72113" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-23">
<rating votes="45">3.77</rating>
<name>Sanguu Mitsuba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mitusuba is an elite who belongs to the Vampire Extermination Unit since 13 years old. Has known Shinoa for a long time. She thinks that she let a member die because of her selfishness, and since then focuses on teamwork during battle.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>213464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72114" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-23">
<rating votes="28">3.06</rating>
<name>Kimizuki Shihou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kimizuki Shihou is http://anidb.net/ch70947 [Hyakuya Yuuichirou]`s brother-in-arms in the Moon Demon Company. He is clear-headed and has excellent combat ability, but is cynical and gets treated as a troublemaker. He has a http://anidb.net/ch76397 [bedridden sister], and enlisted in the army in order to allow her to undergo the treatment.
Source: Official Website</description>
<picture>170800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72115" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="28">2.47</rating>
<name>Saotome Yoichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoichi is a member of the "The Moon Demon Company" fighting vampires with Yuuichiro. His sister has been killed by a vampire, and joined the troop for revenge. Although he is kind-hearted, he has a strong will and stand up against difficulty at times of emergency.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>171131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72885" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="16">2.22</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Kureto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kureto is a Lieutenant General of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army. He is very ruthless as Shinoa calls him a ``monster``, and is willing to retaliate anyone who is against the Hiiragi Family. His ambition is to exterminate vampires from Japan, and have the world under the control of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>171398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72886" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="22">5.77</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Shin`ya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shinya is a Major General of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army. He was chosen to marry Shinoa`s older sister Mahiru and was adopted by the Hiiragi Family. Although he has high capacity of spellcraft from childhood, is not comfortable about the Hiiragi Family, and is good friends with Guren holding the same intention.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>171400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73466" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="89">7.48</rating>
<name>Krul Tepes</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Krul is a queen who rules Sanguinem, the city of vampire. She is the Third Progenitor and holds extraordinary power. 4 years ago, she gave her own blood to Mikaela who was terribly injured from a fight with Ferid, and resurrected him as a vampire.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>171397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73467" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="38">5.58</rating>
<name>Crowley Eusford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Crowley is a noble of the Thirteenth Progenitor and belongs to the faction led by Ferid Bathory. He participated in the battle for Shinjuku, and at the battle with Shinoa`s squad, showed his overpowering ability which even beat down Yuuichirou with the Black Demon gear!!
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>171782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73836" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="18">4.83</rating>
<name>Goshi Norito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Norito is a Colonel of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army, and serves as a member of a team led by Guren. He excels in illusion than physical attacks, and covers Guren who mainly fights in close combat. He is sensual and loves beautiful women.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>172898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73837" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="17">5.76</rating>
<name>Juujou Mito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mito is the daughter of the prestigious Juujou family and a member of Guren`s Moon Demon Company squad. She is a Colonel with a characteristic crimson-red hair. Mito excels in spellcast techniques transmitted from generation to generation in the Juujou family, which enhances her physical ability in the combat.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>172899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3198" picture="160468.jpg">Shimamura Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73838" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="23">5.35</rating>
<name>Hanayori Sayuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sayuri is a servant for the Ichinoses, and is Second Lieutenant of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army. Since young, she had a crush on Guren and is his emotional support. While serving as a member of The Moon Demon Company, she is also an Army instructor for the training classes.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>170558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73839" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="19">5.31</rating>
<name>Yukimi Shigure</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shigure is a Second Lieutenant of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army, and like Sayuri, she is a servant for the Ichinose Family. Her personality is calm and tends to hide her emotions. She is keeping her feelings for Guren to herself. Shigure has incredible battle skills and uses weapons such as hidden weapons with dexterity.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>170559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="443" picture="145927.jpg">Ishikawa Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74001" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-17">
<rating votes="11">2.97</rating>
<name>Lacus Welt</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lacus is a vampire assuming the mission of city guard like Mikaela. He is the one that killed Yoichi`s sister. He is not a noble but has high combat capability. He can`t hide his desire for blood, and sometimes won`t stop drinking blood until the human is dead.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>172522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41905" picture="172030.jpg">Nagatsuka Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74002" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-17">
<rating votes="8">3.56</rating>
<name>Rene Simm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>René is the colleague of Mikaela and Lacus, and has extremely high combat ability. Unlike other vampires who tend to underestimate humans, he thinks they are a "greedy arrogant creature", and consider the fanatical state of Imperial Demon Army`s soldiers very dangerous.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>172523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74003" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-21">
<rating votes="32">6.84</rating>
<name>Ashuramaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A demon that dwells on the Black Demon gear owned by Yuichiro Hyakuya. Dislikes love, favors desire, and only thinks about dominating the body of Yuichiro. However, sometimes gets bewildered when seeing the gentle side of Yuichiro.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>172524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17149" picture="174125.jpg">Yamamura Hibiku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74739" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="18">6.76</rating>
<name>Chess Belle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chess is a Seventeenth Progenitor vampire who serves Crowley. Even though she is a noble, her personality is freewheeling, and behavior is very careless. She often can`t control her desire while drinking blood and end up killing human.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>173397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32911" picture="230127.jpg">Furuki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74740" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="15">7.28</rating>
<name>Horn Skuld</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Horn is a Seventeenth Progenitor, same level as Chess. She is serving Crowley from a certain reason. She takes her duties seriously and scolds Chess for her misbehavior like a big sister. She prefers Crowley`s blood more than anything else.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>173398.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74916" type="appears in" update="2015-05-03">
<rating votes="6">2.55</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Seishirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Seishirou is a member of the Hiiragi Family, and a person of influence as a Major General of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army. He is rude and has an offensive personality. Has a strong complex against his older brother Kureto, and secretly planning to outwit his brother one day.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>172900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76397" type="appears in" update="2015-07-17">
<rating votes="6">2.84</rating>
<name>Kimizuki Mirai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175510.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77488" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="6">7.98</rating>
<name>Inoue Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rika has a free-spirited personality as can be seen from her gal-ish tone or how she wears her uniform. She takes initiative to be a mood maker such as exchanging high-five with others, and is contributing to improve the linkage of the squad.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>177647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16763" picture="45795.jpg">Ishihara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77489" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="6">3.10</rating>
<name>Endou Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yayoi is a kind-hearted peace keeper of the belligerent Narumi squad. In contrary to her quiet looks, she is brave and has a firm attitude to confront a vampire.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>177650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77490" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="4">3.98</rating>
<name>Iwasaki Shuusaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shuusaku is quiet and is a members of the Narumi squad. His Cursed Gear is "Akahebi", and using that power, he plays the central role for the squad in battles. Furthermore, he is a strong player with both wisdom and courage, supporting the leader Narumi in terms of tactics.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>177652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77491" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="12">4.04</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Mahiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mahiru is a beautiful and intelligent genius that has completed the current Cursed Gear, and saved the world. She is the big sister of Hiiragi Shinoa and ex-girlfriend of Guren. She used to have power to be the next successor of the Hiiragi house like Kureto.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>177653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77492" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="4">4.58</rating>
<name>Kagiyama Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tarou is a member of the Narumi squad with a snappy towel wrapped around his head. He has a very strong sense of justice, and is a sober man taking lead in combats with his iron arms.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>177651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="177" picture="170981.jpg">Hoshino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77493" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-17">
<rating votes="7">4.62</rating>
<name>Narumi Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makoto is intrepid, thoughtful of his mates and squad leader of the Narumi squad. He takes the lead by utilizing the trident spear in combat, and also exert leadership to mentally support his squad members from the heart. Makoto has great prestige among the squad.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>177648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77494" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-17">
<rating votes="6">4.67</rating>
<name>Sanguu Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoi is the older sister of Mitsuba, the beauty of Sangu Family who serves the Hiragi Family. She combines the ability as to be chosen as Kureto`s servant, and dedication to sacrifice herself for him. On the other hand, she gives a cold attitude against Mitsuba who became a subordinate of Guren.
Source: Official Page</description>
<picture>177645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77613" type="appears in" update="2015-09-27">
<name>Gekki no Kumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Moon Demon Company is an elite military group that is famous within the Vampire Extermination Unit (吸血鬼殲滅部隊, Kyuuketsuki Senmetsu Butai) of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army (日本帝鬼軍, Nihon Teiki Gun).</description>
</character>
<character id="77614" type="appears in" update="2015-09-27">
<name>Guren no Bun Taichou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="77834" type="appears in" update="2016-02-23">
<rating votes="3">2.85</rating>
<name>Kiseki Ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiseki Ou is a demon of the Black Demon Series owned by http://anidb.net/ch72114 [Kimizuki Shihou]. His appearance is like a juvenile, but talks like an old man. He has a distinctive white tail on his behind, and is an expert of the double sword.
Source: Official Website</description>
<picture>178584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79519" type="appears in" update="2016-01-21">
<name>Narumi no Bun Taichou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="79520" type="appears in" update="2016-01-21">
<rating votes="5">4.11</rating>
<name>Aihara Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79521" type="appears in" update="2016-01-21">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kusunoki Eita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37882" picture="173035.jpg">Yamashita Seiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79522" type="appears in" update="2016-01-21">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Esther Lee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79523" type="appears in" update="2016-01-21">
<rating votes="2">1.83</rating>
<name>Lucal Wesker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79524" type="appears in" update="2016-01-21">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Lest Ka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a Third Progenitor just like http://anidb.net/ch73466 [Krul], who he is currently in a power struggle with. He has destroyed the human organizations in Europe that was researching on the Seraph of the End. He has through extraordinary ability subdued vampire nobles and has his own faction.
translated from http://owarino-seraph.com by Iggdrassil</description>
<picture>181605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="172281" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月鬼のゴウレイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moon Demon`s Orders</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ordre de Gekki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekki no Gourei</title>
<summary>When the Shinoa squad arrives late, they realize just how serious this mission is for Guren. Knowing this is an impossible mission where many will die, Guren puts his emotions aside and orders his men to not necessarily survive, but to win.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="172282" update="2015-11-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帝鬼軍のヤボウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ambition in the Demon Army</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les ambitions de l`armée impériale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teikigun no Yabou</title>
<summary>Shinoa calls her squad for a breakfast meeting, intending to cook a meal for them, but her attempts at cooking with Mitsuba`s help are disastrous, and it is Shihou who manages to cook a fine breakfast. They meet to try to determine whether Guren is really on their side or not, since it seems he is not only manipulating Yuuichirou but the entire squad for his own purposes. Yuuichirou is told of what had happened during the battle for the first time, how he had gone berserk and nearly killed Shinoa. He decides that he wants to continue to stick with Guren as he told them all that they were family and that he promised him that he would find a way to save Mikaela.
Meanwhile, Guren and Hiiragi Kureto meet, and the two men have a discussion about the future plans. Kureto tells him that he plans to restore the world, after destroying all the vampires in Japan he will subjugate all the other human organisations remaining and place the entire world under his command. He orders Guren to bring a hundred of his Moon Demon Company to Nagoya, and defeat the ten vampire nobles who have established a base there.
In the vampire world Mikaela`s craving for blood grows so intense that he takes blood directly from Krul`s neck. She warns him that soon enough her blood alone will not be enough to satisfy him. He questions her motives in letting him and Yuuichiro live, and she whispers to him the reason why she needs the Seraph of the End. She orders him to take Yuuichiro and save him from both the human and vampire forces during the war that commences in a month`s time.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="172283" update="2015-11-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">交錯するカンケイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Complicated Connections</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Relations croisées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kousaku Suru Kankei</title>
<summary>Hiiragi brings her squad to an isolated area to train Yuuichirou and Shihou to manifest their demons. A group of Horsemen approach them and Yoichi manages to make his demon weapon manifest and destroys them, as he managed to figure out how to do so on his own.
Yuuichirou performs the process first, and is restrained by the others as he allows his weapon to take his blood. He enters a trance as he comes into contact with his demon Ashuramaru. He is made to remember how his parents tried to kill him, calling him a dangerous demon known as the "Seraph of the End", and how he had caused the deaths of everyone because he tried to run. His resolve proves stronger than this and he manages to overcome Ashuramaru.
It is then Shihou`s turn and in the same way he made to confront his own demon, Kiseki-ou. He is made to remember how he had prevented a group of children he had been with from killing her because he refused to do so himself, and how afterwards he had been tempted to abandon her, but he also proves stronger than this and gets Kiseki-ou to submit.
Meanwhile, in the vampire world Krul Tepes is in a meeting with the vampire high council. Ferid enters with Mikaela behind him, and he shows them how the humans have somehow made the Seraph of the End into a weapon, though Krul had supposedly destroyed all of the experimental subjects with the Hyakuya sect. This causes many questions to be raised about her handling of the situation. Ferid blackmails her in this way, reminding her that if she acts against him, the fact that she is keeping Mikaela around and that he has permitted Yuuichirou to escape will come to light.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="172284" update="2015-10-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間のセカイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Human World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde des hommes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningen no Sekai</title>
<summary>Shinoa and Guren have a brief confrontation over how he seems to be using Yuuichirou, and how Guren seems to be manipulating him for his own mysterious ends. He does not deny it, but denies that he is doing so because his demon weapon is manipulating him into it. She sees Yuuichirou who has somewhat recovered from his ordeal and is researching ways to turn a vampire back into a human for Mikaela`s sake.
He is called by the Hiiragis, the commanders of the demon army, and is warned by Mitsuba who was interviewed ahead of them of how ruthless and paranoid they are. He is also met by Guren who admonishes him to remember where his loyalties lie. He is tested by Hiiragi Kureto for his loyalty, and is interrogated, with Shihou and Yoichi being tortured in an adjoining room to ensure his honesty. Kureto tells him about the significance of his family name, Hyakuya, which was the name of the orphanage where he lived, and how it was before the vampire war the name of a group of powerful magicians who conducted human experiments on the children in their orphanages, so it is highly probable that Yuuichiro and Mikaela were the subject of such human experiments.
After the interrogation Yuuichiro confronts Guren about Kureto`s revelations, and he does not deny it. Yuuichiro is not resentful, as whatever the reasons Guren had, if he had not saved him, he would be dead anyway.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="172624" update="2015-10-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172625" update="2015-10-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172863" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼のコモリウタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Demon`s Lullaby</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Berceuse pour un démon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oni no Komoriuta</title>
<summary>Shinoa`s squad goes to save Guren, but unfortunately, they run out of time. Reluctantly, they leave him behind and retreat, but Yu just cannot bring himself to do that. Instead, he takes more of the Curse Stimulant Pills to go save Guren himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="172864" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">深夜とグレン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shinya and Guren</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Glenn et Shinya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin`ya to Guren</title>
<summary>Guren, Shinoa, and Narumi squads arrive at the city hall and see the hostages. Knowing it`s a set-up, they still decide to go save the hostages, but Guren and Shinya are way over their heads with Crowley, as they struggle just to run away from him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="172865" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正義のツルギ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sword of Justice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La lame de la justice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seigi no Tsurugi</title>
<summary>The Shinoa squad re-learns the hard cold fact that it`s very possible to lose comrades, but there`s no time to mourn. They must move on to go rescue the hostages. Right after their departure, Mika and the other vampires arrive to Nagoya as well.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="172866" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">反逆するカチク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Livestock Revolt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La révolte du bétail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hangyaku Suru Kachiku</title>
<summary>The Shinoa squad and Narumi squad join forces to carry out their mission - to kill the Fifteenth Progenitor, Lucal Wesker. While they succeed in their mission without losing anybody, others were not so lucky. Nine teams fail and were taken as hostages...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="173195" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりのセラフ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seraph of the End</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Séraphin de la fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owari no Seraph</title>
<summary>Kureto`s trump card was Mirai, Kimizuki`s younger sister and another Seraph of the End test subject. In order to stop the Japanese Imperial Demon Army, Yu has no choice but to reach out to his inner "trumpet" to tap into the angel`s powers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="173196" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傲慢なアイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arrogant Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un amour arrogant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouman na Ai</title>
<summary>The survivors of the Moon Demon Company get to the rendezvous point, only to find out that their orders are to "standby." Enraged, they decide to ignore the orders to save Guren, when Kureto appears. Apparently, Kureto has something else on the agenda.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="173197" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">優とミカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yu and Mika</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yû et Mika</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuu to Mika</title>
<summary>Yu and Mika are finally reunited, but the injuries Mika had sustained from fighting the Demon Company threatens his life. Determined to keep Mika alive, Yu tries to persuade Mika into drinking his blood... Even if it means Mika will become a true vampire.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="173198" update="2018-03-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切りのミカタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Traitorous Allies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un allié traître</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri no Mikata</title>
<summary>Thanks to his "experimentation," Yu makes a miraculous recovery and once again, goes back to save Guren. Pushing too hard, Yu nearly becomes a demon, but Kimizuki stops him by force. The squad carries Yu out and heads for safety, but then encounters Mika.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175827" update="2016-02-28">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わらないセラフ名古屋編 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seraph of the Endless Nagoya arc 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owaranai Seraph Nagoya Hen 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175828" update="2016-02-28">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わらないセラフ名古屋編 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seraph of the Endless Nagoya arc 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owaranai Seraph Nagoya Hen 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175829" update="2016-02-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わらないセラフ名古屋編 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seraph of the Endless Nagoya arc 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owaranai Seraph Nagoya Hen 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178207" update="2016-06-23">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わらないセラフ名古屋編 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seraph of the Endless Nagoya arc 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owaranai Seraph Nagoya Hen 4</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
