<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="110" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-05-25</startdate>
<enddate>2002-05-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nakoruru: Ano Hito kara no Okurimono</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">nakoruru</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ナコルル ~あのひとからのおくりもの~</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="960" type="Character">Samurai Spirits 2: Asura Zanmaden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="771" type="Work">Arms</name>
<name id="1505" type="Direction">Kanazawa Katsuma</name>
<name id="1953" type="Character Design">Umetsu Yasuomi</name>
<name id="31281" type="Music">Yamate Yasuo</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Nakoruru: Ano Hito kara no Okurimono ADV game, using Nakoruru as the main heroine. http://anidb.net/ch14132 [Nakoruru] is a popular Ainu girl from SNK`s Samurai Spirits fighting game and considered one of the most recognised characters and "mascot" of the series.
Nakoruru, finally returned to her home Kamuikotan after a long, fierce battle, receives a warm welcome from dear friends and the village children. Her spirit is uplifted by her reunion with companions Manari and Yantamuu. But as the trauma of battle falls away, Rela appears and challenges Nakoruru and the shadow of misfortune creeps closer...
Note: Originally intended to be a full 13 episode OVA series, this was cut down to 2 episodes due to limited funding. After the 1st episode was released however, the production of 2nd episode was cancelled, leaving this with only one episode.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="186">3.02</permanent>
<temporary count="186">5.46</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>222120.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2147</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1937</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>944</identifier>
<identifier>xfmmfy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nakoruru:_Ano_Hito_kara_no_Okurimono</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>サムライスピリッツ#ナコルル_〜あのひとからのおくりもの〜_郷里之畏友編</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>238777</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5553</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4349</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8108</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4033" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2018-07-29">
<name>discontinued</name>
<description>This anime plot was supposed to run on more episodes, but it was prematurely discontinued before reaching the end.
Generally, we can only reasonably observe that a show is discontinued after the fact. As such, this tag should not be added to an anime until at least 5 years have passed since the anime airing has ended.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6004" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>development hell</name>
<description>Due to unforeseen circumstances, the production or release of this anime has been pushed back, stalled, or cancelled one or more times from when it was first announced.
While some of them have eventually been completed, others might have only had a trailer released or have been changed into another format (e.g. a TV series turned into an OVA).
Common reasons for a work to become stuck in development hell include creative differences, legal issues, financial problems, scheduling conflicts or the death of an involved creator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="14132" type="main character in" update="2010-01-15">
<rating votes="9">7.96</rating>
<name>Nakoruru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakoruru is a popular Ainu girl from SNK`s Samurai Spirits fighting game and considered one of the most recognised characters and "mascot" of the series.</description>
<picture>41532.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12358" picture="41533.jpg">Ikoma Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14133" type="main character in" update="2011-04-11">
<rating votes="2">5.70</rating>
<name>Rimururu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rimururu is a recurring character in the Samurai Spirits series. She made her first appearance in the series as a background character in Nakoruru`s stage during Samurai Spirits II. Her prototype design in this game was formerly a scrapped concept for one of the heroines from another SNK game, Robo Army.
She is the younger sister of Nakoruru, and lives in an Ainu village on Hokkaido. She greatly admires her older sister, and like her, strives to protect nature. Rimururu has also been referred to as a priestess of the Ainu religion. In her ending to Samurai Spirits V, it is revealed to players that Nakoruru adopts her at a young age. Although she is still training and not as adept as her sister at fighting, she repels evil from the forest for her elder sister. When her sister departs, Rimururu often follows her in hopes of offering assistance. Nakoruru originally forbids her younger sister`s attempts to be a priestess but relents once she recognizes Rimururu`s resolve.</description>
<picture>41536.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12361" picture="41537.jpg">Kamitani Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14134" type="main character in" update="2010-01-15">
<rating votes="2">5.89</rating>
<name>Manari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An exclusive character for the Nakoruru ADV game and the OVA based on it.
Childhood friend of Nakoruru.</description>
<picture>41538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14135" type="main character in" update="2010-01-15">
<rating votes="1">3.48</rating>
<name>Yantamuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An exclusive character for the Nakoruru ADV game and the OVA based on it.
Childhood friend of Nakoruru.</description>
<picture>41539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14136" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-15">
<rating votes="2">7.08</rating>
<name>Rera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alter ego of Nakoruru. It is said that Nakoruru suppressed this side of herself as Rera saw killing as a necessity to protect nature.</description>
<picture>41540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="206" picture="228617.jpg">Hikami Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14137" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-15">
<name>Mikato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14138" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-15">
<name>Hokute</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12363" picture="41545.jpg">Morita Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2838" update="2011-07-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2002-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121111" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212692" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Chapter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Hen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
