<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11009" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-04-19</startdate>
<enddate>2015-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Grisaia no Rakuen</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">グリザイアの楽園</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Eden of Grisaia</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">그리자이아의 낙원</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">Het Paradijs van Grisaia</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">灰色的乐园</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13273" type="Sequel">Grisaia: Phantom Trigger - The Animation</anime>
<anime id="11008" type="Prequel">Grisaia no Meikyuu: Caprice no Mayu 0</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="503983">For those who liked the first season, this is a must see. While the first season focused on the five girls, this one focuses on the main character. More reasons to watch, if you liked the main character!

Animation is good. Sound is ok. Plot is interesting enough.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="672527">Quite a bit different from from S1, and in my opinion better. The story isn`t overly complicated and manages in this way to remain coherent and not irritate you like so many harem shows do. There is a lot more action here, and all of it is very well executed. There is some humor too, but inserted just at the right moments. I feel there isn`t anything to dislike ( except for some perhaps the fact it is a harem) so definitely recommend it. don`t forget to watch Grisaia no Meikyuu first!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.grisaia-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="42849" type="Music">Kita Tomohiro</name>
<name id="38777" type="Music">Iwahashi Seima</name>
<name id="21883" type="Animation Work">8bit</name>
<name id="3529" type="Character Design">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="17991" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kumagai Yuuya</name>
<name id="10609" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takasawa Mika</name>
<name id="1553" type="Chief Animation Direction">Satou Tenshou</name>
<name id="14796" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nonaka Masayuki</name>
<name id="27020" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ooshima Midori</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="1368" type="Original Work">Front Wing</name>
<name id="36345" type="Direction">Tenshou</name>
<name id="14866" type="Chief Animation Direction">Echigo Mitsutaka</name>
<name id="2966" type="Chief Animation Direction">Katsura Ken`ichirou</name>
<name id="3529" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watanabe Akio</name>
<name id="8149" type="Music">Fujima Hitoshi</name>
<name id="4672" type="Music">Fujita Junpei</name>
<name id="3894" type="Music">Elements Garden</name>
<name id="39019" type="Music">Mori Haruki</name>
<name id="3892" type="Music">Kikuta Daisuke</name>
</creators>
<description>As http://anidb.net/ch69013 [Yuuji] finds himself detained for suspected involvement with an international terrorist organization, the remaining students at Mihama Academy find themselves with time running out, as the school is set to close within the month due to financial issues. Over the past year, though, the Mihama girls have finally begun to find their own legs, thanks to his involvement. Faced with the end of their time at Mihama Academy and the separation from the man who changed their lives, http://anidb.net/ch69009 [Amane], http://anidb.net/ch69008 [Makina], http://anidb.net/ch69010 [Sachi], http://anidb.net/ch69012 [Yumiko], and http://anidb.net/ch69011 [Michiru] find themselves with their backs against the wall, having to pick a fight with countries and organizations far bigger than any individual could hope to be.
Source: VNDB</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1571">6.81</permanent>
<temporary count="1583">7.37</temporary>
<review count="2">7.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221811.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16673</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>29095</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>31368</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.grisaia-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Fruit_of_Grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>グリザイアの果実</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3686</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352215</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18015</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7724</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2635" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>jungle</name>
<description>This show features jungle(s) as one of its settings.
This can either involve jungle adventures or shady business revolving around deforesting of jungles or forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2671" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>school dormitory</name>
<description>A school dormitory or residence hall is the student living quarters at an elite academy, boarding school, or military school. The main characters may live or work at the dormitory, and it often becomes the backdrop for a reoccurring part of the story.</description>
<picurl>223167.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2787" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-28">
<name>teacher x student</name>
<description>Suggests a relationship involving a teacher and their student, often times sexual in nature.</description>
<picurl>206646.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2964" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>OP variety</name>
<description>Several OP sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique OP for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3037" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Skytree</name>
<description>Tokyo Skytree is a broadcasting, restaurant, and observation tower in Sumida, Tokyo, Japan. It became the tallest structure in Japan in 2010 and reached its full height of 634.0 metres in March 2011, making it the tallest tower in the world, displacing the Canton Tower, and the second tallest structure in the world after Burj Khalifa (829.8 m).
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much older http://anidb.net/t3667 [Tokyo Tower].</description>
<picurl>161122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3489" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>car chases</name>
<description>Car chases occur as part of the action setting in this anime.</description>
<picurl>211263.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3932" parentid="6073" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-11">
<name>older female younger male</name>
<description>This tag indicates that this anime has a male and female lead, and the female is older. If the main cast is greater than two people, then the use of this tag would indicate a romantic relationship between those two.
In case of harems it translates to:
a) majority of the girls are older than the guy
b) the lead girl (or her main rival) is older than the guy</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4646" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-31">
<name>hospital</name>
<description>The place or building where sick people receive medical treatment in the hopes of curing their sickness. Also a dandy setting for creepy happenings in anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7808" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-19">
<rating votes="15">5.87</rating>
<name>Jinno Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced in the second series, Hikari is visiting her brother, and witnesses the defeat of the original Jibril. Partially due to being exposed to the secret of Jibril, and partially since she was the only person available to replace Rika, she ends up recruited as the second Jibril, with the suffix of Aries, in order to rescue Rika from the clutches of Misty May and Rococo.</description>
<picture>2951.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="39199" picture="242466.jpg">Kouno Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69008" type="main character in" update="2014-11-03">
<rating votes="61">5.66</rating>
<name>Irisu Makina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>1st grader of Mihama academy, an innocent and carefree girl. For some unexplainable reasons, it`s hard to understand her personality. In general, she can be explained in one word, "Fool", but sometime her speeches and behaviors make people shed cold sweat. For that uniqueness, most of people who talk with her for 5 minutes will say "This girl is awful". She adores Yuuji as a brother and Amane as a sister. She calls Yuuji "Onii-chan". Although she has her own room in the dormitory, she always stays in Amane`s room. She always wears knee-socks with 2 different colors. Because of her parents work, she stayed in foreign countries until she was 6 so she can talk English. Her family is rumored to be a large financial clique which controls the underworld of Japan, but rarely people know the unhappiness which she suffered for born in such a troublesome family. She used to be the successor of Irisu family but her inheritance right was transferred to her younger sister, Irisu Sarina, after she suffered a mental shock in an accident. Despite all of that, she still has 70 millions yen as her own property.
Her representative fruit is apple.
Source: VNDB</description>
<picture>158862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30184" picture="79564.jpg">Tamiyasu Tomoe</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69009" type="main character in" update="2014-11-03">
<rating votes="100">8.03</rating>
<name>Suou Amane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>3rd grade of Mihama academy, the Onee-san type who always takes care of others. For some circumstances, she skipped one school year at her previous school, so she is actually 2 years older than Yuuji. She is tall and has good body style. Her family manages a long-established restaurant in Ginza, so she is good at cooking. Because her mother comes from Kyoto, when getting excited or panic, she sometimes talks in Kansai dialect. She has a deep interest in car and has acquired automatic two-wheeled vehicle license. She has a dirt bike which was remodeled to a cruiser called "Boba Tarou" (ボバ太郎) and is put in the garage of the academy.
Her representative fruit is cherry.
Source: VNDB</description>
<picture>158867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="638" picture="151683.jpg">Taguchi Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69010" type="main character in" update="2014-11-03">
<rating votes="55">6.34</rating>
<name>Komine Sachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>1st grader of Mihama academy, the maid of Mihama academy. Except when going to school, taking a bath or swimming, she always wears maid uniform. She said that everyone told her to wear maid uniform as much as possible. Polite and has strong sense of responsibility, she never fail to accomplish any request from others. In her action dictionary, there are only 3 words "receive" - "confirm" - "execute". Because of that reason, sometimes she takes a joke too serious and causes a lot of trouble. Her favorite animal is shark. The shark-shaped pouch which Michiru carries around is made by her.
Her representative fruit is strawberry.
Source: VNDB</description>
<picture>158864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="550" picture="151677.jpg">Shimizu Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69011" type="main character in" update="2014-11-03">
<rating votes="78">7.86</rating>
<name>Matsushima Michiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>2nd grader of Mihama academy, a fake tsundere with bleached blond twin tail. she has a deep interest in tsundere character and tries to act like one. Her silly and energetic personality makes her becomes the mood maker of the class. Her study is bad. She always carries with her a shark-shaped pouch which contains lemonade sweets. Despite having difficulty with sour foods, she still try to drink 100% pure Vitamin C in order to "improve her intelligence", as she said. She has encountered many bad lucks since her birth but always manages to get through them in one way or another.
Her representative fruit is the lemon.
Source: VNDB</description>
<picture>158865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69012" type="main character in" update="2014-11-03">
<rating votes="84">7.74</rating>
<name>Sakaki Yumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>2nd grader of Mihama academy, the daughter of "East Beach Railway Express Group" tycoon. After Mihama academy had been established, she was the first student to enroll. Her characteristic is a waist-length black hair. Because of her bluntness and hard-to-please personality, her association with strangers is bad. Always trying to be alone, she hardly meets with the others. She always carries a box cutter with her and use it to threaten others when she`s getting angry. She reads so many books that she`s called a "Bookworm", especially, mystery novel is her favourite. Although she`s such a lady, she changes completely in meal time, junk foods like a cup of fried soba noodles is her favourite dish.
Her representative fruit is grape.
Source: VNDB</description>
<picture>158866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1617" picture="19642.jpg">Tanaka Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69013" type="main character in" update="2014-07-30">
<rating votes="78">7.99</rating>
<name>Kazami Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist of Grisaia. Ace number 9029, Yuuji is the "janitor" for the underworld. Tired of the life, he wanted to live a normal school life. Cool, philosophical, and minimalist, Yuuji is a realist...but also tsundere. Being very cautious, he always plans and scouts before action. Other than his occasional orthodontic military methods, he`s just a fit young man. I do question his choice of disguising as an "exchange student from Canada".
Source: VNDB</description>
<picture>158863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69769" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-16">
<rating votes="35">7.71</rating>
<name>Harudera Yuria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2059" picture="210699.jpg">Narumi Erika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69770" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-31">
<rating votes="19">3.93</rating>
<name>Tachibana Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="640" picture="18167.jpg">Yanase Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70496" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="119">8.65</rating>
<name>Kazami Kazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazami Kazuki is Yuuji`s sister. She was a 1st grader of Takizono private academy and a member of basketball club.</description>
<picture>172616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2011" picture="233461.jpg">Tomonaga Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70655" type="appears in" update="2014-10-13">
<rating votes="12">5.11</rating>
<name>Chiara Farrell</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiara Farrell is a staff of the information division of the "Company", JB`s assistant and junior.</description>
<picture>162696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43310">Tsukigase Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70818" type="main character in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="45">7.41</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Asako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kusakabe Asako is the woman whom Yuuji calls "Master". She took charge of raising Yuuji when his parents passed away.</description>
<picture>172615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13796" picture="172018.jpg">Mizusawa Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71431" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-20">
<rating votes="14">5.40</rating>
<name>Kazami Yuuji (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Kazami.</description>
<picture>164372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34407" picture="202909.jpg">Suwa Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71869" type="appears in" update="2014-12-04">
<rating votes="4">1.89</rating>
<name>Ootsuka Honbuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>JB and Chiara`s boss, the general manager of the "Company".</description>
<picture>165488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10772" picture="38752.jpg">Shirakawa Shuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72432" type="appears in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="6">3.90</rating>
<name>Sakashita Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakashita Chiaki is a 3rd year middle school student at Takizono Private Academy and the captain of the Academy`s basketball club.</description>
<picture>166794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41605" picture="165763.jpg">Funasaka Yasuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72433" type="appears in" update="2014-12-30">
<rating votes="9">3.54</rating>
<name>Koide Ritsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Koide Ritsu a 2nd grader of Takizono private academy and a member of the basketball club.</description>
<picture>166797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46683" picture="190229.jpg">Kobayashi Mii</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72434" type="appears in" update="2014-12-30">
<rating votes="4">1.21</rating>
<name>Ochi Yoshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ochi Yoshihiko is a young male teacher who served as the adviser of Takizono academy basketball club and the driver of the bus.</description>
<picture>166792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41127" picture="163189.jpg">Mitoma Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72435" type="appears in" update="2014-12-30">
<rating votes="7">3.87</rating>
<name>Ibuki Haruna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ibuki Haruna is a 1st grader of Takizono private academy and a member of basketball club.</description>
<picture>166817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43310">Tsukigase Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72436" type="appears in" update="2014-12-30">
<rating votes="6">4.33</rating>
<name>Sakuma Minori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakuma Minori is a 3rd grader of Takizono private academy and a member of basketball club.</description>
<picture>166816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38415" picture="141692.jpg">Kaneko Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72439" type="appears in" update="2014-12-30">
<rating votes="10">3.77</rating>
<name>Kaneda Saaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaneda Saaya is a 2nd grader of Takizono private academy and a member of basketball club.</description>
<picture>166813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41304" picture="163825.jpg">Asakura Yuzuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72445" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-26">
<rating votes="12">2.54</rating>
<name>Heath Oslo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the man responsible for forcing Yuuji into the assassin life and also the man responsible for Asako`s injury the led to her eventual death.</description>
<picture>172614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74773" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="8">3.28</rating>
<name>Agnes Garrett</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46683" picture="190229.jpg">Kobayashi Mii</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74775" type="appears in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="4">2.66</rating>
<name>Justin MikeMyer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33519" picture="239509.jpg">Kobayashi Naoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74776" type="appears in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="4">2.66</rating>
<name>Daniel Bone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43043" picture="172268.jpg">Fujii Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74777" type="appears in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="5">3.75</rating>
<name>Robert Wolson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41127" picture="163189.jpg">Mitoma Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74778" type="appears in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="7">6.27</rating>
<name>Milliera Stanfield</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43100" picture="172637.jpg">Hirayama Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74779" type="appears in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Edward Walker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75525" type="appears in" update="2015-06-01">
<name>Du Pont</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32515" picture="196887.jpg">Sudou Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75526" type="appears in" update="2015-06-01">
<rating votes="2">3.04</rating>
<name>Travis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174062.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43286" picture="174135.jpg">Miyashita Hiromitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75527" type="appears in" update="2015-06-01">
<name>Yamamoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man who prepared Makina`s rifle.</description>
<picture>174063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12671" picture="74490.jpg">Fujinuma Kento</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75810" type="appears in" update="2015-06-08">
<name>Shimohehei-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43310">Tsukigase Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75946" type="appears in" update="2015-06-15">
<rating votes="3">6.28</rating>
<name>Neko Maid Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43244" picture="156343.jpg">Kitano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75947" type="appears in" update="2015-06-15">
<name>Adam Black</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33519" picture="239509.jpg">Kobayashi Naoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75948" type="appears in" update="2015-06-15">
<rating votes="2">4.01</rating>
<name>Zoey Graham</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43244" picture="156343.jpg">Kitano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92343" type="appears in" update="2017-11-18">
<name>Shiritsu Mihama Gakuen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="167862" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カプリスの繭 I</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cocoon of Caprice I</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cocon du caprice 1</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">카프리스의 고치 I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Caprice no Mayu I</title>
<summary>Asako Kusakabe rescues a young Yuuji from terrorists on a certain mission. She has evaded death as a soldier time and time again, and on a whim decides to become Yuuji`s guardian. Although she partially forces it, and despite her coworker JB`s concerns, the awkward female soldier and young man begin to live under the same roof.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678061</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167877" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カプリスの繭 IV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cocoon of Caprice IV</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cocon du caprice 4</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">카프리스의 고치 IV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Caprice no Mayu IV</title>
<summary>Yuuji moves forward on his path as a soldier to protect "an important woman": Asako. However, she leaves his side without waiting until he`s reached maturity. Yuuji is yet again tormented by a sense of helplessness, but is saved by Asako`s parting words and begins to be able to walk on his own two feet once more.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678067</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167878" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カプリスの繭 III</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cocoon of Caprice III</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cocon du caprice 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">카프리스의 고치 III</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Caprice no Mayu III</title>
<summary>Yuuji goes to America to follow the same path as Asako, and through his rigorous military life meets and forms a deep bond with war buddies who go through the same joys and sorrows.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678065</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167879" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カプリスの繭 II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cocoon of Caprice II</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cocon du caprice 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">카프리스의 고치 II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Caprice no Mayu II</title>
<summary>Asako`s poor health begins to interfere with her work. Yuuji senses her change in condition, and as he covers for her, he starts to think he may have found his life`s meaning. Asako tries to respect Yuuji`s resolve, but JB, who watches over both of them closely, is apprehensive about Yuuji`s attempts to return to that violent world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678063</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168067" update="2015-05-19">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168199" update="2015-05-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168288" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブランエールの種 IV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seed of Blanc Aile IV</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les graines de Blanc Aile 4</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">브랑엘의 씨앗 Ⅳ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blanc Aile no Tane IV</title>
<summary>The international terrorist Heath Oslo uses nuclear weapons as a shield to threaten the nation. The nation plans to make Yuuji a human sacrifice in their dealings with Oslo. There is no other way to save Yuuji from this crisis but to rescue him as he is transferred from Ichigaya to Akasaka.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678075</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168289" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブランエールの種 III</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seed of Blanc Aile III</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les graines de Blanc Aile 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">브랑엘의 씨앗 Ⅲ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blanc Aile no Tane III</title>
<summary>A formless supporter, "Thanatos," suddenly supports Amane and the others. "Her" objective is also to liberate and rescue Yuuji Kazami. Thanatos and the Mihama girls` interests align and begin preparing to execute their mission. The girls are perplexed by Thanatos`s seemingly cryptic instructions that unfold via cell phone, but they bring the girls better results than they ever expected in bringing their goal to fruition.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678073</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168290" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブランエールの種 II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seed of Blanc Aile II</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les graines de Blanc Aile 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">브랑엘의 씨앗 Ⅱ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blanc Aile no Tane II</title>
<summary>After Yumiko gets in touch with the informant "Jimmy," she and the other girls at Mihama Academy learn that the current situation is even worse than they thought. Although they have lost Yuuji and have been driven from the academy, they secure a new base of operations and plan a rescue mission for him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678071</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168291" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブランエールの種I</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seed of Blanc Aile I</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les graines de Blanc Aile 1</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">브랑엘의 씨앗 Ⅰ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blanc Aile no Tane I</title>
<summary>After Yuuji suddenly disappears, the girls at Mihama Academy notice him on the TV screen. What`s more, it`s being reported nationwide that he`s a suspect in a terrorist plot which will likely turn into an international incident.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678069</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168526" update="2015-06-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168653" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168755" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブランエールの種 VI</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seed of Blanc Aile VI</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les graines de Blanc Aile 6</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">브랑엘의 씨앗 Ⅵ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blanc Aile no Tane VI</title>
<summary>Tartarus, a gigantic, man-made island, floats on the Pacific Ocean. It is both the adversary of society, and the castle of Heath Oslo, Yuuji Kazami`s mortal enemy. Oslo quietly awaits the moment Yuuji Kazami, the final key he needs to fulfill his ambitions, appears before him once more.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678079</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168756" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブランエールの種 V</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Seed of Blanc Aile V</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les graines de Blanc Aile 5</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">브랑엘의 씨앗 Ⅴ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blanc Aile no Tane V</title>
<summary>The Mihama girls have executed their intense getaway and have rescued Yuuji. Waiting at their goal is Kazuki Kazami, who lived as the core of Thanatos for a long time. This unexpected encounter leaves Yuuji and Amane unable to hide their surprise, but circumstances don`t allow them time to savor their emotional reunion.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678077</identifier>
<identifier>the-fruit-of-grisaia</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="171310" update="2015-09-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">由美子の, ドキドキ湯上がり密着ロッカー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart-Poundingly Close Together in a Locker with Yumiko After a Bath</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">유미코의, 두근두근 목욕 후 밀착 라커</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yumiko no, Dokidoki Yuagari Micchaku Locker</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171811" update="2015-09-24">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みちる編・ツンデレ流 プリクリャ撮影会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tsundere-Style Purikura Photo Session</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">미치루 편 「츤데레류, 스티커 사진 촬영회」</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michiru Hen: Tsudere Ryuu Purikurya Satsueikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171812" update="2015-09-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミリエラの極秘野戦訓練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Milliela`s Top Secret Field Training</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">밀리에라의 극비 야전훈련</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miriela no Gokuhi Yasen Kunren</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173583" update="2016-01-01">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒔菜と幸のイケナイおやつタイム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naughty Snack Time with Makina and Sachi</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">마키나&amp;사치 편「마키나와 사치의 못된 간식 타임」</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makina to Sachi no Ikenai Oyatsu Time</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174149" update="2016-01-02">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天音と一姫の, 日記に書けないマッサージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Amane and Kazuki`s Massage That Can`t Go in a Diary</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아마네&amp;카즈키 편「아마네와 카즈키의, 일기에 쓸 수 없는 마사지」</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amane to Kazuki no, Nikki ni Kakenai Massage</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
