<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11023" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2015-06-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Koukaku Kidoutai Arise: Alternative Architecture</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">攻殻機動隊ARISE ALTERNATIVE ARCHITECTURE</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">攻殻機動隊AAA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Koukaku Kidoutai AAA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">攻殻機動隊 ARISE ALTERNATIVE ARCHITECTURE</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ghost in the Shell Arise: Alternative Architecture</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">攻壳机动队ARISE ALTERNATIVE ARCHITECTURE</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10824" type="Sequel">Koukaku Kidoutai: Shin Gekijouban</anime>
<anime id="61" type="Alternative Setting">Ghost in the Shell</anime>
<anime id="9658" type="Summary">Koukaku Kidoutai Arise: Ghost in the Shell</anime>
<anime id="10382" type="Other">Koukaku Kidoutai Nyuumon Arise</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="118349">So, skip episodes 1-8 and watch the 4 movies instead, then watch episodes 9 &amp; 10, this told, the new GitS Arise series is somehow fascinating, even if it`s a little too slow and Motoko is way too cheerful! Anyway, it`s an interesting premise to the real GitS series. Highly recommended!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kokaku-a.jp/tv/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="1757" type="Character Design">Kise Kazuchika</name>
<name id="1963" type="Series Composition">Ubukata Tou</name>
<name id="871" type="Original Work">Shirou Masamune</name>
<name id="1757" type="Chief Direction">Kise Kazuchika</name>
<name id="35969" type="Music">Cornelius</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Koukaku Kidoutai manga by http://anidb.net/cr871 [Shirou Masamune].
It is 2027, a year after the end of the non-nuclear World War IV. A bomb has gone off in Newport City, killing a major arms dealer who may have had ties with the mysterious 501 Organization. Public Security official http://anidb.net/ch52899 [Aramaki Daisuke] hires full-body cyber prosthesis user and hacker extraordinaire http://anidb.net/ch52359 [Kusanagi Motoko] to investigate. Working on the case with her are: "Sleepless Eyes" http://anidb.net/ch52903 [Batou], who believes Motoko is a criminal; Niihama Prefecture Police Detective http://anidb.net/ch52902 [Togusa], who is investigating a series of prostitute murders he believes are related to the incident; and Lieutenant Colonel http://anidb.net/ch54894 [Kurutsu] of the 501 Organization, who also wishes to keep an eye on Motoko. Meanwhile, bits of the past of the members of this new Public Security organization, http://anidb.net/ch1590 [Section 9], begin to surface.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: The first eight episodes are trimmed down, reordered, and split versions of the http://anidb.net/a9658 [Arise movies], while the final two episodes are new, previously unreleased content.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="788">6.35</permanent>
<temporary count="789">6.99</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>168824.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16786</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>29325</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kokaku-a.jp/tv/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ghost_in_the_Shell:_Arise#TV_series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>攻殻機動隊_ARISE#.E6.94.BB.E6.AE.BB.E6.A9.9F.E5.8B.95.E9.9A.8AARISE_ALTERNATIVE_ARCHITECTURE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3716</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354451</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>351982</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17979</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B014WHG5MI</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="52359" type="main character in" update="2013-02-12">
<rating votes="53">4.14</rating>
<name>Kusanagi Motoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kusanagi Motoko as appears in http://anidb.net/a9658 [Ghost in the Shell: Arise].</description>
<picture>132108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52899" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<rating votes="7">3.96</rating>
<name>Aramaki Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6011" picture="223622.jpg">Juku Ikkyuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52900" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<rating votes="5">3.30</rating>
<name>Ishikawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3264" picture="24262.jpg">Dan Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="144" picture="16904.jpg">Sakuya Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52901" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<rating votes="8">1.27</rating>
<name>Saito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2135" picture="66343.jpg">Nakakuni Takurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52902" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<rating votes="5">5.99</rating>
<name>Togusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132102.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2802" picture="176252.jpg">Shingaki Tarusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52903" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<rating votes="7">5.44</rating>
<name>Batou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2488" picture="186147.jpg">Matsuda Ken`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52904" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<rating votes="5">3.30</rating>
<name>Paz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52905" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-12">
<rating votes="5">1.84</rating>
<name>Borma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54893" type="appears in" update="2013-04-10">
<name>Ibachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54894" type="appears in" update="2016-05-28">
<rating votes="4">1.97</rating>
<name>Kurutsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lieutnant Colonel Kurutsu is the head of the Army 501 Organization, the firm who converted Motoko Kusanagi into a full cyborg and who Kusanagi would replace in the organization had she not joined Section 9.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>135037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1871" picture="20967.jpg">Asano Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54895" type="appears in" update="2013-04-10">
<rating votes="1">1.01</rating>
<name>Tsumugi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>135040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54897" type="appears in" update="2013-04-10">
<name>Raizo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="177" picture="170981.jpg">Hoshino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54898" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-01-10">
<rating votes="23">7.67</rating>
<name>Logicoma</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Note: Logicoma = Logistics Conveyer Machine</description>
<picture>135042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59985" type="appears in" update="2013-09-22">
<name>Soga Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3096" picture="186182.jpg">Sawaki Ikuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59986" type="appears in" update="2013-09-22">
<name>VV</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17008" picture="46192.jpg">Fuji Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66930" type="appears in" update="2014-06-20">
<name>Hose Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66931" type="appears in" update="2014-06-20">
<name>Zhinzhee Bekka Arr Thied</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68049" type="appears in" update="2014-06-20">
<name>Hozumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23484" picture="151668.jpg">Keichou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74067" type="appears in" update="2015-05-02">
<name>Pyromaniac</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170728.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="167588" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ghost Stands Alone 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Stands Alone, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost Stands Alone Zenpen</title>
<summary>When terrorists hijack a peaceful protest, Motoko Kusanagi sees her chance to prove her new squad`s worth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="167726" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ghost Pain 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Pain, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost Pain Kouhen</title>
<summary>The further Motoko investigates her CO`s death, the less sense it makes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="167727" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ghost Pain 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Pain, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost Pain Zenpen</title>
<summary>Motoko returns from a mission abroad to discover that her commanding officer has been murdered--and no one but Aramaki seems interested in doing anything about it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="167728" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ghost Stands Alone 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Stands Alone, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost Stands Alone Kouhen</title>
<summary>A rare disease puts two citizens at the center of a struggle for military and economic power.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="167888" update="2015-04-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168047" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ghost Tears 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Tears, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost Tears Kouhen</title>
<summary>The terrorist attacks on Newport City continue, and the shell squad isn`t making much progress against them. Can Motoko accept help from a man made out of plain old flesh and blood?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="168048" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ghost Tears 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Tears, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost Tears Zenpen</title>
<summary>Motoko`s love life is going better than it ever has, and she`s even managed to take an unprecedented 5-hour vacation. Naturally, that`s when buildings start blowing up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="168049" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ghost Whispers 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Whispers, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost Whispers Kouhen</title>
<summary>Time is running out to stop Pandora`s box from opening.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="168050" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ghost Whispers 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Whispers, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ghost Whispers Zenpen</title>
<summary>After a war hero is convicted of war crimes, he and his former unit hold the entire city hostage. Their demand: access to the state secrets in the Pandora database.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="168340" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PYROPHORIC CULT 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pyrophoric Cult, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pyrophoric Cult Kouhen</title>
<summary>Motoko and the gang have caught their man--or have they?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="168341" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PYROPHORIC CULT 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pyrophoric Cult, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pyrophoric Cult Zenpen</title>
<summary>Motoko and her squad are finally getting closer to Fire-Starter`s broker, but things get tense when they`re instructed to take a backseat role on a sting op.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="181688" update="2016-11-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181689" update="2016-11-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
