<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11059" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-09-26</startdate>
<enddate>2015-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aria the Avvenire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Aria5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Aria 2015</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ARIA The AVVENIRE</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Aria the Avvenire</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">水星领航员 The AVVENIRE</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5424" type="Prequel">Aria the Origination</anime>
<anime id="15499" type="Other">Aria (2020)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="512389">An elegant construction of both new and old, a love letter as warm, wise and beautiful as Aria ever was; while the real-world loss of the two women who provided the speaking and singing voices of Athena is both signified and circumnavigated with great respect.  Practically perfect.  Bring the tissues.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ariacompany.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9212" type="Animation Work">TYO Animations</name>
<name id="5611" type="Original Work">Amano Kozue</name>
<name id="3562" type="Character Design">Onji Masayuki</name>
<name id="3611" type="Series Composition">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="9212" type="Work">TYO Animations</name>
<name id="3611" type="Direction">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: The Blu-ray boxes for each Aria TV series contained one episode of Aria the Avvenire each, for a total of three: the http://anidb.net/a2659 [Aria the Animation] box shipped with the first episode on 24.12.2015, the http://anidb.net/a4243 [Aria the Natural] box shipped with the second episode on 23.03.2016, and the http://anidb.net/a5424 [Aria the Origination] box shipped with the third episode on 24.06.2016. All three episodes were also shown at a special event on 26.09.2015.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="502">8.80</permanent>
<temporary count="504">7.94</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221238.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16769</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>29893</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://comic.mag-garden.co.jp/aria/avvenire.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ariacompany.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Aria_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ARIA_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4758</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>351951</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19577</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2765" parentid="2660" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Mars</name>
<description>Mars is the fourth planet from the Sun and the second-smallest planet in the Solar System after Mercury. In English, Mars carries a name of the Roman god of war, and is often referred to as the "Red Planet" because the reddish iron oxide prevalent on its surface gives it a reddish appearance that is distinctive among the astronomical bodies visible to the naked eye. Mars is a terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere, having surface features reminiscent both of the impact craters of the Moon and the valleys, deserts, and polar ice caps of Earth.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214389.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2964" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>OP variety</name>
<description>Several OP sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique OP for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-04-08">
<name>beauty in simplicity</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3869" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>mono no aware</name>
<description>Literally "the pathos of things", also translated as "an empathy toward things," or "a sensitivity of ephemera"; a Japanese term used to describe the awareness of the transience of things and a gentle sadness (or wistfulness) at their passing.
Also frequently been translated as "the `ahh-ness` of things".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4830" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-03">
<name>flying boats</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5213" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-04">
<name>the effects of time and distance on human relationships</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5779" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-18">
<name>anachronisms</name>
<description>Customs, events, or objects are shown in a period to which they do not belong, e.g. jet planes in medieval Japan.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5963" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-12">
<name>utopia</name>
<description>"Paradise". Portrays a peaceful, united civilization striving for perfection. This may include the world living as one in peace or just an isolated society, at peace with all their surroundings and anything that exists on the outside is irrelevant. In these conditions, humans may have obtained balance with technology which now exists merely to enhance human living standards. Advanced science and technology allow the absence of death and suffering and/or changes in human nature and condition. Technology has affected the way humans live to such an extent that normal functions such as sleep, eating or reproduction are replaced by artificial means (which may include a society comprised of a single gender). A healthier, more intelligent race has been bred. Many or all people exist with traits and special talents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1286" type="main character in" update="2017-06-09">
<rating votes="605">8.79</rating>
<name>Mizunashi Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mizunashi Akari is native of Manhome (Earth) who immigrated to Aqua when she was 15 to become an undine. While not as skillful at sculling a gondola as Alice, nor as familiar with the history of her adopted city as Aika, Akari makes friends quickly and converses easily with customers and other strangers. She finds enjoyment in things or events that others think humdrum and mundane, for which Aika and Alice call her "mysterious." Akari often says "hohe" or "hahi", which is her short version of "wow."
When Akari used gondola simulations on Manhome, she accidentally learned how to row backwards and had to relearn the proper method when she started at Aria Company; however, as Aika notes, "Akari is almost invincible when she rows backwards."
She is promoted last out of three; both Alice and Aika were recently promoted to Primas. Akari received the title "Aquamarine" (遙かなる蒼[アクアマリン], Harukanaru Ao, lit. "Distant Blue") upon her promotion.</description>
<picture>15593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="642" picture="156264.jpg">Hazuki Erino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1287" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-03">
<rating votes="316">8.11</rating>
<name>Alicia Florence</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only other undine with Aria Company, Alicia is one of the three Water Fairies of Neo-Venezia, called the "Snow White" (白き妖精[スノーホワイト], Shiroki Yousei, lit. "White Fairy"). At the start of the series, she is 19 and the most popular undine in the city. Like Akari, she is relaxed and easy-going, but she also likes to tease others (especially her childhood friend Akira). Her favorite phrase is Ara Ara ("Well Well") and she frequently giggles, to Akira`s annoyance.</description>
<picture>15584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1289" type="secondary cast in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="33">6.81</rating>
<name>Grandma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ametsuchi Akino as she appears in the majority of her appearances in Aria</description>
<picture>15586.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7786" type="appears in" update="2011-06-04">
<rating votes="13">8.40</rating>
<name>Aria Company</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Aria Company is a very small water-guide company, with only two employees. Its uniforms are lined with blue, and its president/mascot (and namesake) is http://anidb.net/ch7787 [Aria Pokoteng].
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>26803.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7787" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-26">
<rating votes="176">3.89</rating>
<name>Aria Pokoteng</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>President Aria is the Aria Company`s mascot, a male Aqua breed feline (common traits include larger size compared to Earth breeds, and human-level intelligence). He is smart enough to understand human speech. He was an alley cat before taken in by Grandma 20 years ago, and has been the company`s mascot ever since.</description>
<picture>26811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="551" picture="228658.jpg">Nishimura Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8498" type="main character in" update="2017-06-09">
<rating votes="269">7.12</rating>
<name>Aika S. Granzchesta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aika was the first friend http://anidb.net/ch1286 [Akari] makes on Aqua. She is the only daughter and heir of Himeya Company`s owners, but does not enjoy the distinction as she feels the company`s employees fawned on her too much.
Aika speaks bluntly and often responds to Akari`s idealistic comments with "Embarrassing remarks are not allowed!" (恥ずかしいセリフ禁止!, Hazukashii serifu kinshi!). Despite their contrasting personalities, she gets along well with Akari and http://anidb.net/ch8499 [Alice], but frequently squabbles with her mentor, http://anidb.net/ch8505 [Akira], whom she resembles.
Aika considers herself reliable, especially compared to distractable Akari and antisocial Alice, but both her friends call her a crybaby for her tendency to tear up when emotional. She is proud of her gondola skill as an undine, and can be very competitive about it.
She is promoted second out of three; Alice was recently promoted from Pair to Prima, and Akari was still a Single. Aika received the title "Rosen Queen" (薔薇の女王[ローゼン・クイーン], Bara no Joou, lit. "Queen of Roses") upon her promotion.</description>
<picture>27662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8499" type="main character in" update="2017-06-09">
<rating votes="356">8.79</rating>
<name>Alice Carroll</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alice is friends with Akari and Aika, the undines of Aria and Himeya, respectively. She`s an apprentice of one of the Orange Planet`s Primas - Athena - and has to split her time into going to school and rowing training. Although being only a Pair, her skill surpasses both Akari and Aika`s. They practice together despite working for rival companies.
At the beginning, she is introverted and anti-social, but she lightens up as the series progresses. She often uses dekkai (でっかい, "huge") as an intensifier.
Alice is the first undine to be promoted straight from Pair to Prima, skipping the middle "level". She is promoted first out of three; Akari and Aika were Singles at that time. Alice received the title "Orange Princess" (黄昏の姫君[オレンジ・プリンセス], Tasogare no Himegimi, lit. "Twilight Princess") upon her promotion. She sang the song http://anidb.net/s10336 [Lumis Eterne] during her Prima Undine exam.</description>
<picture>27656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8501" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-12">
<rating votes="111">6.05</rating>
<name>Aino Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ai is a girl from Manhome. She befriends http://anidb.net/ch1286 [Akari] and becomes Akari`s e-mail correspondent, while visiting Aqua whenever she can.
At the end of Aria the Origination she joins http://anidb.net/ch7786 [Aria Company] as a Pair under Akari.</description>
<picture>27658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8505" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-03">
<rating votes="209">7.89</rating>
<name>Akira E. Ferrari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira is one of Neo-Venezia`s Three Water Fairies, and a native of Aqua. As a Prima undine, Akira is called the "Crimson Rose" (真紅の薔薇[クリムゾンローズ], Shinku no Bara) and is famed for her conversational skills. Throughout the story, she`s holding blade oar number 27. She has many admirers among her customers, especially her female ones, but she considers herself very feminine.
Akira is mentor to Aika, who calls her the Demon Instructor for her strictness and her loud, brusque personality. Akira is particularly harsh with Aika because she believes there is potential in her.
Akira and Alicia are childhood friends.</description>
<picture>27665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8506" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-20">
<rating votes="184">7.34</rating>
<name>Athena Glory</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Athena Glory is one of Neo-Venezia`s Three Water Fairies, known by the title "Siren" (天上の謳声[セイレーン], Tenjou no Utagoe, lit. "Heavenly Voice") for her beautiful singing voice. Her blade oar number is 36. She is Alice`s mentor at Orange Planet. She often appears quiet most of the time and an airhead who does not pay attention to her surroundings (in the anime, she is shown more than once forgetting to duck while rowing under a bridge), but she genuinely cares about Alice.
Athena has a strange laugh that comes out sounding as though she is angry. She was a trainee undine with Alicia and Akira, and joined them in joint practice.
Her signature song is http://anidb.net/s7270 [Barcarolle], sung by the vocalist http://anidb.net/cr3917 [Kawai Eri]. Throughout the series, Athena also features two other songs with vocals by Kawai Eri: http://anidb.net/s7258 [Coccoro] and http://anidb.net/s52857 [Lumis Eterne].</description>
<picture>27666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3917" picture="31764.jpg">Kawai Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14175" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="34">4.74</rating>
<name>Izumo Akatsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akatsuki is a trainee "salamander", one of those responsible for maintaining Aqua`s weather. He usually lives on the floating island in Aqua`s atmosphere where the weather controls are, but often comes down to the ground to see his chronically irresponsible brother. Akatsuki was born in Neo-Venezia, but as he spends most of his time on the floating island he doesn`t really know very much about the city.
Akatsuki tends to be cynical and has an even shorter fuse than Aika. But although he`s grumpy and ill-tempered most of the time, he`s really a nice guy who rather likes Akari (though you`ll never see him admit it). He likes to pull on Akari`s pigtails (it`s also his favorite nickname for her).
Source: http://drawerofdreams.net/neo-venezia/chara/akatsuki.html</description>
<picture>41692.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14257" type="appears in" update="2010-02-02">
<rating votes="13">5.24</rating>
<name>Ayanokouji Udo the 51st</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>More commonly known as "Woody." Woody is a Sylph who delivers packages and other goods to people in Neo-Venezia. He has a bad sense of direction and cannot navigate without a map. His physique is well-built, and he is usually seen wearing goggles. He was childhood friends with both Akatsuki and Al.
source: wiki</description>
<picture>42407.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14258" type="appears in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="16">1.91</rating>
<name>Maa-kun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maa-Kun is President of Orange Planet, an Aqua kitten with very tiny blue eyes.Alice calls her "Maa-kun" after her unusual meow.Maa often bites President Aria`s belly.</description>
<picture>42432.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14275" type="appears in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="8">7.81</rating>
<name>Anno Namihei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41789.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14731" type="appears in" update="2010-02-03">
<rating votes="12">3.42</rating>
<name>Hime M. Granzchesta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>President of Himeya Company, a small, delicate, black female cat from Manhome.</description>
<picture>42433.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="75708" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-19">
<rating votes="3">7.21</rating>
<name>Azusa B. McLaren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azusa B. McLaren is a Single undine working in Himeya company. Like her senior http://anidb.net/ch8498 [Aika], she is brave, direct and self-confident. She doesn`t look before she leaps when it comes to something that interests her. She notes any important information in her electronic organizer. She practices with http://anidb.net/ch75709 [Anya] from Orange Planet.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>174280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75709" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-19">
<rating votes="3">7.21</rating>
<name>Anya Dostoyevskaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anya Dostoyevskaya is a Single undine working in Orange Planet and http://anidb.net/ch8499 [Alice]`s junior. She has a calm and gentle personality, but sometimes demonstrates spontaneity, such as blurting out "From Siberia!" to anyone she has just met. She sometimes speaks in a literary tone. She practices with http://anidb.net/ch75708 [Azusa] from Himeya.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>174281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90022" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="2">1.63</rating>
<name>Cait Sith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cait Sith is a giant humanoid cat that resides in Neo Venezia. Throughout the series, the people of Neo Venezia share many folk stories on how the cats of city contribute to its mystique. Cait Sith is said to be the leader of these cats, creating fantasies for those individuals deemed deserving and suitable to bear witness to them.
Throughout the series, especially in http://anidb.net/a4243 [Aria the Natural], http://anidb.net/ch1286 [Mizunashi Akari] has several fantastical encounters with the cats of Neo Venezia and with Cait Sith himself. http://anidb.net/ch8501 [Aino Ai] also has a few encounters of her own. As Akari graduates and becomes a Prima Undine, her ability to encounter fantasies and Cait Sith fade away.
— written by CDB-Man</description>
<picture>203969.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105028" type="appears in" update="2019-08-13">
<name>Ayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237303.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105029" type="appears in" update="2019-08-13">
<name>Atora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237304.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105030" type="appears in" update="2019-08-13">
<name>Anzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237305.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="166684" update="2016-02-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2015-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その 逢いたかったあなたに...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To You, Who I Wanted to Meet...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Aitakatta Anata ni...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167831" update="2015-05-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ARIA The AVVENIRE 特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (30 sec)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aria the Avvenire Tokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168892" update="2016-03-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2015-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その 暖かなさよならは...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Warm Goodbye...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Atataka na Sayonara wa...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168893" update="2016-06-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2015-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その 遙かなる未来へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To That Far Away Future...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Haruka Naru Mirai e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176120" update="2016-03-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
