<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11056" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-04-11</startdate>
<enddate>2015-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Saint Seiya: Soul of Gold</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">聖闘士星矢 黄金魂-soul of gold-</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">聖闘士星矢 -黄金魂 soul of gold-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Saint Seiya: Soul of Gold</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5670" type="Other">Saint Seiya: Meiou Hades Elysion Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://saintseiya-gold.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="25643" type="Direction">Furuta Jouji</name>
<name id="7346" type="Series Composition">Takeuchi Toshimitsu</name>
<name id="3119" type="Main Character Design">Motohashi Hideyuki</name>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="750" type="Work">Bandai Visual</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="1412" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yanagisawa Masahide</name>
<name id="867" type="Original Work">Kurumada Masami</name>
<name id="3518" type="Chief Animation Direction">Koujina Hiroshi</name>
<name id="2463" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsubata Yoshiaki</name>
</creators>
<description>In the Underworld, during the fight against Hades, the 12 Gold Saints gave up their lives to destroy the Wailing Wall and allow Seiya and his friends to keep moving forward. Aioria and the Gold Saints, who should have disappeared, come back to life in this beautiful Earth full of light. How have they resurrected if they were supposed to be dead? While the big mystery remains, Aioria gets involved in a new battle and when his Cosmo exceeds its limits.. a change happens to the Leo Cloth!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="190">4.30</permanent>
<temporary count="192">6.15</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>170228.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16592</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>28215</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://saintseiya-gold.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Saint_Seiya:_Soul_of_Gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>聖闘士星矢_黄金魂_-soul_of_gold-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3896</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>351807</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17972</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10499" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="20">8.53</rating>
<name>Libra no Douko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Libra Douko is the Libra Gold Saint in Lost Canvas. He shows signs of slight rashness and immaturity, and has big respect for his partners, turning pretty furious if they are in danger. However, in these occasions, he does not quite concern about consequences. He is a good friend of Aries Shion and Taurus Aldebaran to whom he often talks to and sometimes say his way of thinking is thanks to them.</description>
<picture>31481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10544" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="29">7.93</rating>
<name>Aries no Muu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Under the tutelage of Shion, the Pope of the Sanctuary, Muu was able to become the Gold Saint of Aries at a young age. While all gold saints have a base of psychic powers to some degree, Muu has been stated to possess the strongest raw psychic talent among all living gold saints. This allows him to manipulate his gift to various degrees: psychokinesis, telepathy, teleportation, and various other powers are at his command.
Muu is very soft spoken, with a scholarly-like personality; his demeanor is very tranquil and logical, almost as if he is a professor of the Sanctuary. He is good friends with Taurus Aldebaran, and is very respectful to the 243 year old master Libra Douko.</description>
<picture>31552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10553" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="12">6.22</rating>
<name>Taurus no Aldebaran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aldebaran is one of the 12 Guardians of Sanctuary, with the Taurus as his destined constellation. He was the physically strongest of the Gold Saints of modern era. He is Brazilian in origin.
Unlike most of the characters, Aldebaran is often depicted as a friendly guy, laughing and being less serious in times of peace. He was a good friend of Aries Mu, and with Pegasus Seiya (as this last is said in the anime adaptation of the Hades Saga, when Aldebaran sacrificed himself with the other eleven Gold Saints to destroy the Wailing Wall).</description>
<picture>31560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17680" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="4">9.17</rating>
<name>Pisces no Aphrodite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pisces Aphrodite is the last of the Gold Saints introduced by Kurumada in his manga, formally presented in vol.11. Aphrodite was a Saint famous not only because of his incredible, mesmerizing beauty, but also for his reputation as one of the strongest among the 88 Saints. However, this reputation is not explored very well in the series itself, as he is killed by Andromeda Shun rather easily by Gold Saint standards, and is beaten rather easily by Aries Mu during the Hades Saga.
Gold Saint Gemini Saga once stated that Aphrodite`s beauty was the greatest among Athena`s Saints. Kurumada named him after the Greek Goddess of love and beauty as a reference to the Greek myth associated to the Pisces constellation. However, Aphrodite never claimed to be the most beautiful creature, unlike the Silver Saint, Lizard Misty who claimed that even the stars` splendor dimmed next to his glory.
It is notable that despite his incomparable beauty, Aphrodite is not narcissistic. He is often described as cruel as his fellow Gold Saint, Cancer Deathmask, but not as sadistic. He is also ironic and sarcastic. According to Saga, despite his beauty, Aphrodite is the most feared of all the 88 Saints of Athena, however, as explained above, this may be due to his cruel nature as opposed to his fighting prowess. His reputation is supported more in the still non-canonical Saint Seiya Episode G, when Aphrodite appeared in front of the Titan`s soldiers who were awe-struck due to his beauty but also paralyzed by fear in his presence.
A recurring motif in the Pisces Saint is that he considers victory as the greatest beauty of all and, therefore, he believes what makes him really beautiful would not be his physique, but absolute power. Aphrodite is depicted as a man who believes the power is the only way to keep the order and assure the justice. Subscribing to this theory, he believes the stronger is allowed to rule over the weak.
Some casual fans believe Aphrodite is a female because of his name. In the French, European Spanish -first dubbing- and Chinese dubbing of the anime adaptation, he is voiced by a female actress.</description>
<picture>48024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17681" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="3">6.73</rating>
<name>Gemini no Saga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Along with Leo Aiolia, Saga disguised as the Pope was the first Gold Saint that Masami Kurumada introduced in his manga, although their rank wasn`t revealed until later volumes. In his first appearance, Saga presided the event in which Pegasus Seiya acquired the status of Saint. In the anime adaptation, he was introduced in identical manner, in episode 1.
Saga managed to put himself in control of the sanctuary treacherously for many years after killing Pope Shion, the original Grand Pope of Sanctuary by stealing his identity.
Saga is often described by other characters as someone with the kindness of an angel but with the darkness of a demon. This ambivalence ended up creating a split personality: a good Saga that was extremely loyal to Athena and an evil one that keeps control of the body most of the time and killed the previous Pope to steal his place. When it takes control of Saga`s body, his hair turns from blond to jet-black (the color schemes were altered for the anime, in which Saga`s normally blue hair turned light grey). Saga`s two "sides", can also communicate between them : in a dialogue the good Saga reproaches his evil "side" to have forced him to hurt Athena.</description>
<picture>1427.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17682" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="2">9.63</rating>
<name>Cancer no Deathmask</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Deathmask was one of the first Gold Saints to be shown in both manga and the anime adaptation. Since his first appearance, he was depicted as a very sadistic and malevolent man who used his power as he wanted without bending to Athena`s will. Deathmask covers his temple with the faces of his fallen victims - warriors and civilian men, women and even innocent children. Deathmask is one the few Saints who knows the truth about the Pope and the Gemini Saint, along with Pisces Aphrodite, but he continues obeying his orders. He believes that justice is not a real concept and is just a name given to the will of the stronger, since those with power can force their wills on the weak and call it fair. Even after joining sides with Athena, Deathmask remains a diabolic, sadistic person, facing Aries Mu and Pegasus Seiya without showing remorse and even attempting to kill the latter. In the US version his name was changed to Mephisto. It is unknown if Deathmask is his real name or a title since he collects the faces of his victims.</description>
<picture>48025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3268" picture="24747.jpg">Tanaka Ryouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17683" type="main character in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="7">9.28</rating>
<name>Leo no Aiolia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As Masami Kurumada uses the revered Osamu Tezuka`s Star System, (A stable cast of characters which play a different or similar role in the author`s various works, sometimes with the same personality and sometimes with an entirely new one), he designed Aiolia`s appearance very similar to Zaji, the main character in Raimei no Zaji, a manga that Kurumada wrote and drew years before Saint Seiya.
In his manga, Kurumada gave Aiolia blonde hair. In the anime adaptation, due to a relative excess of yellow tones in Kurumada`s design, Aiolia`s hair color was modified to light brown to achieve a better color balance and contrast.</description>
<picture>1428.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17684" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="11">5.91</rating>
<name>Virgo no Shaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Although Gemini Saga and Leo Aiolia were the first Gold Saints introduced by Masami Kurumada in his manga, Virgo Shaka was the first one he showed fully revealing his status as Gold Saint and wearing his Gold Cloth, in the chapter 18, contained in vol. 5.
Shaka is one of the Twelve Gold Saints. As the guardian of the Temple of Virgo along the path of Sanctuary, Shaka has played a pivotal role chiefly in the battle between Athena and the Pope in the Sanctuary arc, and also in the Hades arc. He is referred to many times on the story as the "the man who is almost a god" due to his immense power and is also considered the only Gold Saint that has full control over the Araya Shiki (8th sense). He is supposed to be Buddha`s reincarnation.
Shaka alone of all saints occupies the rarefied spot between God and man, but living between two worlds has its blessings as well as curses. As a Bodhisattva, and endowed with the most powerful cosmos of all the saints, Shaka well deserves his reputation as the man closest to God. Even as a child in India, Shaka was precocious and communed with God himself—a scene recounted in the flashbacks moments before Shaka`s death in the Twin Sala`s Garden. For someone whose life has just begun, he had been unusually sensitive to sufferings and mortality of human life. Seeing pain and death as reflected in the Ganges gives the boy Shaka enough despair, if not a crisis of faith. With esoteric learning and training, Shaka eventually became powerful enough to don the Gold Cloth of Virgo, which he wore even as a boy in the manga, and wise enough to rise above human passions and attachments. For most of his life, he would look on human feelings with a mix of pity and compassion without being bound to them, with charity but not always with love. Detachment seems to be Shaka`s answer to the poignant questions raised by human life, and he is seeing humanity from the point of God rather than living the experience. He would be disabused of this attitude in his encounter with Ikki. In the end, Shaka would have to remember that he is a man, as well, and return to whence he came.</description>
<picture>48026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3270" picture="30153.jpg">Mitsuya Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17685" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="2">9.63</rating>
<name>Capricorn no Shura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shura belongs to the fabled rank of Gold Saint hierarchy among the other 12 Gold Saints. His guardian star is of the zodiac sign of Capricorn. Shura is the Gold Saint that underwent some modifications in his ideology when the manga was adapted to animation. While the anime series shows Shura as being the most loyal Saint to Athena, Kurumada depicted in his manga a Capricorn Saint that at first was somewhat reluctant, but short moments before his death, rediscovered his loyalty to Athena, and remained faithful to her even after his death. According to the manga, Shura, just like Cancer Deathmask and Pisces Aphrodite, knew that Gemini Saga was behind the Pope`s mask but he still was obeying his orders. As he says in his fight against Shiryu, he doesn`t believe anyone fights for a god anymore, so he doesn`t care about fighting for Athena. He considered that those with power, were automatically qualified to be judged just. He thought that the Pope, even being evil, using that power, could use it for some good.
The new Saint Seiya Episode G manga, authored by Megumu Okada under commission by Masami Kurumada, although still non-canonical, shows a version of Shura that conciliate both previous versions: here, Shura is a very loyal Gold Saint, but when he discovers the truth about Gemini Saga, he is attacked by the Demon Emperor Fist, a technique that controls the mind of its victim. According to Saga`s will, Shura starts to follow his orders, but remains loyal to Athena at heart. Masami Kurumada named Shura after Asura, the Hindu demon who eternally hungers for battle and war.</description>
<picture>1429.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17686" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="5">9.73</rating>
<name>Aquarius no Camus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a Gold Saint, guardian of the temple of Aquarius, and also Cygnus Hyoga and Kraken Isaac`s master in manga. In the anime, he was the master of the Crystal Saint, who was Hyoga and Isaac`s master. Camus is a cold looking Saint, since he believes the Gold Saint, as the strongest among Athena`s guards, should never show exasperation or it would draw the people into despair. In the manga, he reveals that he actually knew that the Pope wasn`t working under Athena`s will, but he still kept working under his orders to fulfill his role as the Aquarius Gold Saint. Even so, he was glad to see his pupil Hyoga fighting for the real Athena. Since Milo fought Hyoga, he mentioned Camus in a way that led the fans to believe they were close friends. Apparently, this was made official since the animation of the Hades saga included more personal interaction between them than the manga, and they are depicted as friends in Saint Seiya Episode G. He is named after Albert Camus.</description>
<picture>1430.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17688" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="5">7.60</rating>
<name>Sagittarius no Aiolos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurumada introduced Aiolos in chapter 24 of his manga, contained in vol. 6.
He is one of the 12 Guardians of Sanctuary, with the Sagittarius as his destined constellation. Aiolos is the famous gold saint who died protecting Athena when she was an infant.
Aiolos always was a paradigm of righteousness, seen as the perfect Saint and one of the two Gold Saints who could succeed Aries Shion as the next Pope of Sanctuary and the chosen one.
Not much is known about Aiolos, since he died before the main story began. More of him is seen in Saint Seiya Episode G, like his relationship with Garan, a servant of his young brother, Leo Aiolia, who once trained with Aiolos for the Sagittarius cloth.
Despite his condition, Aiolos managed to help the main characters many times sending his cloth to aid them.
Aiolos is probably named after the Greek god of Wind, Aeolus.</description>
<picture>48028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17689" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="4">8.66</rating>
<name>Scorpio no Milo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurumada introduced Milo in vol.7 of his manga. Though in the manga the first Gold Saints introduced are Aiolia and Saga, Kurumada didn`t revealed their rank until further volumes. The first Gold Saint he introduced revealing his rank was Virgo Shaka, in vol.5. In the anime adaptation, these introductions occur in the same manner, although Shaka`s is delayed and the first Gold Saint that appeared fully wearing a Gold Cloth was Scorpio Milo.
Milo is the Scorpio Gold Saint. Since his main technique inflicts immense pain to its victims, Milo always gives his opponents the option to either surrender, or become insane due to the unbearable pain. He also sees great importance in the pride of the Gold Saints and seems to be always ready to clean the name of his companions. Even so, he is a noble warrior who can admit defeat even against a weaker or inferior enemy. Since Milo fought Hyoga, he spoke to Aquarius Camus in a way that led the fans to believe they were close friends. Apparently, this was made official since the anime adaptation of the Hades arc of the manga included more interaction between them and they are depicted as friends in Saint Seiya Episode G.</description>
<picture>48029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83479" type="main character in" update="2016-08-02">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Rifia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83480" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Andreas Lise</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83481" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Gurinburusuti no Furodi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>God Warrior of Odin</description>
<picture>189575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4032" picture="77662.jpg">Okamoto Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83482" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Tangurisuniru no Herakurusu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>God Warrior of Odin</description>
<picture>189576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83483" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Nizuheggu no Fafuna</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>God Warrior of Odin</description>
<picture>189578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83484" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Eikushuniru no Suruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>God Warrior of Odin</description>
<picture>189580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83485" type="appears in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Helena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="321" picture="17158.jpg">Yamazaki Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83486" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Guraniru no Shigumundo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>God Warrior of Odin</description>
<picture>189582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83487" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-08-12">
<name>Sinmone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>was the younger sister of Eikpyrnir Surt, Sinmone died due to an avalanche caused by the friend of her brother, Camus.</description>
<picture>189584.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="83488" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Furesuverugu no Barudoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>God Warrior of Odin</description>
<picture>189585.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="84" picture="16692.jpg">Tai Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83489" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Garumu no Utogaruza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>God Warrior of Odin</description>
<picture>189586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83490" type="appears in" update="2016-08-02">
<name>Shounen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2982" picture="23710.jpg">Hibi Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="167834" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よみがえれ! 黄金伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gold Legend Revived!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Tornate alla vita, cavalieri d`oro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaere! Ougon Densetsu</title>
<summary>The 12 Gold Saints gave their lives to destroy the Wailing Wall to break the way for Seiya and the Saints in their battle against Hades in the Underworld. Though presumed to have perished, Aiolia and the other Gold Saints return to the beautiful earthly world of radiating luminescence. Why have these lost souls been brought back to life? Following a new encounter, Aiolia becomes embroiled in a duel amid this deep mystery. And when he burns his Cosmo to its limit…the Cloth of Leo transforms!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678841</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167837" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">集結! 七人の神闘士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The 7 God Warriors Assembled!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Adunata! I sette cavalieri di Asgard!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuketsu! Nananin no Shintoushi</title>
<summary>When Miro’s life is at stake under Surt’s malicious scheme, there emerges the strongest Gold Saint of Athena – Gemini Saga! Meanwhile, Helena, whom Deathmask secretly fancies, falls for the ferocious God Warrior Fafner’s offer for “medical treatment”.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678847</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167838" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 黄金聖闘士[ゴールドセイント]VS黄金聖闘士[ゴールドセイント]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gold vs. Gold: Clash of the Saints!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Scontro micidiale! Cavaliere d`Oro contro Cavaliere d`Oro!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Gold Saint vs Gold Saint</title>
<summary>Scorpio Miro finally faces off against one of the God Warriors, Surt. However, standing in his way is none other than Gold Saint Aquarius Camus! Meanwhile in town, Aiolia and Lyfia run into Cancer Deathmask on their quest for Yggdrasil.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678845</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167839" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴け!ユグドラシルの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of Yggdrasil Revealed!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abake! Yggdrasil no Himitsu</title>
<summary>Aiolia defeats God Warrior Frodi. However, he passes out as the mysterious marks reappear. Lyfia runs about to save Aiolia, but she, too, collapses. When she awakens, she finds she’s been taken in by a boy and Aries Mu with a Gold Cloth Box.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678843</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168187" update="2015-04-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168188" update="2015-04-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168620" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突入! ユグドラシルの7つの間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Entering the 7 Chambers of Yggdrasil!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsunyuu! Yggdrasil no Nanatsu no Ma</title>
<summary>The Gold Saints are lured into Yggdrasil by Andreas after breaking Fimbulwinter. Lyfia states the brewing evil can be stopped by destroying the statues in the 7 chambers. The Gold Saints advance with renewed resolve, while a change occurs in Lyfia.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678851</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168621" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">究極! 神聖衣[ゴッドクロス]の力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">God Cloth`s Ultimate Power!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Limite estremo! La forza delle armature divine!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuukyoku! God Cloth no Chikara</title>
<summary>Learning of the God Cloths’ powers from Shaka, Mu telepathically tells Aiolia and Lyfia, who are headed to Yggdrasil, that its barrier can be broken using their God Cloths to raise their Cosmo to the limit to attack the 3 key points of the Great Root.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>678849</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168909" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激震! 神聖衣[ゴッドクロス]VS神聖衣[ゴッドクロス]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown: God Cloth vs. God Cloth!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekishin! God Cloth vs God Cloth</title>
<summary>A showdown of Gold Saints vs. God Warriors in the 7 chambers starts at last! Taurus Aldebaran faces God Warrior Hercules yet again. Meanwhile, in the chamber of ice, Gold Saints Shura and Camus engage in an ultimate battle of God Cloth vs. God Cloth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681399</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169073" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バルドル! 神に選ばれし男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Balder, the Man Chosen by the Gods!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Balder! Kami ni Erabareshi Otoko</title>
<summary>Shaka, the man closest to the gods, faces God Warrior Balder in the chamber of light. He lives up to his reputation, but Balder subdues him with immense power! Meanwhile, Deathmask takes Fafner to the gateway to the land of the dead to settle all scores.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681401</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169511" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サガ! 熱き兄弟の絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Saga, the Unbreakable Bond of Brothers!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saga! Atsuki Kyoudai no Kizuna</title>
<summary>Sigmund, determined to avenge his younger brother Siegfried, is brushed aside by the immense power of the “strongest” Gold Saint Saga. Meanwhile, in the chamber of the brave, a fierce battle continues between Aiolia and Frodi, when Lyfia steps in!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681403</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169926" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! アイオリアVS[たい]アンドレアス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash: Aiolia vs. Andreas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Aiolia tai Andreas</title>
<summary>Holding Lyfia’s words close to heart, Aiolia finally faces Andreas! Andreas scornfully recounts how he manipulated Lyfia. Fuming with rage, Aiolia’s immense Cosmo turns into a God Cloth! Meanwhile, Frodi is cornered by Utgardar’s forceful swordplay.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681405</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170404" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活! アスガルドの邪神ロキ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Return of the False God Loki!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu! Asgard no Jashin Loki</title>
<summary>The ultimate forbidden attack Athena Exclamation by Mu, Saga, and Dohko annihilates Andreas! However, the evil fruit continues to grow, swallowing the Gold Saints! While stripped of his Gold Cloth, Aiolia faces Loki with a burning Cosmo in his heart!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681407</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170806" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誕生! 神器グングニルの槍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sacred Spear of Gungnir Reborn!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanjou! Jingi Gungnir no Yari</title>
<summary>Empowered by his brother’s determination, Lyfia’s faith, and the Odin Robe, Aiolia, with Odin’s sword and Draupnir in hand, faces off against Loki! The ultimate battle reaches its climax - Aiolia’s fist vs. the Spear of Gungnir – who will take victory?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681409</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="171032" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届け我らの想い! 永遠の黄金伝説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let Our Prayers Be Heard! The Eternal Golden Legend!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todoke Warera no Omoi! Eien no Ougon Densetsu</title>
<summary>All 12 Gold Saints gather since the Wailing Wall! With the purpose of reviving on earth close at heart, they face the false god Loki who’s armed with the Spear of Gungnir! However, the 12 Gold Saints are overpowered by the absolute power of god.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>681411</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-soul-of-gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
