<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1106" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2004-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ocha-ken: Chokotto Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Tea-dog</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">お茶犬 ちょこっとものがたり</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9679" type="Sequel">Ocha-ken: Hotto Monogatari</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.ocha-ken.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="1160" type="Work">Four Some</name>
<name id="1460" type="Direction">Ooya Mitsuko</name>
</creators>
<description>Ocha-ken is a children`s programme about tea-dogs and tea-cats, each representing a different blend. The episodes are very short and geared to teaching the audience various values. The lesson, or moral of the episode is displayed at the end.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="98">3.57</permanent>
<temporary count="99">5.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>131271.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3015</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2233</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2288</identifier>
<identifier>hjdcij</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ocha-ken.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>319280</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="11708" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, お茶入りています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Will You Be Making Some Tea Soon?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Ocha Irite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11835" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, だらだらしていません?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Will You Be Pouring the Tea Soon?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Daradara Shite Imasen?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12071" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, お気に入りあります?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Have a Favorite?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Oki ni Iri Arimasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12175" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 趣味しています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Taken Up Any Hobbies Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Shumi Shite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12433" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, ニガテなものあります?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is There Anything That You Don`t Like?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Nigate na Mono Arimasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12792" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 落ち込んだりしていません?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haven`t You Felt Sad Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Ochikondari Shite Imasen?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12919" update="2004-08-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 冒険しています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Will You Be Going to an Adventure?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Bouken Shite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13007" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 謎めいています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lately, Have Things Been Mysterious?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Nazomeite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13442" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, ほのぼのしています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lately, Have You Had a Heartwarming Feeling?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Honobono Shite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13485" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 季節を感じています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lately, Have You Experienced the Seasons?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Kisetsu o Kanjite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13810" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 努力しています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lately, Have You Been Working Hard?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Doryoku Shite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14091" update="2004-08-13">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 星を見ています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Looked At the Stars Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Hoshi o Mite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14092" update="2004-08-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 集まっています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Had a Gathering Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Atsumatte Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14489" update="2007-09-11">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, リフレッシュしています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lately, Have You Refreshed Yourself?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Refresh Shite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14889" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 安らぎ感じています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Felt Peaceful Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Yasuragi Kanjite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15142" update="2004-08-13">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, いい汗かいています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Had a Good Sweat Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Ii Ase Kaite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15540" update="2004-08-13">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, ひとりになっていません?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Haven`t You Been by Yourself Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Hitori ni Natte Imasen?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15677" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 耳をすましています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Been Listening Carefully Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Mimi o Sumashite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16211" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, ときめいています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Been Excited Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Tokimeite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17482" update="2004-08-13">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 小さな楽しみあります?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Had a Little Fun Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Chiisa na Tanoshimi Arimasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17961" update="2004-08-13">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, ゆったりしています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Been Calm Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Yuttari Shite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18386" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, はしゃいでいます?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Been Having Fun Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Hashaide Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19973" update="2005-02-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 夢を見ています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lately, Have You Been Having Dreams?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Yume o Mite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19974" update="2004-08-12">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, ウキウキしています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Been Cheerful Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Ukiuki Shite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23696" update="2004-09-01">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, うるおいあります?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Been Enriched Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Uruoi Arimasu?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23697" update="2004-09-01">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最近, 発見しています?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Made a Discovery Lately?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikin, Hakken Shite Imasu?</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
