<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11085" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2015-04-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Etsuraku no Tane</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">悦楽の胤</title>
</titles>
<url>http://ms-pictures.com/label/mitsu/products/1504/tane/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1387" type="Animation Work">Studio Eromatick</name>
<name id="42797" type="Original Work">Wendy Bell</name>
</creators>
<description>A tentacle monster that feeds on girl cum takes over schoolgirl http://anidb.net/ch73442 [Murasawa Itsuki], driving her to seduce and pleasure other cute schoolgirls. How long will they last before becoming nothing but slaves to the pleasure?
Source: HentaiHaven</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="176">3.86</permanent>
<temporary count="179">5.51</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>169025.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30132</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ms-pictures.com/label/mitsu/products/1504/tane/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12587</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2693" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-10">
<name>handjob</name>
<description>A handjob is the manual stimulation of the penis by another person`s hand. The female equivalent is http://anidb.net/t7229 [fingering].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2704" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-15">
<name>cum play</name>
<description>Fetish of sorts where the focus is of the semen that is ejaculated. This can include snowballing, drinking copious amounts of semen, eating it off food, using it to brush one`s teeth, acting as a urinal for semen, gargling it, rinsing one`s mouth with it, or any other act where semen is involved that does not have to do with fertilization of an egg.
This should not be used if one cannot visibly see semen in scenes or if the scene is extremely short.</description>
<picurl>236279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2705" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>creampie</name>
<description>The act of a man ejaculating inside a girl`s vagina, leaving the semen oozing out of her.</description>
<picurl>160720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2708" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>uncensored version available</name>
<description>There`s an uncensored version available of the porn anime this tag is added to, which in most cases means, that there was a region 1 DVD (R1 DVD = North America) release.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2709" parentid="4656" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-30">
<name>netorare</name>
<description>Netorare is what happens when the protagonist gets his wife/girlfriend stolen from him by someone else. It is a sexual fetish designed to cause sexual jealousy by way of having the heroine indulge in sexual activity with someone other than the protagonist.
The intent or reason causing the scenario does not have any bearing as to whether the scenario is netorare or netori; perspective is the only differentiating factor.
Netorare is generally caused by, but not limited to: the stealing party has malicious intent to harm the protagonist, or the wife/girlfriend hopes to improve their relationship by causing the protagonist to be jealous.
Netorare Type A
The heroine is willingly cheating on the protagonist with another guy, and enjoys every second of it. No rape, blackmail, drugs etc. involved; it`s consensual sex from the very beginning.
Netorare Type B
Initially, the heroine is raped, blackmailed, drugged, or otherwise tricked to have sex with someone other than the protagonist. However, she eventually starts enjoying it, and the sex becomes fully consensual in the end.
Netorare Type C
The heroine is raped in front of the protagonist, and he can only helplessly watch it. It`s non-consensual from start to finish.
Note: Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2716 [Netori].</description>
<picurl>150946.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2722" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>doggy style</name>
<description>Bang her from behind and use her boobies as a steering wheel!</description>
<picurl>161394.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2724" parentid="2848" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>double penetration</name>
<description>Double penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by two penises or strap-ons.</description>
<picurl>172771.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2725" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-20">
<name>ahegao</name>
<description>A term for the weird face occasionally seen in adult games/anime/manga. Canonically, ahegao has eyes rolled up, mouth open and tongue sticking out. Sometimes also referred to as "fucked silly".</description>
<picurl>175637.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2732" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-04">
<name>female rapes female</name>
<description>Both the perpetrator and victim are female; a same-sex rape results.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2733" parentid="2715" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>enjoyable rape</name>
<description>This anime features a rape scene during which the raped character also reaches orgasm or somehow else derives sexual pleasure from the act.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2914" parentid="2704" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-25">
<name>bukkake</name>
<description>Bukkake is a group sex practice wherein a group of men ejaculate onto a woman.</description>
<picurl>208870.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2935" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-19">
<name>stomach bulge</name>
<description>Visible stomach distortion caused by large quantities of fluid or air having been inserted into the vaginal or anal cavity. Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2727 [stomach stretch] or http://anidb.net/t775 [pregnancy].</description>
<picurl>236454.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4046" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>foursome</name>
<description>When four people have sex with each other at the same time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4656" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-06">
<name>infidelity</name>
<description>Infidelity is a violation of a couple`s assumed or stated contract regarding emotional and/or sexual exclusivity, sometimes according to the subjective feeling that one`s partner has violated a set of rules or relationship norms; this violation results in feelings of sexual jealousy and rivalry. What constitutes an act of infidelity is dependent upon the exclusivity expectations within the relationship. In marital relationships, exclusivity expectations are commonly assumed although they are not always met. When they are not met, research has found that psychological damage can occur, including feelings of rage and betrayal, lowering of sexual and personal confidence, and damage to self-image.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5750" parentid="2724" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>triple penetration</name>
<description>Triple penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by a minimum of three penises or strap-ons. Usually, this means one oral penetration, one vaginal penetration, and one anal penetration. Triple penetration happens most often during http://anidb.net/t2719 [gang bang] and particularly http://anidb.net/t4492 [gang rape] scenes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="73440" type="main character in" update="2016-12-12">
<name>Nonohara Rena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34577">Tezuka Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73441" type="main character in" update="2016-01-18">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Terashima Touka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28781" picture="63532.jpg">Momozono Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73442" type="main character in" update="2016-12-12">
<name>Murasawa Itsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42500">Nagase Yuzuha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73443" type="main character in" update="2016-12-12">
<name>Fujimori Hiyori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42499">Minae Kotori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="166639" update="2015-04-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
