<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="111" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>5</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-08-25</startdate>
<enddate>2005-08-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sentou Yousei Yukikaze</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Yukikaze Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Battle Fairy Yukikaze</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Боевая фея Вьюга</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">戦闘妖精雪風</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Yukikaze</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Yukikaze</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Yukikaze</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">전투요정 유키카제</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2857" type="Other">Sentou Yousei Shoujo Tasukete! Maeve-chan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5310" approval="7" total="10">Sky Crawlers</anime>
<anime id="673" approval="2" total="7">Texhnolyze</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="220389">This will keep u in a rush. Not bad at all.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="471741">Military sci fi &amp; action greatness of epic proportions. Transformercraft and mecha should be ashamed :D
Probably the best technofantasy (realistic flavoured!) animation out there.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="441125">I should have watched this years ago! 
And if you are reading this - do not repeat my mistake.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.faf.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="735" type="Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="1135" type="Original Work">Kanbayashi Chouhei</name>
<name id="1519" type="Series Composition">Yamaguchi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="6530" type="Direction">Ookura Masahiko</name>
<name id="1604" type="Animation Character Design">Aizawa Masahiro</name>
<name id="9620" type="Animation Character Design">Hashimoto Kouichi</name>
<name id="27923" type="Character Design">Tada Yumi</name>
<name id="26059" type="Music">Mishiba Satoshi</name>
<name id="31530" type="Music">Shiono Dougen</name>
</creators>
<description>Thirty-three years ago, an alien force known as the "JAM" invaded Earth through a dimensional portal over Antarctica. Earth`s forces managed to drive the JAM back through the portal to their home planet designated as "Fairy." While majority of Earth`s population is unaware of the JAM`s presence, the war continues on Fairy.
Sentou Yousei Yukikaze chronicles the life of http://anidb.net/ch9586 [Fukai Rei], an SAF (Special Air Force) pilot assigned to pilot "Yukikaze" - an advanced reconnaisance fighter plane equipped with a near-sentient A.I. that detects the presence of the JAM within its path.
Source: ANN (edited)</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1609">6.51</permanent>
<temporary count="1629">7.53</temporary>
<review count="4">7.62</review>
</ratings>
<picture>222111.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>902</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1080</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2418</identifier>
<identifier>xijmvv</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>917</identifier>
<identifier>hetkuu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jvcmusic.co.jp/flyingdog/yukikaze/top.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.faf.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yukikaze_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>戦闘妖精・雪風#OVA.E7.89.88</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>387</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239229</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5685</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/141</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8193</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="355" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-30">
<name>wings</name>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1528" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-12">
<name>artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligence of machines and the branch of computer science that aims to create it. AI textbooks define the field as "the study and design of intelligent agents" where an intelligent agent is a system that perceives its environment and takes actions that maximize its chances of success. John McCarthy, who coined the term in 1956, defines it as "the science and engineering of making intelligent machines."
The field was founded on the claim that a central property of humans, intelligence—the sapience of Homo sapiens—can be so precisely described that it can be simulated by a machine. This raises philosophical issues about the nature of the mind and the ethics of creating artificial beings, issues which have been addressed by myth, fiction and philosophy since antiquity. Artificial intelligence has been the subject of optimism, but has also suffered setbacks and, today, has become an essential part of the technology industry, providing the heavy lifting for many of the most difficult problems in computer science.
AI research is highly technical and specialized, and deeply divided into subfields that often fail to communicate with each other. Subfields have grown up around particular institutions, the work of individual researchers, the solution of specific problems, longstanding differences of opinion about how AI should be done and the application of widely differing tools. The central problems of AI include such traits as reasoning, knowledge, planning, learning, communication, perception and the ability to move and manipulate objects. General intelligence (or "strong AI") is still among the field`s long term goals.</description>
<picurl>71305.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2968" parentid="4831" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-05">
<name>faceless alien invasion</name>
<description>Uncommunicative, faceless aliens suddenly invade Earth from outer space or a parallel world thus causing a war with humans.
If the humans are lucky, the invasion may go off without a war that would cause untold destruction and death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3421" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-03">
<name>aviation</name>
<description>"These magnificant men in their flying machines"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3815" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>human cannibalism</name>
<description>Cannibalism is the practice of an individual of a species eating parts or the whole of another individual of the same species; as such, human cannibalism is when a human eats the flesh, organs, or other parts of another human being.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9586" type="main character in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="4">2.40</rating>
<name>Fukai Rei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5233" picture="29252.jpg">Sakai Masato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9587" type="appears in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="4">10.00</rating>
<name>Yukikaze</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>63728.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17926" type="main character in" update="2010-05-30">
<rating votes="3">5.35</rating>
<name>James Bukhar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17934" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="3">3.75</rating>
<name>Lynn Jackson</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3703" picture="151656.jpg">Ikeda Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17935" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="3">3.00</rating>
<name>Lydia Cooley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3697" picture="78864.jpg">Asagami Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17936" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="3">3.75</rating>
<name>Edith Foss</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17939" type="appears in" update="2010-05-22">
<rating votes="3">5.04</rating>
<name>Tom John</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18224" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-30">
<rating votes="3">1.96</rating>
<name>Ansel Rombert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>48791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18226" type="appears in" update="2010-07-12">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Richard Burgadish</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Richard Burgadish served as one of Rei`s radar officers.</description>
<picture>51061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="294" picture="53586.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18231" type="appears in" update="2010-07-11">
<rating votes="2">1.09</rating>
<name>Hiroshi Yazawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiroshi Yazawa was a major at forward base TAB-14.
He was cloned by the JAM in an attempt to extract information from Rei regarding Yukikaze</description>
<picture>51058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3102" picture="24178.jpg">Chou Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18232" type="appears in" update="2010-07-11">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Marnie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marnie was a nurse at forward base TAB-14.
Like http://anidb.net/ch18231 [Major Yazawa], she was cloned by the JAM in an attempt to extract information from Rei regarding Yukikaze</description>
<picture>51059.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19517" type="appears in" update="2010-07-11">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Carl Gunow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Carl Gunow was a colonel in the System Corps. He was in charge of the unmanned fighter development program, FRX-99.</description>
<picture>51077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19523" type="appears in" update="2010-07-11">
<name>Gavin Mayle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3315" picture="196861.jpg">Mizuuchi Kiyomitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19524" type="appears in" update="2010-07-12">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Norman Hughes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Norman Hughes is Rei`s radar officer in the Super Sylph.</description>
<picture>51079.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41711" type="appears in" update="2012-02-26">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>FFR-31MR/D Super Sylph</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The FFR-31MR/D Super Sylph is a high speed tactical recon plane. Although its model number makes it look like a variant of the FFR-31 Sylphide, the design and the capabilities are completely different. The FFR-31MR/D further improved aerodynamics to reduce friction at high speeds and improved manoeuvrability. There are hardpoints for air-to-air missiles under the wing and the engine pod on the belly. It was originally developed as an unarmed recon plane but after lessons learned in the early stages of combat on planet Fairy, it was decided that this plane should have weapons for self defence. The D model has the same sensor and datalink performance as the original FFR-31MR. Like the B and C models, the D can be fitted with a sensor pod called the TARPS (Tactical Airborne Reconnaissance Pod System). Depending on the mission, a TARPS can be configured with cameras, infrared sensors, imaging radar, or multi-band ESM (Electronic Support Measures - used to detect, intercept, identify, locate, record, and/or analyse sources of radiated electromagnetic energy for the purposes of immediate threat recognition). The D model has a more compact TARPS than those used on the B and C models.
Originally, the D model was designed to be a tactical recon plane like the original FFR-31MR. However the ramjet booster on the D model was expected to improve speed so most of the produced D models are high speed strategic recon planes. However, there are some planes without the ramjet boosters. They were not fitted with ramjet boosters because of testing purposes and other reasons. It was suspected that the main reason why they were not fitted with boosters is because of financial restrictions.
It is well known that the FAF often changes their plans while the plane is in construction or being developed. The D model production had difficulties in funding. The reason why is that the serial number of the D model is dispersed among the ordinary FFR-31MR models. It is very difficult to determine how many D models are produced even though the serial numbers are not classified. However, most of the D models are stationed at the FAF Aeronautical Space Defence Agency Defense Reconnaissance Wing and conduct recon missions on planet Fairy and airspace under JAM control. Based on this information, only 5 to 7 D models are in service.
The Super Sylph flown by Rei for the first half of the story is named Yukikaze.
Technical specifications
Manufacturer: Fairy Air Force (FAF)
Accommodation: Pilot and co-pilot in separate cockpits
Total Length: 22m
Wingspan: 13.2m
Total Height: 6.25m; with TARPS activated 9.75m
Weight: empty 12,188 kg; standard mission 25,500 kg; maximum 37,890 kg
Powerplant Type: FNX-5011-D Phoenix MK XI D turbofan x2; optional ramjet booster
Powerplant Output: 10,220 kg; afterburner 14,480 kg; ramjet output unknown
Speed: cruise Mach 1.7; max Mach 3.2 (at 16,000m, Earth`s atmosphere)
Fuselage Load Limit: 9g+
Maximum Altitude: 24,000m (Earth`s atmosphere)
Armament:
* 1x 20mm Gatling gun

* 2x hardpoint under-wing

* 2x hardpoint fuselage engine pod

* Can take the following missiles:

[ul]* Short-range air-to-air missile AAM-III

* Medium-range air-to-air missile AAM-V

* Long-range air-to-air missile AAM-VII

* Ultra-high-speed air-to-air missile HAM
[/ul]
Equipment: TARPS, real time digital data link, Yukikaze AI system
Adapted from Gears Online (http://www.gearsonline.net/series/yukikaze/super-sylph/super-sylph-d.html) and JP wiki.</description>
<picture>82143.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41712" type="appears in" update="2012-02-25">
<name>FA-1 Fern I</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The FA-1 Fern was the tactical mainstay of the FAF. The original FA-1 was already in service at the time of the first JAM incursion, and served to stem the assault. The aircraft design featured forward-swept wings and twin vertical and horizontal stabilizers for an overall "3 surface" system. In addition, a forward vertical canard allowed for the direct control of lateral force on the underside. The turbofan engine had a vectored-thrust nozzle. In combination, these features served to give the FA-1 excellent lateral mobility and manouevrability.
As indicated by its primary designation, the FA-1 served as a multi-role air superiority and ground attack aircraft. While the FA-1 started as a capable opponent for the JAM, later model JAM craft acquired the upper hand and the role of air superiority was ceded to the http://anidb.net/ch41714 [FFR-31 Sylphide] and the http://anidb.net/ch41713 [FA-2 Fern II]. In spite of its obsolescence, the cost of procurement of the FFR-31 led to the continued deployment of the FA-1 with the 442nd Tactical Fighter Squadron in its air superiority role.
The FA-1 has several variants, including the single-seat type A/B and the twin-seat type C/D trainers. The FA-1 type B featured increased load and range capabilities and upgraded avionics. The twin-seat type C trainer was later modified to suppress enemy radar and anti-aircraft artillery/SAM batteries. In this role, it was designated the FA-1 C (SEAD) and was colloquially known as the Fairy Weasel (note: SEAD stands for Suppression of Enemy Air Defenses and SEAD attacks are sometimes called "wild weasel" missions). Total FA-1 production across all types amounts to 1,042. About half of these are deployed to the FAF Air Wings.
Technical Specifications
Manufacturer: Japan Air Self-Defence Force (JASDF)
Accommodation: pilot
Total Length: 16.45m
Wingspan: 11.56m
Total Height: 4.83m
Weight: empty 11,876 kg; standard air-superiority mission 16,662 kg; maximum takeoff 24,669 kg
Powerplant Type: FNX-5010-K turbofan x1
Powerplant Output: 8,221kg; afterburner 12,877kg (within Earth`s atmosphere)
Speed: cruise Mach 0.8; max Mach 2.1 (at 11,940m within Earth`s atmosphere)
Fuselage Load Limit: 9g
Maximum Altitude: 17,700m (within Earth`s atmosphere)
Armament:* 1x 20mm Gatling gun

* 7x hardpoint (4 wing, 3 fuselage) carrying a maximum of 5,800kg of precision-guided munitions such as AAMs and ASMs
</description>
<picture>82194.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41713" type="appears in" update="2012-02-25">
<name>FA-2 Fern II</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The FA-2 Fern II was designed by the FAF as a replacement for the aging http://anidb.net/ch41712 [FA-1]. It serves in a high-manoeuvrability air superiority role.
Technical Specifications
Manufacturer: Fairy Air Force (FAF)
Accommodation: pilot
Total Length: 15.16m
Wingspan: 12.6m
Total Height: 4.76m
Weight: empty 11,022kg; standard air-superiority mission 16,112kg
Powerplant Type: FNX-5010-K Phoenix Mk.XI F turbofan x1
Powerplant Output: 10,220kg; afterburner 14,780kg
Speed: cruise Mach 0.9; max Mach 1.8
Fuselage Load Limit: 9g+
Maximum Altitude: 20,880m
Armament:* 1x 20mm Gatling gun

* 5x hardpoint (2 wing, 3 fuselage) carrying a variety of precision-guided munitions
</description>
<picture>82195.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41714" type="appears in" update="2012-02-26">
<name>FFR-31 Sylphide</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The FFR-31 Sylphide (Sylph) is the flagship air superiority fighter of the Fairy Air Force (FAF). Featuring a clipped "3-surface" delta design with forward canards and twin vertical/horizontal stabilisers along with twin engines with vectored-thrust nozzles, the Sylphide is an aircraft that can perform equally well in supersonic cruise or dogfight manoeuvres. Nicknamed the "Fairy of the Wind" (風の妖精, Kaze no Yousei), the Sylphide is the mainstay of the FAF.
The original program called for a long-range interceptor armed with long-range AAMs, but this role was changed during development to include capacity for melee combat. The FFR-31 showed its class immediately upon introduction in to the war on Fairy. After introduction, it received a series of upgrades to its avionics, control surfaces, control software and also to its weapon-carrying ability. These improvements, collectively known as the Sylphide Enhancement Experiments (SEEX/SEX) were originally to consist of 13 stages, starting from 0 (baseline) through 12. The actual program was only executed up to stage 9.
While boasting exceptional performance compared to other aircraft, the FFR-31 Sylphide suffered from an extremely high per-aircraft procurement cost. The first production run, consisting of blocks 0-10 and including flight test prototypes, amounted to only 94 machines. Of these, only 49 were fielded in three Air Wings, as per FAF doctrine. Though scarce in deployment, the FFR-31 wings acquired a legendary reputation, especially the 526th Tactical Fighter Squadron known as "Ghoul Squadron".
Due to the desperate need for air superiority as provided by the FFR-31, a second production run of 113 machines was commissioned, consisting of blocks 11-20. To reduce procurement costs, various small accessories and upgrades were omitted, the top speed was slightly reduced etc. While each such simplification was minor in itself, the cumulative effect was to make the 2nd run machines unpopular with FAF personnel, who referred to the block 0-10 machines as the "original Sylphide".
While it shares its major designation with the http://anidb.net/ch41711 [FFR-31MR/A-D Super Sylph], there is very little in common between the two aircraft.
Technical Specifications
Manufacturer Fairy Air Force (FAF)
Accommodation: pilot
Total Length: 18.5m
Wingspan: 13.77m
Total Height: 5.01m
Weight: empty 11,876kg; maximum 35,660kg
Powerplant Type: 2x FNX-5010-H/J Phoenix Mk.X turbofan
Powerplant Output: 9,677kg; afterburner 12,644kg (within the Earth`s atmosphere)
Speed: cruise Mach 1.4; max Mach 2.7 (at 14,400m within the Earth`s atmosphere)
Fuselage Load Limit: 9g+
Maximum Altitude: 18,000 meters
Armament:* 1x 20mm Gatling gun

* 7x internal hardpoint (weapons bay, usually used for AAMs)

* 2x external hardpoint (usually used for drop tanks)
</description>
<picture>82151.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41715" type="appears in" update="2012-02-25">
<name>FRX-00/FFR-41 Maeve</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>82199.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41716" type="appears in" update="2012-02-25">
<name>FRX-99 Rafe</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>82201.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41717" type="appears in" update="2012-02-26">
<name>AAC Banshee</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The AAC Banshee is a nuclear-powered airborne aircraft carrier and mother ship. The first two prototypes, Banshee I and Banshee II, were ground-based and used to prove the platform systems. Banshee III and Banshee IV were commissioned as AAC-03 and AAC-04 respectively. As with naval aircraft carriers, the Banshee platform serves as a mother ship deploying a host of smaller aircraft providing umbrella air cover over a wide area. One unique feature of the Banshee is that it is not expected to ever land during normal operation. Nuclear-powered as they are, the Banshees operate as semi-permanent satellites of Fairy.
The Banshee is broadly divided into 3 decks: top, middle and lower. The top deck houses anti-aircraft batteries, the command and control centres and the crew quarters. In addition to the residential areas, the living quarters include cafeterias and medical facilities, and the overall standard of living is relatively high.
The middle deck contains hangars, the propulsion systems and the take-off and landing bays. The runway is mounted in the centre of the fuselage. The landing arrestor system works by snagging the front wheel of fighter and transport aircraft and an internal counterbalance is used to avoid sudden changes in the centre of gravity when a large craft lands/takes off. The lower deck houses anti-aircraft batteries, the nuclear reactors, more hangars and more take-off bays.
Original plans called for the operation of 4 airborne Banshee-class ships, but construction budget delays and the observation that two Banshees were sufficient to defend FAF airspace led to the cancellation of Banshee V and Banshee VI.
Technical Specifications
Manufacturer: Fairy Air Force (FAF)
Total Length: 687m
Total Width: 1,400m
Weight: 409,650t
Propulsion: Nuclear-powered turbofan engine x16</description>
<picture>82190.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41746" type="appears in" update="2012-02-25">
<name>Kisha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41747" type="appears in" update="2012-02-25">
<name>Ishikawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Liaison officer on board the Admiral.</description>
<picture>82212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2207" picture="41549.jpg">Makishima Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41748" type="appears in" update="2012-02-25">
<name>Nagumo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41749" type="appears in" update="2012-02-26">
<name>F/A-27C</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The F/A-27C is the primary fighter-attack aircraft fielded by the Imperial Japanese Navy. A single-seat, single-engine design featuring forward canards, twin vertical/horizontal stabilizers, a vectored-thrust engine nozzle and generous weapon carrying ability, the F/A-27C is a versatile aircraft. Designed and manufactured 100% in Japan, the cost of procurement per plane spiralled out of control and is rumoured to be the same as that of a FAF FFR-31 Super Sylph.
The type C is the carrier variant of the Air Force F/A-27A. A STOVL ground attack version, the F/A-27B, was planned for the Army, but was eventually cancelled due to turf wars between the Army and the Air Force.
Technical Specifications
Manufacturer: Japan Air Self-Defence Force (JASDF)
Accommodation: pilot
Length: 16.04m
Wingspan: 11.76m
Height: 2.80m
Weight: empty 12,040kg; 18,998kg gross weight
Powerplan Type: MHF-1180-JF turbofan engine 1x
Powerplant Output: 9,778kg; after-burner 11,030kg
Speed: cruise Mach 0.88; top speed Mach 1.8 (at 12,000m)
Fuselage Load Limit: 9g+
Maximum Altitude: 21,200m
Armament:* 1x 20mm Gatling gun

* 6x hardpoint capable of carrying guided missiles/bombs, recon pods or drop tanks
</description>
<picture>82217.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="41750" type="appears in" update="2012-02-25">
<name>Admiral 56</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>The Admiral 56 is the sole nuclear-powered aircraft carrier in service with the Imperial Japanese Navy. It is similar to the US Navy Hillary Clinton class or the English-Australian Eagle class or the joint European developed Graf Zeppelin class carriers. The original plan called for a single common carrier design, but varying national requirements, budget constraints and build times led to many variants.
The angled flight deck is positioned identically to the USN Hillary Clinton. The design of the Admiral 56 incorporates active stealth and advanced ECM. Unique among its sister ships, it incorporates a Vertical Launch System (VLS) for anti-aircraft missiles, located behind the island. Equipped with a stream catapult, the Admiral 56 normally houses about 80 http://anidb.net/ch41749 [F/A-27C] fighter aircraft.
Technical Specifications
Displacement: empty 89,000t; maximum 123,000t
Length: 390m
Width: maximum 110m; flight deck 85m
Height: 80m; draft 12m
Weight: empty 12,040kg; 18,998kg gross weight
Powerplan Type: 8x pressurised water reactors, 4x steam-turbine generators, 8x 4-axis motors
Powerplant Output: 298,000hp
Speed: 30kn
Crew: 3,200
Aircraft: ~80
Armament: 4x anti-aircraft missile PDS, 4x CIWS</description>
<picture>82218.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="578" update="2012-10-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2002-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation 1</title>
<summary>The human race has beaten an invasion by an alien race called the JAM back to its home planet Fairy. Fairy Air Force, the UN-mandated military organization tasked with neutralizing and eventually eliminating the alien threat, assigns and armed strategic reconnaissance aircraft codenamed "Yukikaze" and equipped with an AI to Lt. Rei Fukai of the subordinate Special Air Force with the intention to record data on JAM movements and battlefield tactics. One day, however, an encounter with the "Grey Sylph" (a JAM duplicate of the Yukikaze) lands him in hot water with his superiors. During another patrol, Fukai is captured by JAM clones wanting to study the plane. He kills one of his captors and escapes with the plane from an alien entity disguised as a FAF forward airbase but ends up being pursued and shot down by the "Grey Sylph". As the "Grey Sylph" attempts to finish off Fukai`s aircraft, the Yukikaze AI hijacks an FRX-99, a prototype UCAV that was undergoing operational tests at that time, and uses it to destroy the "Grey Sylph". The AI uploads its files to the FRX-99, ejects Fukai, and obliterates</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6556" update="2012-10-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2003-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation 2</title>
<summary>The ordeals from the previous mission leaves Rei Fukai in a catatonic state, which proves short-lived when he responds to the Yukikaze AI, now transferred into the prototype FRX-00 Mave (a manned version of the FRX-99 that has been equipped with a countermeasure system to detect JAM computer infiltrations), as the latter strafes a FAF tactical airfield that it identifies as a JAM entity during a test flight. This and several suspected acts of sabotage made on other FAF aircraft raise alarms to some FAF officials, including Brigadier General Cooley, on possible JAM infiltrations. She assigns Rei to the prototype Mave under the observations of Edith Foss, who will soon have an opportunity to profile both Rei and Yukikaze under combat situations.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="9205" update="2013-05-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 0</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11641" update="2012-10-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2003-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation 3</title>
<summary>Rei and another Fairy Air Force crewmember investigate a Banshee flying aircraft carrier that opened fire on friendly forces prior. Further inspection on the seemingly-deserted carrier reveals that it is being used by JAM to create human clones. When transmission of their finding triggers the FAF`s computerized command and control system into launching a SRBM to destroy the Banshee, Rei escapes, but his companion, upon discovery that he himself is a JAM clone, elects to stay behind onboard the doomed air fortress.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="19459" update="2012-10-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2004-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation 4</title>
<summary>Rei and Yukikaze fly back to Earth to test the plane`s new engines but JAM forces follow them out of the portal. An Earth-borne Japanese Navy aircraft carrier battlegroup, mistaking the JAM attackers for unauthorized FAF aircraft, is taken by surprise and quickly fall into disarray. The Admiral, the Japanese flagship, is only saved from a final ramming attempt by the aliens by Rei`s timely intervention. The Yukikaze is forced to land on the Admiral for refueling, and it is right there Rei would find out how ignorant Earth has become to the war raging on Fairy.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="36685" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37569" update="2012-10-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2005-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation 5</title>
<summary>Concluding that planet Fairy is in fact the collective of JAM itself and that JAM infiltrators are on the eve of starting a mutiny, the FAF devises a plan to lure JAM infiltrators into a trap while pulling the rest of their forces out of Fairy. In response, JAM arrays its entire fighting force between the FAF and their portal of escape and hijacks some of the FAF`s UCAVs, causing chaos within FAF formations. Intent on settling scores with JAM, who have repeatedly tried to hack the Yukikaze AI, Rei Fukai and the AI launch in one final sortie to escort nuclear weapons into the heart of the JAM collective, giving the FAF the opening they need to escape and seemingly sacrificing themselves in the process.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="44677" update="2015-01-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of</title>
<summary>A live action commentary about the aircraft designs.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="53685" update="2015-01-28">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>75</length>
<airdate>2005-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">FAF航空戦史</title>
<title xml:lang="en">FAF Aviation Military History</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">FAF Koukuu Senshi</title>
<summary>Contains interviews with main staff and scenes from the anime with special editing.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="86087" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Undetermined Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86088" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Undetermined Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86089" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Undetermined Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86090" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Undetermined Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86091" update="2015-01-28">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CMs</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86092" update="2015-01-28">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CMs 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86093" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Undetermined Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86094" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Undetermined Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121114" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121115" update="2010-08-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134252" update="2015-01-28">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150328" update="2013-05-04">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦闘妖精雪風 EXPERIMENTAL MOVIE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sentou Yousei Yukikaze: Experimental Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentou Yousei Yukikaze: Experimental Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
