<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11110" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>2015-09-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aoharu x Kikanjuu</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Млади и въоръжени</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">青春x機関銃</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Aoharu x Machinegun</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Aoharu x Machinegun</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">青春x机关枪</title>
</titles>
<url>http://twitter.com/aoharu_anime</url>
<creators>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="5795" type="Character Design">Yamanaka Junko</name>
<name id="18012" type="Direction">Nakano Hideaki</name>
<name id="5795" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamanaka Junko</name>
<name id="8625" type="Series Composition">Konuta Kenji</name>
<name id="34207" type="Music">Tachibana Asami</name>
<name id="43416" type="Original Work">Naoe</name>
</creators>
<description>The high school student http://anidb.net/ch74008 [Tachibana Hotaru] is a girl disguised as a boy. Through strange circumstances she finds herself drawn into the world of survival games by a host, http://anidb.net/ch74007 [Matsuoka Masamune]. The two form a team with ero-manga artist http://anidb.net/ch74009 [Yukimura Tooru] and aim to become the best in Japan.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="864">3.94</permanent>
<temporary count="869">6.06</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>175430.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16816</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31754</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>30205</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/aoharu/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Aoharu_x_Kikanjū</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>青春×機関銃</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3807</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352403</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18265</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>aoharu_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2978" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-28">
<name>aim for the top</name>
<description>This can be a positive or negative plot device. A character may strive to become the best in an altruistic way (e.g. best healer, most widely learned master), or it can be quite banal and primitive (e.g. challenged delinquents wanting to be the strongest fighters).
Alas in fighting anime the latter usually prevails.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="74007" type="main character in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="3">4.90</rating>
<name>Matsuoka Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74008" type="main character in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="7">6.60</rating>
<name>Tachibana Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74009" type="main character in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="4">5.04</rating>
<name>Yukimura Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75276" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="4">3.53</rating>
<name>Midori Nagamasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75277" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="5">4.40</rating>
<name>Akabane Ichi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75785" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="3">6.73</rating>
<name>Yajima Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76172" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="2">5.74</rating>
<name>Fujimoto Takatora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175123.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77560" type="appears in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Sagara Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77561" type="appears in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Usagi Toshizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77562" type="appears in" update="2015-09-25">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Kamenashi Souji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>177913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="169256" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こいつはあの大会には向いてねぇよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He`s Not Cut Out for That Tournament</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koitsu wa Ano Taikai ni Muitenee yo</title>
<summary>Having acquired her very own gun, Tachibana excitedly participates in survival games. However, when Tachibana can`t follow Matsuoka`s orders, she finds herself placed on the opposing team...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682045</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169257" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最高の戦友[パートナー]になるんだからよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`ll Become Your Greatest Partner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou no Partner ni Narunda kara yo</title>
<summary>Unable to suppress her desire to play survival games with Matsuoka and Yukimura, Tachibana returns to the team. Matsuoka sends Tachibana to buy her very own gun, but what trials will she find waiting for her there...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682043</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169258" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仲間なんて要らないって言ったよね?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Didn`t I Tell You I Don`t Need Friends?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakama Nante Iranaitte Itta yo ne?</title>
<summary>Tachibana joins Matsuoka`s survival game team, but one of the members, Yukimura Tohru, has mixed feelings about Tachibana.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682041</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169259" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死なない殺し合いを始めようか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Start This Deathless Death Match</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinanai Koroshiai o Hajimeyouka</title>
<summary>Hotaru Tachibana is the righteous student council president. He has a poor impression of his new neighbor, Matsuoka Masamune.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682039</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169525" update="2015-07-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169526" update="2015-07-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169943" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今, 君の心を支配するもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Controls Your Mind Now</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima, Kimi no Kokoro o Shihaisuru Mono</title>
<summary>Matsuoka suffers a dismal defeat against Midori. Yukimura attempts to avenge him, but he does not stand a chance against Midori, and he tastes humiliation as well. The success of the team comes down to Tachibana`s battle against Midori.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682053</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169944" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その希望, 早くブチ壊してあげなきゃね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`ll Have to Crush That Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Kibou, Hayaku Buchikowashite Agenakya ne</title>
<summary>Learning of Matsuoka`s past from Yukimura, Tachibana decides she will try to change Matsuoka through her efforts at TGC. Their showdown against their old enemy, Team Hoshishiro, has begun.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682051</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169945" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐が, 来る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Storm Is Coming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi ga, Kuru</title>
<summary>Learning of Matsuoka`s past from Yukimura, Tachibana decides she will try to change Matsuoka through her efforts at TGC. Their showdown against their old enemy, Team Hoshishiro, has begun.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682049</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169946" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">このチームを抜けたくないっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Don`t Want to Leave the Team!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Team o Nuketakunai!</title>
<summary>When Tachibana learns Matusoka`s true feelings, she does her best to rejoin the team. However, Toy Gun Gun doesn`t allow female members--
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682047</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170622" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この人たちと一緒に戦いたいっ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Fight with These People</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Hitotachi to Issho ni Tatakaitai</title>
<summary>Tachibana resolves to tell her teammates she is a girl, but she finds herself unable to tell them. For some reason they hold a grilling party in Yukimura`s apartment, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682057</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170623" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">だから私はかっこいいっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s What Makes Me Cool!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakara Watashi wa Kakkoii!!</title>
<summary>Depressed after her loss at TGC, Tachibana tells her friend Kanae that she`s going to quit survival games. Kanae suggests a plan to help cheer her up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682055</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170779" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この場所は譲らないっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Won`t Yield!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Basho wa Yuzuranai!</title>
<summary>Tachibana reserves the survival game field and challenges Matsuoka to a one-on-one. As Tachibana stubbornly faces Matsuoka again and again after countless losses, her determination begins to melt his heart...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682061</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170780" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いいこと, しましょうか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Do Something Fun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ii Koto, Shimashouka</title>
<summary>After finishing her shooting match against Midori, Tachibana returns to her apartment to find Yukimura waiting for her. What happened in Toy Gun Gun`s past? When Tachibana learns the truth, what will she do?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682059</identifier>
<identifier>aoharu-x-machinegun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173755" update="2015-12-12">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">獣たちの戦場だなっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is a Battlefield for Beasts!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kemono-tachi no Senjou Da na!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
