<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11124" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2015-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yuru Yuri San Hai!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゆるゆり さん☆ハイ!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">摇曳百合 3☆High!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11276" type="Prequel">Yuru Yuri Nachuyachumi!+</anime>
<anime id="14047" type="Other">Yuru Yuri Ten</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="502713">As per the ratings show, this is the best season yet, took a while but the studio finally graduated from elementary school levels of production, Akari isn`t getting the short end of the stick every episode anymore, there isn`t an overplayed nosebleed/sexual fantasy scene every 10 seconds anymore, stuff doesn`t randomly and unrealistically blow up anymore, etc. 
They got rid of most of the stupid stuff so the anime is finally starting to become a true slice of life anime, and hell, by the very end even Kyouko becomes sorta likeable too.
There are still a lot of problems (obviously), some of the characters are way to immature and therefor annoying (for their age), some resemblance of a story wouldn`t hurt either and i`m not sure why they even added romance if they were never gonna do anything with it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://yuruyuri.com/3hai/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9212" type="Animation Work">TYO Animations</name>
<name id="7900" type="Character Design">Taniguchi Motohiro</name>
<name id="27337" type="Original Work">Namori</name>
<name id="15782" type="Direction">Hata Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="7900" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Motohiro</name>
<name id="34196" type="Series Composition">Fukami Makoto</name>
<name id="15782" type="Series Composition">Hata Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga series written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr27337 [Namori], serialised in Comic Yuri Hime S from June 12, 2008, before being moved over to http://anidb.net/cr34017 [Comic Yuri Hime] in September 2010.
The Amusement Club foursome — http://anidb.net/ch31745 [Akari], http://anidb.net/ch31744 [Yui], http://anidb.net/ch31742 [Kyouko], and http://anidb.net/ch31739 [Chinatsu] — continue their lively activities at the all-girls Nanamori Private Middle School, still occupying the picturesque former tea ceremony club`s outbuilding, next to a small pond. Together with the quirky student council — http://anidb.net/ch31741 [Ayano], http://anidb.net/ch31743 [Chitose], http://anidb.net/ch31738 [Himawari], and http://anidb.net/ch31740 [Sakurako] — not an uneventful day passes by.
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="999">7.43</permanent>
<temporary count="1004">7.57</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>239976.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16843</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30279</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://yuruyuri.com/3hai/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/yuruyuri3/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>YuruYuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゆるゆり</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3884</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352240</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18472</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2758" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-05">
<name>volleyball</name>
<description>Volleyball is a team sport in which two teams of six players are separated by a net. Each team tries to score points by grounding a ball on the other team`s court under organized rules.
Use the http://anidb.net/t7147 [competitive beach volleyball] tag for competition or professional beach volleyball play. Use the http://anidb.net/t6478 [beach volleyball episode] tag when the beach volleyball game is a one-off event, such as during a beach or pool visit.</description>
<picurl>221599.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4030" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-13">
<name>mental cinema</name>
<description>The ability to imagine all kinds of things, as if they were real.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5276" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-25">
<name>typhoon</name>
<description>A typhoon is a mature tropical cyclone that develops in the north-western part of the Pacific Ocean between 180° and 100°E. This region is referred to as the north-west Pacific basin. Identical phenomena in the eastern north Pacific are called hurricanes, with tropical cyclones moving into the western Pacific re-designated as typhoons.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6577" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-17">
<name>student government</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="31738" type="main character in" update="2019-01-12">
<rating votes="129">6.86</rating>
<name>Furutani Himawari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31739" type="main character in" update="2012-08-07">
<rating votes="133">5.07</rating>
<name>Yoshikawa Chinatsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31740" type="main character in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="170">6.92</rating>
<name>Oomuro Sakurako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31741" type="main character in" update="2011-05-09">
<rating votes="174">8.18</rating>
<name>Sugiura Ayano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31742" type="main character in" update="2012-08-07">
<rating votes="256">8.37</rating>
<name>Toshinou Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31743" type="main character in" update="2019-01-02">
<rating votes="149">6.89</rating>
<name>Ikeda Chitose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31744" type="main character in" update="2012-08-07">
<rating votes="159">6.86</rating>
<name>Funami Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21823" picture="131326.jpg">Tsuda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31745" type="main character in" update="2012-08-07">
<rating votes="217">7.46</rating>
<name>Akaza Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4007" picture="25937.jpg">Mikami Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33211" type="appears in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="22">4.82</rating>
<name>Miraclerun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35571" type="appears in" update="2011-08-13">
<rating votes="58">7.70</rating>
<name>Furutani Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>44681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35953" type="appears in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="4">2.19</rating>
<name>Ganboo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35954" type="appears in" update="2012-03-04">
<rating votes="13">5.40</rating>
<name>Rivalun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35958" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="43">7.27</rating>
<name>Funami Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35965" type="appears in" update="2012-08-19">
<rating votes="21">6.52</rating>
<name>Yoshikawa Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8996" picture="151657.jpg">Ishikawa Ayano</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35966" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-23">
<rating votes="52">4.37</rating>
<name>Ikeda Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29681" picture="78340.jpg">Kuraguchi Momo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36111" type="appears in" update="2012-02-23">
<rating votes="66">7.35</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Rise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36113" type="appears in" update="2012-02-23">
<rating votes="24">7.01</rating>
<name>Nishigaki Nana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46956" type="appears in" update="2012-08-19">
<rating votes="18">6.66</rating>
<name>Oomuro Nadeshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46957" type="appears in" update="2012-08-19">
<rating votes="22">6.41</rating>
<name>Oomuro Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47801" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-13">
<rating votes="40">7.94</rating>
<name>Akaza Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79079" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<name>Dezaki Takane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29400" picture="157186.jpg">Yamaguchi Rikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79080" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="3">3.85</rating>
<name>Kitamiya Hatsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79081" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="3">3.85</rating>
<name>Azuma Shihoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38750" picture="145599.jpg">Hashimoto Chinami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79082" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Minamino Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24615" picture="73810.jpg">Watanabe Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79083" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="2">5.77</rating>
<name>Raika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79084" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="3">5.88</rating>
<name>Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79085" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Yoshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37896" picture="138980.jpg">Hatanaka Marie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79086" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<name>Akemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180700.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43472" picture="175837.jpg">Shimogama Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79087" type="appears in" update="2015-12-23">
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<name>Koyama Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="171843" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その夜は, みんなの想いをつないでゆく.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Night Will Bring Them Together</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cette nuit, on resserre nos liens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Yoru wa, Minna no Omoi o Tsunaide Yuku.</title>
<summary>Hello, everyone. This is Akari`s sister Akaza Akane. Thank you for looking after Akari. Akari`s so cute. She`s always such an angel. She`s the apple of my eye. I could do this to Akari`s that, and... Oh, excuse me. My friends are coming over today. I must get ready.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686347</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="171844" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自覚無し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Self-Awareness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Par inadvertance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jikaku Nashi</title>
<summary>Tada! Omuro Sakurako-sama has arrived! Has everyone been doing well? I`m always full of energy! Come to think of it, the other day I studied with Himawari. I think Himawari`s... uh... b-breasts might have gotten bigger again... Argh! She even lectured me, too. Okay, I`ve got a good idea!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686345</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="171845" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さぁおびえるがいい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tremble in Fear</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tremblez, maintenant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saa Obieru ga Ii</title>
<summary>S-Sugiura Ayano here! No one told me it was my turn to do this! I`m glad to be back here with everyone. I-I didn`t come back here for you! But thanks for waiting! Huh? My mom`s calling me. What could it be...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686343</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="171846" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは, すなわち, 娯楽の始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Is the Beginning of Amusement</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et là, maintenant, place au fun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa, Sunawachi, Goraku no Hajimari</title>
<summary>Yuru Yuri`s protagonist Akaza Akari here!! Yuri Yuri has returned to TV!
Since summer vacation is over and school is starting, I hope to have lots of fun with the members of the Amusement Club! Now let`s head to the club room!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686341</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172402" update="2015-10-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172403" update="2015-10-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172699" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは, 誰もが手にする笑顔のカケラ.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Is the Piece of a Smile Everyone Acquires</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce qu`on peut tous obtenir, un fragment de sourire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa, Daremo ga Te ni Suru Egao no Kakera.</title>
<summary>・・・・・・・・・・・・。・・・・・・・・・・・・・・。 ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・。
・・・・・、・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・。・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・。
(Student council president Matsumoto Rise here. I`m glad to see all of you.
Since I apparently have a turn as well, I`d appreciate your continued support.
Come to think of it, Nishigaki-sensei has a new colleague. I hope you`ll enjoy it.)
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686355</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172700" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忘れられない一日になる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Will Be an Unforgettable Day</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce sera une journée inoubliable</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wasurerarenai Ichinichi ni Naru</title>
<summary>Ha ha ha! Yuru Yuri`s true protagonist Toshino Kyoko here! I know I`m a bit late, but did everyone wait like good girls and boys? The Amusement Club is off to defeat new enemies, so come along! What? That`s not in the script? Too bad.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686353</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172701" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見えない顔は, 其処にある.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Invisible Face Is There</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un visage invisible se trouve ici</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mienai Kao wa, Soko ni Aru.</title>
<summary>Yoshikawa Chinatsu here. Seeing Yui-senpai doing this and that, I`m just... overjoyed! I suppose I can let the rest of you take a peek as well! I`ve invited Yui-senpai to my house again today. I`d better dress myself up!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686351</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172702" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女は, 闇に落ちる.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl Falls into Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La jeune fille déprime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo wa, Yami ni Ochiru.</title>
<summary>Ikeda Chitose here. I`m glad to see everyone again. Also, Ayano-chan and Toshino-san have already shown me so much already... It`s great fodder for my fantasies. Oh, no. My nose is bleeding... No, wait. Today I have plans to go out with Ayano-chan! I`m so excited!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686349</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173178" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">満開桜に浪漫の嵐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cherry Blossoms in Full Bloom and a Romantic Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tempête romantique sous les cerisiers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mankai Sakura ni Rouman no Arashi</title>
<summary>Yuru Yuri`s protagonist Akaza Akari here!! This is the final episode of Yuru Yuri San Hai!. But if you want to see us again, you probably will! Now let`s head to the club room!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686363</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173179" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どうあがいても土壺</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Terrible No Matter How Much You Struggle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je suis dans la panade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dou Agaite mo Tsuchi Tsubo</title>
<summary>Good to see you again, everyone. Furutani Himawari here. I thought we`d finally get to be together again, but time flies, doesn`t it? And... it seems Sakurako is causing more trouble. I need to look after her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686361</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173180" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君とならいつまでも</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With You, Forever</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Avec toi, pour toujours</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi to Nara Itsumademo</title>
<summary>Funami Yui here. I`m glad to see you all again. Kyoko still isn`t doing her homework and still causes trouble by bringing weird things to school... But with Akari, Chinatsu-chan, and even Kyoko around, nothing really serious happens, but I do have fun.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686359</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173181" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは, 小さな愛と, 少しの勇気の物語.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is the Story of a Little Love and Courage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une histoire d`amour et de courage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa, Chiisana Ai to, Sukoshi no Yuuki no Monogatari.</title>
<summary>Ikeda Chizuru here. I guess I`m gratefull to see you again. Tsk! Anyway, she had to get involved and make things complicated again... Sheesh. I`m not mad because I want to be, but... Sometimes I wish I could smile like my sister.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686357</identifier>
<identifier>yuruyuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173985" update="2015-12-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218975" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218976" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218977" update="2019-07-23">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD CM 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
