<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11130" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>2015-09-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Monster Musume no Iru Nichijou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Everyday Life with Monster Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Monster Mädchen</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Ежедневието с момичета-чудовища</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Момичета-чудовища</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">monmusu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">モンスター娘のいる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Monster Musume: Everyday Life with Monster Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Die Monster Mädchen</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">魔物娘的同居日常</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11926" type="Side Story">Monster Musume no Iru Nichijou (2016)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="14969" approval="9" total="17">Ishuzoku Reviewers</anime>
<anime id="12637" approval="4" total="11">Centaur no Nayami</anime>
<anime id="4821" approval="3" total="7">Seto no Hanayome</anime>
<anime id="9479" approval="3" total="6">Namiuchigiwa no Muromi-san</anime>
<anime id="10069" approval="1" total="4">Gokukoku no Brynhildr</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="283605">If you have ever tough of putting your penis into a snake, bird, big nope or a horse (JRHNBR) papa bless! Then this series is 100% for you! If not, but your penis still gets hard. Blame it on the huge boobs.

You might get a few laughs out of it. It`s your mediocre daily life, ecchi, harem series, with a little bit romance mixed in. No real plot just doing stuff with reptile women in a sitcom manner.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="624639">This is THE perfect mixture between harem, comedy, ecchi and a little romance. It´s a MUST!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://monmusu.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3724" type="Series Composition">Fudeyasu Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="26662" type="Character Design">Sunagawa Takaya</name>
<name id="26662" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sunagawa Takaya</name>
<name id="27220" type="Animation Work">Lerche</name>
<name id="19251" type="Direction">Yoshihara Tatsuya</name>
<name id="43383" type="Chief Animation Direction">Akasaka Shunji</name>
<name id="20876" type="Music">Tsutsumi Hiroaki</name>
<name id="42654" type="Original Work">Okayado</name>
<name id="43393" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakazume Takahito</name>
<name id="6434" type="Music">Manzo</name>
</creators>
<description>Three years ago, the world learned that harpies, centaurs, cat girls, and all manners of fabulous creatures are not merely fiction; they are in fact of flesh and blood — not to mention scale, feather, horn and fang! Thanks to the Cultural Exchange Between Species Act, these once-mythical creatures have assimilated into society, or at least they are trying.
When a hapless human teenager named http://anidb.net/ch75969 [Kurusu Kimihito] is inducted as a "volunteer" into the government exchange program, his world is turned upside down. A snake-like lamia named http://anidb.net/ch73747 [Miia] comes to live with him, and it is Kurusu`s job to take care of her and make sure she integrates into his everyday life. Unfortunately for Kurusu, Miia is undeniably sexy, and the law against interspecies breeding is very strict. Even worse, when a flirtatious harpy named http://anidb.net/ch73748 [Papi] and a ravishing centaur girl, http://anidb.net/ch73749 [Centorea Shianus], move in, what should a teenage human with raging hormones do?!
Source: ANN
Note: The first two episodes premiered at a special event on 27.06.2015. Regular airing started on 08.07.2015. </description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2219">4.86</permanent>
<temporary count="2238">6.63</temporary>
<review count="3">4.94</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221962.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16856</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30307</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>31121</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://monmusu.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Monster_Musume</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>モンスター娘のいる日常</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3818</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352297</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18309</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1155" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-28">
<name>mermaid</name>
<description>A creature that is half-human (usually the upper body) and half-fish (usually the lower body). A male mermaid is called merman (but they can appear under many different names). Since mermaids are often confused with Sirens in media, they may posses special abilities akin to Sirens such as enchanting voice (on the other hand Sirens are often being portrayed as mermaids). Some mermaids might be able to transform their whole body into human (which is not surprising since mermaids are often associated with the "want to become human" theme) and that should not disqualify them from getting this tag.</description>
<picurl>209970.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2746" parentid="2901" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-26">
<name>shibari</name>
<description>Not to be confused with Hojoujutsu (捕縄術) or Nawajutsu (縄術), which is the traditional Japanese martial art of restraining a person using cord or rope.
More commonly known as Kinbaku (緊縛) in Japan, Shibari is the word for "erotic bondage" or Kinbaku-bi which means "beautiful bondage". Kinbaku (also Sokubaku) is a Japanese style of sexual bondage or BDSM which involves tying up the bottom using simple yet visually intricate patterns, usually with several pieces of thin rope usually hemp or jute (generally 6 mm or 8 mm in diameter). The person`s body can also be hanging from the rope while tied to it.
The word Shibari came into common use in the West at some point in the 1990s to describe the bondage art Kinbaku. Shibari (縛り) is a Japanese word that literally means "to tie" or "to bind". It is used in Japan to describe the artful use of twine to tie objects or packages.
In anime/manga, Shibari or Kinbaku is often seen as a tool of rape or torture, rather than intended for a concept of bondage aesthetics.</description>
<picurl>161702.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2824" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>pseudo tentacle rape scene</name>
<description>If this was porn she (or rather the audience) would have even more fun!</description>
<picurl>160554.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2843" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>sexual abuse -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be split into the following new tags under the http://anidb.net/t7220 [sexual abuse] category. Afterwards, delete this tag.

* http://anidb.net/t7222 [groping / molestation]
* http://anidb.net/t1306 [chikan]
* http://anidb.net/t7221 [psychological sexual abuse]
* http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape / attempted rape]
</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2890" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>foot fetish</name>
<description>Anime contains scenes which revolve around foot-fetishism.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="73747" type="main character in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="70">7.46</rating>
<name>Miia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miia is a lamia (part human, part snake), the first liminal to live with Kimihito.</description>
<picture>169971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73748" type="main character in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="57">6.56</rating>
<name>Papi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Papi is a harpy and is the second housemate. She is petite and physically appears to be much younger than the other girls, even though she is the same age as they are (harpies have evolved with smaller, slimmer bodies to enable flight).</description>
<picture>169972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39007" picture="148258.jpg">Ozawa Ari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73749" type="main character in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="57">7.00</rating>
<name>Centorea Shianus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173771.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37377" picture="188508.jpg">Aikawa Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75231" type="main character in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="55">7.96</rating>
<name>Suu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suu is a Slime, an amoeba-like creature that can change shape and color without effort</description>
<picture>173774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35872" picture="131992.jpg">Nomura Mayuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75232" type="main character in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="45">6.01</rating>
<name>Mero</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75233" type="main character in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="71">7.56</rating>
<name>Rachnera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>173773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29850" picture="203454.jpg">Nakamura Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75480" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="36">7.43</rating>
<name>Smith</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ms. Smith is one of the coordinators of the exchange program. She is a caricature of a civil servant.</description>
<picture>173963.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75969" type="main character in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="34">7.32</rating>
<name>Kurusu Kimihito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76088" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="36">6.26</rating>
<name>Zombina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23608" picture="65179.jpg">Mochizuki Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76089" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="37">6.66</rating>
<name>Tionishia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76090" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="40">5.51</rating>
<name>Doppel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Doppel calls herself a doppelganger, but is actually a shapeshifter.</description>
<picture>174920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76091" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="30">7.14</rating>
<name>Manako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37985" picture="175206.jpg">Asakura Momo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76467" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="22">5.44</rating>
<name>Kii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76468" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-24">
<rating votes="14">2.69</rating>
<name>Draco</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40614" picture="185784.jpg">Ootsu Airi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76469" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="28">6.98</rating>
<name>Lala</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76470" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="19">3.81</rating>
<name>Lilith</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81193" type="appears in" update="2016-07-24">
<rating votes="15">5.68</rating>
<name>Polt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34603" picture="175431.jpg">Natsukawa Shiina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89054" type="appears in" update="2017-04-28">
<name>Chara Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39583" picture="186257.jpg">Hamano Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89055" type="appears in" update="2017-04-28">
<name>Chara Kuro Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201725.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9510" picture="185781.jpg">Shimizu Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89062" type="appears in" update="2017-04-29">
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<name>Kasegi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89082" type="appears in" update="2017-04-29">
<rating votes="2">6.95</rating>
<name>Keikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33387" picture="23121.jpg">Kousaka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="168517" update="2015-07-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラミアのいる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with a Lamia</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit einer Lamia</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien aux côtés d’une lamia</title>
<title xml:lang="la">Vita Cotidiana cum Lamia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lamia no Iru Nichijou</title>
<summary>Kurusu Kimihito has found himself host to a beautiful lamia named Miia under the Cultural Exchange Between Species Act. She has taken quite a liking to him, despite the prohibition against interspecies breeding in the law. Life with her is rough in more ways than one, as she many times inadvertently strangles or knocks him about, and she constantly tries to seduce him, which would be prohibited by law. There is still a lot of prejudice against monsters in the human population. One day, as they go out into town, a pair of bigots insults Kimihito for his hosting a monster like Miia, which angers her, and she tries to attack them, but is stopped by Kimihito, who receives the blow instead. This attracts the attention of a crowd, and so the two are chased into a love hotel, where they are stopped from having a sexual liaison by Ms. Smith, the government official overseeing them. As they leave they see the same pair of bigots again, who this time insult Miia, which leads Kimihito to punch them.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682321</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168518" update="2015-07-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハーピーとケンタウロスのいる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with a Harpy and Centaur</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit Harpyie und Zentaurin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien aux côtés d’une harpie et d’une centaure</title>
<title xml:lang="la">Vita Cotidiana cum Harpyia et Centauro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harpy to Centauros no Iru Nichijou</title>
<summary>Kimihito`s troubles are just beginning as he is abducted from his backyard by a harpy, who drops him into a tree in a public park. The harpy, named Papi, had already escaped from two previous host families and is on the point of being deported, but she is such a literal bird-brain that she doesn`t seem to understand what this means. Miia finds them and takes exception to Papi`s attentions to her "darling" Kimihito, but in the meantime a child has gotten stuck in a tree and Papi helps save her. A policeman comes by in response to the incident, though it has been resolved, and asks for Papi`s papers after Kimihito claims to be her host. Ms. Smith comes by with these papers, explaining that she actually planned to send Papi to Kimihito after she ran away from her previous host families.
A few days later as Papi is getting settled in his home, Kimihito goes for groceries early in the morning, when he sees a centaur named Centorea. A snatcher is abroad in the neighbourhood, and they watch as the thief steals a woman`s purse, making his getaway on a scooter. Centorea, outraged, chases after the thief, dragging Kimihito along for the ride, as it is illegal for monsters like her to harm humans. They eventually catch the thief, and Centorea is so impressed by Kimihito that she declares him her "master".</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682323</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="168546" update="2015-05-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169401" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スライムのいる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with a Slime</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit Schleim</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien aux côtés d’une slime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Slime no Iru Nichijou</title>
<summary>A slime monster has invaded the house, and leaves everyone frantic after she nearly suffocates Miia and slimes Centorea and Kimihito. The two of them are in the bath trying to get themselves clean when the slime appears again, and Kimihito notices how she seems to be mimicking everyone`s actions. After some further mishaps Papi befriends her, giving her the name Suu. Miia and Centorea consider that she is quite possibly an illegal, and as such they ought to report her to Ms. Smith as soon as possible to avoid trouble. This worries Papi who suddenly flies off with her, and Kimihito chases after them. They play with a bunch of neighborhood kids who are friends with Papi, and Suu saves a little girl from getting hit by a truck. They arrive home to find that Ms. Smith is there.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682327</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169402" update="2015-07-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アブない事情な日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life Under Dangerous Circumstances</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gefährlicher Alltag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un quotidien aventureux</title>
<title xml:lang="la">Vita Cotidiana in Statui Periculoso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abunai Jijou na Nichijou</title>
<summary>Kimihito finds that the three monster girls have difficulty getting along, and he is in the middle. At one point the fighting between them gets so out of hand that Ms. Smith has to intervene, but she winds up shooting Kimihito with the tranquilliser darts instead. The girls are chastened by the incident and promise to behave themselves, while Kimihito declares that they are supposed to be like family. After receiving Centorea`s application forms Smith offhandedly mentions that there are some amendments to the law that are coming that will legalise inter-species marriage, but forgets to mention that it is a night of a full moon. That night the full moon combined with all the talk of marriage makes all the three girls crazy, and Kimihito has to flee from them and it is only when he falls onto a bottle of ketchup making them all think he was killed that they sober up. The next morning, Kimihito, sporting bandages from the rough night, says that it is his fault for being indecisive, and promises to date all three of them with an eye to marriage.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682325</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169634" update="2017-12-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169635" update="2017-12-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169649" update="2018-08-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月8日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169696" update="2015-07-09">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月9日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169714" update="2015-07-10">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-07-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月10日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169719" update="2015-07-10">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月11日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169760" recap="true" update="2015-08-20">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169784" update="2015-07-14">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-07-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月14日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169803" update="2015-07-20">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月15日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169823" update="2015-07-15">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月16日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169838" update="2015-07-20">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月17日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169947" update="2015-07-18">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月18日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169999" recap="true" update="2015-07-20">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170121" update="2015-07-20">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2015-07-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月21日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170149" update="2015-08-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">体調不良な日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life in Poor Health</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit Krankheit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un quotidien bouleversé par la maladie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taichou Furyou na Nichijou</title>
<summary>Rachnera begins integrating herself into the household, and as before Papi and Suu are nonplussed, Miia openly dislikes her, while Centorea tries to hide her similar dislike and mistrust behind a veneer of politeness. One night, Rachnera enters Kimihito`s room as he sleeps, seals the door and traps him in a web, intending to seduce him, but Centorea intervenes, breaking open the door and running away from the house with him. She attracts stares out in the street, and when they get to a dark area a group of anti-monster bigots confronts them. They restrain Kimihito and attempt to molest Centorea, but Rachnera intervenes, and wraps them in her silk, and terrifies them out of their wits. Centorea, though thankful, openly proclaims her dislike for Rachnera, but they try to get along regardless.
Later, Kimihito falls ill with the flu, which Smith regards as a danger to all the monster girls as it could mutate and produce a pandemic affecting all their species. The girls are mostly forbidden to attempt to care for him, but Suu will clearly not be affected. They try to teach her the various ways they intend to nurse him back to health, with mixed results. Suu later cares for him herself in her own way, and after he gets well, she explains in an uncharacteristic long and coherent speech how she is sorry that she caused him to get so sick by making him pick her up when she went outside on a rainy day, and declares that she loves him too.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682335</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170150" update="2015-08-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MONとアラクネのいる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with MON and an Arachne</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit Mon und Arachne</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien aux côtés des MON et d’une arachné</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">MON to Arakune no Iru Nichijou</title>
<summary>A group of orc terrorists has taken over an anime shop and is holding the patrons and staff hostage. The police are prevented by law from harming non-humans, so a special squad of elite monsters known as MON is dispatched to deal with them. The four of them, Zombina, Doppel, Manako, and Tionishia, use a combination of deception and brute force to subdue the monster terrorists.
MON are later dispatched to Kasegi`s house as he managed to make an emergency call before Rachnera wrapped him completely. She manages to escape, and abducts Kimihito at the door to his house. She brings him to a warehouse where she torments him, certain that he will affirm her misanthropic outlook as she had been mistreated by many humans before, but this does not faze him, and he even finds her spider form sexually alluring. A security guard at the warehouse sees them and MON is dispatched there, but Rachnera surrenders peacefully, and Smith assigns Kimihito to be her new host, as it seems he might be able to get along with her properly.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682333</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170151" update="2015-08-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脱皮と産卵する日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with Shedding and Egg Laying</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit Häuten und Eierlegen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un quotidien où mue et ponte se côtoient</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dappi to Sanran Suru Nichijou</title>
<summary>Miia is attempting to learn how to cook, and picks up a boiling pot with her bare hands and gets severely burned. This comes at the worst possible time, as soon after she begins shedding her skin, which she can`t peel off with her burned hands, and can`t leave as is since she could get an infection that way, so Kimihito has to help her. This proves to be a highly embarrassing operation as he has to touch her in her most intimate places.
Later, Papi says she is about to lay an egg, which has not been fertilised, much to the relief of the other girls. A dubious "film director" named Kasegi appears, claiming to be making a documentary on the interspecies exchange programme. He asks the girls rather embarrassing questions and tries to take titillating shots of them, and they are all suspicious, but Papi is about  to lay her egg. Suu exhibits a sort of telepathic ability and exposes Kasegi`s true intentions, which include stealing Papi`s egg, which can be sold for millions. Kimihito is incensed and punches him in the face with one of the eggs from the refrigerator. Papi lays her egg, and later Miia winds up cooking it.
Kasegi is also host to another monster, a an arachne named Rachnera, and he gripes to her about his misadventure. This intrigues her, and she wraps her erstwhile host in spider silk and goes out to seek Kimihito.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682331</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170152" update="2015-08-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マーメイドのいる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with a Mermaid</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit Meerjungfrau</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien aux côtés d’une sirène</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mermaid no Iru Nichijou</title>
<summary>Worried that the authorities will take Suu away, Miia, Centorea, and Papi take her outside and hide from them, but Kimihito did not follow them. Suu, dried out from being outside proceeds to molest the other three girls in an attempt to gain moisture. The government people who come by however don`t seem out to arrest someone, but seem to be construction people who make more alterations to the house. Kimihito goes out to find the girls and gets hit by a girl on a wheelchair heading down the slope named Mero, who saw where they had gone.
Mero, who turns out to be a mermaid, is yet another monster girl put under Kimihito`s care, and the construction work at the house, which added a deep pool, was for her benefit. Smith tells them that with so much work to do she can`t really be bothered to worry about Suu. The girls have varied reactions to their new housemate, with Papi nonplussed and Centorea impressed by her regal bearing, but Miia is jealous and behaves churlishly. Later, Miia dives into the new pool after Mero and Kimihito, nearly drowning, but after she is rescued she apologises for her rudeness and Mero explains how she has no plans to marry Kimihito but rather wishes for a tragic romance like the Little Mermaid`s.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682329</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170157" update="2015-07-21">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月22日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170189" update="2015-07-22">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月23日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170215" update="2015-07-23">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月24日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170228" update="2015-07-24">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月25日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170252" recap="true" update="2015-07-25">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170314" update="2015-07-28">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月28日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170357" update="2015-07-29">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月29日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170368" update="2015-07-30">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月30日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170380" update="2015-07-31">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 7月31日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170446" update="2015-08-05">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月1日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170447" update="2015-08-05">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月4日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170448" recap="true" update="2015-08-11">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170449" update="2015-08-05">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月5日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170455" update="2015-08-06">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月6日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170482" update="2015-08-07">
<epno type="2">S28</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月8日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170483" update="2015-08-20">
<epno type="2">S27</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月7日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170499" update="2015-09-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モンスター娘たちのいる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with Monster Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit den Monster-Mädchen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien avec des demi-humaines</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monster Musume-tachi no Iru Nichijou</title>
<summary>The girls are in a panic after the dullahan`s declaration that Kimihito will soon die, and they try their best to get him away, with Papi flying into an electric sign while carrying him, Centorea dragging him behind as she runs, being nearly drowned by Mero, and inadvertently strangled by Miia. Kimihito, however, is nonplussed, and recognises the dullahan`s ominous declarations for what they are: delusions of someone suffering from "8th-grader syndrome" (chuunibyou), which Ms. Smith later confirms, She reveals the dullahan`s name to be Lala, and she too becomes a guest of Kimihito.
With the addition of yet another monster girl to his household Kimihito finds that he is in dire financial straits, as all the food is gone, and he has little money left. They go to the shopping district to get some food, and the shopkeepers kindly give them less than perfect merchandise that they are unable to sell, but is perfectly edible. Kimihito also goes back to the forest where Kii lives, and they collect wild vegetables, with Suu being able to distinguish the poisonous ones from the safe ones. Thus with a well-stocked larder he is able to get by, until Smith shows up with the MON girls and they manage to eat all the food they so painstakingly gathered. Smith later informs Kimihito that he could have applied for reimbursement for his guests` food expenses, so he went through all that hard work for nothing.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682343</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170500" update="2015-09-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デュラハンのいる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with a Dullahan</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit Dullahan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien avec un Dullahan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dullahan no Iru Nichijou</title>
<summary>Kimihito receives a second threatening letter, more poetic than the first, and the members of MON go on a date with him in a final attempt to smoke out the writer. After a number of embarrassing situations with them they notice someone following, and it turns out to be none other than Doppel, who wrote the first letter in an attempt to make Kimihito`s love progress towards one of the girls, but it instead caused his relationships to all of them to deepen. She did not write the second letter though.
On his way home Kimihito is confronted by a headless woman, whom he brings home, and was apparently the author of the second letter. The girls help him look for her head, except for Rachnera and Suu, who remain behind to watch her body. They eventually find the disembodied head in the park, which makes strange noises as Rachnera and Suu molest her body. She is a dullahan, which supposedly appears when someone is about to die, and later implies that Kimihito is the one who will soon die.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682341</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170501" update="2015-09-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dのいる日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with D</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit D</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien avec D</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">D no Iru Nichijou</title>
<summary>Kimihito continues going on dates with the girls in an attempt to smoke out the writer of the threatening letters. He goes out this time with Papi and Suu, and they go for a barbecue picnic in a wild forest near Mt. Fuji. They are attacked by a giant tree monster, a dryad whom Papi had befriended named Kii, grown large due to the illegal dumping of experimental nutrients in the area, the pollution giving her a hatred of humans. Suu also absorbs some of the nutrients and grows just as large as Kii and begins fighting with her. Kimihito manages to get Kii to calm down and shrink back down to normal size after sucking on her breasts. Kii also cannot be the author of the threatening letters as she is completely illiterate.
Next, Kimihito goes on a date with Centorea, who goes out in full battle gear, which Manako, who is to watch over them, points out will probably frighten away the letter writer. Her large size causes her to break things as they go around, and she is depressed because she always seems to just be making trouble for Kimihito. They have a picnic where she gives some flavourless sandwiches that Kimihito is too nice to comment on, but Rachnera points this out and this depresses her even more, so she goes for a walk by herself for a moment. She meets the mischievous succubus Lilith who uses her powers on Centorea, saying that there is something she can do for Kimihito, which removes her inhibitions and she tries to seduce him, letting him fondle her breasts. Meanwhile, Lilith is attacked by a wild boar in the park, breaking the spell before it goes too far, and it later turns on Kimihito but Centorea manages to subdue it. Rachnera has afterwards captured Lilith, believing she might be the letter writer, but after torturing her Rachnera learns that she isn`t responsible.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682339</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170502" update="2015-09-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">脅迫状が来た日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyday Life with Threatening Letters</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Alltag mit Drohbrief</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un quotidien assombri par une lettre de menace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouhakujou ga Kita Nichijou</title>
<summary>Kimihito seems to be going on a date with Ms. Smith, much to the consternation of all the girls. They follow them around, with Suu providing disguises for each of them, but they wind up in compromising situations as they do this. It turns out that they were on a plan to smoke out the sender of threatening letters that Kimihito has received, saying that if he marries someone he will die.
The date with Ms. Smith failed to smoke out the perpetrator, so they arrange a date with Miia, with Mero tagging along. They go to a public aquarium where Mero is treated like a celebrity, and the attention Kimihito seems to be giving her irritates Miia enough that she eventually walks out on him. A reptilian monster tries to console her and eventually declares that as a fellow reptile he is more appropriate to marry her than Kimihito, saying he is Draco the Dragonewt. Kimihito runs to save Miia before Draco can do more, and reveals that Draco is actually female. MON has been observing them, and they arrest Draco, but she was not the one who was sending the threatening letters.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682337</identifier>
<identifier>monster-musume-everyday-life-with-monster-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170651" update="2015-08-11">
<epno type="2">S30</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月11日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170652" recap="true" update="2015-08-20">
<epno type="2">S29</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2015-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170765" update="2015-08-12">
<epno type="2">S32</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月13日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 27</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 27</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170766" update="2015-08-12">
<epno type="2">S31</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月12日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 26</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170797" update="2015-08-14">
<epno type="2">S33</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月14日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 28</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 28</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170803" update="2015-08-14">
<epno type="2">S34</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月15日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 29</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 29</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170820" recap="true" update="2015-08-20">
<epno type="2">S35</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2015-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170881" update="2015-08-18">
<epno type="2">S36</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月18日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 30</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 30</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170894" update="2015-08-19">
<epno type="2">S37</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月19日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 31</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 31</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170905" update="2015-08-20">
<epno type="2">S38</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月20日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 32</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 32</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170921" update="2015-08-21">
<epno type="2">S39</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月21日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 33</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 33</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170937" update="2015-08-22">
<epno type="2">S40</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月22日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 34</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 34</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170944" recap="true" update="2015-08-22">
<epno type="2">S41</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170984" update="2015-08-25">
<epno type="2">S42</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月25日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 35</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 35</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170998" update="2015-08-25">
<epno type="2">S43</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月26日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 36</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 36</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171008" update="2015-08-26">
<epno type="2">S44</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月27日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 37</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 37</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171093" recap="true" update="2015-08-30">
<epno type="2">S47</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2015-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171094" update="2015-08-30">
<epno type="2">S46</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月29日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 39</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 39</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171095" update="2015-08-30">
<epno type="2">S45</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 8月28日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 38</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 38</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171265" recap="true" update="2015-09-06">
<epno type="2">S53</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171266" update="2015-09-06">
<epno type="2">S52</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月5日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 44</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 44</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171267" update="2015-09-06">
<epno type="2">S51</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月4日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 43</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 43</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171268" update="2015-09-06">
<epno type="2">S50</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月3日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 42</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 42</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171269" update="2015-09-06">
<epno type="2">S49</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月2日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 41</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 41</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171270" update="2015-09-06">
<epno type="2">S48</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月1日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 40</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 40</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171345" recap="true" update="2015-09-12">
<epno type="2">S59</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171346" update="2015-09-12">
<epno type="2">S58</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月12日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 49</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 49</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171347" update="2015-09-12">
<epno type="2">S57</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月11日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 48</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 48</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171348" update="2015-09-12">
<epno type="2">S56</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2015-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月10日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 47</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 47</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171349" update="2015-09-12">
<epno type="2">S55</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月9日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 46</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 46</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171350" update="2015-09-12">
<epno type="2">S54</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月8日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 45</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 45</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171768" recap="true" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S65</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171769" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S64</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月19日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 54</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 54</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171770" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S63</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月18日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 53</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 53</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171771" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S62</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月17日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 52</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 52</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171772" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S61</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2015-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月16日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 51</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 51</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171773" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S60</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月15日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 50</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 50</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171775" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S66</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">羊を数えるララ 翻訳版比較</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life: Lala Sheep Counting Translated Version</title>
<title xml:lang="x-other">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 54 Extra - Hitsuji o Kazoeru Lala Honyaku-ban Hikaku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitsuji o Kazoeru Lala Honyaku-ban Hikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171776" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S68</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月23日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 56</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 56</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171777" update="2015-09-22">
<epno type="2">S67</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月22日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 55</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 55</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171993" update="2015-09-27">
<epno type="2">S71</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2015-09-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月26日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 59</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 59</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171994" update="2015-09-27">
<epno type="2">S70</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月25日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 58</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 58</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171995" update="2015-09-27">
<epno type="2">S69</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月24日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 57</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 57</title>
</episode>
<episode id="171996" recap="true" update="2015-09-27">
<epno type="2">S72</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2015-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 増刊号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life Special Issue 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga Special Issue 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172218" update="2015-10-01">
<epno type="2">S73</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画 9月29日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life 60</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga 60</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177808" update="2017-12-29">
<epno type="2">S75</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Long</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177809" update="2017-12-29">
<epno type="2">S74</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2015-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Long</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204421" update="2018-10-14">
<epno type="2">S76</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2016-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほぼ毎日◯◯! 生っぽい動画~実録! モン娘の60 日~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monster Musume - Almost Daily Life - Complete</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hobo Mainichi OO! Namappoi Douga - Jitsuroku! Monmusu no 60 Nichi</title>
<summary>Anime shorts that offer a secret candid look at the daily lives of Monster Musume.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228705" update="2020-04-25">
<epno type="2">S77</epno>
<length>140</length>
<airdate>2016-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「モンスター娘のいる日常 スペシャルイベント~他種族間交流パーティー」イベント映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Monster Musume: Everyday Life with Monster Girls Special Event: Cultural Exchange Between Species Party" Event Video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Monster Musume no Iru Nichijou Special Event: Tashuzokukan Kouryuu Party" Event Eizou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
