<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11140" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-11-04</startdate>
<enddate>2011-11-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="main">Eun-sil-i</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Dearest</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">THE DEAREST</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">은실이</title>
</titles>
<description>In-hye and Sun-mi visit their hometown, a small and quiet village in the countryside, after a long time only to face unexpected news: their old friend Eun-sil died while giving birth. The town is left in an uproar because of the baby, whose father is unknown, and it is neglected, protected by no one. While In-hye and Sun-mi try to save the baby with the help of Ji-young, their friend who has stayed in town, they find out that Eun-sil, who was mentally retarded, was a plaything of the village. In-hye and Sun-mi are troubled with the rage they feel against the village people and the guilty conscience they feel towards Eun-sil. Although they abandoned Eun-sil in the past, will they be able to protect her baby until the end?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="20">4.69</permanent>
<temporary count="20">5.40</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>170344.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30193</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2673" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Korea</name>
<description>Korea is a historical country in East Asia; since 1945, it has been divided into two distinct sovereign states: North Korea (officially the "Democratic People`s Republic of Korea") and South Korea (officially the "Republic of Korea"). Located on the Korean Peninsula, Korea is bordered by China to the northwest and Russia to the northeast. It is separated from Japan to the east by the Korea Strait and the Sea of Japan.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214324.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6166" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-23">
<name>South Korean production</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/t6762 [North Korean production]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6850" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-13">
<name>STAFF MISSING</name>
<description>This anime is missing staff credits. If you can, please assign staff credits to the anime accordingly and then remove the tag.
If the tag is set on an anime level, please assign preferably all credits and then remove it from the anime. If that is not feasible, please assign, at a minimum, credits for all the major/key staff and then transfer it to all relevant episodes (broadly speaking, regular episodes and S-type episodes containing animation). If the tag is already set on an episode level, please assign all credits, including minor staff, to the episode and then remove the tag from it.
Likewise, this tag should either be applied on an anime level, when it is missing key staff (in full or in part), or to all relevant episodes, when key staff is present but at least some episodes don`t have full staff.
For further information on assigning staff credits, please see http://wiki.anidb.net/Content:Staff_Credits [the AniDB Wiki article on them].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="108276" type="main character in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Sun-mi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244284.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108277" type="main character in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>In-hye</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244285.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108278" type="appears in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Sun-mi Mother</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244286.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108280" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Ji-young</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244288.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108281" type="appears in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Ji-young Mother</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244289.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108283" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Eun-sil</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244291.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108284" type="appears in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>Eun-sil Baby</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244292.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108285" type="appears in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>In-hye Father</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244295.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108287" type="appears in" update="2020-02-04">
<name>In-hye Mother</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244297.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="167440" update="2015-05-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>70</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
