<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11164" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Drifters</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">DRIFTERS Battle in a Brand-new World War</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Скитальцы</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドリフターズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Drifters</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Drifters</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">漂流武士</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12685" type="Sequel">Drifters (2017)</anime>
<anime id="12038" type="Summary">Drifters: Special Edition</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3296" approval="35" total="45">Hellsing (2006)</anime>
<anime id="13255" approval="5" total="11">Angolmois: Genkou Kassenki</anime>
<anime id="4575" approval="2" total="12">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</anime>
<anime id="10982" approval="2" total="12">Gate: Jieitai Kanochi nite, Kaku Tatakaeri</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="614578">Major figures from all through history (both good and bad) are transported to another world when they die and they end up doing things very similar to what we they did in our world. The bad people have decided to annihilate humans by siding with the monsters and the good people are trying to save the humans.

Pretty straight forward story but what made it interesting was the execution. Most of the good people have learned from their mistakes and are trying to be better versions in this new world. So there is character development and a lot of humour to allow us to quickly understand why they are doing something the way they are doing. A lot of tactics, strategy, idiosyncracies, kindness and bravery of each person was probably the highlight of this show.

Feels like an 8.5 anime. The author is an history nut and patriotic jap, so there are innuendos that 75% of the audience will not fully understand, and this might be the reason for its lower than expected rating.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="727472">Hugely entertaining with a willdly varying art style allong with character depictions, moves from serious gorefest to completely flippant and from completely camp to deadly serious in an instant...and back again. Been ages since I`ve seen anything as good as this. There`s some depth to it as well with some serious military strategy buried in amongst the general plot. Also, in amongst the madness, doesn`t lose the point that war is hell and people is wondrous strange &amp; complex. Hope season 2 can attain the same quality and, like others, can`t wait.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="331199">Another good anime from the author of Hellsing. Lots of funny episodes and a little twist on how the good vs evil plot plays out. Fights are cool and the people on the drifters side are just hilarious. 

Can`t wait till season 2 comes out.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="491381">at the very begining it looked somewhat chaotic for me. but became more and more charming. one second they throw some gags then became serious right after. i liked the gap between comedy and seriousness.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="540669">In one word epic.
I can just agree with previous recommendations.
Simliar to style as Hellsing Ultimate. Gore, animations, battle.
Highly recommendet.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nbcuni.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/drifters/</url>
<creators>
<name id="12197" type="Character Design">Nakamori Ryouji</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="12357" type="Direction">Suzuki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="12197" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakamori Ryouji</name>
<name id="3564" type="Original Work">Hirano Kouta</name>
<name id="2529" type="Music">Matsuo Hayato</name>
<name id="4588" type="Music">Ishii Yasushi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Shimazu Toyohisa], while involved in the Battle of Sekigahara, manages to mortally wound http://anidb.net/ch85630 [Ii Naomasa], but is critically wounded in the process. As he walks from the field wounded and bleeding, Toyohisa finds himself transported to a corridor of doors where a bespectacled man at a desk waits for him. This man, http://anidb.net/ch83939 [Murasaki], sends Toyohisa into the nearest door where he wakes up in another world. There, Toyohisa meets other great warriors like him who have been transported as well, to be part of a group known as http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters].
This world contains both native humans and a number of fantastical races, including elves, dwarves, and hobbits. However, the world is at war, with the humans waging a losing war against another group of great warriors, the http://anidb.net/ch86430 [Ends], who wish to take over the world and kill all the Drifters. Under the Ends` command are many terrible creatures, including dragons, which they use to destroy everything in their wake. At the start of the series, the Ends` army has control of the northern part of the continent and is currently trying to invade the south through a pivotal fortress at the northernmost tip of a nation called Carneades. Meanwhile, the http://anidb.net/ch86428 [Octobrist Organization], a group of human magicians native to this world, attempt to bring together the many individual Drifters to save their world from the brutal Ends.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1921">7.21</permanent>
<temporary count="1936">7.54</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>192198.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18181</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37034</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>31339</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nbcuni.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/drifters/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Drifters_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドリフターズ_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4284</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352568</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19509</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B075NLV2L1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2868" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-20">
<name>racism</name>
<description>Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of an ethnically different background based on the pseudo-scientific belief that biological differences between peoples form so-called "races" and that one`s own "race" is superior to another, possibly also holding that members of different "races" should be treated differently. Some definitions include only consciously malignant forms of discrimination, and some views include discriminatory behaviors and beliefs based on cultural, national, ethnic, caste, or religious stereotypes. In works of fiction, this may also include similar actions against other sentient species.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5003" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-10">
<name>imperialism</name>
<description>Imperialism is a type of advocacy of empire. Its name originated from the Latin word "imperium", which means to rule over large territories. Imperialism is "a policy of extending a country`s power and influence through colonization, use of military force, or other means".
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5150" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-11">
<name>asymmetric warfare</name>
<description>Asymmetric warfare is war between conflicting groups whose relative military power differs, or whose strategy or tactics differ significantly.
Asymmetric warfare can describe a conflict in which the resources of two groups differ in essence, and in the struggle, they interact and attempt to exploit each other`s weaknesses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5842" parentid="2925" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-23">
<name>guerilla warfare</name>
<description>Guerrilla warfare is a form of irregular warfare and refers to conflicts in which a small group of combatants including, but not limited to, armed civilians use military tactics, such as ambushes, sabotage, raids, the element of surprise, and extraordinary mobility to harass a larger and less-mobile traditional army, or strike a vulnerable target, and withdraw almost immediately.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6328" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-01">
<name>biological weapons</name>
<description>Use of biological agents (bacteria, viruses, fungi, etc.) to inflict harm on humans and/or other targets.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="79268" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="32">8.45</rating>
<name>Shimazu Toyohisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shimazu Toyohisa is the main protagonist and leader of the http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters]. Historically, he died in 1600 during the Battle of Sekigahara. When he first arrived in the new world, he was critically injured, only to be brought to http://anidb.net/ch79269 [Nobunaga] and http://anidb.net/ch79270 [Yoichi]`s hideout by the young elves, http://anidb.net/ch81509 [Marsha] and http://anidb.net/ch81508 [Mark].
Although impulsive and reckless, Toyohisa possesses a fearless, determined, and chivalrous spirit, assisting the elves and dwarves by liberating them from the Orte Empire. Born and raised in a war-torn era, Toyohisa has a keen sense for battle and tactics, though he remains unaware of these talents himself. Toyohisa primarily uses a nodachi in battle, though he is seen carrying a wakizashi. He also carries a Tangeashima on the back of his waist, which he only uses when his swords are infeasible to use against his enemies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>183705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79269" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="36">8.54</rating>
<name>Oda Nobunaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oda Nobunaga is a famous warlord who conquered most of Japan during Sengoku period. He is known for being the daimyo who took the first step of unification of the Japan, and the first Japanese military commander to utilize arquebuses in battles, using one as his main weapon in battle as a http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter]. Historically, he died during the Honnou-ji incident, the mutiny conducted by http://anidb.net/ch11507 [Akechi Mitsuhide].
As a Drifter, he has only aged six months since arriving in the new world. Nobunaga is highly ambitious and cunning, desiring to establish a multiracial federation in the new world with http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa] as their leader. Nobunaga acts as the group`s military strategist.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>183704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79270" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="19">7.10</rating>
<name>Nasu no Yoichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoichi is very effeminate man of nineteen. Although he lived hundreds of years before http://anidb.net/ch79269 [Nobunaga] and http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa], Yoichi is the youngest in the group. Born as the youngest of eleven siblings, Yoichi is a powerful warrior and military commander who served http://anidb.net/ch83938 [Minamoto no Yoshitsune] during the Genpei War. Yoichi`s exploits were recorded throughout Japanese history, including in The Tale of the Heike, though Nobunaga notes that Yoichi acts very differently from these historical accounts. During the Genpei War, he was forced to commit several dishonorable acts by Yoshitsune, despite having a strong belief of Bushido.
Now as a http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter], Yoichi resolves to maintain his honorable nature, and is the most level-headed of the trio. Yoichi acts as the group`s archer, killing fleeing enemies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>183706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80624" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="23">7.10</rating>
<name>Olminu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Olminu is a young magician of the http://anidb.net/ch86428 [Octobrists]. She is charged with watching http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa]`s group of http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters]. She seems to be quite incompetent at reconnaissance, and is terrified of the Drifters she must follow.
After she is discovered and kidnapped by Toyohisa`s group, she tells them the story of the Drifters and http://anidb.net/ch86430 [Ends]. She is often used as comic relief, shown in a generally incompetent, powerless, and cowardly way, and is a frequent target of sexual harassment by http://anidb.net/ch79269 [Nobunaga], but can be helpful due to her skills in sorcery. Olminu can also serve as an spectator to the story, with the narrative enlightening plot elements through her perception. Her codename is Sem.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>184612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38593" picture="223625.jpg">Kokido Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80625" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="2">3.84</rating>
<name>Kafeto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kafeto is a member of http://anidb.net/ch86428 [The Octobrist Organization], a group of magicians dedicated to fighting against the http://anidb.net/ch81510 [Black King] and his forces. He is often seen assisting http://anidb.net/ch80626 [Abe no Haruakira] in one way or another. His codename is Ham.
Source: Drifters Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>184611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16886" picture="151720.jpg">Nishida Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80626" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="7">6.59</rating>
<name>Abe no Haruakira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Abe no Haruakira, also known as Abe no Seimei, is a legendary Japanese magician who devoted his life to the extermination of the Ends soon after he first appeared in the new world as a http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter]. He now serves as the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch86428 [Octobrist Organization].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>184613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81068" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="5">6.78</rating>
<name>Anastasia Nikolaevna Romanova</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anastasia Nikolaevna Romanova is the youngest daughter of the last Russian tsar, Nicholas II. Anastasia and her family were shot by a Bolshevik firing squad when Anastasia was seventeen.
She has the supernatural ability to create blizzards. Anastasia is depicted as an emotionless woman with little interest in the war between the http://anidb.net/ch86430 [Ends] and http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters]. She apparently has some attachment to http://anidb.net/ch81069 [Jeanne], as http://anidb.net/ch81071 [Rasputin] noted that she was angered that Jeanne was hurt during her battle against http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>184617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6941" picture="31861.jpg">Kitanishi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81069" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="6">4.78</rating>
<name>Jeanne d`Arc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jeanne d`Arc is the heroine of the Hundred Years` War between France and England. Jeanne, who was driven insane after being burned at the stake, now desires nothing more than to see the world burn.
As an http://anidb.net/ch86430 [End] - with her Christian crosses now upside down - she has manifested the ability to manipulate fire. Surprisingly, she seems to be self-conscious of her (lacking) femininity, though this could be another result of her insanity.
After being defeated by http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa], Jeanne is able to flee the scene alive due to Toyohisa`s personal vow to never kill a woman, leading Jeanne to vow revenge.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>184615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81070" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="8">4.75</rating>
<name>Gilles de Rais</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gilles de Rais is a French nobleman who was once one of http://anidb.net/ch81069 [Jeanne]`s companions-in-arms, but was later executed for multiple cases of alleged murder, sodomy, and heresy. He possessed incredible strength and durability. He continued to accompany Jeanne to battle as a spearman, remaining loyal to her until his death.
He was defeated by http://anidb.net/ch83937 [Butch Cassidy] and the http://anidb.net/ch83936 [Sundance Kid], disintegrating into salt after that. An enraged Jeanne swears to avenge Gilles de Rais`s death. He is the first http://anidb.net/ch86430 [End] to be killed in the series.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>184616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81071" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="6">3.51</rating>
<name>Grigorii Rasputin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grigorii Rasputin is a famous Russian mystic who once held a great influence over the Russian Imperial Court because of his ability to supposedly heal the Romanov`s hemophiliac heir, Alexei.
He now serves the http://anidb.net/ch81510 [Black King] as a spymaster for his army, and is often seen by http://anidb.net/ch81068 [Anastasia]`s side. Similar to the http://anidb.net/ch86428 [Octobrists], Rasputin uses magic to possess others via the use of talismans, which he also uses for communication among the Black King`s army.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>184618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="284" picture="225436.jpg">Tanaka Masahiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81072" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="6">6.26</rating>
<name>Hijikata Toshizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hijikata Toshizou is the former vice-commander of the Shinsengumi who died fighting in the name of the Tokugawa Bakufu during the Boshin War. Hijikata has the ability to use smoke to manifest ghostly images of members of the Shinsengumi and uses them to cut apart his enemies. He has become http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa]`s rival following a battle between the two that ended in a draw.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>184614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81504" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="5">5.92</rating>
<name>EASY</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>EASY is a young woman with long, black hair, and violet eyes. Apparently at odds with http://anidb.net/ch83939 [Murasaki], she is responsible for the http://anidb.net/ch86430 [Ends], an opposing force similar in origin to the http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters]. She primarily uses her laptop to keep tabs on the battles taking place in the other world. In the corridor, she is associated with and accompanied by darkness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>195262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81505" type="appears in" update="2016-10-17">
<rating votes="2">5.72</rating>
<name>Shara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81506" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Scipio Africanus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81507" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="3">6.63</rating>
<name>Hannibal Barca</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hannibal Barca is a famous Carthaginian military commander. Now a http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter] and elderly, he is first seen arguing with http://anidb.net/ch81506 [Scipio Africanus] over the latter`s "plagiarism" of Cannae at the Battle of Zama. Despite nearly being killed by the http://anidb.net/ch81510 [Black King]`s army, Hannibal still insists that victory is still possible. After being separated from Scipio, Hannibal becomes depressed and senile, but he is still able to articulate battle tactics to his fellow Drifters via indirect means. He acts as http://anidb.net/ch79269 [Nobunaga]`s military advisor since being left in http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa]`s group`s care.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>193129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81508" type="appears in" update="2016-10-17">
<rating votes="3">4.53</rating>
<name>Mark</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42872" picture="171894.jpg">Tsuzuki Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81509" type="appears in" update="2016-10-17">
<rating votes="2">3.81</rating>
<name>Marsha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2945" picture="177565.jpg">Ishizuka Sayori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81510" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Kokuou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Black King is the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch86430 [Ends]. He claims that he once tried to "save" humans, but he has since shifted his agenda towards non-humans after humans "denied" his efforts. His identity has yet to be established, but he is shown to possess healing powers and the ability to multiply any life form he wishes, infinitely producing food or wood. He also has puncture scars in both of his palms.
His ultimate goal is to eradicate all humans and create a new civilization of non-humans in a perpetual Dark Age, ensuring that they never advance far enough to become as destructive as humans, creating what the Black King believes will be a utopia. In order to achieve this, the Black King has instructed http://anidb.net/ch81071 [Rasputin] to create a simple alphabet and a syncretic religion to allow the different non-human races to find a common ground.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>188041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83936" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="2">3.84</rating>
<name>The Sundance Kid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83937" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2">4.75</rating>
<name>Butch Cassidy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Butch Cassidy is the leader of the Wild Bunch gang. He, along with http://anidb.net/ch83936 [Sundance Kid], was transported from Bolivia, and is now fighting against the http://anidb.net/ch81510 [Black King] and his armies. Unlike his partner, Butch has a more wild personality. He favors the use of firearms, particularly a pair of pistols, in battle.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>193131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83938" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="2">1.49</rating>
<name>Minamoto no Kurou Hougan Yoshitsune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83939" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="3">1.57</rating>
<name>Murasaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Murasaki is a bespectacled man who is apparently the one responsible for the appearance of the http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters], using them as a means to right the wrong of the http://anidb.net/ch86430 [Ends]` conquest of the unknown world and allowing the Drifters to find some form of redemption for their crimes on Earth. He is seen sitting in the middle of the door corridor, smoking, and reading a newspaper that gives news of the events relating to the Drifters. In the corridor, he is associated with and accompanied by light.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>193134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83940" type="appears in" update="2016-12-31">
<rating votes="3">5.58</rating>
<name>Kanno Naoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanno Naoshi is a World War II fighter pilot. During the battle with the http://anidb.net/ch81510 [Black King], with the http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters]` side under attack by dragons, he was transported into the world in his plane. He decided to attack the dragons when their attacks reminded him of the U.S. bombing of Tokyo.
His plane later crashed and he soon found himself worshiped as a god by natives, only to be found by http://anidb.net/ch81506 [Scipio], who decides to use his status to unite the various anthropomorphic animal tribes under him to bolster the Drifters` army. He does not initially trust http://anidb.net/ch83937 [Butch] or http://anidb.net/ch83936 [Sundance Kid], as they are American, but Butch manages to convince him that they are Bolivian instead.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>193128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85378" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="3">2.16</rating>
<name>Alesta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alesta is an aide to Count http://anidb.net/ch85379 [Saint-Germi].</description>
<picture>195268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37719" picture="138626.jpg">Fukuda Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85379" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="4">6.01</rating>
<name>Saint-Germi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saint-Germi is a nobleman and http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter] who owns a quarter of the http://anidb.net/ch86431 [Orte Empire] and was Hitler`s closest ally in its formation. It is said that the Empire could not have existed without his "betrayal", and as such, he is free to live as he pleases without criticism from any of his peers. Despite this position, however, he is not loyal to the Empire and later betrays the Empire when he realizes its impending demise.
He forms an alliance with the Drifters and their allies to take over the Empire. In spite of the fact he is well over fifty years old, Saint-Germi appears as a youthful drag queen with an effeminate personality. He has knowledge of the modern era (due to the fact that he is aware of the existence of firearms and gunpowder), as well as some knowledge of Japanese history.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>195274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85380" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="3">2.16</rating>
<name>Flame</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Flame is an aide to Count http://anidb.net/ch85379 [Saint-Germi].</description>
<picture>195269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85381" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="2">5.90</rating>
<name>Yamaguchi Tamon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamaguchi Tamon is a former Japanese Rear Admiral (posthumously Vice Admiral) and the commander of the Second Carrier Division of the First Air Fleet during World War II.
Tamon appeared as http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter] along with his badly-damaged aircraft carrier Hiryuu which is now beached on a small rocky island. He helped the http://anidb.net/ch86432 [Merchant Guild of Gubinnen] defeat the http://anidb.net/ch86431 [Orte Empire] and take control of the sea trading routes.
Source: Drifters Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>195272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="415" picture="241624.jpg">Nakano Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85630" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="2">3.81</rating>
<name>Ii Naomasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ii Naomasa was a general under Tokugawa Ieyasu`s forces. He was first seen persuading the Shimazu forces as the were about to retreat, and telling his men that if they let them return to Satsuma, it will be disgrace for them and Tokugawa. Eventually he faced http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Shimazu Toyohisa], who stayed behind to allow http://anidb.net/ch85632 [his uncle] to escape and clashed swords with him. Naomasa`s men quickly tried to protect him and surrounded Naosama aiming their spears at Toyohisa. To the surprise of Naosama, Toyohisa jumped forward and ended pierced by multiple spears. Naomasa though he was a fool, but Toyohisa told him that he is the fool and then took out his gun and shot Naomasa near the heart. Naomasa`s men quickly took him and retreated, while Toyohisa was telling him to leave his head behind.
Source: Drifters Wiki</description>
<picture>193147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85631" type="appears in" update="2016-10-17">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Shimazu Iehisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85632" type="appears in" update="2016-10-17">
<rating votes="2">4.75</rating>
<name>Shimazu Yoshihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="324" picture="223539.jpg">Saitou Jirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85633" type="appears in" update="2016-10-17">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Fukushima Masanori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44807" picture="182277.jpg">Jou Kirian</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85634" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="2">1.04</rating>
<name>Alam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alam is a cold-blooded knight of the http://anidb.net/ch86431 [Orte Empire]. After being brutally defeated by http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa], he is killed by the elves out of retribution for massacring their people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>193145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85635" type="appears in" update="2016-10-17">
<rating votes="2">1.98</rating>
<name>Sonchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="235" picture="17053.jpg">Saizen Tadahisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86428" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="2">3.81</rating>
<name>Octobrist Organization</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Octobrist Organization is a group of humans, known as magicians, native to the world whose duty is to observe and gather Drifters together to fight the Ends. Unlike many humans in this world, Octobrists do not subjugate the demihumans. It is led by http://anidb.net/ch80626 [Abe no Seimei], who is also a Drifter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>195261.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86429" type="appears in" update="2016-12-26">
<rating votes="2">7.64</rating>
<name>Drifters</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The titular Drifters are heroes, leaders, and great warriors from different eras and cultures that have been brought to an unknown world by http://anidb.net/ch83939 [Murasaki], where they are meant to fight the Ends. A common element to the Drifters is that, although they are driven by violence, victory, and conquest, most of them are not cruel and do not tolerate the hurting of innocents. Unlike the Ends, the Drifters have no magic abilities unless they were born with them, and therefore must largely rely on their technology and tenacity to survive.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>196180.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86430" type="appears in" update="2016-12-26">
<rating votes="2">4.75</rating>
<name>Ends</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The opposing force in the unknown world, the Ends are, like the http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters], mainly composed of powerful historical figures who died under unorthodox and often violent circumstances. Unlike the Drifters, however, the Ends are revered humans that have forsaken their humanity, and are thus capable of using supernatural powers. Most of the Ends are driven completely by an intense hate for humanity for the various betrayals each suffered back on Earth. They seem to have been brought into the new world by http://anidb.net/ch81504 [Easy], who is at odds with http://anidb.net/ch83939 [Murasaki].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>196181.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86431" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Orte Empire</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Orte Empire is a country that was established by Hitler. It expanded through the conquest of neighboring territories and continued to adhere to Hitler`s principles, which involves the persecution of demihumans races. Recently, the Empire was sold to http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa] and the http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters] by Count http://anidb.net/ch85379 [Saint-Germi], as Hitler had bankrupted the empire before his death. Its capital is Berlina.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>195265.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86432" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>GuBinnen Tsuushou Guild Rengou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Merchant Guild of GuBinnen was the organization that waged war against http://anidb.net/ch86431 [Orte Empire] at the sea.</description>
<picture>195266.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="180250" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アクティブハート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Active Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Active Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Active Heart</title>
<summary>The Black King is dealing with the aftermath of the conquest of Carneades.  Simultaneously, on the other side of the empire, the Drifters are preparing for backlash and starting to grow their own ambitions.  
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180251" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺軍 暁の出撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Army of Ours: Sortie at Dawn</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Meine Armee - Einsatz im Morgengrauen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore Gun Akatsuki no Shutsugeki</title>
<summary>The Black King’s army is marching on the Northern Wall of Carneades while the Octobrists attempt to convince Carneades` defenders to hand over control of the defensive force to Hannibal and Scipio. This will be the "Ends” debut on the battlefield.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180252" update="2018-02-04">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">踵 鳴る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Footsteps</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fersenlaute</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakato Naru</title>
<summary>As Orte sets the Elven village ablaze in the distance, Nobunaga and Yoichi are dragged into action by Toyohisa`s fearless forward charge. Meanwhile on the other side of the world, the march of the Black King is about to Commence.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180253" update="2018-02-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FIGHT SONG</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fight Song</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fight Song</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fight Song</title>
<summary>In the aftermath of the Battle of Sekigahara, warrior Shimazu Toyohisa is suddenly thrust into a mysterious world where he is shocked to encounter the supposedly Oda Nobunaga and the historical figure Nasu Suketaka Yoichi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180890" update="2016-10-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181252" update="2016-10-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181377" update="2016-12-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議CAll ME</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mystery Call Me</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fushigi Call Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi Call Me</title>
<summary>With the dust settling throughout the battlefield, Toyohisa declares that he acts based on his own rules. Far from the battlefield, the axis powers of World War II reunite, and proceed to fall apart. Elves liberated, next up...the Dwarves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="181378" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カオスダイバー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chaos Diver</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Chaos Diver</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chaos Diver</title>
<summary>As Toyohisa and Joan clash in the moonlight, the strings of fate that tie the Drifters together start to converge, and the strength of their alliance is revealed. As the dust settles, the identity of the leader of the Octobrists is unveiled. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="181379" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">MEN OF DESTINY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Men of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Men of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Men of Destiny</title>
<summary>As the Elves tear apart the magistrate’s castle, a new player with unknown allegiances looms.  Meanwhile, Oda starts work on creating the final nail in Orte’s coffin and bringing about a change that will shatter the foundations of this world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="181380" update="2016-12-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛をとりもどせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bring Back Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Holt euch die Liebe zurück</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai o Torimodosu</title>
<summary>As the lord`s suppression force marches into the seemingly abandoned Elven village, a trap laid by the Drifters waits to be sprung. As a result of the clash, the lack of Elven women in the village is explained, and the flames of vengeance ignited.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182235" update="2016-12-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みつめて☆新選組~熱血九州男児の唄~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Staring at Shinsengumi: The Song of the Fervid Kyushu Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsumete Shinsengumi: Nekketsu Kyuushuu Danji no Uta</title>
<summary>As Toyohisa and Hijikata dance a deadly duet in the inferno of a capital, Nobunaga slowly moves to turn the tide. As the ashes settle on the city, a Pyrrhic victory is achieved with the line between victory and defeat not being so clear cut.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182236" update="2016-12-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピストル大名の冒険~火縄丸数え歌~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Adventure of the Pistol Daimyo: Bullet Counting Song</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Abenteuer des Pistolen-Daimyos ~ Lieder um die Lunte ~</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pistol Daimyou no Bouken: Hinawamaru Kazoeuta</title>
<summary>The coup begins yet right from the start there is an unexpected wrench thrown into the plans. The roar of muskets now rips across the new world, and the Drifters find their places leading armies. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182237" update="2016-12-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Baba Yetu</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Baba Yatu</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Baba Yetu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baba Yetu</title>
<summary>After freeing the Dwarves, the Drifters’ plans continue getting derailed as unexpected guests show up. Meanwhile, far to the north, the Black King’s plan continues to unfurl as the Ends regroup and recover in preparation to strike back.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182238" update="2016-12-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本気ボンバー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Serious Bomber</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Honki Bomber</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honki Bomber</title>
<summary>Gadolka begins with the culmination of the effort spent on black powder and ends with a paradigm shift in the warfare of the new world. The full extent of the Dwarves suffering reveals itself, and a new cog is added to the war machine. 
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="192408" update="2017-11-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black King Show</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192409" update="2017-11-02">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192410" update="2017-11-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192411" update="2017-11-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
