<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11169" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-10-17</startdate>
<enddate>2015-10-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Cyborg 009 vs. Devilman</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">デビルマン (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Devilman (2015)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">人造人009VS惡魔人</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">サイボーグ009VSデビルマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Cyborg 009 vs. Devilman</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Cyborg 009 vs Devilman</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">人造人009VS恶魔人</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1236" type="Character">Devilman</anime>
<anime id="1527" type="Character">Cyborg 009</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="174306">awesome OP song. beautiful ED sequence. I know these sound trivial but they do show the love of the creators for the original source material.

The first battle with Jinmen is a beautiful recreation of the one in the Devilman manga.
The fights are for the most part really exciting. I don`t think there`s a reason NOT to watch this. At worst you`ll find it mediocre but entertaining.

I think the first episode was the best. That fight with Pazuzu (if he`s called that) on the first episode is a GAR treat. I enjoyed all three episodes though. If you`re into that kind of stuff deffo watch this.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ishinomori.co.jp/009_50th/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6195" type="Character Design">Itou Takeshi</name>
<name id="7464" type="Series Composition">Hayakawa Tadashi</name>
<name id="6195" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Takeshi</name>
<name id="23461" type="Music">Terada Shiho</name>
<name id="23462" type="Music">Yokozeki Atsushi</name>
<name id="1038" type="Animation Work">Actas</name>
<name id="1211" type="Original Work">Ishinomori Shoutarou</name>
<name id="868" type="Original Work">Nagai Gou</name>
<name id="5667" type="Direction">Kawagoe Jun</name>
<name id="45108" type="Animation Work">Bee Media</name>
</creators>
<description>After discovering the existence of demons in Tokyo, the original Cyborg crew led by http://anidb.net/ch40548 [Dr. Gilmore] find themselves in conflict with http://anidb.net/ch7692 [Devilman], a strong demon believed to be in league with the war-profiteering terrorist organisation, Black Ghost. Meanwhile, a bigger threat emerges when Dr. Adams, a Black Ghost scientist unleashes his new line of high-teen Cyborg models against http://anidb.net/ch40557 [009] and his friends.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="137">5.86</permanent>
<temporary count="139">6.49</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>177080.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17324</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31050</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ishinomori.co.jp/009_50th/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://009vsdevilman.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Cyborg_009_Vs._Devilman</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352756</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18553</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="898" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-17">
<name>submarine</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3192" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-26">
<name>hidden base</name>
<description>Someone wants to be secretive when he plans to take over the world...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5293" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>crash landing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7692" type="main character in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="43">7.47</rating>
<name>Devilman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7693" type="main character in" update="2015-02-04">
<rating votes="93">6.75</rating>
<name>Fudou Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira Fudou lost his birth parents at a young age to an accident while exploring the Himalayas, killing his mother and father. He was then taken in to live in the care of close family friends. He has always been timid, shy, with very little courage and was often bullied before becoming into contact with the `Demon Lord of Battles`, Amon. It is Akira`s pure soul that keeps Amon trapped within Akira; allowing him to use Amon`s power and strength to transform freely into Devilman.</description>
<picture>26558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7694" type="main character in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="41">3.81</rating>
<name>Asuka Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryo Asuka is the best friend of Akira Fudo, the main character of Nagai Go`s classical horror manga Devilman. As Akira is the strength, Ryo is the brain. His father discovered the existence of demons in our world and decided to fight them. He asked his friend Akira`s help. Ryo knew that to be able to beat a demon, one had to become a demon. He and Akira went through a ritual to fuse with demons, but in the end, only Akira was able to do so and became Devilman, leaving Ryo remain as a normal human.</description>
<picture>26559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7706" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="18">6.07</rating>
<name>Makimura Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7709" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="5">3.33</rating>
<name>Psycho Jenny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26577.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40548" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-22">
<rating votes="7">3.33</rating>
<name>Isaac Gilmore</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4185" picture="224827.jpg">Ushiyama Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40549" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="15">5.18</rating>
<name>Cyborg 001</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33578" picture="225440.jpg">Shiraishi Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40550" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="15">8.51</rating>
<name>Cyborg 002</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40551" type="main character in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="28">6.63</rating>
<name>Cyborg 003</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40552" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="15">5.18</rating>
<name>Cyborg 004</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40553" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="15">5.18</rating>
<name>Cyborg 005</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40554" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="15">4.05</rating>
<name>Cyborg 006</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3272" picture="172136.jpg">Mizushima Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40555" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="15">8.51</rating>
<name>Cyborg 007</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40556" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="15">3.68</rating>
<name>Cyborg 008</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149581.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40557" type="main character in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="15">8.51</rating>
<name>Cyborg 009</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="169229" update="2015-06-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170919" update="2019-07-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2015-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
<summary>After the battle with the Mythos Cyborgs, Ivan warns the others of a Devil. Devilman too senses his enemy. The ultimate encounter is about to unfold.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="171756" update="2015-09-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="173348" update="2019-07-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2015-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
<summary>Akira’s search for the abducted Miki Makimura leads to Devilman coming face to face with cybernetic demons generated through a horrifying ritual.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="173349" update="2019-07-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2015-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
<summary>Dr. Gilmore notices animal cells mutating into human cells on Joe’s wounds. Humankind’s worst enemy - humans? Joe and Akira’s fates are yet unknown.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
