<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1118" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>59</episodecount>
<startdate>1964-08-03</startdate>
<enddate>1965-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Big X</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ビッグX</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7876" type="Character">Ravex in Tezuka World</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/31.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="782" type="Unknown Relation">Tokyo Movie</name>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="2078" type="Music">Tomita Isao</name>
</creators>
<description>Invited to Nazi Germany during World War II, Dr. Asagumo is asked by Hitler to collaborate in researching the new weapon "Big X". Concerned about the possible effects of this weapon, Dr. Asagumo intentionally delays the progress of the research, conspiring with his co-researcher, the devious Dr. Engel. Immediately before Germany is defeated by the Allies, Dr. Asagumo is shot to death by the German army but not before implanting a card inscribed with the secret of Big X into his son, Shigeru. An organization claiming alliance with the Nazis appears, steals the card from Shigeru, who now lives in Tokyo, and completes the Big X project, which is revealed to be a drug that can expand the human body without limitation. Dr. Engel`s grandson has joined the Nazi Alliance. Recovering Big X from the enemy, Shigeru`s son Akira fearlessly challenges the Nazi Alliance and Hans Engel, who are plotting to conquer the world.
Source: Wiki</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="22">2.59</permanent>
<temporary count="22">3.86</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>151144.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1217</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30839</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>9613</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>595</identifier>
<identifier>fisnip</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/31.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.co.jp/search/introduction.php?pdt_no=54</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Big_X</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ビッグX</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>162098</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1541</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="21443" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Door To Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Jou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21444" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">空中都市</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Aerial City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuuchuu Toshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21445" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">要塞脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evacuation from the Fortress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousai Dasshutsu</title>
<summary>Akira is sent to a concentration camp after being captured by a villain. Though he is subjected to terrible torture by the chief of the camp, named Lamp, Akira will not give them the information on where the Big X pencil is kept. Akira himself is actually no longer aware of where it might be. At the nadir of his fortunes, he senses a mysterious girl communicating with him by telepathy. The girl, named Nina, is also a captive, and tells Akira that she knows where the pencil is kept.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21446" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">グレート3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Great 3</title>
<summary>Akira and his party happen to witness the kidnapping of the prime minister while visiting the fast-developing country of Lilly. The prime minister has been taken away by a flying saucer operated by a group of three men named the "Great Three." The prime minister surrenders after learning that the Great Three have taken over the town, and all other politicians turn to the group. Lilly is then placed under the complete control of the audacious group of three. Akira is captured, deprived of his pen, and sentenced to death as a political offender.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21447" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒いオーロラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Aurora</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Aurora</title>
<summary>A mammoth creature of previous centuries appears at the North Pole. Akira sets out to investigate, and finds out that it is actually a mammoth-shaped robot used by the North Party to expand upon their control of the land encircling the North Pole.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21448" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">火の馬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret Undersea Laboratory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hi no Uma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21449" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">大氷原の決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown at the Grand Glacier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daihyougen no Kessen</title>
<summary>A meteorite falls crashes into the South Pole. While researching the site, Dr. Hanamaru, Akira, and the party discover that destruction has occurred in the South Pole base and that the observation site staff have disappeared. Dr. Hanamaru and Nina, who had begun investigating the incidents, are kidnapped and spirited away to the secret base of Dr. Black Jaguar. Akira loses his thinking power and collapses after being exposed to a beam. It becomes clear later that the meteorite is a flying saucer from the planet Barius, and the scientist on the disc is forced to develop ultra photon energy because his daughter has been taken hostage by Black Jaguar. Rescued by the scientist from the planet Barius, Akira turns into Big X, and takes on the giant robot manipulated by Black Jaguar.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21450" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀河に向って</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toward the Galaxy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginga ni Mukatte</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21451" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しき昆虫博士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sad Insect Doctor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashiki Konchuu Hakase</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21452" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハンスの復讐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hans` Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hans no Fukushuu</title>
<summary>Dr. Hanamaru and the party, who had been enjoying their vacation in the Republic of Biruji-a peaceful and quiet neutral country-are suddenly attacked by a flock of balls called "electric wave beasts." More powerful than Big X, the balls destroy the town. Nina telepathically communicates with the manipulator of the balls, who is a man of the subterranean culture that has built an empire under the ground of the Republic of Biruji. The man says that his people are taking revenge for the underground testing performed by humans. Who in the world is performing underground tests? Akira and the party find out later that it was Hans. Hoping to settle old scores with Big X, Hans challenges Akira by transforming himself into a cyborg.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21453" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙の虎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Metropolis Destruction Campaign</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu no Tora</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21454" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">サンゴ礁の奇蹟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miracle of the Coral Reef</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sangoshou no Kiseki</title>
<summary>Dr. Hanamaru has developed radioactive iodine in order to save coral on the verge of extinction. The coral should be able to come back to life if radioactive iodine is released in its vicinity. In the midst of his experiment, Dr. Hanamaru and Akira are caught in a violent storm, and are cast up on the shore of a coral island. The storm has actually been caused by Hans Engel. In order to deprive Akira of his magnet pencil, Hans Engel uses a fake version of the radioactive iodine developed by Dr. Hanamaru, and causes mutation among the creatures on the bottom of the sea. Enormously large lobsters, crabs, and sharks attack Akira and his party. Akira turns into Big X and takes on Hans.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21455" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">V3号の襲撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Attack of V3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">V3 Gou no Shuugeki</title>
<summary>The Nazis urge Akira-who has returned from overseas-to surrender Big X in exchange for his mother, but Akira refuses. As a last resort, the Nazi Leader has their secret weapon-the giant robot V3-attack Akira. A fierce battle then begins between Big X and V3.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21456" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂った大噴水</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Mad Fountain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurutta Daifunsui</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21457" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">砂漠の対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown in the Desert</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sabaku no Taiketsu</title>
<summary>After having succeeded in breaking out of the concentration camp, Akira and Nina wander through a desert of boiling sand with the Nazis is at their heels. Just barely escaping from their pursuers, Akira and Nina seek refugee at a native village. A search notice has already been distributed in the village, and Akira and Nina are captured by the Nazis.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21458" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">キングの電送作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The King`s Electricity Transmission Campaign</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">King no Densou Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21459" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦20対21</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown 20 vs. 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen 20 tai 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21460" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪男の泉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fountain of the Snowman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukiotoko no Izumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21461" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Showdown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Kessen</title>
<summary>The female chemist who has proposed a new use for volcanic energy, called the "Active Volcano Guiding System" at the energy chemists` conference, is named Irena Engel. The name means something to Akira; and he suspects that she could be somehow related to Hans Engel. As feared, the conference venue is suddenly thrown into chaos by an ultrasonic wave beam, and Irena is kidnapped and her research confiscated. The culprit is undoubtedly Hans. He has been planning to threaten the world by converting the new volcano energy use system, developed by his sister Irena, into a missile. Irena grieves over the actions of her brother. But Hans is doggedly determined to take revenge on Dr. Asagumo, who developed Big X, as he believes that his father was killed by the doctor. Hans challenges Akira to a final showdown, expecting to settle old scores at last. Akira, however, tries to persuade Hans not to fight a useless battle. Irena also begs him to return to being the kind brother that he used to be.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21462" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球第五氷河期</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Earth`s 5th Ice Age</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Dai Go Hyougaki</title>
<summary>A new island suddenly emerges in the South Pacific Ocean. But when closely examined, it is found to actually be comprised of a mass of unknown chemical substances and not an island at all. Nina receives a mysterious message on the island from a different human race, called "Hypocra," which supposedly became extinct 20,000 years ago. The Hypocras are attempting to take revenge on humans, who ruined them by using this island. Everything touched by the black smoke rising from the island freezes instantly. Monsters come forth from the island and attack the world as it freezes land by land. Akira turns into Big X and to get the crisis under control.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21463" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">大昔ミサイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Antique Missile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oomukashi Missile</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21464" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">サマリンガの魔法使い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Magician of Samaringa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samaringa no Mahoutsukai</title>
<summary>Akira has been tricked by a magician and robbed of his pen, and it is a tenderhearted boy named Carl who takes it back for him. Akira visits Carl at his home to thank him, and meets his little sister, Clara. Clara is unable to walk as her legs are paralyzed. Learning that she believes she can recover if she takes a dewdrop of Samaringa, which blooms only once every ten years, Akira leaves for the top of the mountain where the Samaringa is found.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21465" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビッグXの危機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crisis of Big X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Big X no Kiki</title>
<summary>Akira falls very ill upon entering a small European town. The Nazis mercilessly attack Akira to rob him of Big X, but the people in town grow angry at the tyranny of the Nazis and move to protect him. Weakened by disease, Akira needs to wait to be cured, but at the same time is obliged to use Big X as he is being pursued by the Nazi V13 robot.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21466" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">大竜神対ビッグX</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Dragon God vs. Big X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dairyuujin tai Big X</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21467" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">真空人間サルベージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebellion of a Rubber Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkuu Ningen Salvage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21468" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虹の国から</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Rainbow Country</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niji no Kuni kara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21469" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニーナの危機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nina in Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nina no Kiki</title>
<summary>Dr. Hanamaru, Akira and his party are caught in a severe storm while driving, and take shelter at a Western-style house. There is no one at the house but a cat. Nina reads the cat`s mind, and finds out that the house is owned by a certain Dr. Science. Some days later, Akira and the party hear that the rocket that Dr. Science had developed has been stolen. As soon as they start to investigate, Nina is kidnapped and taken to a secret base floating on the sea where she witnesses Dr. Science being tortured.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21470" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">アマゾンの黒雲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Cloud on the Amazon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amazon no Kurokumo</title>
<summary>Dr. Hanamaru is visiting Rio de Janeiro to present his study results when he and his party get on a plane to go sightseeing in South America. They get caught in a block cloud and crash-land on an uncultivated island. The island is devastated by a man named Kid, who plans to conquer the world. The natives start to attack Dr. Hanamaru, Akira, and the party as they mistake them for Kid`s allies.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21471" update="2016-10-11">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">大都市全滅作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Salvage, the Vacuum Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daitoshi Zenmetsu Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21472" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンゼル星よりの使者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet Angel (aka Messenger from Planet Angel)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Boshi yori no Shisha</title>
<summary>The Washington International Police Office obtains information that planet Angel, an ally planet of the earth, has been attacked by planet Satan. Learning that a messenger from planet Angel has crash-landed in Africa, Akira rushes to the scene. He tries to save the messenger, who is just barely breathing. Akira then learns about the miserable circumstances of the war through telepathic communication with Nina, and fumes over the fact that planet Saturn is controlled by his archrival Hans Engel.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21473" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">死の湖の対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown at Death Lake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shi no Mizuumi no Taiketsu</title>
<summary>Dr. Michaelsky, who has been tormented by his own guilty conscience for having once cooperated in the manufacture of the atomic bomb, becomes involved in the construction of a "city of science," partly to make amends for his wrongdoings. But the Nazis plan to deprive him of the city once it is complete.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21474" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">死火山の怪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mystery of the Dead Volcano</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikazan no Kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21475" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">スペードバイキング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spade Viking</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Spade Viking</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21476" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙ランドの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of Spaceland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu Land no Himitsu</title>
<summary>Spaceland is under construction in the Sahara in Africa, and His Highness Tsuara meanwhile happens upon treasure at the construction site. The International Police obtain information that His Highness Tsuara is in fact Hans Engel. In the meantime, Akira receives an invitation to Spaceland. The moment Akira opens the envelope, he immediately takes ill due to the poison it contained. Rescued just in time with the help of an antidote, Akira flies to the Sahara to overthrow Hans.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21477" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビッグX登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Big X Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Big X Toujou</title>
<summary>Dr. Asagumo has been hiding in his body the blueprint (in metal form) of the secret weapon Big X. His friend, Dr. Hanamaru, extracts the metal from Dr. Asagumo-now in critical condition-but it is then snatched by a Nazi. Not knowing how to use the metal, the Nazis experimentally inject it into a mouse to see what will happen. Seeing that they create a huge mouse that attacks the town, Akira volunteers to be injected with Big X.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21478" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻の海賊船</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Phantom Pirate Ship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no Kaizokusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21479" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">仮面の男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Masked Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamen no Otoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21480" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れビッグX</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run, Big X!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashire Big X</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21481" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">軽くて重い男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fire Horse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karukue Omoi Otoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21482" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライオン帝国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lion Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lion Teikoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21483" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロボット撃破指令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Robot Bombing Order</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Robot Gekiha Shirei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21484" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙人スナルリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spaceman Sunaruri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuujin Sunaruri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21485" update="2012-09-09">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">盗まれた実験</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stolen Experiment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nusumareta Jikken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21486" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの耳を狙え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Target That Ear</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Mimi o Nerae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21487" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">パール博士の発明</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dr. Pearl`s Invention</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pearl-hakase no Hatsumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21488" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">蟻地獄作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ant Lion Campaign</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arijigoku Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21489" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">毒ガス列車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Poisonous Gas Train</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doku Gas Ressha</title>
<summary>The town where Akira and Nina have been hiding falls under Nazi control. Growing impatient with the tyranny of the Nazis, Akira petitions the enemy leader, Hans Engel, to stop torturing the people in the town in exchange for Big X. Hans chuckles to himself, and decides to challenge Akira to a showdown on the footbridge.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21490" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">大怪鳥ヒンメル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Himmel, the Big Mysterious Bird</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daikai Tori Himmel</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21491" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴム人間の反乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Robot Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomu Ningen no Hanran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21492" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">カイザー0号との対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown with "Kaiser 0"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaiser 0 Gou to no Taiketsu</title>
<summary>A friendship treaty is to be signed between the Republic of Karst and Japan. But in the middle of the signing ceremony, a mysterious whirlwind arises and interferes with the proceedings. The president of the Republic of Karst mistakenly believes that the disturbances have been caused by Big X, and decides to abandon the friendship treaty with Japan. Akira finds out that the whirlwind has in fact been caused by an insect robot named Kaiser 0, and that it was manipulated by the Punch Party.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21493" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">月世界の対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown on the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gessekai no Taiketsu</title>
<summary>Dr. Hanamaru finally completes a rocket fueled by photon energy, which represents the fulfillment of a dream of human beings. Akira and Nina congratulate him from the bottom of their hearts on his outstanding accomplishment. But a man who is trying to take away the invention is monitoring every process of the test: that man is Hans Engel. Tricked by the cunning Hans, Akira is unable to rescue Dr. Hanamaru and the photon rocket, and Akira himself is shot away into space. He is just barely saved by a rescue rocket of the International Police, but Hans obstinately continues to attack Akira using a giant robot. So begins a showdown on the moon between Hans and Akira.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21494" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">セントローザの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of St. Rosa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saint Rosa no Himitsu</title>
<summary>The bell of the St. Rosa Church in Rosaland has become a familiar symbol of peace for the people, until the bell is stolen. Akira and the party hear an episode about the bell from the church guard. They are told that the bell holds the key to hidden treasures. According to the guard, if the single bell that sounds the bell of the church is chosen from among the 108 bells in the cave, the hidden door to the treasure in the cave opens. Akira and his party set out to protect the treasure.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21495" update="2016-10-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海の墓場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cemetery of the Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi no Hakaba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21496" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔の太陽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sun of the Devil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma no Taiyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21497" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">どれい狩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Slave Hunting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dorei Kari</title>
<summary>Akira departs for the Pamirs in pursuit of a famous scientist who has gone missing. Arriving there, he is mistaken as a spy of the Nazis and captured by the locals, who are treated badly by the Nazis. Akira transforms into Big X and plays a crucial role in saving the captive scientist and local people.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21498" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">海底秘密研究所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Space Tiger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitei Himitsu Kenkyuujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21499" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">人面獣ゾンビー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zombie, the Human-Faced Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinmen-juu Zombie</title>
<summary>All the scientists who have been investigating the ruins of the Nine Empire on top of Mt. Yelv have gone missing. As the leader of the scientists was a friend of Dr. Hanamaru, the doctor departs for the site with Akira and his party. But the group is shot at by an unseen foe, and strays into the mountain. Akira and his party find out that a mysterious thief called "Dump of the Walta Group" is manipulating things behind the scenes. After a battle with them, Akira and his men succeed in rescuing the scientists. But the giant human-faced beast Zombie, protector of the ruins, stands in the way of Big X.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21500" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">無重力線</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Weightless Line</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mujuuryokusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="55102" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">大くらげ出現</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Giant Jellyfish Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Kurage Shutsugen</title>
<summary>A large tanker is attacked by a mysterious giant jellyfish in the waters surrounding Japan. The Akatsuki, a defense warship, departs to exterminate the jellyfish, but the task is beyond its capacity. Even Akira and the party who joined to offer their support are swallowed by the jellyfish. This giant jellyfish is actually a giant robot that Hulahope, the boss of the Chinchira Party, has developed. The mammoth jellyfish unceasingly attacks oil tankers, bringing the world into a serious oil crisis.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="168675" update="2015-05-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビッグX 00</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 0</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Big X 00</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180938" update="2016-10-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
