<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1119" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1969-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>1969-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dororo to Hyakkimaru</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">どろろ (1969)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dororo and Hyakkimaru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Dororo (1969)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">どろろと百鬼丸</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dororo</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8770" type="Alternative Setting">Dororo</anime>
<anime id="13946" type="Alternative Setting">Dororo (2019)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5293" approval="2" total="4">Sabu to Ichi Torimono Hikae</anime>
<anime id="3494" approval="1" total="5">Onikirimaru</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="294857">Surprisingly dark for a kids show and interesting use of animation for the time period.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/37.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1195" type="Original Work">Tezuka Osamu</name>
<name id="833" type="Work">Mushi Production</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="2078" type="Music">Tomita Isao</name>
<name id="3665" type="Chief Direction">Sugii Gisaburou</name>
</creators>
<description>Hyakkimaru is a young man who lacks 48 body parts because they were taken from him by demons before birth, which was promised by his father, Kagemitsu Daigo to obtain his wish to take over the country. When the baby boy was born, he was missing 48 parts of his body, and thus was abandoned, thrown into a river. Hyakkimaru has grown up and now has obtained fake body parts so he can eliminate the 48 demons that were made from his body, to retrieve his missing body parts. Along for the adventure is the boy thief, Dororo, that he becomes friends with.
Source: ANN
Note: Before this anime series was made, there was a colour http://anidb.net/a8770 [Dororo pilot movie] created in 1968.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="98">6.97</permanent>
<temporary count="98">6.43</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>90254.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1320</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5760</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>621</identifier>
<identifier>nxikeg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/jp/anime/37.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tezukaosamu.net/en/anime/37.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dororo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>どろろと百鬼丸#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5209</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89608</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>974</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>74</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3363" parentid="2876" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-04">
<name>Buddhism</name>
<description>Buddhism is a nontheistic religion or dharma, "right way of living", that encompasses a variety of traditions, beliefs and practices largely based on teachings attributed to Siddhartha Gautama, commonly known as the Buddha ("the awakened one").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169453.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3763" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>Sekai Meisaku Gekijou</name>
<description>World Masterpiece Theatre is a Japanese TV anime staple that showcases an animated version of a different classical book or story each year. It originally aired from 1969 to 1997 and then resumed in 2007. WMT series were originally produced by http://anidb.net/cr833 [Mushi Production] and Zuiyo Eizo, and then by the latter`s successor http://anidb.net/cr728 [Nippon Animation], and originally air primarily on http://anidb.net/cr741 [Fuji Television].
The series has been known by various different names over the years, often reflecting changes to the sponsors, but "World Masterpiece Theatre" is the name most commonly used by viewers. Nippon Animation`s official English name for the series is The Classic Family Theater Series.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>234097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6028" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-10-12">
<name>Shintoism</name>
<description>Shintoism presents a blessed being or creature that governs over areas of terrain, general space of existence, or an individual object (be it alive or inanimate). Everything has its own "spiritual essence".
Defined as the earliest Japanese thoughts of an unified religion, the word Shinto comes from the Chinese hanzi "神道", combining two kanji: "shin" (神), meaning gods or spirits; and "tō" (道), meaning a philosophical path or study.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="94490" type="main character in" update="2018-03-26">
<name>Dororo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3286" picture="24711.jpg">Matsushima Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94531" type="main character in" update="2018-03-14">
<rating votes="2">7.33</rating>
<name>Hyakkimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3380" picture="187130.jpg">Nozawa Nachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94559" type="appears in" update="2018-03-15">
<name>Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15692" picture="228933.jpg">Mutou Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94640" type="appears in" update="2018-03-19">
<rating votes="1">8.17</rating>
<name>Tahoumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3371" picture="24398.jpg">Nakamura Shuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94721" type="appears in" update="2018-03-22">
<name>Daigo Kagemitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215226.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1818" picture="20692.jpg">Naya Gorou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94755" type="appears in" update="2018-03-23">
<name>Zatou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215291.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3790" picture="50436.jpg">Takiguchi Junpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94756" type="appears in" update="2018-03-23">
<name>Tanosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1818" picture="20692.jpg">Naya Gorou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94759" type="appears in" update="2018-03-23">
<name>Kanekozou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23892" picture="66565.jpg">Tamura Kinto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94760" type="appears in" update="2018-03-23">
<name>Nuinokata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6374" picture="30939.jpg">Kitahama Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="17850" update="2011-06-30">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Official Preview Clips</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21121" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">百鬼丸の巻・その一</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of Hyakkimaru: Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakkimaru no Maki: Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>Daigo Kagemitsu, a warrior in the Age of Civil Wars offers his soon-to-be-born baby`s body to the 48 devils as a sacrifice to fulfill his ambitions. Then the baby is born with 48 parts of his body missing, and is thrown into the river because of its horrifying ugliness. The baby, however, survives. A gifted doctor supplies him with the missing parts, and he grows up with the name "Hyakkimaru." Wherever he goes, demons follow him, but he attacks them with a sharp sword attached to his artificial arms. One day, he meets a thief girl called Dororo who can steal swords of any kind.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21122" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖怪万代の巻・その一</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of Bandai: Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkai Bandai no Maki: Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>Hyakkimaru and Dororo are sleeping in the open by the river when they come across a goblin called Kanekozo. The next day, when they tell the villagers of their encounter with the harmless goblin, they are caught by the villagers and confined in a small hut on the grounds of a female headman called Bandai. That night, a horrifying monster comes out of the old well by the hut. Hyakkimaru tries to destroy it.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21123" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖刀似蛭の巻・その二</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of the Demon Sword Nihil: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youtou Nihiru no Maki: Sono Ni</title>
<summary>Tanosuke succeeds in getting the sword back after he sets fire to the blacksmith`s hut where Dororo is barricading herself. Immediately after that, she starts to slay the villagers. The sword has become even more bloodthirsty. Hyakkimaru saves Dororo and confronts Tanosuke, engaging in battle with the evil sword. During the fight, Tanosuke realizes he is controlled and manipulated by the sword, and thrusts it through his body. Tanosuke does not want to be taken over by a monster, and this, his act as a human being, breaks the sword into pieces. When Hyakkimaru defeats the evil sword, his real eyes are returned. What he sees with those eyes, however, is a ruthless human world that tries to exclude him by discrimination.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21124" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">3.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人食い大木</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Man-Eating Tree</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitokui Taiboku</title>
<summary>A huge tree that is over 2000 years old is going to be cut down because it was hampering the construction of a fortress. Hyakkimaru happens to be there, and he senses something very strange coming from the huge tree. While it is not unusual for old trees to have spirits dwelling in them, this huge tree seems to have something evil about it. A woodcutter tries to drive his axe into the tree, saying that he senses nothing, but Hyakkimaru stops him and tries to cut the tree with his sword. Then his arm, with the sword, is swallowed into the tree. Dororo is stunned to see her big brother being eaten by the tree!
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21125" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白面不動の巻・その二</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of the Fair Fudou: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shirafu Fudou no Maki: Sono Ni</title>
<summary>Hakumenfudo demands that its subordinate get Dororo`s face, telling her to throw Dororo into the basin of the waterfall. Meanwhile, she has developed tender feelings toward Dororo, who is attached to her as if she were her own mother. So she cannot obey Hakumenfudo`s orders. When she manages to escape from Hakumenfudo with Dororo, however, stray dogs manipulated by Fudo attack her, tearing her body into pieces. The dogs try to attack Dororo next, but Hyakkimaru defeats them all. He has come into the mountains following the smell of demons. Hyakkimaru finds out about the monster Hakumenfudo that haunts the waterfall, and defeats it. Then Hakumenfudo, who has killed many ascetics by taking their faces, turns out to be just the mold on the rocks.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21126" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="3">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まいまいおんば</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Moth Mother</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maimai Onba</title>
<summary>On the way, Hyakkimaru senses an unusual evil air when he passes by a cow-drawn cart. The cart is drawn by the warrior Sabame riding with his wife Maimaionba. She also senses something extraordinary about Hyakkimaru, and asks Sabame to kill him. Hyakkimaru dodges the attack, and sneaks into the house of Maimaionba to find out what she really is. In the basement, he finds numerous moth eggs. They are all Maimaionba`s eggs. As it turns out, she is a huge moth-monster with silver powder.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21127" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ばんもんの巻・その一</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of the Banmon: Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Banmon no Maki: Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>On a small hill stands a huge board called "Banmon." When Hyakkimaru and Dororo decide to stay there for a night, the fox goblin of Kuo attacks them. At dawn, the fox goblin disappears, but then the execution of those who have tried to cross the border without permission begins. Kagemitsu, who has put a curse on Hyakkimaru, takes command of the execution. Getting angry about the brutality of it all, Hyakkimaru challenges Kagemitsu without knowing that he is his own father. Looking at Hyakkimaru`s abnormal body, Kagemitsu realizes that the young man is the caterpillar-like baby that he had thrown into the river. Kagemitsu gets flustered, and withdraws his soldiers. Later, Hyakkimaru meets a young warrior named Tahomaru. They fight at first, but soon become friends. Together the two decide to defeat the fox goblin of Kuo.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21128" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四化入道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shike Nyuudou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shike Nyuudou</title>
<summary>Dororo`s arm gets caught in a fishing-trap when she is bathing at the riverside. Hyakkimaru finds her asking for help, and goes to a nearby temple to borrow a tool to loosen the trap. The chief priest of the temple willingly lends him the tool, but Hyakkimaru senses something odd about the priest. When he returns to the river, Dororo is gone. Taking it to be the doing of the chief priest Shikanyudo, he challenges him to a fight. In fact, the priest was buried alive by a warrior for refusing to surrender the temple, and later turned into a demon. Then the spirit got mixed with the spirits of mice, weasels and moles, finally turning into a monster. After killing the monster, Hyakkimaru puts the priest`s spirit to rest with respect.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21129" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="3">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖馬みどろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Demon Horse, Midoro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youba Modoro</title>
<summary>Tokino Kageyuki is almost within reach of becoming a leader of warriors thanks to his pet horse Midoro`s good work, but he is conceited enough to believe that the credit all goes to him. Then he blames Midoro`s pony for causing Midoro to be slow by following her around. He takes the pony away from her and sells it off. It turns out that Dororo and Hyakkimaru buy the pony. Losing her child breaks Midoro`s heart. Then Midoro becomes a ferocious horse and gets possessed by a demon, setting the city aflame and killing Kageyuki. Although she has become a monster, she understands her pony`s love for her. Nevertheless, Hyakkimaru defeats the monster-horse Midoro with his sword.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21130" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">百鬼丸の巻・その二</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of Hyakkimaru: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakkimaru no Maki: Sono Ni</title>
<summary>Hyakkimaru is tired of being followed by Dororo, so he tells her his cursed history in an attempt to make her go away. The story goes like this: Hyakkimaru was born without arms and legs, like a caterpillar, but a doctor named Juko supplied him with artificial limbs and glass eyes so that he could manage to survive. Hyakkimaru, however, was always followed by demons. They were drawn to him, probably because he should have been dead with such a body. Being in Hyakkimaru`s company therefore meant being constantly scared of demons. Hearing the story, however, Dororo replies that she finds it "interesting." Hyakkimaru continues on his journey, believing the mysterious voice that tells him, "If you kill 48 devils, you will have a complete body." At a temple that was burned down during the war, he meets a girl called Mio, who is taking care of orphans. Her gentleness touches him and his mind is calmed for the first time in his life, but warriors break into the temple and kill Mio and the orphans.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21131" update="2018-04-19">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖怪もんもん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Demon Monmon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkai Monmon</title>
<summary>There is only one girl in the village. When asked, she says all the villagers have gone to the mountains to look for gold and have never come back. Hearing that there is plenty of gold lying around in the mountains, Dororo also goes there with the girl guiding her. Hyakkimaru thinks the villagers` disappearance did not happen recently. Sensing the presence of a monster in the mountains, Hyakkimaru follows Dororo. Waiting there is a monster called Momonga. The girl is, in fact, Momonga in disguise. She lures travelers into the mountains by telling them about the gold, and feeds her huge slug on them.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21132" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">8.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖怪万代の巻・その二</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of Bandai: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkai Bandai no Maki: Sono Ni</title>
<summary>Kanekozo is a spirit born of buried money. When he tells Hyakkimaru the location of the loot, the villagers dig up the ground to find the money right where the spirit has said it was. It turns out to be the money once stolen by the horrifying monster. The female headman Bandai, who pities the villagers, has been giving them money. When Hyakkimaru hears this story, he guesses what the monster really is. At night, when the monster assaults the village again, Hyakkimaru injures the monster with the help of the villagers. The monster runs into Bandai`s mansion, where Dororo sees it transform into Bandai. As Hyakkimaru has guessed, the female headman is the monster, and she has been controlling the village by giving them money that she had taken from them in the first place. The monster turns out to be a human face-wound on her body.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21133" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖怪土坊主</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Demon Tsuchibouzu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkai Tsuchi Bouzu</title>
<summary>There lives a pauper called Gutaro in the city. He is said to be very lazy, sitting at the same place and not bothering to move for ten years. In truth, however, it is not laziness that keeps him there. He cannot move even if he wants to. On his buttocks is written a text of a sutra, which makes him sit with his buttocks touching the ground in order to keep a monster underground. Out of pity, Dororo washes the pauper`s body, and at the same time washes away the sutra. Then a monster called Tsuchibozu jumps out of the ground. Hyakkimaru fights against the monster, but gets pulled into the ground instead.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21134" update="2018-04-19">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="3">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おんぶら鬼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Piggy-Back Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onbura Oni</title>
<summary>A Jizo wanted a babysitter. It had been threatening the villagers that it would ruin the village unless they baby-sit it for it. Whenever they send a babysitter, however, the babysitter is eaten to death. So the villagers are forced to hire a traveler, who knows nothing about it, as a babysitter under good conditions. Unaware of the situation, Dororo happily offers herself as a babysitter when she sees the advertisement. Hyakkimaru senses an evil air filling the village. Then he finds out that the Jizo is possessed by a spider-monster. The monster attacks the babysitter tied to the back of the Jizo with a string, and feeds on it.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21135" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="3">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の妖怪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Final Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-other">The Last Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Youkai</title>
<summary>On learning that poor farmers like his late parents are going to start a riot, Dororo also volunteers to join them, and parts with Hyakkimaru. Hyakkimaru continues his journey alone, defeating monsters one after another. Now he need kill only one more monster to make it the 48 monsters he needs to get his body back. Then a strange old woman says to him, "The last monster is your father, Daigo Kagemitsu." Kagemitsu, who has given his soul to a monster in order to become a general, seems in the end to have become a monster himself. In order to defeat his father, who has put a curse on him, Hyakkimaru runs to his father`s house. There he finds Dororo held in captivity. Kagemitsu is executing the rioting farmers. When he sees Hyakkimaru, who has killed his beloved son, his fury is uncontrollable. He offers his wife, Onui, as a sacrifice, and asks for the unearthly power of monsters. Then he becomes the 48th monster, and the last fight between Kagemitsu and Hyakkimaru begins.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21136" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖怪かじりんこん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Demon Kajirinkon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkai Kajirinkon</title>
<summary>Dororo and Hyakkimaru set out on a journey again. They spend a night at a temple where Dororo accidentally sets free Amanojaku, who has been trapped by a guardian god at the temple gate. Amanojaku happily runs down to the village where he causes uproar by doing countless misdeeds. Dororo tries to stop him, but the villagers chase her, taking her for Amanojaku`s friend. During her flight, she knocks down a stone monument, but this is no ordinary monument. It is there to seal off a dreadful monster. Now the seal is broken, and a monster called Hitokuchi-kajiri rushes out of the ground. It has been born of the perpetual greediness of an extremely cruel headman after his death. Dororo and Amanojaku run into a five-storied pagoda, with Hitokuchi-kajiri after them.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21137" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いないいない村</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Empty Empty Village</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inai Inai Mura</title>
<summary>Dororo and Hyakkimaru run into a warrior called Tawara Gorobei, who has enough superhuman strength to easily lift an unruly bull over his head, and the three travel together. Gorobei boasts that he does not believe in monsters and demons, but as long as he is with Hyakkimaru, demons are drawn to them. Soon after they enter a deserted village, a ghostly air engulfs them. Then weird things begin to happen. Blood drips from the ceiling, furniture moves on its own, houses suddenly collapse, and cats and crows are manipulated by demons. Gorobei is scared not of these weird incidents but of Hyakkimaru, who challenges monsters as a matter of course.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21138" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白面不動の巻・その一</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of the Fair Fudou: Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shirafu Fudou no Maki: Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>Being left by Hyakkimaru, Dororo cries all alone in the world. Then a woman appears in front of her. She looks exactly like her late mother Ojiya. So when the woman gently comforts her, Dororo goes to her house. Dororo sees her dear mother`s image in her, becomes fond of her, and starts to depend on her. The woman, in fact, is working for a monster called Hakumenfudo, who lives in a waterfall among the mountains. As Hakumenfudo does not have its own face, it steals faces from among the ascetics who practice in the waterfall. Now it is after Dororo`s face.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21139" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ばんもんの巻・その三</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of the Banmon: Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Banmon no Maki: Sono San</title>
<summary>Sukeroku`s parents are killed and the village is burned in a surprise attack by Tahomaru`s army. Sukeroku and Dororo are taken to Banmon with their companions to be crucified there. Sukeroku is shot dead with several arrows. Then it is Dororo`s turn, but Hyakkimaru saves her in the nick of time. Seeing Hyakkimaru save the enemy, Tanomaru tries to slay him, only to be killed by Hyakkimaru instead. Watching all this, the fox goblin of Kuo laughs scornfully, "You have just killed your own brother." Now Kagemitsu, who is raging about his son`s death, begins to pursue Hyakkimaru. He finally loses hope to live as a man, for he has killed his brother, has turned from his mother, and has made his father pursue him. He is driven to so much despair that he closes his heart even to Dororo...
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21140" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">9.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無残帖の巻・その一</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of the Misery Chronicles: Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muzan Jou no Maki: Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>While nursing Dororo, who has fallen ill from a fever during their journey, Hyakkimaru comes to know of Dororo`s tragic past for the first time. Dororo was born to poor farmers. In order to survive, they become thieves. In time, her father, Hibukuro, becomes the leader of bandits who attack only warriors and the rich. The three of them, however, are turned over to government officers when Hibukuro`s subordinate betrays him. They escape from jail during a storm, with pursuers chasing them from behind. Hibukuro takes on the pursuers alone so that his wife and child can escape.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21141" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ばんもんの巻・その二</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of the Banmon: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Banmon no Maki: Sono Ni</title>
<summary>Kagemitsu suggests that Hyakkimaru become an officer, counting on his ability to defeat the fox goblin. Hyakkimaru, however, goes looking for Dororo, who has been thrown into the river after an unjustified lynching. There, he meets the woman who is his mother. Even though he does not know his mother`s face, he sees in the woman`s eyes total love and sorrow. Although they have lead separate lives, the bond between mother and her child reveals who they are in a flash. Hyakkimaru, however, turns his back on his mother. Meanwhile, a boy called Sukeroku saves Dororo on the other side of Banmon, and they become friends. Sukeroku explains the circumstances under which Banmon`s neighboring countries have come to hate each other. Both countries would still be friendly if it were not for the wall. Could they someday mend things between them? Sukeroku looks up at the wall while, beyond his gaze, Tahomaru is preparing his army for the launch of an all-out attack on the other side.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21142" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">9.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無残帖の巻・その二</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of the Misery Chronicles: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muzan Jou no Maki: Sono Ni</title>
<summary>The leader of the pursuers turns out to be the subordinate who had betrayed Hibukuro. The traitor does not kill him because he is indebted to Hibukuro. Instead, he shoots arrows into Hibukuro`s legs, making him unable to move. Hibukuro, unable to walk, and his wife Ojiya, who carried a baby in arms, in the end fall as low as beggars. Then a warrior kills Hibukuro as a joke. After some time, Ojiya passes away protecting Dororo from the harsh cold. Dororo looks back on her past as she suffers from fever, but reminds herself that she is still alive.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21143" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖刀似蛭の巻・その一</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scroll of the Demon Sword Nihil: Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youtou Nihiru no Maki: Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>A sword has the evil power of controlling its owner by taking over his mind. A man called Tanosuke, who is possessed by this evil power, suddenly challenges Hyakkimaru to a fight. The sword is craving for blood. Sword-thief Dororo is so fascinated by the sword that she finally steals it from Tanosuke. The evil sword, however, gains control of Dororo`s mind at the same time, turning her into a bloodthirsty killer who slays people one after another. After causing uproar in the city, Dororo barricades herself into a blacksmith`s hut. Tanosuke, now without the evil sword, is so desperate to get it back that he sets fire to the hut where Dororo is hiding.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21144" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海獣ビラビラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Birabira the Sea Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaijuu Birabira</title>
<summary>Dororo and Hyakkimaru come to a fishing village. Dororo pulls out a harpoon from a rock just for fun. The harpoon, however, has contained a skeleton ray-monster called Bira-Bira. Hyakkimaru dives into the sea following Bira-Bira, which has escaped from underground to the sea. After a duel, Hyakkimaru disappears. The villagers think he must be dead. So in order to calm Bira-Bira`s anger, they throw Dororo and a village girl into the sea as sacrifice.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21145" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷火犬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raikaken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raikaken</title>
<summary>Dororo and Hyakkimaru are approaching a pass with a puppy when a monster dog suddenly attacks them. The dog controls thunder, hitting Dororo unconscious with lightning and throwing Hyakkimaru down to the bottom of a ravine. In a village down the river where Hyakkimaru is saved, he learns that dog fighting is popular. When he sees the cruelty happening there, he realizes what the monster dog on the pass is. It must be the accumulated grudge held against humans by dogs that have been treated so badly. More terrifying than the monster is the cruelty of humans that can change even the faithful dog into a monster. Hyakkimaru destroys the monster dog, nevertheless, and buries the corpse with due ceremony.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="21146" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="2">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖怪どんぶりばら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monster Donburibara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkai Donburibara</title>
<summary>A greedy village headman is possessed by the monster Donburibara. It makes the village headman eat as much cereal as possible, and enters his body from the navel to siphon off all nourishment. So the village headman tries to eat up all the cereals in the village, because he does not get full no matter how much he eats. Dororo and Hyakkimaru, who are passing by the village, destroy the monster. It turns out to be the spirit of a turtle in the marsh. The great turtle was too old to eat, so it sent out its spirit in the form of a monster that feeds on others` nourishment.
Source: tezukaosamu.net</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="186984" update="2017-04-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2016-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extras: Episode 26 Storyboard</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187201" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187202" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187203" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
