<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11207" restricted="false">
<type>TV Special</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-08-13</startdate>
<enddate>2010-08-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Akai Shouzou: Char, Soshite Frontal e</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Gundam Recap</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">赤い肖像 ~シャア, そしてフロンタルへ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Portrait of the Red</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6517" type="Sequel">Kidou Senshi Gundam Unicorn</anime>
<anime id="715" type="Full Story">Kidou Senshi Gundam</anime>
<anime id="718" type="Full Story">Kidou Senshi Z Gundam</anime>
<anime id="719" type="Full Story">Kidou Senshi Gundam ZZ</anime>
<anime id="720" type="Full Story">Kidou Senshi Gundam: Gyakushuu no Char</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.gundam-unicorn.net/sp/event04.html</url>
<description>A recap of Gundam, Gundam Z, Gundam ZZ, and Char`s Counterattack as experienced by Char Aznable, as well as a precursor to Gundam Unicorn.
Originally a live event consisting of a public recitation done by Char`s voice actor with simultaneous screenings of the anime, the DVD version fades to and from the recitation and the anime.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="33">3.80</permanent>
<temporary count="33">5.04</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>172638.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14007</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2130</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3216" parentid="2626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>Universal Century</name>
<description>Refers to the Universal Century timeline in Gundam anime. Gundam anime with this tag all belong in the same universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3974" type="main character in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="332">9.00</rating>
<name>Char Aznable</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as the "Red Comet" for his high-speed attack tactics, Char is the most famous of Zeon`s ace mobile suit pilots. He earned his nickname by destroying five Federation battleships during the Battle of Loum, and after the attack on Side 7, he becomes the dreaded nemesis of the White Base crew. However, defeating the Federation isn`t the only thing on Char`s mind, and his distinctive mask hides the face of a young man bent on his own personal quest for revenge. As the story continues, Char begins putting his own complicated schemes into motion, even as he becomes distracted by his growing rivalry with the Gundam`s pilot.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85692.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="43418" type="main character in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="12">8.71</rating>
<name>Char Aznable</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The legendary "Red Comet" has now reappeared as the leader of his own Neo Zeon movement. During the One Year War, Char fought for the Principality of Zeon as an ace mobile suit pilot. He then helped found the AEUG resistance group, which opposed the tyranny of the Federation`s Titans faction - a role which put Char briefly on the same side as his former adversaries Amuro Ray and Bright Noa. However, Char`s new goal is to complete the work of his father Zeon Zum Deikun by forcing all of humanity to emigrate to space, and he once again faces Amuro as an adversary. Amongst themselves, Neo Zeon`s officers suspect that Char`s true purpose is simply to avenge himself upon Amuro, and that their glorious cause is merely an afterthought.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85674.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="168232" update="2015-04-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2010-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
