<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11210" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>131</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-07-05</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dragon Ball Super</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Super</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Chou (Super)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">DBS</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">DB Super</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドラゴンボール超[スーパー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dragon Ball Super</title>
<title xml:lang="ca" type="official">Bola de Drac Super</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">דרגון בול סופר</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">七龍珠超</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">龙珠超</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13657" type="Sequel">Dragon Ball Super: Broly</anime>
<anime id="1530" type="Prequel">Dragon Ball Z</anime>
<anime id="9314" type="Alternative Setting">Dragon Ball Z: Kami to Kami</anime>
<anime id="10742" type="Alternative Setting">Dragon Ball Z: Fukkatsu no "F"</anime>
<anime id="14086" type="Other">Super Dragon Ball Heroes</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="301225">This is what DBGT should have been although it has its flaws. For fans of the DB franchise. Good soundtrack though.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="415669">If you`re a fan of Dragon Ball, you`ll like DBS. The first 30 ish episode is about what we see in the 2 movies. After that, it becomes more and more interesting right until the last episode.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/dragon_s/</url>
<creators>
<name id="19524" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ide Takeo</name>
<name id="1902" type="Original Work">Toriyama Akira</name>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
<name id="2099" type="Character Design">Yamamuro Tadayoshi</name>
<name id="733" type="Work">Yomiko Advertising</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="15540" type="Music">Sumitomo Norihito</name>
<name id="12887" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsuji Miyako</name>
<name id="13415" type="Direction">Chioka Kimitoshi</name>
<name id="14075" type="Direction">Hatano Kouhei</name>
<name id="14841" type="Direction">Hatano Morio</name>
<name id="2168" type="Direction">Nagamine Tatsuya</name>
<name id="32460" type="Direction">Nakamura Ryouta</name>
</creators>
<description>Reuniting the franchise`s iconic characters, Dragon Ball Super will follow the aftermath of Goku`s fierce battle with Majin Buu, as he attempts to maintain earth`s fragile peace.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1133">4.67</permanent>
<temporary count="1155">6.53</temporary>
<review count="3">2.77</review>
</ratings>
<picture>174682.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17006</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30694</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/tv/dragon_s/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dragon_Ball_Super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドラゴンボール超</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3830</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>352869</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18302</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B077VTZ56H</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3738" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-05">
<name>aliens living on earth</name>
<description>There`s an alien or a hive of aliens blending into society near you!</description>
<picurl>70750.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4584" parentid="2637" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-13">
<name>time machine</name>
<description>A machine (or sometimes a living being) that accomplishes time travel. The details (what travels in which direction in time and how far) vary wildly from anime to anime.</description>
<picurl>214767.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6017" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>perpetual ongoing</name>
<description>No end in sight!
No matter what the genre may be or what the storyline consists of, this series just keeps on going... and on... and on.
The obvious downside to this is the lack of story-related focus, usually some vague goal is simply never reached. This lack of conclusion can tend to annoy, making the whole series pretty much pointless.
Examples: One Piece, Naruto, Bleach, Detective Conan, Dragon Ball (Z), or Pocket Monsters (Pokemon).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7131" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-05">
<name>Crunchyroll Anime Awards</name>
<description>Crunchyroll Anime Awards are annual awards given to recognize anime from the previous year. The awards were first held in January 2017. The judges create a short list in different categories and public votes for the winners are held online.</description>
<picurl>219996.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2085" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="689">8.50</rating>
<name>Kame Sennin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kame Sennin is an ancient and wise martial arts master and the first Earthling to wield the Kamehameha. Though he seems frail, he is a mighty warrior, having trained Grandpa Gohan, Gyuumaou, Son Gokuu, and others.</description>
<picture>135368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2103" type="main character in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="2804">8.56</rating>
<name>Son Gokuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son Gokuu is a Saiyajin warrior who was sent to Earth when he was a child.</description>
<picture>135352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2105" type="main character in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="1212">8.57</rating>
<name>Vegeta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vegeta is the prince of the Saiyajin race and http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu]`s most fearsome rival. He is a very prideful person and, as a full-blooded saiyajin, loves the prospect of a good battle.</description>
<picture>230630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="132" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6879" type="appears in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="62">5.32</rating>
<name>Kame</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch2085 [Kame Sennin]`s turtle.
He`s celebrating his 1000th birthday in http://anidb.net/e16565 [episode 117] of http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z]</description>
<picture>24911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3998" picture="33313.jpg">Fujimoto Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6881" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="128">4.59</rating>
<name>Oolong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oolong is a shapeshifting, anthropomorphic pig that uses his abilities for his own greedy desires. He was expelled from shapeshifting training for stealing the teacher`s underwear, so he lacks the ability to change his form for more than five minutes at a time without a break. He joins with Goku to search for the Dragon Balls and eventually steal them, but he abandons his plans. In Dragon Ball Z, he is often in the company of Roshi.</description>
<picture>135369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6917" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="56">4.03</rating>
<name>Puar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Puar is a soft-spoken shapeshifting blue creature and the constant companion of Yamcha. He uses his abilities to shapeshift into anything to help Yamcha rob passersby in the desert. Afterwards, he travels with Yamcha and Goku during Dragon Ball, and continues to live with Yamcha afterwards.</description>
<picture>135370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3057" picture="23959.jpg">Watanabe Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7015" type="appears in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="63">5.25</rating>
<name>Shenlong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shenron is the dragon that appears when someone collects all seven of Earth`s Dragon Balls and calls him forth. He will grant one wish and then vanish, scattering the 7 Dragon Balls throughout the Earth once again.</description>
<picture>25280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7089" type="appears in" update="2009-09-08">
<rating votes="40">4.41</rating>
<name>Uranai Baba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch2085 [Kame Sennin]`s older sister.</description>
<picture>25350.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9009" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="176">5.16</rating>
<name>Freezer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Freezer was the main antagonist in the Freezer Saga of http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z]. He`s an alien tyrant with plans of universal domination. He`s cunning, charismatic, arrogant, imperative and, of course, powerful. He possesses different abilities such as ki manipulation and transformation. He also has high survivability, as he could live on even when wounded and thrown away into outer space.</description>
<picture>133698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9915" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="187">5.58</rating>
<name>Son Gohan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gohan is introduced as the first son of the primary protagonist, Son Goku, and his wife, Chi Chi, in volume #17 of the original manga, or the premiere episode of its animated adaptation, Dragon Ball Z. Gohan is the first Saiyan/Human hybrid in the series.
As opposed to full-blooded Saiyans, whose hair stays the same from birth, Gohan`s is drawn at varying lengths, and changes markedly in style. Many of Yamcha`s hairstyles are used by Gohan at various points in his life.
Initially, Gohan is illustrated garbed in a Hanfu-like surcoat with the Chinese character 孫, fixed on the front and the four-star Dragon Ball fitted on top of his hat. Piccolo later supplies him with a keikogi fashioned after Goku`s, but substitutes it with the demon character "魔" as a sign of his admission into the Demon Tribe. Normally thereafter, Gohan is drawn with a keikogi modeled after Piccolo`s own, with the anime recoloring his wristbands from blue to red and, during the Cell Games tournament, his obi from red to blue, despite reverting to the original colors for the former. On Namek, Gohan is portrayed in battle armor worn by Frieza`s henchmen, having been given it by Vegeta in preparation for their encounter with Frieza. Prior to his second fight with Majin Buu, Gohan asks Kibito for an outfit resembling his father`s, and is then drawn in a keikogi identical to Goku`s.</description>
<picture>135354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11405" type="appears in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="18">6.47</rating>
<name>Bubbles</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bubbles is the monkey pet of Kaiou. He serves a special purpose during Kaiou`s training lessons, particularly one of two endurance tests, where trainees are instructed to chase after Bubbles in an effort to catch him.
His name is a reference to Michael Jackson`s pet monkey, who is also named Bubbles.</description>
<picture>34057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3998" picture="33313.jpg">Fujimoto Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11406" type="appears in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="7">6.09</rating>
<name>Gregory</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gregory is a little flying cricket and http://anidb.net/ch11407 [Kaiou]`s pet.
He only appears in the anime and in a few movies.</description>
<picture>34058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3702" picture="25829.jpg">Numata Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11407" type="appears in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="37">5.44</rating>
<name>Kaiou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaiou is the kaiou of the northern quadrant of the galaxy. His companion is a pet monkey named http://anidb.net/ch11405 [Bubbles] and in anime adaptation, http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z], he also has a flying cricket companion named http://anidb.net/ch11406 [Gregory]. If a fighter that was allowed to keep his body manages to reach his small planet at the end of Hebi no Michi (Snake Way in the English adaptations), Kaiou trains them. Before training any students though, he forces them to appeal to his strange sense of humor, catch Bubbles, and hit Gregory with a mallet.</description>
<picture>135374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11408" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="105">3.10</rating>
<name>Chaozu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chaozu is a small human that resembles a doll with white skin, red cheeks, and one hair under his hat. Though he is not physically strong, he is skilled with psychokinesis and telepathy</description>
<picture>135367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3271" picture="171421.jpg">Emori Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11410" type="appears in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="8">3.92</rating>
<name>Enma Daiou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Enma Daiou is the boss of all ogres, who judge the dead. He is based on the Hindu deity Yama. A line of souls leads to his office where he decides whether a soul goes to Heaven or Hell. Compared to the other oni, he is of a different colour, he wears a beard, he has two horns and a helmet (it is unclear whether the horns are his own or belong to the helm), and he is colossal in size.</description>
<picture>34063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11413" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="81">6.86</rating>
<name>Karin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karin is a Senbyou (immortal cat) and is at least 800 years old when introduced in Dragon Ball. He is a deity who lives at the top of Karin Tower. The tower is located right underneath Kami`s palace.</description>
<picture>34067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22" picture="231891.jpg">Uoken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11416" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="557">7.67</rating>
<name>Piccolo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Piccolo, whose full name is Piccolo Jr., was first introduced as the reincarnation of the evil http://anidb.net/ch22168 [Piccolo Daimaou] in http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], making him a demon and arch-rival of the primary protagonist, http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Son Gokuu]. However, it is later revealed that he is from the race of alien beings called Namekians and he decides to team up with http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] and his friends in order to beat newer, more dangerous threats.</description>
<picture>135357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11417" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="67">6.16</rating>
<name>Mr. Popo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is an immortal genie who tends the grounds of Kami`s Lookout and is bound there eternally as the gardener and caretaker. He uses a magic carpet for Instant Transportation. Though he may not appear to physically age, Mr. Popo is very old; having served Kami, the Guardian of Earth for hundreds of years, he also served Kami`s predecessor, as well as every other guardian of the Earth in the past. Being the loyal and faithful servant that he is, his purpose consists mainly of tending to Kami`s Palace, keeping the Lookout clean, helping to reconstruct Shenron if needed, and most importantly, taking care of Kami. He also tends to the ancient butterfly garden that he planted thousands of years ago, and enjoys the more simple things in life.</description>
<picture>34072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2401" picture="23194.jpg">Kawazu Yasuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11420" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="85">5.23</rating>
<name>Tenshinhan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Initially an enemy of Goku who was trained by Kame Sennin`s rival Tsuru Sennin, Tenshinhan soon makes peace with Goku and becomes a Z Fighter along with his friend Chaozu.</description>
<picture>135362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11421" type="appears in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="85">5.16</rating>
<name>Yajirobe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yajirobe is an overweight samurai that Goku meets in Dragon Ball. He is often considered to be rude, unmannered, timid, lazy, and cowardly. He helps Goku prepare for the battle against Piccolo Daimao, and continues to support Goku and his companions, though often from the sideline</description>
<picture>34076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11593" type="appears in" update="2009-09-08">
<rating votes="49">3.62</rating>
<name>Briefs Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Brief is an elderly, brilliant and eccentric scientist. He is Bulma`s father and founder of Capsule Corporation.</description>
<picture>35028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3268" picture="24747.jpg">Tanaka Ryouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11594" type="appears in" update="2009-09-08">
<rating votes="59">3.90</rating>
<name>Bulma no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bulma`s Mother`s primary role in the series is to take on a housewife-esque role at Capsule Corporation, not working and simply being the wife of a rich scientist.
Her name is unknown.</description>
<picture>35032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3271" picture="171421.jpg">Emori Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12210" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-21">
<rating votes="108">2.27</rating>
<name>Mr. Satan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mr. Satan (known as Hercule in the English adaptations) is a flamboyant martial artist. After http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] and his companions stop attending the Tenkaichi Budoukai, Mr. Satan starts winning them and becomes the reigning champion for many years.
On a Q&amp;A with mangaka http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira] published in Super Exciting Guide - Character Volume on April 3, 2009, it is revealed that Mr. Satan is just a stage/ring name and that his actual first name is "Mark". While it seems like a common name, it is actually written out in katakana as マーク (maaku). If you rearrange the syllables, as you would with many names in the series to derive their puns, you end up with akuma (meaning "devil" or "demon"), which is in concordance with his daughter`s name being a pun on the English word "devil".
During the Cell Games, he attempts to fight http://anidb.net/ch24822 [Cell], but even after being swatted away, he is given credit for Cell`s death by the media. He is soon called a world hero, gaining great wealth and a city named after him. Though Gokuu and his companions find his inflated ego and arrogance very annoying, he becomes close to them after befriending the good http://anidb.net/ch41758 [Majin Buu] and by helping defeat Kid Buu by using his appeal to the people of Earth to get energy for the Genki Dama. His daughter, http://anidb.net/ch12209 [Videl], marries http://anidb.net/ch9915 [Gohan].</description>
<picture>135363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12611" type="appears in" update="2009-10-27">
<rating votes="12">2.33</rating>
<name>Ginyu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ginyu is leader of the Ginyu Tokusentai (Ginyu Special Force) and posses the "Body Change" abillity to transfer his mind into another body.</description>
<picture>37951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13302" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="146">8.37</rating>
<name>Trunks</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son of Vegeta and Bulma; came from the future.</description>
<picture>189106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18382" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="137">4.77</rating>
<name>Trunks</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19619" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-22">
<rating votes="219">7.16</rating>
<name>Jinzouningen 18 Gou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jinzouningen 18 Gou (Android #18 in the English adaptations) is a fictional character who first appears in the Dragon Ball manga created by http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira], followed by the shows http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z] and http://anidb.net/a233 [Dragon Ball GT]. She is a mass murderer in http://anidb.net/ch13302 [Future Trunks]` timeline.
Originally a human, she and her brother were modified into cyborgs by http://anidb.net/ch18381 [Dr. Gero].
On a Q&amp;A with mangaka http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira] published May 2nd, 2014 it was revealed that her human name was Lazuli.
After http://anidb.net/ch20915 [Cell] is defeated, http://anidb.net/ch11414 [Kuririn] uses the Dragon Balls to wish for her and her brother to be turned into humans; http://anidb.net/ch7015 [Shenron] is unable to perform this task because of the unfathomable differences in power between him and the duo, so he wishes instead for their self destruct devices to be removed. Kuririn pursues her and, at some point, they marry and have a daughter named http://anidb.net/ch30874 [Marron].
To clear up the heavily espoused misconception that she is a pure android and therefore could not have a child, Kuririn went on to explain to http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Son Gokuu] during the Tenkaichi Budoukai Saga that she was originally human but that Dr. Gero just "remodeled her a little bit."</description>
<picture>135365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19620" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-22">
<rating votes="48">6.20</rating>
<name>Jinzouningen 17 Gou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jinzouningen 17 Gou (Android #17 in the English adaptations) is a fictional character who first appears in the Dragon Ball manga created by http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira], followed by the shows http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z] and http://anidb.net/a233 [Dragon Ball GT]. He is a mass murderer in http://anidb.net/ch13302 [Future Trunks]` timeline.
Originally a human, he and his sister were modified into cyborgs by http://anidb.net/ch18381 [Dr. Gero].
On a Q&amp;A with mangaka http://anidb.net/cr1902 [Toriyama Akira] published May 2nd, 2014 it was revealed that his human name was Lapis.
During the events of the Jinzouningen &amp; Cell arc, he and his sister drive around in a van with http://anidb.net/ch19618 [Jinzouningen 16 Gou], looking for http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu]. When they finally get to the Kame House, http://anidb.net/ch11416 [Piccolo] tells them Gokuu is not there and refuses to tell them where he went. Piccolo then challenges him to a battle and as they fight, Piccolo`s ki leads http://anidb.net/ch20915 [Cell] (who needs to absorb both jinzouningen to reach its perfect form) to the battlefield. Cell tells Jinzouningen 17 Gou to surrender so he can become a part of "greatness". He refuses and is then defeated during the ensuing battle.
After Cell is defeated, http://anidb.net/ch11414 [Kuririn] uses the Dragon Balls to wish for him and his sister to be turned into humans; http://anidb.net/ch7015 [Shenron] is unable to perform this task because of the unfathomable differences in power between him and the duo, so he wishes instead for their self destruct devices to be removed.</description>
<picture>68142.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2218" picture="226178.jpg">Nakahara Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22167" type="appears in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="26">6.44</rating>
<name>Jinzouningen 8 Gou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of http://anidb.net/ch18381 [Dr. Gero]`s early creations. He refuses to fight http://anidb.net/ch2116 [Gokuu] when told to, and instead helps him. The two quickly become friends.</description>
<picture>56095.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="22251" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="169">5.69</rating>
<name>Son Goten</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Goten is first introduced at age 7, basically appearing out of nowhere. He is the second son of Goku and ChiChi, and it is said he was born shortly before Goku died. There is no explanation as to why he was never shown or mentioned earlier.</description>
<picture>135356.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29319" type="appears in" update="2011-02-28">
<rating votes="27">8.75</rating>
<name>Trunks</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Trunks` Super Saiyajin version.</description>
<picture>66657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39361" type="appears in" update="2011-12-05">
<rating votes="14">5.56</rating>
<name>Great Saiyaman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Great Saiyaman is Son Gohan`s superhero disguise to hide his identity from his classmates.</description>
<picture>78058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41758" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="46">6.05</rating>
<name>Majin Buu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2405" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53770" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-19">
<rating votes="11">5.20</rating>
<name>Whis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Whis is the caretaker as well as trainer of http://anidb.net/ch53774 [Beerus], the god of destruction of Universe 7.
He and his siblings are one of the strongest beings in all of creation, only admitting that his father http://anidb.net/ch84322 [Daishinkan] and http://anidb.net/ch82121 [King of All] are stronger.</description>
<picture>60037.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53771" type="appears in" update="2015-08-09">
<rating votes="6">2.15</rating>
<name>Yogen-gyo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yogen-gyo is a blue fish which has prophetic powers, which http://anidb.net/ch53774 [Beerus] keeps as a pet.
Source: Dragon Ball Wikia</description>
<picture>135381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3929" picture="25678.jpg">Nakagawa Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53774" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="31">5.08</rating>
<name>Beerus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Beerus is the God of Destruction, an individual that`s been around for centuries having destroyed several planets, solar systems and races. Even the mighty saiyajin king Vegeta once bowed in terror infront of him. Beerus even sees Freezer as little more than a nuisance that was too far away to deal with.
Beerus spends most of his time either sleeping for decades at a time or traveling around the universe destroying planets, eating whatever people offer him or in general doing whatever he feels like doing.
Beerus might have a short temperament and with his title God of Destruction may sound quite evil but despite all this, he is not a bad guy in general but rather more of in the gray area, always honoring his words and not doing things unnecessarily.
He is currently the second strongest individual in the Dragonball world. http://anidb.net/ch9004 [Super Saiyajin 3 Gokuu] was nothing but a toy for him. Even after http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] ascended to Super Saiyajin God and came back with an increased power, he still did not manage to push Beerus to fight at more than 60% of his full power.
Note: As is the case with most of the main cast from Dragonball, Beerus`s name is a pun. In this case, it`s two puns meshed into one. The original pun was on the word `virus` as scriptwriter, Watanabe Yuusuke, stated in an interview with DVD &amp; Blu-ray Magazine that he had written a scenario in which the God of Destruction was actually the one responsible for originally infecting the Saiyajins with evil. However, when Toriyama Akira stepped in and changed a great deal of the movie`s backstory, he thought Beerus`s name was a pun on the English word `beer` and then followed suit by naming http://anidb.net/ch53770 [Whis] (ウイス or uisu) after `whiskey`, another alcoholic beverage.</description>
<picture>169214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55082" type="appears in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="17">5.75</rating>
<name>Super Saiyajin Gotenks</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135351.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55083" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="14">3.08</rating>
<name>Kuririn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135358.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55084" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="20">5.15</rating>
<name>Videl</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55085" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-22">
<rating votes="143">6.68</rating>
<name>Bulma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55086" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="2">1.50</rating>
<name>Yamucha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55087" type="appears in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="8">2.55</rating>
<name>Kibito Kaioushin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kibito Kaioushin is a result of Potara Fusion between http://anidb.net/ch67299 [Kaioushin] and his servant http://anidb.net/ch67300 [Kibito]. His personality is for the most part similar to the Kaioushin`s, except the unusual amount of concern he had for the damage the fight with http://anidb.net/ch41758 [Buu] was doing to his planet.
Source: Dragon Ball Wikia</description>
<picture>135378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2025" picture="23203.jpg">Oota Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55089" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="3">9.63</rating>
<name>Rou Kaioushin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3268" picture="24747.jpg">Tanaka Ryouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55090" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="28">3.39</rating>
<name>Chichi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3057" picture="23959.jpg">Watanabe Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55091" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="14">2.91</rating>
<name>Dende</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55092" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="7">5.71</rating>
<name>Pilaf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55093" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="9">3.50</rating>
<name>Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55094" type="appears in" update="2013-11-20">
<rating votes="14">3.92</rating>
<name>Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1811" picture="222844.jpg">Yamada Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55095" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="8">2.22</rating>
<name>Marron</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12784" picture="171452.jpg">Ushida Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55681" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-08">
<rating votes="9">7.63</rating>
<name>Vegetto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vegetto is the immensely powerful result of the fusion between Goku and Vegeta by the use of the Potara Earrings.</description>
<picture>60433.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="56030" type="appears in" update="2013-05-22">
<rating votes="5">8.66</rating>
<name>Gatchan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3133" picture="25830.jpg">Nishihara Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56034" type="appears in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="28">8.12</rating>
<name>Norimaki Arale</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Norimaki Arale is an android built by Norimaki Senbei, known for her naivety, energetic personality, superhuman strength, and lack of common sense. She is also nearsighted and needs to wear glasses. Senbei`s mission is to convince the other citizens of Penguin Village that Arale is no more than a typical 13-year-old girl, which they appear to believe in, despite taking notice to Arale`s numerous displays of superhuman athletic capability.
Source: Dragon Ball Wikia</description>
<picture>136959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56035" type="appears in" update="2013-05-22">
<rating votes="6">9.45</rating>
<name>Norimaki Senbei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56123" type="appears in" update="2013-05-24">
<rating votes="5">2.08</rating>
<name>Shi Buta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67299" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="5">8.66</rating>
<name>Shin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shin is the kaioushin of Universe 7; because of that, his life is linked to that of http://anidb.net/ch53774 [Beerus].
In Dragon Ball Z, he was one of five kaioushin of the universe, known as Higashi no Kaioushin and subordinate to http://anidb.net/ch107117 [Dai Kaioushin]. However, when http://anidb.net/ch104276 [Maijin Buu] appeared, three of his peers were killed and Buu absorbed Dai Kaioushin, making the surviving Shin the de facto Dai Kaioushin.
In Dragon Ball Super, the concept of five kaioushin is ignored and the terms Dai Kaioushin and Higashi no Kaioushin are never used. Instead, the show introduces figures similar to Shin from each universe and refers to them each of them simply as kaioushin.</description>
<picture>68154.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2025" picture="23203.jpg">Oota Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67300" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="3">5.59</rating>
<name>Kibito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kibito is the assistant of http://anidb.net/ch67299 [Shin].</description>
<picture>68171.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="609" picture="1835.gif">Aomori Shin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67999" type="appears in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="6">5.15</rating>
<name>Dabura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72561" type="appears in" update="2015-01-05">
<rating votes="3">1.64</rating>
<name>Sorbet</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4731" picture="27599.jpg">Saitou Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72562" type="appears in" update="2015-01-05">
<rating votes="4">1.60</rating>
<name>Tagoma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>167182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77685" type="appears in" update="2019-02-13">
<rating votes="6">1.03</rating>
<name>Vegeta-ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78089" type="appears in" update="2020-02-22">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Piiza</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38300" picture="236362.jpg">Morishita Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78090" type="appears in" update="2020-02-22">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Piroshiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244571.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78117" type="appears in" update="2015-11-04">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Galbi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2067" picture="186243.jpg">Hoshino Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78124" type="appears in" update="2020-02-22">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Caroni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3998" picture="33313.jpg">Fujimoto Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78125" type="appears in" update="2015-11-04">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Bee</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78649" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-26">
<rating votes="3">7.48</rating>
<name>Vados</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78969" type="appears in" update="2017-11-26">
<rating votes="2">2.93</rating>
<name>Champa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78995" type="appears in" update="2015-12-20">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Shisami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79026" type="appears in" update="2015-12-22">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Jaco</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81418" type="appears in" update="2016-03-30">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Tights</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81773" type="appears in" update="2016-04-19">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Zuno</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3395" picture="24474.jpg">Sonobe Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81824" type="appears in" update="2019-12-02">
<name>Monaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Monaka is a delivery man from Universe 7. Beerus recruits him in a tournament with Universe 6, and fabricates a claim that Monaka is stronger than Goku, in order to inspire Goku to become even stronger.</description>
<picture>68221.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81825" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="3">4.19</rating>
<name>Kyabe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyabe is a saiyajin from Universe 6. His inner super saiyajin awakes during a martial arts match with Vegeta. He plays an active role as the ace of the Sadala Defense Corps.</description>
<picture>241372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81826" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Botamo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Botamo is one of the strongest warriors from Universe 6. He has a rather confident attitude as he is extremely prideful in his abilities.
Source: dragonball wikia</description>
<picture>241385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81965" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="2">1.93</rating>
<name>Frost</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Frost is a member of the Frieza Race. He is a dirty fighter, who is extremely cunning and deceptive.
Source: dragonball wikia</description>
<picture>241375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82030" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="3">6.36</rating>
<name>Hit</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hit is a legendary hitman from Universe 6. During the martial arts tournament against Universe 7, Goku struggled against Hit`s time-stopping technique, "Time Tobashi".</description>
<picture>241373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="245665.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82121" type="appears in" update="2016-05-20">
<rating votes="2">1.25</rating>
<name>Zen`ou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>186907.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82955" type="appears in" update="2016-07-13">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Pan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83223" type="appears in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Potage</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4731" picture="27599.jpg">Saitou Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83224" type="appears in" update="2016-07-21">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Gryll</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="324" picture="223539.jpg">Saitou Jirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83269" type="appears in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="7">5.18</rating>
<name>Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mai from future.</description>
<picture>189109.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1811" picture="222844.jpg">Yamada Eiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83270" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="5">6.17</rating>
<name>Gokuu Black</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83271" type="appears in" update="2016-07-23">
<rating votes="16">4.85</rating>
<name>Bulma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bulma from future.</description>
<picture>189113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83278" type="appears in" update="2016-07-24">
<rating votes="2">4.17</rating>
<name>Gotenks</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189119.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="83286" type="appears in" update="2016-07-25">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Koneko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43794" picture="177499.jpg">Kingyo Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83818" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-15">
<rating votes="7">6.04</rating>
<name>Zamasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83890" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Gowasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gowasu is the kaioushin of Universe 10. The betrayal of his trusted disciple http://anidb.net/ch83818 [Zamasu] made him prudent.</description>
<picture>68173.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="300" picture="226467.jpg">Gotou Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84322" type="appears in" update="2019-12-02">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Daishinkan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86040" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-07">
<rating votes="3">7.06</rating>
<name>Gattai Zamasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86041" type="appears in" update="2016-11-07">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43794" picture="177499.jpg">Kingyo Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86042" type="appears in" update="2016-11-07">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Haru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194226.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12783" picture="225340.jpg">Fujii Yukiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86607" type="appears in" update="2016-12-06">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Dr. Mashirito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86608" type="appears in" update="2016-12-06">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Honmono Machine Mark 2</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45579" picture="211758.jpg">Kirimoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87210" type="appears in" update="2017-01-22">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Barry Kahn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87211" type="appears in" update="2017-01-22">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Amaguri Cocoa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88329" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Rou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rou is the kaioushin of Universe 9.</description>
<picture>68175.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4004" picture="77763.jpg">Masutani Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88330" type="appears in" update="2018-12-16">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Sidra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88331" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Kai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kai is the kaioushin of Universe 11. He is a kind spirit and an optimist.</description>
<picture>68176.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88332" type="appears in" update="2019-02-10">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Basil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88333" type="appears in" update="2019-02-17">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Bergamo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88544" type="appears in" update="2017-03-30">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Lavender</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88545" type="appears in" update="2017-03-30">
<rating votes="3">6.08</rating>
<name>Helles</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88546" type="appears in" update="2017-03-30">
<rating votes="3">4.19</rating>
<name>Toppo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88706" type="appears in" update="2019-11-24">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Anato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anato is the kaioushin of Universe 1. He has a gentle smile.</description>
<picture>200772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4587" picture="26895.jpg">Oda Yuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88707" type="appears in" update="2019-11-24">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Ea</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ea is the kaioushin of Universe 3. He believes that the robots of his universe could win the Tournament of Power.</description>
<picture>200773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2252" picture="223545.jpg">Naruse Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88708" type="appears in" update="2019-11-24">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Kuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuru is the kaioushin of Universe 4. He is a pompous and and self-conscious god who uses archaic speech.</description>
<picture>200774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88709" type="appears in" update="2019-11-24">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Oguma</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oguma is the kaioushin of Universe 5. He has a gentle personality and emphasizes the balance between intelligence and power.
Source: Toei</description>
<picture>200775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5342" picture="224845.jpg">Urawa Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88710" type="appears in" update="2019-09-24">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Vermoud</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Belmod is the god of destruction of Universe 11. He asks Jiren to defeat Son Goku during the Tournament of Power.</description>
<picture>200776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88711" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Agu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Agu is the kaioushin of Universe 12.</description>
<picture>200777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88724" type="appears in" update="2017-04-08">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Margarita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25522" picture="77632.jpg">Sasaki Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88785" type="appears in" update="2017-04-13">
<rating votes="2">1.64</rating>
<name>Bra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200964.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89265" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Dispo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89266" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Quitela</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3702" picture="25829.jpg">Numata Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89325" type="appears in" update="2017-05-15">
<rating votes="3">9.63</rating>
<name>Norimaki Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202469.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89549" type="appears in" update="2017-05-27">
<rating votes="2">3.33</rating>
<name>Obake</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3268" picture="24747.jpg">Tanaka Ryouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90048" type="appears in" update="2017-06-19">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Rensou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90079" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="7">6.25</rating>
<name>Caulifla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caulifla is a Saiyan from Universe 6 and a member of Team Universe 6 who participates in Zeno`s Tournament of Power. She is the the leader of a group of Saiyan criminals.
Source: dragonball wikia</description>
<picture>241383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2801" picture="23195.jpg">Komatsu Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90080" type="appears in" update="2017-06-24">
<rating votes="2">4.61</rating>
<name>Yuurin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90091" type="appears in" update="2017-06-25">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Rumsshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2401" picture="23194.jpg">Kawazu Yasuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90092" type="appears in" update="2017-06-25">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Cus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1429" picture="18686.jpg">Konno Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90096" type="appears in" update="2017-11-26">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Murichim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2988" picture="171404.jpg">Hirai Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90110" type="appears in" update="2019-12-02">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Kahseral</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kahseral is a cyborg warrior from Universe 11; he is also the general of Pride Troopers.</description>
<picture>68225.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90111" type="appears in" update="2017-06-25">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Mojito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90121" type="appears in" update="2017-06-25">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Ribrianne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39164" picture="149508.jpg">Kitagawa Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90122" type="appears in" update="2017-11-01">
<rating votes="2">2.93</rating>
<name>Brianne de Chateau</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209094.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39164" picture="149508.jpg">Kitagawa Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90196" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="5">2.95</rating>
<name>Kale</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kale is a Saiyan from Universe 6 and a member of Team Universe 6. Kale is Caulifla`s best friend, sister-figure, and protégé. She is the latest Legendary Saiyan of Universe 6, a demon warrior who appears once every 1,000 years.
Source: dragonball wikia</description>
<picture>241384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90201" type="appears in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Ganos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ganos is a fighter from Universe 4. His special ability makes him stronger each battle.</description>
<picture>209928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="552" picture="23199.jpg">Miura Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90315" type="appears in" update="2019-07-28">
<rating votes="6">6.47</rating>
<name>Jiren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204894.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="277" picture="223606.jpg">Hanawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90316" type="appears in" update="2017-07-08">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Arack</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204895.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23534" picture="74510.jpg">Murata Taishi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90317" type="appears in" update="2017-07-08">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Liquir</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90381" type="appears in" update="2019-11-30">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Napapa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Napapa is a fighter from Universe 10. He is a skilled practitioner of a martial art that resembles sumo wrestling.</description>
<picture>68215.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90382" type="appears in" update="2017-11-26">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Cocotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90400" type="appears in" update="2017-11-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Hop</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90685" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Narirama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Narirama is a cyborg warrior from Universe 3. Narirama was modified for the Tournament of Power.</description>
<picture>205621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90818" type="appears in" update="2019-12-02">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Kettol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68226.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3702" picture="25829.jpg">Numata Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90819" type="appears in" update="2019-12-02">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Tupper</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68227.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="50466" picture="236024.jpg">Volcano Oota</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91024" type="appears in" update="2019-11-24">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Peru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Peru is kaioshin of Universe 2. He is very fond of the battle maidens of his universe.</description>
<picture>206407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2405" picture="23217.jpg">Shioya Kouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91025" type="appears in" update="2017-11-01">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Jimizu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209093.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91026" type="appears in" update="2017-11-01">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Sanka Kuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91027" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Suu Roas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suu Roas is a female fighter from Universe 2 and a part of Ribrianne`s entourage.</description>
<picture>68180.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4006" picture="25936.jpg">Saitou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91028" type="appears in" update="2017-12-23">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Zirloin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50466" picture="236024.jpg">Volcano Oota</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91145" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Rozie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rozie is a female fighter from Universe 2 and a part of Ribrianne`s entourage.</description>
<picture>68181.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4006" picture="25936.jpg">Saitou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91146" type="appears in" update="2017-11-01">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Kakunsa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91147" type="appears in" update="2019-12-02">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Obuni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Obuni is a fighter from Universe 10.</description>
<picture>68219.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6854" picture="216700.jpg">Tani Atsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91152" type="appears in" update="2017-08-30">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Jokantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91153" type="appears in" update="2017-08-30">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Kantoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91230" type="appears in" update="2017-09-02">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Maji=Kayo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91231" type="appears in" update="2017-11-26">
<rating votes="2">2.19</rating>
<name>Caway</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1662" picture="25819.jpg">Kouda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91278" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Pran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pran is a fighter from Universe 2. He has the ability to deflect energy bullets.</description>
<picture>68179.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91279" type="appears in" update="2019-11-22">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Dr. Rota</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dr. Rota is a boar-like alien and a doctor from Universe 6. During the Tournament of Power, Vegeta throws him off the ring before he can demonstrate his fighting ability.</description>
<picture>68146.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91412" type="appears in" update="2017-09-14">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Minotaurus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50466" picture="236024.jpg">Volcano Oota</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91474" type="appears in" update="2019-11-24">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Fuwa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fuwa is the kaioushin of Universe 6. He was impressed by Son Gokuu`s fighting ability during the tournament between his universe and that of Universe 7.
Source: Toei</description>
<picture>207328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4004" picture="77763.jpg">Masutani Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91846" type="appears in" update="2019-11-22">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Iwan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iwan is the god of destruction of Universe 1. Contrary to his gentle appearance, his emotions are intense.
Source: Toei</description>
<picture>208566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91847" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Pilina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pilina is a Namek from Universe 6. He fights in an exquisite combination with Saonel.</description>
<picture>241374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91848" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Saonel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91849" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Biala</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91850" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Catopesra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Catopesra is a policeman from Universe 3. His belt allows him to alter between different modes.</description>
<picture>208576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4587" picture="26895.jpg">Oda Yuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91996" type="appears in" update="2017-10-28">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Monna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="321" picture="17158.jpg">Yamazaki Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91997" type="appears in" update="2017-10-28">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Campari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92070" type="appears in" update="2017-11-01">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Zarbuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209092.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2401" picture="23194.jpg">Kawazu Yasuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92195" type="appears in" update="2017-11-07">
<rating votes="3">3.36</rating>
<name>Kafla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="2801" picture="23195.jpg">Komatsu Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93038" type="appears in" update="2017-12-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Damon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93039" type="appears in" update="2017-12-26">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Mosco</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211236.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93040" type="appears in" update="2017-12-26">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Koitsukai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3702" picture="25829.jpg">Numata Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93041" type="appears in" update="2017-12-26">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Bollarator</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93042" type="appears in" update="2017-12-26">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Paparoni</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="417" picture="24695.jpg">Hori Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93047" type="appears in" update="2017-12-26">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Mule</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93048" type="appears in" update="2017-12-26">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Anilaza</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211258.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93864" type="appears in" update="2018-02-18">
<rating votes="3">2.58</rating>
<name>Kodomo Jiren</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213216.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38300" picture="236362.jpg">Morishita Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95922" type="appears in" update="2018-06-06">
<name>Vuon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95923" type="appears in" update="2018-06-06">
<name>Zoiray</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38300" picture="236362.jpg">Morishita Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95924" type="appears in" update="2018-06-06">
<name>Kunsi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218659.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95925" type="appears in" update="2018-06-06">
<name>Riribeu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100921" type="appears in" update="2019-02-18">
<name>Vikal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100922" type="appears in" update="2019-02-18">
<name>Dercori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100923" type="appears in" update="2019-02-18">
<name>Shousa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100924" type="appears in" update="2019-02-18">
<name>Majora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100925" type="appears in" update="2019-02-18">
<name>Nink</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100927" type="appears in" update="2019-02-19">
<name>Shantza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100945" type="appears in" update="2019-02-19">
<name>Jirasen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100946" type="appears in" update="2019-02-19">
<name>Hermila</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100947" type="appears in" update="2019-02-19">
<name>Rabanra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105541" type="appears in" update="2019-09-21">
<name>Pride Troopers</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>238614.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105579" type="appears in" update="2019-09-24">
<name>Jiin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jiin is the god of destruction of Universe 12.</description>
<picture>238707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4587" picture="26895.jpg">Oda Yuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105588" type="appears in" update="2019-09-26">
<name>Freezer Gun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Freezer Gun is the organisation controlled a majority of Universe 7 at the peak of its power and serves as the primary antagonistic force of the first half of the Dragon Ball Z series. Freezer`s father, Cold Daio was the leader of the organisation prior to passing control over to his son.
The organisation employs and enslaves powerful races, such as the Saiyans, to take over suitable planets so that they can be sold to the highest bidders, or alternatively to destroy planets which are determined to be not financially viable. Freezer`s forces are equipped with scouters, portable computers mainly used to measure power levels, and wear standard-issue battle armor which usually have dual shoulder guards, matching gloves and Buuts, and some form of skirt armor or crotch guard.
Freezer himself does not really consider his soldiers as an army, looking at them more as a convenient group of followers. In reality, the soldiers follow him and his relatives out of fear, though some soldiers are known to be fiercely loyal to Freezer such as the Ginyu Force.
Source: Wikipedia
When Freezer took over the business from his father in 732, most of the soldiers came from Planet Vegeta. However, Freezer became fearful of the power of the saiyajin and worked to make the army less saiyajin reliant. In five years from his accession, he destroyed Planet Vegeta, and cutting the size of the army in half.
In 762, the army took heavy losses while fighting on Planet Namek for the Dragon Balls, but was ultimately defeated.
In 764, the army attempt to invade Planet Earth, which proved even more fatal, as Freezer and Cold Daio were slain. Hence the army has reduced to a rump under http://anidb.net/ch72561 [Sorbet].
In 779, the army had become a shadow of its former self, as many words had liberated themselves. Thus Sorbet made a desperate attempt to fix the empire by resurrecting Freezer with the help of the Dragon Balls. However, Freezer was disinterested in fixing his empire and instead set on wasting the remaining resources of the army in order to pursue vengeance; a decision which ended in his, Sorbet`s and the bulk of the army`s soldiers` deaths.
In 780, when Freezer was resurrected for the second time, with the guidance of http://anidb.net/ch105587 [Beriblu] and http://anidb.net/ch105586 [Kikono], he decided to rebuild the army.</description>
<picture>67928.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107018" type="appears in" update="2019-11-17">
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<name>Dai 7 Uchuu Yakyuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="107019" type="appears in" update="2019-11-17">
<name>Dai 6 Uchuu Yakyuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="107020" type="appears in" update="2019-11-23">
<name>Auta Magetta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Auta Magetta comes from a robot-like race called "Metalman" from Universe 6. Despite being sturdy build, he is sensitive to insults.</description>
<picture>68149.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107050" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="1">9.65</rating>
<name>Dai 7 Uchuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>68182.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107051" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<name>Awamo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Awamo is a warm and sublime spirit, that is said to see everything.</description>
<picture>68128.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107052" type="appears in" update="2019-11-18">
<name>Sawaa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241334.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107059" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<name>Dai 6 Uchuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>68177.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107064" type="appears in" update="2019-11-20">
<name>Za Pricho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Za Pricho is a cyborg warrior from Universe 6. He was blown off the ground by new "Qi Gong gun"-technique of Tenshinhan and dropped out.</description>
<picture>68125.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107160" type="appears in" update="2019-11-27">
<name>Iru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iru is kaioushin of the Universe 8. He is a passionate planner.</description>
<picture>68166.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107184" type="appears in" update="2019-11-28">
<name>Dai 2 Uchuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>68178.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107187" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Dai 3 Uchuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>68183.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107188" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Nigurisshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68184.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107189" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Panchia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68185.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107211" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Dai 4 Uchuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>68187.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107212" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Konikku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68188.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107214" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Dai 9 Uchuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>68192.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107215" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Rouzeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68193.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107216" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Oregano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oregano is a fighter from Universe 9.</description>
<picture>68194.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4004" picture="77763.jpg">Masutani Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107217" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Hyssop</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68195.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107218" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Chappil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107219" type="appears in" update="2019-11-29">
<name>Sorell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107221" type="appears in" update="2019-11-30">
<name>Comfrey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Comfrey is a fighter from Universe 9.</description>
<picture>68196.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3268" picture="24747.jpg">Tanaka Ryouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107222" type="appears in" update="2019-11-30">
<name>Trio de Dangers</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="107250" type="appears in" update="2019-11-30">
<name>Dai 10 Uchuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>68213.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107251" type="appears in" update="2019-11-30">
<name>Murisarm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68214.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2252" picture="223545.jpg">Naruse Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107252" type="appears in" update="2019-11-30">
<name>Methiop</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68216.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107275" type="appears in" update="2019-12-01">
<name>Rubaruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68217.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107276" type="appears in" update="2019-12-01">
<name>Jirukoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68218.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107277" type="appears in" update="2019-12-01">
<name>Jiumu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68220.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107284" type="appears in" update="2019-12-02">
<name>Dai 11 Uchuu Team</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>68224.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="107325" type="appears in" update="2019-12-06">
<name>Dai 1 Uchuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="107327" type="appears in" update="2019-12-06">
<name>Dai 2 Uchuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="107337" type="appears in" update="2019-12-06">
<name>Dai 3 Uchuu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="169296" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">目指せドラゴンボール! ピラフ一味の大作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aim for the Dragon Balls! Pilaf Gang in Action!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezase Dragon Ball! Pilaf Ichimi no Daisakusen!</title>
<summary>With all guests now gathered, except for Son Gokuu and Vegeta, Bulma`s birthday party gets underway. Trunks shows Son Goten where his mother hid the bingo tournament grand prize – the Dragon Balls. Not far off from the ship, Pilaf Gang, now poor and hungry, are trying to get by until they find the Dragon Balls and make their wishes come true. When his Dragon Radar picks up a signal coming from Bulma`s ship, Pilaf and his henchmen hastily board the ship, with Trunks and Goten`s help. Meanwhile, on his planet, Kaiou-sama explains to Gokuu who and what Beerus exactly is and that for every benevolent God there must be a malevolent one in order to keep the Universe in balance. Just as he finishes, Beerus and Whis arrive.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723195</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169297" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の続きはどこだ!? 超[スーパー]サイヤ人ゴッドを探せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where`s the Rest of the Dream?! In Search of the Super Saiyan God!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¿Cómo continúa el Sueño? ¡En Busca del Super Saiyan Dios!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Tsuzuki wa Doko Da!? Super Saiyajin God o Sagase!</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">¿En dónde está la otra mitad del sueño? ¡Buscando al Súper Saiyajin Fase Dios!</title>
<summary>Fearing what might happen knowing that the God of Destruction is awake, the Kaioushin urge Kaiou-sama to ensure that Son Gokuu never finds out about Beerus. However, Gokuu overhears the conversation and becomes curious. Back in his temple, Beerus and Whis continue their search for the Super Saiyan God. They soon learn of Son Gokuu and his feats and decide to pay him and Kaiou-sama a visit. Meanwhile, back on Earth, Gokuu`s friends and family members begin gathering on the cruise ship for Bulma`s birthday party except for Vegeta who is still training to overpower Gokuu and everyone else in the Universe.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723171</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169298" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">2.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束のリゾートへ! べジータが家族旅行!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Promised Resort! Vegeta Goes on a Family Trip?!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">El Paraíso Prometido ¿¡Vegeta en unas Vacaciones en Familia!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku no Resort e! Vegeta ga Kazoku Ryokou!?</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">¡Vacaciones en un resort! ¿Vegeta irá a un viaje familiar?</title>
<summary>Son Gokuu goes to Planet Kaiou to train with Kaiou-sama. Meanwhile, Vegeta, Bulma, and Trunks take a family trip to a resort. Bulma and Trunks are enjoying the family time together while Vegeta is bothered by the fact that Gokuu gets to train. Fed up with what he considers a waste of time, Vegeta flies away and heads back to the Capsule Corporation to train. Somewhere in space, Beerus and Whis scour an alien planet in search of dinosaur meat. They are confronted by the planet`s strongest dweller, but he proves to be no match for them. Shortly afterwards, Beerus destroys the planet in order to have another vision of his destined opponent – the Super Saiyan God.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723167</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169299" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">平和の報酬1億ゼニーは誰の手に!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Peace Reward: Who Will Get the 100 Million Zeni!?</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡El Gran Premio de la Paz! ¿Quién se llevará los 100 millones de Zenís?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heiwa no Houshuu 1-oku Zeni wa Dare no Te ni!?</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">¡El Premio Mundial de la Paz! ¿Quién se quedará con los 100 millones de Zenis?</title>
<summary>After Son Gokuu defeated the dangerous Majin Buu, peace has returned to Earth once again. Chichi wants Gokuu to get a job, so he works as a farmer. Son Goten and his friend Trunks search for a gift for Videl, soon to be his sister-in-law when his older brother, Son Gohan, is engaged to her. First, they decide on rings, then they decide on make-up, but unable to afford any, head for the hot springs in the woods to bottle some mineral water instead. While there, they are attacked by a giant snake, which they manage to scare away. For his purported role in saving Earth from Majin Buu, Mr. Satan has been awarded with 100 million Zeni that he does not want. He decides to give the money to one of the fighters; namely Gokuu. Gokuu gives the money to Chichi, so she would let him train. Meanwhile, somewhere in the depths of space, Beerus, the God of Destruction, has awakened from his slumber. Keen on battling the worthy opponent that appeared to him in his visions, Beerus and his attendant Whis set out to discover who this opponent is.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723163</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="169435" update="2015-06-29">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169436" update="2015-06-29">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169609" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="169610" update="2017-02-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="170425" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空見参! ビルス様からのラストチャンス!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goku Arrives! A Last Chance from Beerus Sama?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu Kenzan! Beerus-sama kara no Last Chance!?</title>
<summary>Having powered up, Vegeta charges towards Beerus. He manages to land a few punches before Beerus, who was using only a fraction of his power, knocks him out. Just as he is about to destroy Earth, Beerus has a sudden idea. He decides to give the Earthlings another chance at saving Earth. Meanwhile, fearing for their lives, Pilaf Gang disembark Bulma`s ship on a rowboat and sail away. Thinking he is the same as Majin Buu because of his pink hue, Beerus picks Oolong out of the crowd and challenges him to a game of janken (じゃんけん) to decide the fate of Earth. Oolong manages to draw twice, but Beerus eventually wins and proceeds to power up his attack. Just as Beerus is about to fire, Gokuu chimes in saying he has thought of a way to find out about the Super Saiyan God – by summoning and asking Shenron.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723191</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170426" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よくもオレのブルマを! ベジータ怒りの突然変異!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Dare You Hurt My Bulma! Vegeta`s Sudden, Angry Shift?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokumo Ore no Bulma o! Vegeta Ikari no Totsuzen Hen`i!?</title>
<summary>Beerus effortlessly disposes of Majin Buu, while Vegeta stands by in awe. Vegeta tries to persuade Beerus to calm down and enjoy himself, but he refuses to listen. Trunks and Goten fuse into Gotenks and attack to no avail. Powerless to do anything else, Gotenks starts insulting Beerus for which he is promptly punished. Piccolo, Tenshinhan, and Android 18 try taking on Beerus with little success. Majin Buu attacks again but is unable to land a single hit. While observing the battle, Dende realizes what Beerus actually is and immediately informs Piccolo. Before Piccolo is able to warn him, Gohan powers up and charges towards Beerus. Using Majin Buu as a weapon, Beerus repels Gohan, taking them both out. Being the last one standing, Vegeta confronts Beerus, but he is swiftly brought to the ground. Beerus tells Vegeta that he is disappointed with him; that he is just as weak as his father was. Just as Beerus is about to finish Vegeta, Bulma walks up and slaps him for ruining her party. Beerus retaliates in similar fashion. Seeing Bulma struck infuriates Vegeta; he explodes and powers up immensely.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723187</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170427" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破壊神を怒らせるな! ドキドキ誕生パーティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Anger the God of Destruction! Excitement at the Birthday Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakaishin o Okoraseruna! Dokidoki Tanjou Party</title>
<summary>Beerus and Whis arrive on Earth, where Bulma`s birthday party is underway. Initially, Vegeta is paralyzed by Beerus` presence. He recalls a childhood encounter with the deity a long time ago when Beerus visited Planet Vegeta and threatened his father, King Vegeta. Shortly after, Bulma pops up. She invites Beerus and Whis to join the party. Beerus gladly accepts her offer and enjoys the food available. The two start mingling with the other guests, while Vegeta tries his best to ensure that Beerus remains calm. Whis soon learns of pudding, which he finds to be extraordinary delicious; so much so that he urges Beerus to have some too. It turns out that Majin Buu had taken the remaining pudding cups for himself and refuses to share. Angered by Majin Buu`s insolence, Beerus attacks him.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723183</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170428" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">界王星の決戦! 悟空VS[たい]破壊神ビルス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Fight on King Kai`s Planet! Goku vs the God of Destruction Beerus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaiousei no Kessen! Gokuu tai Hakaishin Beerus</title>
<summary>Beerus and Whis arrive on Kaiou-sama`s planet and detect Gokuu`s presence. While he is initially disappointed that Gokuu does not know what a "Super Saiyan God" is, he agrees to test his strength in a sparring match. Gokuu attempts to fight him in all of the Super Saiyan transformations but is outclassed every time. Beerus and Whis head for Earth shortly afterwards while Kaiou-sama uses his telepathy to warn Vegeta ahead of their arrival.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723175</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170879" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見せろ悟空! 超[スーパー]サイヤ人ゴッドの力[パワー]!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unleash It, Goku! The Power of the Super Saiyan God!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misero Gokuu! Super Saiyajin God no Power!!</title>
<summary>Now a Super Saiyan God, Gokuu confronts Beerus. He is amazed by the immense power his body has gained with the transformation, so much so that he is initially unable to fully grasp its newfound potential. Fighting with Beerus, Gokuu manages to grow gradually into his new form. Seeing as how Gokuu might turn out to be a worthy adversary after all, Beerus decides it is time for them to unleash their true power and have a real battle of Gods.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723199</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="170880" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お待たせ, ビルス様 ついに超[スーパー]サイヤ人ゴッド誕生!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sorry for the Wait, Beerus Sama. The Super Saiyan God Is Finally Born!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omatase, Beerus-sama: Tsui ni Super Saiyajin God Tanjou!</title>
<summary>Gokuu gathers the Dragon Balls together and summons Shenron who is startled by Beerus` presence. Shenron quickly explains that the Super Saiyan God is not a person but a legendary transformation that only kindhearted Saiyans can achieve by fusing their power together. The Saiyans attempt to transform Gokuu but fail, as they are one Saiyan short. Growing tired of waiting, Beerus starts preparing his attack to destroy the planet. Suddenly, Videl jumps in front of the Saiyans. She says that there is one more Saiyan who might be able to help them – her and Gohan`s unborn child. The Saiyans and Videl attempt the transformation again and manage to transform Gokuu into the Super Saiyan God.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723197</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="171294" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空よ, 超[スーパー]サイヤ人ゴッドを超えてゆけ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goku, Surpass the Super Saiyan God!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu yo, Super Saiyajin God o Koeteyuke!</title>
<summary>The Kaioushin are surprised that the Universe is still intact following the battle, but they fear the worst is still to come. On Earth, Vegeta, Whis, and the others are still standing by, watching the battle. Whis is surprised by the Super Saiyan God`s power and its ability to keep up with his trainee. In space, Gokuu struggles to keep up with Beerus` attack, which ultimately ends up in a massive explosion, blinding everyone on Earth. Shortly after, the light clears out, revealing everything to be as it was prior to the explosion. Beerus explains that he used his full power to negate the explosion, thereby saving the Universe. Seeing it as a perfect opportunity to boast, Mr. Satan arranges to have him be falsely credited with saving the planet yet again. Despite being at his limit, Gokuu remains calm, which annoys the God of Destruction. Beerus thinks Gokuu might have a strategy that he has been hiding which Gokuu promptly denies, saying that everything he had been doing was improvised as they fought. The Gods quickly power up and continue fighting, but this time, both at their limit. As soon as they start, Gokuu loses his Super Saiyan God aura and reverts to the ordinary Super Saiyan form. Upon noticing that, Beerus decides to quit, thinking it is pointless to fight an ordinary Saiyan. Gokuu, however, does not notice and keeps going at it. Able to sense Gokuu`s energy, Whis assumes that the battle has concluded and that Gokuu lost, but Piccolo begs to differ. Surprised that Gokuu is still able to hit him even after losing his God form, Beerus surmises that Gokuu`s body has adjusted to the Super Saiyan God power, making him stronger in his ordinary form. Gokuu proclaims that, with or without the Super Saiyan God form, it is still him that Beerus is up against, and the two resume their battle.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723543</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="171295" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙が砕ける!? 激突! 破壊神VS[たい]超[スーパー]サイヤ人ゴッド!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Universe Crumbles?! Clash! God of Destruction vs. Super Saiyan God!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu ga Kudakeru!? Gekitotsu! Hakaishin tai Super Saiyajin God!</title>
<summary>Gokuu and Beerus continue to fight in space. As both of them power up and clash, the universe begins to crumble under the power of the gods. Celestial bodies blow up due to the shockwaves. Meanwhile, Old Kaioushin reveals to the younger Kaioushin that with three more blows the whole universe would be destroyed along with Beerus and Gokuu. Gokuu, on landing the third clash with Beerus, unknowingly stops the universe`s collapse by balancing Beerus` attack with his own. Beerus gets enraged and uses his atomic bomb attack on Gokuu. Gokuu uses the Super Saiyan God energy to power up his Kamehameha attack to keep Beerus` attack at bay.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723539</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="171296" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">続けようぜビルス様! 神と神の戦いを!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Keep Going, Beerus Sama! Our Battle of Gods!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuzukeyouze Beerus-sama! Kami to Kami no Tatakai o!</title>
<summary>Having somewhat got a grip on the Super Saiyan God form, Gokuu initially manages to keep up with Beerus, but he soon realizes that his opponent is still not fighting at his maximum. It is revealed that Beerus is doing so only to motivate Gokuu to catch up with him. To that end, Beerus drags Gokuu to space where he swiftly knocks him out. Gokuu comes crashing down back to Earth and ends up in an ocean. Amazed by such power, Gokuu gets excited and powers up, healing himself in the process. Willing to have another go, he flies out of the ocean and dashes towards Beerus.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723535</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172529" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇者サタンよ奇跡を起こせ! 宇宙からの挑戦状</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Make a Miracle, Satan the Hero! A Challenge from Outer Space</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡Héroe Satán! ¡Haz el milagro! ¡Un desafío desde el espacio exterior!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuusha Satan yo Kiseki o Okose! Uchuu kara no Chousenjou</title>
<summary>With Earth no longer in danger, Gokuu and the others return to their ordinary lives. Chichi orders Gokuu to leave training behind and find a job so he can support the family. Meanwhile, Mr. Satan`s self-promotion goes awry when a group of aliens land in the city. The aliens reveal that they are ambassadors who wish to thank and reward whoever defeated Beerus; thus protecting their planet from destruction. Before he is given the reward, however, Mr. Satan is asked to demonstrate his godlike power against the alien`s mightiest champion in a sparring match. Knowing that he does not stand a chance, Mr. Satan quickly scampers away to safety and calls for help, but no one answers him. Suddenly, Gokuu arrives at the scene in need of Mr. Satan`s help. Mr. Satan arranges to have Gokuu fight in his stead. Just before the fight, however, Gokuu spots Chichi and immediately runs away to avoid being scolded for disobeying her. Mr. Satan is left to confront the alien champion on his own. Suddenly, the aliens spot Mr. Satan`s dog and run away in fear. With the aliens gone, the crowd praises Mr. Satan, whom they think saved them and Earth yet again.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723553</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172530" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これがオラのありったけの力だ! 決着! 神と神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is Every Ounce of Power I Have! The Battle of Gods` Conclusion!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore ga Ora no Arittake no Chikara Da! Kecchaku! Kami to Kami</title>
<summary>Now with only a Super Saiyan form at his disposal, Gokuu powers up and attacks but to no avail as Beerus knocks him out effortlessly. With Gokuu knocked out, Beerus prepares to destroy Earth. In a final effort to stop Beerus, Gokuu once again powers up and charges his Kamehameha attack. Gokuu manages to prevent Beerus` attack, but he completely depletes what was left of his energy in the process. He comes crashing down to Earth onto Bulma`s ship, where Vegeta manages to catch him. Beerus lands on the planet shortly after to finish what he started, but he suddenly falls asleep. Whis explains that Gokuu must have tired Beerus out and that by the time he wakes up he will have forgotten about their trip to Earth. Beerus, who was faking his sudden sleep because humanity`s food convinced him to spare the planet, and Whis leave for Beerus` planet shortly after. With Earth safe again, Gokuu decides to relax and enjoy the party.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723547</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172537" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望ふたたび! 悪の帝王・フリーザの復活!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Despair Rises! The Emperor of Evil, Frieza, Resurrected!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou Futatabi! Aku no Teiou - Freezer no Fukkatsu!</title>
<summary>Goku and Vegeta continue their training under Whis on Beerus` planet. Meanwhile, Sorbet and his assistant Tagoma depart their ship and head for Earth in order to find the Dragon Balls, with which they intend to resurrect their leader Freeza. They run into the Pilaf Gang who had collected all seven Dragon Balls just before their arrival. Sorbet coerces Pilaf into summoning Shenlong. At first, Shenlong refuses to revive Freeza, seeing it as pointless given his current state – cut in pieces, just as he was when Future Trunks killed him. Tagoma suggests using their advanced healing technology to make Freeza intact again. Sorbet has Freeza resurrected, and they return to their ship. Freeza is completely renewed shortly afterwards.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723569</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172538" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オラも来たぞ! ビルス星で修行開始だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Here, Too! Training Begins on Beerus` Planet!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ora mo Kita zo! Beerus-sei de Shuugyou Kaishi Da!</title>
<summary>Goku and Whis arrive on Beerus` planet, where Vegeta is tasked with housekeeping. Goku is surprised to learn that Vegeta has gotten considerably stronger training under Whis and so wants to start his training right away. Before he is allowed to, however, Whis orders him to help Vegeta with the chores including changing Beerus` bed sheets without waking him up. Goku and Vegeta promptly do their chores and start their training with Whis. Whis` training routine quickly wears Goku out, and he falls asleep, while Vegeta, willing to surpass Goku at any cost, keeps on training. The next day, Whis decides to have a sparring match with his apprentices in order to gauge their speed. The two prove to be no match for Whis, being too slow to land a single hit. Meanwhile, somewhere in space, surviving members of Freeza`s army, led by Sorbet, continue with their effort of resurrecting their leader. Not far off, mysterious beings from a different Universe, known only as Shanpa and Vados, continue their search for Beerus.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723565</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172539" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パン誕生! そして悟空は修行の旅へ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pan Is Born! And Goku Goes on a Training Trip?!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¡El nacimiento de Pan! ¿¡Y el viaje de entrenamiento de Gokú!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pan Tanjou! Soshite Gokuu wa Shuugyou no Tabi e!?</title>
<summary>Pan has been born. While most of her family members and friends think that she should be taught martial arts, Chi-Chi is revolted by the very idea. She believes that Pan should be raised to be a lady and not a mindless fighter like her grandfather Goku. Everyone tries to persuade Chi-Chi to change her mind but to no avail. Bulma accidentally mentions that Vegeta has been away training with Whis for six months, which shocks Goku. After some time, Whis returns to Earth to enjoy more of the food Earth has to offer. Goku approaches Whis and asks to become his pupil. Whis accepts, thinking it is the perfect time for Goku to join Vegeta in training. Just as the two are about to depart, Chi-Chi runs up and stops Goku from leaving. Despite her wishes, Goku ends up leaving with Whis. Chi-Chi then has a sudden change of heart, saying that Goku will return once he gets hungry anyway.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723561</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172540" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベジータが弟子入り!? ウイスを攻略せよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vegeta Becomes an Apprentice?! Winning Whis Over!</title>
<title xml:lang="es">¿¡Vegeta se convierte en un discípulo!? Conquista a Wiss</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vegeta ga Deshiiri!? Whis o Kouryaku Seyo!</title>
<summary>Chi-Chi still has Goku doing work out on the farm. Instead of working, however, Goku decides to rest and falls asleep. Krillin flies in and wakes up Goku. Krillin is very surprised to hear that Goku is still on Earth and not training with King Kai. He reminisces about his training with Goku under Kame-Sennin and the power level difference between them since they were children. Curious to see how large the gap is, Krillin tells Goku to punch him with all his power. Reluctant Goku tries to change Krillin`s mind, but Krillin insists. Goku obeys and punches Krillin, sending him flying into a boulder. Shortly afterwards, Goku heads home, while Android 18 attends to Krillin`s wounds. Krillin states that he misses martial arts and wishes to start training again. Meanwhile, Vegeta is seen in the wastelands standing determined. He states his intent to surpass Goku without the aid of others. Elsewhere, Whis and Bulma are having lunch together. Whis is enjoying all the food Bulma is having her chef make. While they dine, Bulma asks Whis to protect Earth from Beerus in case he ever shows up again. Vegeta arrives and sees Whis. He asks Whis to see Beerus, but Whis refuses to do so. Whis tells Vegeta that he is Beerus` teacher and that, with the proper tutelage, he could one day surpass Goku. Vegeta bows and kneels before Whis and begs to become his student. An unimpressed Whis walks past him. Vegeta decides to convince Whis by giving him the tastiest food on Earth. After several failed attempts, Vegeta finally impresses Whis with a cup of instant noodle. Before Vegeta heads off with Whis to Beerus` planet, Bulma hands him new armor. They arrive on Beerus` planet shortly afterwards and prepare to train.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723557</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172967" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チェーンジ! まさかの復活! その名はギニュー!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Change! An Unexpected Return! His Name Is Ginyu!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Change! Masaka no Fukkatsu! Sono Na wa Ginyu!</title>
<summary>Tagoma proves to be a tough opponent and even Piccolo can’t take him. Gotenks joins the battle but suddenly Tagoma is taken over by…Ginyu?! Gohan is able to face him as a Super Saiyan but can he keep up when Frieza makes his move?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723917</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172968" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復讐のはじまり! フリーザ軍の悪意が悟飯を撃つ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Start of Revenge! The Malice of Frieza Army Strikes Gohan!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu no Hajimari! Freezer-gun no Akui ga Gohan o Utsu!</title>
<summary>Without any way to get a hold of Goku or Vegeta, only Gohan and the remaining Z fighters are ready to face Frieza. Up against 1000 troops and the emperor of evil, our heroes may face more of a challenge than expected!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723913</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="172969" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャコからの警告! 迫り来るフリーザと1000人の兵士達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jaco`s Warning! Frieza and His 1000 Troops Approach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jako kara no Keikoku! Semarikuru Freezer to 1000 Nin no Heishi-tachi</title>
<summary>Once restored, Freeza plans revenge against Goku and Future Trunks. Tagoma objects to Freeza`s plans, but Freeza promptly subdues him. When Freeza finds out that Goku has gotten much stronger since they last met, he decides to train in order to become more powerful. He reveals that, since his power was inborn, he had never felt the need to train a day in his life before now. Four months pass before Freeza and his army head for Earth. All the while, Goku and Vegeta continue their training under Whis. Jaco the Galactic Patrolman travels to Earth to inform Bulma that Freeza had been revived and that he will be approaching Earth shortly with an army of one thousand soldiers. With Freeza`s army fast approaching, Bulma gathers the remaining Z fighters to face Freeza`s army in hopes of holding out until Goku and Vegeta make it back to Earth.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723573</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173444" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全開バトル! 復讐のゴールデンフリーザ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An All-Out Battle! The Revenge of Golden Frieza</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenkai Battle! Fukushuu no Golden Freeza</title>
<summary>Not to be outdone by Goku’s new form, Frieza reveals a new one of his own. Once again the two face off in an evenly matched battle. Meanwhile, Beerus and Whis make their way to Earth but run into allies of their own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723929</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173445" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! フリーザVS[たい]孫悟空 これがオラの修行の成果だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash! Frieza vs Son Goku: This Is the Result of My Training!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Freeza tai Son Gokuu: Kore ga Ora no Shuugyou no Seika Da!</title>
<summary>Goku and Frieza finally face off! With their powers matched, Frieza begins attacking Goku’s friends to catch him off guard. Frustrated, Vegeta pushes him to give it his all and face Frieza in his ultimate form!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723923</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="173446" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2015-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球が! 悟飯が! 絶体絶命! 早く来てくれ孫悟空!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Earth! Gohan! Absolute Peril! Hurry and Get Here, Son Goku!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu ga! Gohan ga! Zettaizetsumei! Hayaku Kite Kure Son Gokuu!</title>
<summary>Piccolo falls after attempting to save Gohan but there’s no time to deal with the loss. While Bulma finally gets a message to Whis for Goku and Vegeta, Gohan powers up to his highest level. And so does Freiza. Will Goku make it in time?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723921</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174115" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第6宇宙の破壊神 その名はシャンパ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The God of Destruction from Universe 6: His Name Is Champa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 6 Uchuu no Hakaijin: Sono Na wa Champa</title>
<summary>Vegeta and Goku are continuing their training under Whis when they receive a pair of visitors—Beerus’ brother and Whis’ sister! After a comparison of culinary delights, Champa challenges Beerus to a universe-versus-universe tournament.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723941</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174116" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球爆発!? 決着のかめはめ波</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Earth Explodes?! The Deciding Kamehameha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu Bakuhatsu!? Kecchaku no Kamehame Ha</title>
<summary>With Goku badly injured, Vegeta steps in to face Frieza. Stronger than ever, Vegeta proves to be a challenge and an enraged Frieza destroys the planet! Protected by Whis, the Z fighters are given a chance to save Earth, if they act fast enough.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723937</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174117" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大ピンチに勝機が見えた! 反撃開始だ孫悟空!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Glint of Hope Shines Through in a Crisis! Time to Fight Back, Son Goku!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Pinch ni Shouki ga Mieta! Hangeki Kaishi Da Son Gokuu</title>
<summary>Goku is having trouble facing Golden Frieza until he realizes the other is quickly losing stamina. Gaining the upper hand, Goku gives Frieza a chance to leave Earth for good. But the emperor of evil isn’t ready to give up his revenge just yet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723933</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174789" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">驚け第6宇宙よ! これが超[スーパー]サイヤ人・孫悟空だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Behold, Universe 6! This Is the Super Saiyan? Son Goku!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Odoroke Dai 6 Uchuu yo! Kore ga Super Saiyajin Son Gokuu Da!</title>
<summary>The fight between Gokuu and Botamo commences. Gokuu takes a while to warm up due to having overeaten during the trip. Although Gokuu seems faster and more well trained than Botamo, none of the hits that he lands seem to have an effect. Botamo seems content to simply take the punishment. Urged by Vegeta to think before he acts, Gokuu drags Botamo to the side of the ring and then throws him out. This results in a win for Universe Seven. The next match begins almost immediately. The Freezer look alike named Frost is Goku`s next opponent. In direct contrast to Freezer, Frost is a kind and beloved hero in Universe Six who looks forward to a challenge. Gokuu surprises Frost with knowledge of his transformations. Frost assumes a form that mirrors Freezer`s third form. Gokuu mentions his ability to transform as well. He transforms into a Super Saiyan. Frost responds by transforming into his final form. Frost seems greatly outmatched by Gokuu even in his final transformation. Suddenly, a strange effect comes over Gokuu that severely weakens him and allows Frost a chance to strike. Frost knocks Gokuu out of the ring, which stuns everyone from Universe Seven.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724329</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174790" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">試合開始だ! みんなで「名前のない星」へ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Match Begins! Let`s All Go to the "Nameless Planet!"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiai Kaishi Da! Minna de "Namae no Nai Hoshi" e!</title>
<summary>On Earth everyone gathers for the trip to the tournament, with Goku and Vegeta arriving after having trained in the Room of Spirit and Time. After stopping at Beerus` planet to get both him and Monaka, everyone proceeds to the tournament. The group meets their competition who are all somewhat strange, and include a Saiyan with a radically different history, as well as a fighter who looks like Freeza. After the written test the Universe Seven team is left one man down as Majin Buu falls asleep and is disqualified. Beerus decides that Monaka will go last, and after a round of rock-paper-scissors it is Goku that will fight first, followed by Vegeta and Piccolo. Goku and his competitor Botamo, who is a giant bear-like creature, enter the ring and square off for the first match.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724325</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174791" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ズノー様のもとへ! 超ドラゴンボールのありかを聞き出せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Off to Zuno Sama`s! Find Out Where Super Dragon Balls Are!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zunoo-sama no Moto e! Super Dragon Ball no Arika o Kikidase!</title>
<summary>To find out more about the Super Dragon Balls, Jaco takes Bulma to the all-knowing alien, Master Zuno. But their trip is disturbed when they encounter the criminal, Geppuman. They’re given three questions to ask Zuno—will they get the answers they need?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724319</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174792" update="2018-06-29">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">『格闘試合』へのおさらい 残り二人のメンバーは誰だ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Review Before the `Martial Arts Match`: Who Are the Last Two Members?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kakutou Shiai" e no Osarai: Nokori Futari no Member wa Dare Da!?</title>
<summary>Goku and Vegeta recruit Piccolo and Majin Buu as the remaining combatants of the Universe Seven team. Gohan considered joining the team, but he was unable to do so as he had a business meeting on the day of the tournament. Beerus and the others think back over recent events. A series of flashbacks recapping the series is shown.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723949</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174793" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">格闘試合開催決定! 主将は悟空よりも強いヤツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Martial Arts Match Has Been Decided! The Team Captain Is Stronger Than Goku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakutou Shiai Kaisai Kettei! Shushou wa Gokuu yori mo Tsuyoi Yatsu</title>
<summary>Bulma suggests summoning Shenron to find the remaining Super Dragon Balls, but even his power is not enough. As they prepare for the upcoming match, Beerus reveals there’s a fighter stronger than Goku who’s going to join the team of the 7th Universe!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723945</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175342" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まさかの大苦戦! ベジータ怒りの大爆発!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Unexpected Desperate Battle! Vegeta`s Furious Explosion!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masaka no Daikusen! Vegeta Ikari no Daibakuhatsu!</title>
<summary>The battle literally heats up as Magetta starts a heatwave. Cornered, Vegeta destroys the barrier around him and unleashes his power against his opponent. Will he bring this battle to a cool conclusion or melt under pressure?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724341</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175343" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒りを力に変えろ! ベジータの全開バトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Turn Rage Into Strength! Vegeta`s Full-On Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikari o Chikara ni Kaero! Vegeta no Zenkai Battle</title>
<summary>Vegeta prepares to face Frost, who has no intention of discontinuing his cheating. But with a single hit, Vegeta knocks Frost completely out of the ring for the win. Before the next round, Goku is added back to the lineup, and Champa adds a new rule.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724337</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175344" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ピッコロVS[たい]フロスト 魔貫光殺砲にすべてをかけろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Piccolo vs. Frost: Put It All on the Special Beam Cannon!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Piccolo tai Frost: Makankousappou ni Subete o Kakero!</title>
<summary>After Goku’s sudden defeat, Piccolo steps into the ring! Frost continues to be a challenge, and right when Piccolo is beaten, Jaco makes a discovery—Frost hasn’t been fighting fair! But Vegeta’s not ready to let him off with a disqualification.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724333</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176127" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176128" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176129" update="2016-03-21">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176130" update="2016-03-21">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176131" update="2016-03-21">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-12-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176132" update="2017-02-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176133" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ついに決着! 勝者はビルス? それともシャンパ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At Last, It Comes to an End! Is the Winner Beerus? Or Is It Champa?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsui ni Kecchaku! Shousha wa Beerus? Soretomo Champa?</title>
<summary>Goku and Hit continue to fight evenly matched as they reach unbelievable heights with their abilities. But as Goku continues to strain his body—he does the unthinkable! Will the 6th Universe be named the winners?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724355</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176134" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">成長した"時とばし"の反撃!? 出るか!? 悟空の新たな技!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Advanced "Time-Skip" Fights Back?! Will It Come Forth? Goku`s New Technique!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seichou Shita "Toki Tobashi" no Hangeki!? Deruka!? Gokuu no Arata na Waza!</title>
<summary>Figuring out Hit’s “time-skipping” ability allows Goku to keep up—until Hit powers up! Will Goku finally face defeat, or does the Saiyan have a secret power of his own?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724353</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176135" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第6宇宙最強の戦士! 殺し屋ヒット見参!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Warrior of Universe 6! Assassin Hit Appears!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 6 Uchuu Saikyou no Senshi! Koroshiya Hit Kenzan!!</title>
<summary>Vegeta goes up against the last member of the 6th Universe, the assassin Hit! With movements so fast nobody can even see him, Hit proves to be a true match for Vegeta. Will the prince of Saiyans finally fall?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724349</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176136" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイヤ人の誇りを忘れるな! ベジータVS[たい]第6宇宙のサイヤ人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Forget Your Saiyan Pride! Vegeta vs the Saiyan of Universe 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiyajin no Hokori o Wasurena! Vegeta tai Dai 6 Uchuu no Saiyajin</title>
<summary>It’s Saiyan versus Saiyan in this next epic battle! The two seem evenly matched until Vegeta demands Cabbe transform into a Super Saiyan, only to learn the boy is incapable. Will Vegeta show mercy, or has he strayed to his old, evil ways?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724345</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177017" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポトフ星の封印 解き放たれた"超人水"の秘密!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet Potaufeu`s Seal. The Secret of the "Superhuman Water" Unleashed!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Potofu Sei no Fuuin: Tokihanatareta "Choujinsui" no Himitsu!</title>
<summary>After getting stuck in Monaka’s truck, Goten and Trunks wind up on Planet Pot-au-feu. Here, they protect an old man and get caught in a fight over…water?! But the truth about this water could leave them high and dry!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724609</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177018" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空の「気」が制御不能!? パンのお世話で四苦八苦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goku`s "Energy" Is Out of Control?! Caring For Pan Is a Handful</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu no "Ki" ga Seigyo Funou!? Pan no Osewa de Shikuhakku</title>
<summary>Goku starts having trouble controlling his body and energy! After visiting with King Kai, he learns he’s on strict bed rest until his energy levels out. But when he goes to stay at Gohan’s, he finds taking it easy with baby Pan around isn’t so easy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724605</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177019" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">波乱の祝勝会! 遂に対決!? モナカVS[たい]孫悟空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Victory Celebration of Chaos! They Battle at Last?! Monaka vs Son Goku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haran no Shukushoukai! Tsui ni Taiketsu!? Monaka tai Son Gokuu</title>
<summary>Bulma plans a victory party for all the fighters and wants to include Monaka. Beerus fears Goku will learn the truth of his newest rival and tries to keep him from going. But when Monaka shows up, they’ll have to figure out a way to keep it all secret!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724601</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177020" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出でよ神の龍 そして願いを叶えてちょんまげ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come, Dragon of the Gods: And Grant Me My Wish, Pretty Peas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ide yo Kami no Ryuu: Soshite Negai o Kanaete Chonmage!</title>
<summary>Before the winner can gloat, a newcomer appears in the ring! Beerus and Champa are struck with fear—just who is this Zeno? And finally, it’s time to make a wish on the Super Dragon Balls, that is, if they can find the last one.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724597</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177647" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HOPE[きぼう]!! 再び 現在[いま]で目覚めよトランクス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hope!! Once More Awaken in the Present, Trunks</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kibou!! Futatabi: Ima de Mezameyo Trunks</title>
<summary>With barely enough time to stop the dark entity that’s after him, Trunks travels back to the past. But when he arrives, can present Trunks handle seeing his future self?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722907</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177648" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来からのSOS! 黒き新たな敵現る!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An SOS from the Future! A Dark New Enemy Emerges!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai kara no SOS! Kuroki Arata na Teki Arawaru!!</title>
<summary>Life in the present may be peaceful but trouble is stirring in the future! Trunks is risking everything to get back to the past to find help. But will he escape the new evil that threatens the future in time to get help from our heroes?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722903</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177649" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空VS[たい]複製ベジータ! 勝つのはどっちだ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goku vs. the Cloned Vegeta! Which One Will Win?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu tai Fukusei Vegeta! Katsu no wa Docchi Da!?</title>
<summary>As Vegeta begins to disappear, Goku faces the duplicate Vegeta! But can he defeat the copy and save the original before he vanishes? And when the fight starts, is Vegeta rooting for…his clone?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724617</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177650" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベジータが消える!? 複製ベジータの脅威!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vegeta`s Disappearing?! The Threat of the Cloned Vegeta!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vegeta ga Kieru!? Fukusei Vegeta no Kyoui!</title>
<summary>After being drained of his energy, Vegeta and the others escape and learn more about the Superhuman Water. And if they don’t stop the clones, Vegeta could disappear—for good! With time running out, will Gotenks be enough to stop them?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724613</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177967" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空VS[たい]ブラック! 閉ざされた未来への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goku vs Black! The Closed Path to the Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu tai Black! Tozasareta Mirai e no Michi</title>
<summary>Black suddenly appears from a mysterious portal. Goku sees this as an opportunity to test his look-alike’s power firsthand. But while the battle rages on, Black glances at the time machine with a sinister look in his eye.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722913</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177968" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来からのメッセージ ゴクウブラック襲来!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Message from the Future: Goku Black Strikes!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai kara no Message: Gokuu Black Shuurai!</title>
<summary>After regaining consciousness, Future Trunks describes how he came to arrive in the present. But apparently not even the gods are allowed to meddle with the past. Bulma and Future Trunks might have a bit of explaining to do.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722909</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178145" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">師弟再会 孫悟飯と"未来"トランクス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Teacher and Student Reunited: Son Gohan and "Future" Trunks</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitei Saikai: Son Gohan to "Mirai" Trunks</title>
<summary>Repairs on the time machine continue, so Future Trunks goes to visit an old friend. However, times have changed, and the reunion isn’t quite what he expected.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722921</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178146" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時をこえた想い トランクスとマイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Feelings That Travel Beyond Time: Trunks and Mai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki o Koeta Omoi: Trunks to Mai</title>
<summary>Bulma gets to work repairing the old time machine that she’s kept. Meanwhile, Future Trunks recalls his experiences with Mai. But two questions remain: why does Black have a time ring? And what’s the extent of his power?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722915</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178612" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2016-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178692" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再戦ゴクウブラック! 超[スーパー]サイヤ人ロゼ登場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rematch with Goku Black! Super Saiyan Rose Appears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saisen Gokuu Black! Super Saiyajin Rose Toujou</title>
<summary>Future Trunks, Vegeta, and Goku finally use the time machine with intention to confront Black. But when they arrive, they’re greeted by a familiar face and an unfamiliar power. Will they be able to stand up to this new threat?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722933</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178693" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孫悟空に会いたいのね 全王様からのよびだし!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to See Son Goku: Zen-Oh Sama`s Summoning!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Son Gokuu ni Aitai no ne: Zen`ou-sama kara no Yobidashi!</title>
<summary>Zeno demands to meet with Goku and asks him for something very odd. Meanwhile in the 10th Universe, Zamasu’s hatred for humans grows.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722931</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178694" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイヤ人の血をひく者 トランクスの決意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One Who Inherits the Saiyan Blood: Trunk`s Resolve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiyajin no Chi o Hiku Mono: Trunks no Ketsui</title>
<summary>The time machine repairs are finishing up. Vegeta and Future Trunks go training, but the extent of Vegeta’s power is unlike anything Future Trunks has ever seen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722929</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178695" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブラックの正体を暴け! いざ第10宇宙の界王神界へ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uncover Black`s Identity! To the Sacred World of the Kais!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Black no Shoutai o Abake! Iza Dai 10 Uchuu no Kaiou Shinkai e!</title>
<summary>The nature of Black’s power remains a mystery, so Whis, Beerus, and Goku go to the 10th Universe to find answers. Will challenging an apprentice Supreme Kai really help with the investigation? Goku seems to think so.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722925</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179846" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再び未来へ 明かされるゴクウブラックの正体!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Back to the Future: Goku Black`s Identity Is Revealed!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatabi Mirai e: Akasareru Gokuu Black no Shoutai!!</title>
<summary>Beerus is convinced that his actions should’ve influenced the future, but Future Trunks isn’t so sure! Now it’s time for Goku, Vegeta, and Future Trunks to see for themselves—and Bulma is going, too!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722947</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179847" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">界王神ゴワスを守れ ザマスを破壊せよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protect Supreme Kai Gowasu: Destroy Zamasu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaioushin Gowasu o Mamore: Zamasu o Hakai Seyo!</title>
<summary>Supreme Kai Gowasu is in grave danger! Now that gods are involved, Zamasu’s treachery isn’t a mortal matter anymore. Beerus will have to take matters into his own hands.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722943</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179848" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ザマスとブラック 深まる二人の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zamasu and Black: The Mystery of the Two Deepens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zamasu to Black: Fukumaru Futari no Nazo</title>
<summary>Zamasu’s mind is wandering down a dark path. Goku and Whis think they’ve solved the riddle regarding his and Black’s strength. His malice may be unnoticed now, but Zamasu’s ill will is beginning to dismantle his innocent facade!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722941</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179849" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不死身の体を持つ神 ザマス降臨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The God with the Immortal Body: Zamasu Descends</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fujimi no Karada o Motsu Kami: Zamasu Kourin</title>
<summary>With Vegeta out of the fight, Goku and Future Trunks must fight Future Zamasu and Black with a man down. But can they hope to defeat an opponent who brushes off even the strongest attacks?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722937</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180507" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">崇めよ! 讃えよ! 合体ザマス爆誕!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revere Him! Praise Him! Fusion Zamasu`s Explosive Birth!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Agame yo! Tatae yo! Gattai Zamasu Bakutan!!</title>
<summary>Vegeta’s rage inspires Black to draw upon his own anger and unleash a devastating new ability. Mortal arrogance is proving to be a large enough thorn in Future Zamasu’s side that a permanent decision must be made!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722897</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180508" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイヤ人の細胞を汚すな! ベジータの壮絶バトル開演!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Disrespect Saiyan Cells! Vegeta`s Heroic Battle Begins!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiyajin no Saibou o Kegasuna! Vegeta no Souzetsu Battle Kaien!!</title>
<summary>Future Trunks challenges Black and Future Zamasu on his own. Goku, Vegeta, and Bulma hurry back to save him, but upon arrival, the time machine is damaged! This time the Saiyan prince is itching to dish out some payback!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722895</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180509" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界はオレが守る! トランクス怒りの超[スーパー]パワー炸裂!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Protect the World! Trunks` Furious Super Power Explodes!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai wa Ore ga Mamoru! Trunks Ikari no Super Power Sakuretsu!</title>
<summary>Fighting rages on, and things are looking grim for our heroes. They might not be able to win, but Future Trunks can at least defend the others while they escape! Time is running out, but a new strategy may be the key to victory.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722953</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180510" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ザマスの野望 語られる恐怖の「人間0計画」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zamasu`s Ambition: The Awful "Zero Mortal Plan" Is Revealed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zamasu no Yabou: Katarareru Kyoufu no "Ningen 0 Keikaku"</title>
<summary>The future is unchanged, Black isn’t what Goku had initially thought, and the situation has escalated to something more severe. With this new information, will the Saiyan trio fare better than before?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722951</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181422" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">68</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いでよ神龍[シェンロン]! 叶える願いは誰のもの!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come Forth, Shenron! Whose Wish Will Be Granted?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ide yo Shenron! Kanaeru Negai wa Dare no Mono!?</title>
<summary>Bulma tries to secretly build a time machine despite Beerus’ disapproval. Meanwhile, Goku gathers the Dragon Balls to revive King Kai.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723749</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181423" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新たなHOPE[きぼう]!!を胸に さらばトランクス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With New Hope!! in Our Hearts: Farewell, Trunks</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arata na Kibou!! o Mune ni: Saraba Trunks</title>
<summary>Merged Zamasu’s ashes rises a universe encompassing darkness. Out of energy and out of options, Goku needs some help, and fast!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723747</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181424" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! あきらめない戦士たちの奇跡の力[パワー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Climactic Battle! The Miraculous Power of a Relentless Warrior!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Akiramenai Senshi-tachi no Kiseki no Power</title>
<summary>Merged Zamasu’s immortality is limited! Vegeta and Goku ask the Supreme Kais for help. Will their combined strength prevail over such a significant threat? Is this the chance for Future Trunks to get his revenge?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723745</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181425" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の審判か!? 絶対神の究極の力[パワー]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is This the Final Judgement?! The Ultimate Power of the Absolute God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Shinpan ka!? Zettaishin no Kyuukyoku no Power</title>
<summary>Zamasu and Black merge into an immortal being with limitless power. Is this the end of Future Trunks’ world? Is there any hope left for a victory?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722899</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182464" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">72</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">反撃なるか!? 見えない殺しの技!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Will There Be a Counterattack?! The Invisible Killing Strike!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hangeki Naruka!? Mienai Koroshi no Waza!!</title>
<summary>After cleverly saving himself from an instant death, Goku is itching to find out the nature of Hit’s abilities. Will Goku’s deductions prevent his untimely destruction?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723757</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182465" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">71</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空死す! 絶対執行の暗殺依頼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Death of Goku! The Guaranteed Assassination Mission</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu Shisu! Zettai Shikkou no Ansatsu Irai</title>
<summary>Goku is convinced someone is trying to kill him, and he’s ready to fight for his life. However, can Goku withstand an assassination attempt from the brutally efficient Hit?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723755</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182466" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">70</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャンパからの挑戦状! 今度は野球で勝負だ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Champa`s Challenge! This Time We Fight with Baseball!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Champa kara no Chousenjou! Kondo wa Yakyuu de Shoubu Da!!</title>
<summary>Champa really wants delicious Earth food, and what better way to convince Beerus to let him visit than with a friendly game of baseball? But when the thrill of competition heats up, “friendly” could turn to deadly!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723753</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182467" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">69</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空VS[たい]アラレ! ハチャメチャバトルで地球が終わる!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goku vs Arale! A Ridiculous Battle Will End the Earth?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu tai Arale! Hachamecha Battle de Chikyuu ga Owaru!?</title>
<summary>During an invention award show that Bulma is attending, a robot girl named Arale crashes the party. Tricked by the spectral Dr. Mashirito, she has an incredible urge to play and won’t let Saiyans get in her way! How can Goku and Vegeta defeat an opponent who blissfully ignores the laws of physics?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723751</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182985" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">73</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟飯の災難! グレートサイヤマンまさかの映画化!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gohan`s Misfortune! An Unexpected Great Saiyaman Movie?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gohan no Sainan! Great Saiyaman Masaka no Eigaka!?</title>
<summary>Gohan accepts an opportunity to be a stunt double in the Great Saiyaman movie. But keeping his identity as the real Great Saiyaman a secret will be difficult when there’s a parasitic alien floating around town!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723759</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183110" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">77</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やろうぜ全王様! 宇宙一武道会!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Do It, Zen-Oh Sama! The All-Universe Martial Arts Tournament!!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Vamos Nessa, Senhor Zen`Ou! O Torneio de Artes Marciais entre Todos os Universos!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yarouze Zen`ou-sama! Uchuuichi Budoukai!!</title>
<summary>The Tournament of Power has been on the back burner for a while. Bored of day-to-day work and tired of waiting, Goku convinces Zeno to get the ball rolling!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727863</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183111" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">76</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強敵を打ち破れ! クリリンの闘志ふたたび!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defeat These Terrifying Enemies! Krillin`s Fighting Spirit Returns!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Derrote esses Inimigos Terríveis! O espírito de luta de Kuririn retorna!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouteki o Uchiyabure! Krillin no Toushi Futatabi!</title>
<summary>Upon entering a strange cave, Krillin and Goku are confronted by enemies from their past. Can Krillin find the courage to defeat them, or is history destined to repeat itself?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727861</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183112" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">75</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空とクリリン 懐かしの修行の場へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goku and Krillin: Back to the Old Training Grounds</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Goku e Kuririn: De volta para o antigo campo de treinamento</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu to Krillin: Natsukashi no Shugyou no Ba e</title>
<summary>Everyone is too busy to spar with Goku, so he seeks out Krillin for old times’ sake. Disappointed in his current combat ability, Krillin decides that he’s in dire need of retraining.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723763</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183113" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">74</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛するもののために! 不屈のグレートサイヤマン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For the Ones He Loves! The Unbeatable Great Saiyaman!!</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Pelos que Ele Ama! O Imbatível Grande Saiyaman!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai Suru Mono no Tame ni! Fukutsu no Great Saiyaman!!</title>
<summary>Barry, the self-absorbed actor, tries to undermine Gohan’s reputation! But when the parasite chooses Barry as its host, it’s not just Gohan who’s in trouble. With the main actor under alien control, can Gohan save both the city and the movie?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723761</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183901" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">80</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眠った闘志を呼び覚ませ! 孫悟飯の闘い!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awaken Your Sleeping Battle Spirit! Son Gohan`s Fight!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemutta Toushi o Yobisamase! Son Gohan no Tatakai!!</title>
<summary>Gohan is up next. Out of practice and lacking knowledge of his opponent’s tactics, he’ll have to learn as he goes. But soon after the round begins, Gohan is forced to fight blind in more ways than one.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727869</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183902" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">79</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第9宇宙蹴りのバジルVS第7宇宙魔人ブウ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Universe 9`s Basil the Kicker vs Universe 7`s Majin Buu!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 9 Uchuu Keri no Basil vs Dai 7 Uchuu Majin Buu!!</title>
<summary>First round of the exhibition match is Basil versus Buu! With no energy signatures to hint at their power levels, the 9th Universe’s warriors could be much more powerful than they seem. But that won’t distract Buu from his playtime.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727867</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183903" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">78</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全宇宙の神様もドン引き!? 負けたら消滅「力の大会」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gods of Every Universe in Shock?! Losers Erased in the Tournament of Power</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Os deuses de todos os universos em choque ?! Perdedores apagados no Torneio do Poder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zen Uchuu no Kamisama mo Donbiki!? Maketara Shoumetsu "Chikara no Taikai"</title>
<summary>It’s official, the Tournament of Power is announced. There’s just one problem: the losers of the tournament will have their universes erased! To introduce his future self to the joys of martial arts, Zeno calls for an exhibition match between the 7th and 9th Universe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727865</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184759" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">84</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スカウトマン孫悟空 クリリンと18号を誘う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Son Goku the Recruiter Invites Krillin and No. 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scout Man Son Gokuu: Krillin to 18 Gou o Sasou</title>
<summary>Krillin must prove himself to both Gohan and Goku if he wants to enter the Tournament of Power. With martial arts tournament rules in play, Krillin’s strength isn’t solely based on his power level!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733115</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184760" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">83</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第7宇宙代表チームを結成せよ! 最強の10人は誰だ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Form the Universe 7 Representing Team! Who Are the Strongest Ten?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 7 Uchuu Daihyou Team o Kessei Seyo! Saikyou no 10 Nin wa Dare Da!?</title>
<summary>Time to choose a roster for the Tournament of Power, but finding ten of the strongest fighters in the universe is no easy task! Meanwhile, Vegeta and Bulma’s child is close to being born.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733113</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184761" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">82</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孫悟空許すまじ! 正義の戦士トッポ乱入!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Never Forgive Son Goku! Toppo the Warrior of Justice Intrudes!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Son Goku Yurusumaji! Seigi no Senshi Toppo Rannyuu!!</title>
<summary>Insulted by Goku’s nonchalance regarding the Tournament of Power, a warrior from the 11th Universe challenges Goku to a battle for justice!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727873</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184762" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">81</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">潰しのベルガモVS孫悟空! 青天井の強さはどっちだ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bergamo the Crusher vs Son Goku! Which One Wields the Limitless Power?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubushi no Bergamo vs Son Gokuu! Aotenjou no Tsuyosa wa Docchi Da!?</title>
<summary>The 9th Universe’s third combatant tries to talk Zeno out of erasing losing universes. Zeno agrees on one condition: the 9th Universe must win the exhibition match. However, if Goku throws the fight, all universes will suffer the consequences!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727871</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184920" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184921" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186450" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">88</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟飯とピッコロ 師弟激突の限界修業!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gohan and Piccolo: Teacher and Pupil Clash in Max Training!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gohan to Piccolo: Shitei Gekitotsu no Genkai Shugyou!</title>
<summary>Piccolo tries to retrain Gohan. But Gohan will have to draw from past experiences if he wants to reach his full potential.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733825</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186451" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">87</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">密猟団を狩れ! 悟空と17号の共闘!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hunt the Poachers! Goku and No. 17`s United Front!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitsuryoudan o Kare! Gokuu to 17 Gou no Kyoutou!!</title>
<summary>When intergalactic poachers threaten Android 17’s island, it’s up to Goku to help him save the animals.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733121</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186452" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">86</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めて交わる拳! 人造人間17号VS孫悟空!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fists Cross for the First Time! Android #17 vs Son Goku!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete Majiwaru Kobushi! Jinzouningen 17 Gou vs Son Gokuu!!</title>
<summary>Android 17 has been busy. Not only has he started a family, but he’s been training as well. Will Goku see him as a worthwhile member of the team? And is he even interested in joining?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733119</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186453" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">85</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">動き出す宇宙 それぞれの思惑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Universes Begin to Make Their Moves: Their Individual Motives</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ugokidasu Uchuu: Sorezore no Omowaku</title>
<summary>Goku tries to find Android 17. In the meantime, the tournament stress is affecting the gods of each universe, causing them to bicker among themselves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733117</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187296" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">92</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">緊急実態発生! そろわない10人のメンバー!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emergency Development! The Incomplete Ten Members!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinkyuu Jittai Hassei! Sorowanai 10 Nin no Member!!</title>
<summary>Buu is stuck in a hibernation-like sleep! Meanwhile in the 6th Universe, Cabba teaches Caulifla how to become a Super Saiyan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733833</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187297" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">91</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝ち残るのはどの宇宙だ!? 続々と集う最強の戦士たち!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Which Universe Will Survive?! The Strongest Warriors Are Gathering!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kachinokoru no wa Dono Uchuu Da!? Zokuzoku to Tsudou Saikyou no Senshi-tachi!!</title>
<summary>The Zenos can hardly contain their excitement for the tournament to come. The participating universes are recruiting at different rates, so hopefully they can gather enough warriors before the deadline!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733831</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187298" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">90</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">越えるべき壁を見据えて! 悟空VS悟飯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">See the Wall That Must Be Passed! Goku vs Gohan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koerubeki Kabe o Misuete! Gokuu vs Gohan</title>
<summary>There’s time for a sparring match before the tournament. It’s an all-out fight between two Saiyans!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733829</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187299" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">89</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">現れた謎の美女! 天津流道場の怪!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Unknown Beauty Appears! The Tenshin-Style Dojo`s Mystery?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arawareta Nazo no Bijo! Tenshin Ryuu Doujo no Kai!?</title>
<summary>Goku finds the last two members for the Tournament of Power. But someone from Tien’s past interferes with the recruitment process.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733827</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187814" update="2017-05-18">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187892" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">96</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時はきた! 宇宙の命運をかけ無の世界へ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Time Is Here! To the World of Void for the Fate of the Universe!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki wa Kita! Uchuu no Meiun o Kake Mu no Sekai e!!</title>
<summary>The stage is set and the teams are ready. The universes finally gather in the World of the Void for the Tournament of Power!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733841</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187893" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">95</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最凶! 最悪! フレーザ大暴れ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Worst! The Most Evil! Frieza`s Rampage!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou! Saiaku! Freezer Ooabare!!</title>
<summary>Ambushed and outnumbered, Frieza shows his strength. Can he be trusted, or will his psychopathic tendencies get the best of him?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733839</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187894" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">94</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪の帝王復活! 出迎える謎の刺客たち!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Emperor of Evil Returns! A Reception of Mysterious Assassins?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aku no Teiou Fukkatsu! Demukaeru Nazo no Shikaku-tachi!?</title>
<summary>Goku meets with Fortuneteller Baba to resurrect Frieza. Will attempts on Frieza’s new life delay their return to the group?! With disqualification on the table, time is running out!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733837</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187895" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">93</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">10人目の戦士はおめえだ! 悟空フリーザのもとへ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`re the Tenth Warrior! Goku Goes to See Frieza!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">10 Ninme no Senshi wa Omee Da! Gokuu Freezer no Moto e!!</title>
<summary>The 7th Universe is desperate for a tenth member, so Goku seeks out Frieza as a potential candidate. In the 6th Universe, Cabba and Caulifla try to goad Kale into training with them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733835</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188401" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">100</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大暴走! 目覚め荒ぶる狂戦士!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Out of Control! The Savage Berserker Awakens!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Bousou! Mezame Araburu Kyousenshi!!</title>
<summary>Following Universe 7’s first loss, the fighting stage is starting to clear out. As ranks are thinned, Goku finds Caulifla and her protégée. But Goku and Caulifla’s dueling triggers a frenzied rage that will permanently alter the arena.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741893</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188402" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">99</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見せつけろ! クリリンの底力!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Show Them! Krillin`s True Power!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Misetsukero! Kuririn no Sokojikara!!</title>
<summary>The erasure of Universe 9 serves as a grim reminder that existence itself is at risk. When the dust settles, Krillin and No. 18 break out their spousal synergy against a combatant from Universe 4.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741891</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188403" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">98</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あぁ無常! 絶望する宇宙!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh, Uncertainty! A Universe Despairs!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aa Mujou! Zetsubou Suru Uchuu!!</title>
<summary>Goku finds himself facing most of Universe 9’s warriors by himself. But when Vegeta interjects, suddenly the playing field seems a lot more level!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741889</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188404" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">97</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生き残れ! ついに開幕「力の大会」!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Survive! The Tournament of Power Begins at Last!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikinokore! Tsui ni Kaimaku "Chikara no Taikai"!!</title>
<summary>Let the battle begin! With so many competitors on one stage, teamwork is in short supply. Going off alone could mean the elimination of some powerful warriors!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733843</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189123" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">104</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超絶光速バトル勃発! 悟空とヒットの共同戦線!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate High Speed Battle Begins! Goku and Hit Join Forces!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chouzetsu Kousoku Battle Boppatsu! Gokuu to Hit no Kyoudou Sensen!!</title>
<summary>Universe 6’s Hit and Universe 11’s Dyspo clash at breakneck speed. Even Hit’s signature Time Skip is too slow to be effective against Dyspo! But when a second Pride Trooper intervenes on his teammate’s behalf, Goku arrives to tip the scales.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741901</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189124" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">103</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟飯よ非情なれ! 第10宇宙との決戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gohan, Show No Mercy! Showdown with Universe 10!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gohan yo Hijou Nare! Dai 10 Uchuu to no Kessen!!</title>
<summary>Angered by the loss of their teammate but in no position to fight, the remaining warriors from Universe 2 retreat and regroup. Gohan and Piccolo face off against the last two fighters from Universe 10.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741899</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189125" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">102</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の力が大爆発!? 第2宇宙の魔女っ子戦士!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Power of Love Explodes?! Universe 2`s Little Witch Warriors!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Chikara ga Daibakuhatsu!? Dai 2 Uchuu Majokko Senshi!!</title>
<summary>Brianne and her companions from Universe 2 reveal their more powerful forms. It’s time to see what they’re made of! Has No. 17 bitten off more than he can chew?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741897</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189126" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">101</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迫りくる正義の戦士! プライド・トルーパーズ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Impending Warriors of Justice! The Pride Troopers!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Semarikuru Seigi no Senshi! Pride Troopers!!</title>
<summary>Three Saiyans are cut off from their teams, so the Pride Troopers attack! As the Tournament of Power progresses, teamwork is proving to be a threateningly powerful tactic.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741895</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189984" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">108</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリーザとフロスト! 交わる悪意!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Frieza and Frost! Conjoined Malice?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Freezer to Frost! Majiwaru Akui!?</title>
<summary>While Goku is busy fighting Ribrianne, Gohan faces a fighter from the 2nd Universe, and Frieza’s loyalty to the 7th Universe comes into question. What could Frieza possibly be planning?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741909</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189985" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">107</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復讐の「F」! しかけられた狡猾な罠!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge "F"! The Cunning Trap?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu no "F"! Shikakerareta Koukatsu na Wana!?</title>
<summary>There are 36 warriors left, and quality is beginning to overtake quantity. Since most of the 7th Universe’s fighters remain, the 4th Universe’s Frost is ready to pick a fight with them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741907</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189986" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">106</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見極めろ! 姿なきアタッカーとの死闘!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Find Him! Death Match with an Invisible Attacker!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikiwamero! Sugatanaki Attacker to no Shitou!!</title>
<summary>The 4th Universe has it out for Master Roshi! Against multiple opponents, how will technique fare against power?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741905</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189987" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">105</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奮戦! 武天老師命を燃やす!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Desperate Battle! Master Roshi`s Sacrifice!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funsen! Muten Roushi Inochi o Moyasu!!</title>
<summary>The 4th Universe has it out for Master Roshi! Against multiple opponents, how will technique fare against power?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741903</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190778" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">110</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孫悟空覚醒! 目覚めし者の新たなる極意!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Son Goku Wakes! New Level of the Awakened!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Son Gokuu Kakusei! Mezameshi Mono no Aratanaru Gokui!!</title>
<summary>An awesome flash of light marks the end of Goku and Jiren’s clash. When the dust settles, what kind of power will rise from the ashes?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741913</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190779" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">109</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空に迫る最強の敵! 今こそ放て! 必殺の元気玉!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Enemy Approaches Goku! Now, Let Loose! The Killer Spirit Bomb!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu ni Semaru Saikyou no Teki! Imakoso Hanate! Hissatsu no Genkidama!!</title>
<summary>Jiren finally confronts Goku and so begins a spectacle that will affect everyone on the battlefield!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741911</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191538" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">114</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼気せまる! 新たな超戦士の爆誕!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intimidating Passion! The Birth of a New Super Warrior!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiki Semaru! Aratana Chou Senshi no Bakutan!!</title>
<summary>Kale goes berserk in her and Caulifla’s fight with Goku. Power levels continue to grow in a duel that will push both parties to the limit!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750763</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191539" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">113</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嬉々として! 戦闘狂サイヤ人バトル再び!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With Great Joy! The Repeat Battle-Crazy Saiyan Fight!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiki Toshite! Sentoukyou Saiyajin Battle Futatabi!!</title>
<summary>Goku is still recovering from his previous fight, but Caulifla has ambitions that only Goku can help her achieve. The two fighters quickly gain power in this Saiyan vs. Saiyan blitz!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750761</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191540" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">112</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイヤ人の誓い! ベジータの覚悟!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Saiyan`s Vow! Vegeta`s Resolution!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiyajin no Chikai! Vegeta no Kakugo!!</title>
<summary>After their tough loss, it’s up to the three Saiyans of the 6th Universe to press onward. But with only half the time left and opportunistic fights cropping up across the arena, Cabba is on his last leg.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750759</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191541" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">111</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異次元の極致バトル! ヒットVSジレン!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Surreal Supreme Battle! Hit vs Jiren!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ijigen no Kyokuchi Battle! Hit vs Jiren!!</title>
<summary>With Goku out of the fight, Hit takes this opportunity to rid the field of its biggest threat. Maybe the key to Jiren’s downfall is time itself!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>750757</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192341" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">116</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆転の兆し! 身勝手の極意が大爆発!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sign of a Comeback! Ultra Instinct`s Huge Explosion!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakuten no Kizashi! Migatte no Gokui ga Daibakuhatsu!!</title>
<summary>Goku and Kefla’s battle comes to a head! With Goku’s Ultra Instinct kicking in, Kefla must risk it all if she has any hope of defeating her opponent! Who will come out on top?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>753991</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192342" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">115</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悟空VSケフラ! 超[スーパー]サイヤ人ブルー敗れる!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goku vs Kefla! Super Saiyan Blue Defeated?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuu vs Kefla! Super Saiyajin Blue Yabureru!?</title>
<summary>Goku and Kefla take center stage as fighting continues among the other universes. How will Goku’s stamina hold up against the multiplied strength of two fused Saiyans?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>753989</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192802" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">120</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">完璧なる生存戦略! 第3宇宙脅威の刺客!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Perfect Survival Tactic! Universe 3`s Menacing Assassin!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanpeki Naru Seizon Senryoku! Dai 3 Uchuu Kyoui no Shikaku!!</title>
<summary>There are three universes left! The 3rd Universe’s strategy has worked well thus far, but how will it fare against Gohan, Goku, and Vegeta?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>753999</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192803" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">119</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">回避不能!? ステルス攻撃の猛威!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unavoidable?! The Fierce Stealth Attack!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaihi Funou!? Stealth Kougeki no Moui!!</title>
<summary>As more and more universes drop out of existence, most of the remaining combatants are either strong or deceptive. The warriors from the 7th Universe are taken by surprise by hidden threats that are finally making themselves known!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>753997</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192804" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">118</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">加速する悲劇 消えゆく宇宙...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Accelerated Tragedy: Vanishing Universes...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kasoku Suru Higeki: Kieyuku Uchuu...</title>
<summary>On the verge of annihilation and with only a few warriors left, the 2nd and 6th Universes are reinvigorated. Desire to win will push their fighters to new heights!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>753995</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192805" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">117</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛の大決戦! 人造人間VS第2宇宙!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Showdown of Love! Androids vs Universe 2!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai no Daikessen! Jinzouningen vs Dai 2 Uchuu!!</title>
<summary>With most of Goku’s stamina spent, fighters from the other universes rush to knock him out of the tournament. The 2nd Universe’s warriors of love are out for blood, and it’s up to the androids of the 7th Universe to stop them!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>753993</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193605" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">122</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">己の誇りをかけて! ベジータ最強への挑戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For One`s Own Pride! Vegeta`s Challenge to Be the Strongest!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onore no Hokori o Kakete! Vegeta Saikyou e no Chousen!!</title>
<summary>Only two universes remain! The strongest of the 7th Universe are pitted against the strongest of the 11th Universe. As the tournament nears its end, it’s time for the combatants to push themselves above and beyond!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>754003</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193606" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">121</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">総力戦! 究極の4体合体VS第7宇宙総攻撃!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All-Out War! The Ultimate Quadruple Merge vs Universe 7`s Full-Scale Attack!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souryokusen! Kyuukyoku no 4 Tai Gattai vs Dai 7 Uchuu Soukougeki!!</title>
<summary>The 3rd Universe activates its secret final weapon! The 7th Universe will need to combine all their strength if they hope to defeat this quadruple-fused foe!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>754001</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194251" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">124</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疾風怒涛の猛襲! 悟飯背水の陣!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fiercely Overwhelming Assault! Gohan`s Last Stand!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shippuu Dotou no Moushuu! Gohan Haisui no Jin!!</title>
<summary>Frieza and Dyspo’s duel is accelerating out of control! As Frieza gets pushed back, Gohan enters the mix in hopes of getting a quick elimination.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760337</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194252" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">123</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全身全霊全力解放! 悟空とベジータ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Body and Soul, Full Power Release! Goku and Vegeta!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenshinzenrei Zenryoku Kaihou! Gokuu to Vegeta!!</title>
<summary>Jiren shrugs off even the strongest individual attacks! However, can the combined strength of Goku and Vegeta stand up against his immense power?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760335</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194923" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">125</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">威風堂々! 破壊神トッポ降臨!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With Imposing Presence! God of Destruction Toppo Descends!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ifuudoudou! Hakaishin Toppo Kourin!!</title>
<summary>Because of the 7th Universe’s numbers advantage, Android 17 hopes to run out the clock. When Frieza comes over to provide support, Top is forced to rethink his motivations and will unleash a familiar destructive power!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760339</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195139" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">126</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神をも超えろ! ベジータ捨て身の一撃!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Surpass Even a God! Vegeta`s Desperate Blow!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami o mo Koero! Vegeta Sutemi no Ichigeki!!</title>
<summary>Both sides are becoming more and more desperate. Top has given up everything to survive! Vegeta gives up nothing! In the end, who will be looking down on whom?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760341</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195154" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">128</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">気高い誇り最後まで! ベジータ散る!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Noble Pride to the End! Vegeta Falls!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kedakai Hokori Saigo made! Vegeta Chiru!!</title>
<summary>Following Android 17’s sacrifice, the remaining Saiyans need time to recover. As Goku rests, Vegeta takes it upon himself to challenge Jiren one on one!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760345</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195155" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">127</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迫りくる障壁! 希望を託した最後のバリア!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Approaching Wall! The Final Barrier of Hope!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Semarikuru Shouheki! Kibou o Takushita Saigo no Barrier!!</title>
<summary>Jiren is all that remains between the 7th Universe and victory. But with Frieza out for the count and Vegeta low on stamina, how will they compare to one who values strength above all else?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760343</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195963" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">131</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡の決着! さらば悟空! また会う日まで!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miraculous Conclusion! Farewell, Goku! Until We Meet Again!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Kecchaku! Saraba Gokuu! Mata Au Hi made!!</title>
<summary>Goku and Jiren are at the end of their ropes as the clock winds down! Will the 7th Universe finally emerge victorious?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760351</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195964" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">130</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空前絶後の超決戦! 究極のサバイバルバトル!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greatest Showdown of All Time! The Ultimate Survival Battle!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuuzenzetsugo no Chou Kessen! Kyuukyoku no Survival Battle!!</title>
<summary>Goku fights for everyone dear to him. Jiren fights only for himself. Overwhelmed and on the verge of defeat, Jiren’s resolve is reignited. He’ll stop at nothing to prevent his past from repeating!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760349</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195965" update="2020-04-07">
<epno type="1">129</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">限界超絶突破! 身勝手の極意極まる!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limits Super Surpassed! Ultra Instinct Mastered!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genkai Chouzetsu Toppa! Migatte no Gokui Kiwamaru!!</title>
<summary>Once again, Goku ascends to new heights. As Ultra Instinct takes over, now it’s a matter of whether surpassing his own limits is enough to surpass Jiren!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760347</identifier>
<identifier>dragon-ball-super</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="228326" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228327" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228328" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228329" update="2020-04-18">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
