<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11223" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shingeki no Bahamut: Virgin Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Гневът на Бахамут: Чиста душа</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">神撃のバハムート VIRGIN SOUL</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Rage of Bahamut: Virgin Soul</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">신격의 바하무트 VIRGIN SOUL</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">巴哈姆特之怒 VIRGIN SOUL</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10373" type="Prequel">Shingeki no Bahamut: Genesis</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="673908">Almost a masterpiece, didn`t expect that. Quality were all the prequel has. Heck, I almost forgot everything there. But this one truly hits all the marks. Basically, it`s a bunch of neutral factions, with clear reason and stuff. Almost everything is rational, no stupidity. And the ending just amplifies all of those points.

You`re going to be amused by some of the characters, and captivated to one of them -- someone which is way more than he is.

It`s a bunch of equally great aspects. But unlike its prequel and a lot of high quality series, it`s actually brave enough to delve way deeper than just a "pretty story".</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://shingekinobahamut-virginsoul.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="31375" type="Animation Work">MAPPA</name>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="3728" type="Direction">Satou Keiichi</name>
<name id="4410" type="Music">Ike Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="44461" type="Original Work">Cygames</name>
<name id="2163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="15969" type="Chief Direction">Matsuda Kiyoshi</name>
<name id="11871" type="Chief Animation Direction">Haneda Kouji</name>
<name id="6065" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hayama Kenji</name>
</creators>
<description>10 years after the world escaped destruction due to the revival of Bahamut, humans at the royal capital gather wealth, the demons are enslaved to assist with the capital`s revival, and the gods lose their power due to a decrease in religious piety. The world is thrown off balance as humans, gods, and demons hold their own ideas of justice.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="977">6.36</permanent>
<temporary count="985">7.07</temporary>
<review count="1">6.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>199126.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18190</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30736</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://shingekinobahamut-virginsoul.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://shingekinobahamut-virginsoul.jp/en/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>神撃のバハムート</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4550</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356333</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20165</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B06Y3PR794</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="201" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>bounty hunter</name>
<description>A bounty hunter is one who hunts and captures targets (be it people, animals, etc.) for monetary gain, preferably without killing/destroying their target. Despite being illegal in most of the world today, it is a legal profession in the United States and Philippines (a former commonwealth of the US), who are known as "bail enforcement agents".
If they are only and constantly hired to kill, they are likely an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2391" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>bishoujo</name>
<description>In Japanese, a bishoujo is any pretty female from toddlerhood to late adolescence. In the West, the word specifically refers to attractive girls generally from late childhood or early adolescence, especially those that appeal to males, and particularly to fictional characters designed in a way traditionally associated to shoujo manga. Fictional bishoujo tend to be cute, pastel-coloured teenagers; they lack the sophistication of older women, instead having detailed eye and hair design, fluttery costumes often including ribbons, and all sorts of generally sparkly fluff.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2827" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>sudden naked guy appearance</name>
<description>A male specimen previously unknown to the viewer and not dressed in any clothes suddenly appears out of nowhere.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3269" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-11">
<name>genocide</name>
<description>The systematic killing of substantial numbers of people on the basis of ethnicity, religion, political opinion, social status, or other particularity.
Acts committed with intent to destroy, in whole or in part, a national, ethnic, racial or religious group.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3610" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-12-19">
<name>game references</name>
<description>Be it the sound of a 1-up being grabbed, three golden triangles appearing on someones shirt or a blatant parody portraying a monkey throwing barrels down a poorly constructed facility, this anime contains characteristics dedicated to the remembrance/worship of an actual video game.</description>
<picurl>166123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3647" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-05">
<name>drastic change in sequel</name>
<description>This anime differs greatly in genre and/or overall mood from its prequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3718" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>love between enemies</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3818" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-21">
<name>kids in war</name>
<description>When minors participate in armed conflict.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4342" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-06">
<name>large-scale war</name>
<description>When the whole world, or, at least, a big part of it, partakes in the hell that is war.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4413" parentid="6563" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-16">
<name>heaven</name>
<description>Heaven, the Heavens or Seven Heavens, is a common religious, cosmological or transcendent place from which heavenly beings (such as a God, angels, the jinn, and sky deities like King or Queen of Heaven, Heavenly Father, Heavenly Mother, Son of Heaven, heavenly saints or venerated ancestors) originate, are enthroned or inhabit.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5095" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>slums</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5794" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-01">
<name>forbidden love</name>
<description>This anime contains characters pursuing a romantic interest that their parents, grandparents, the police, the fire department, the neighbourhood watch association and local politicians do not approve of.
Potential relationships defined as such may be ones that are incestuous, violations of caste systems, or socially unsanctioned.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6371" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-30">
<name>red-light district</name>
<description>A red-light district is a part of an urban area where there is a concentration of prostitution and sex-oriented businesses, such as sex shops, strip clubs, adult theaters, etc. The term originates from the red lights that were used as signs of brothels. There are areas in many big cities around the world which have acquired an international reputation as red-light districts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6528" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-22">
<name>palace</name>
<description>A palace is a grand residence, especially a royal residence or the home of a head of state or some other high-ranking dignitary, such as a bishop or archbishop.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>177729.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6614" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-12">
<name>Animeism</name>
<description>Animeism is a late-night Japanese programming block established in April 2012. It is devoted to anime and broadcast each Thursday night on MBS, in a fashion similar to Fuji TV`s http://anidb.net/t3865 [noitaminA] that also airs on Thursdays. Just like noitaminA, the block airs two series back to back. From April 2015 onwards, the block was moved to Friday nights.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>63625.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6901" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-23">
<name>underground</name>
<description>Some or all of the action occurs underground, in caves, mines, sewers, subways or underground cities.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7509" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-31">
<name>fall of a country</name>
<description>The fall of a country is the demise of a national state, generally as the result of foreign conquest or large-scale natural disasters. The former is commonly characterized by the invaders pillaging the capital, often with the death or capture of the ruler. In some cases, it may be the result of another internal power wrestling control over large portions of territory, population, and national wealth away from the hands of the central authorities, which may pave the way to the immediate rise of a successor state or to fragmentation into numerous minor states. On a larger scale, the concept may also be applied to entire civilizations or to the world as known by its inhabitants.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7579" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2020-03-31">
<name>Judeo-Christian mythology</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="69468" type="appears in" update="2014-08-17">
<rating votes="54">6.70</rating>
<name>Amira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159775.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69811" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="29">6.11</rating>
<name>Jeanne d`Arc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69885" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<rating votes="12">5.71</rating>
<name>Hamsa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69886" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-09">
<rating votes="8">4.94</rating>
<name>Bacchus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4841" picture="55063.jpg">Iwasaki Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70020" type="appears in" update="2014-09-16">
<rating votes="18">4.95</rating>
<name>Cerberus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70193" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-29">
<rating votes="56">8.07</rating>
<name>Rita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rita is a seemingly young necromancer, known for being the only surviving citizen of the Nebelville massacre. For two hundred years she revived and lived with the zombified remnants of the town until she was, in the end, bitten by her own parents, driving a bypassing http://anidb.net/ch69469 [Kaisar Lidfard] into killing her out of mercy. After being spared by Kaisar and becoming an undead she now follow the former knight in his travels.
Source: shingeki-no-bahamut-genesis.wikia.com</description>
<picture>211385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70544" type="appears in" update="2014-10-08">
<rating votes="7">1.49</rating>
<name>Gabriel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70545" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-02-05">
<rating votes="2">2.42</rating>
<name>Michael</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162465.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70546" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-10-08">
<rating votes="4">8.44</rating>
<name>Raphael</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162466.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70547" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-10-08">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Uriel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162467.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="71282" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-11-10">
<rating votes="2">4.20</rating>
<name>Martinet</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163925.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="71874" type="appears in" update="2014-12-04">
<rating votes="3">5.06</rating>
<name>Lucifer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81468" type="appears in" update="2016-04-03">
<name>Bahamut</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185179.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81476" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Jeanne d`Arc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jeanne D`Arc in her demon form.</description>
<picture>185187.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86912" type="main character in" update="2017-03-01">
<rating votes="11">4.60</rating>
<name>Charioce XVII</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86913" type="main character in" update="2017-03-01">
<rating votes="30">4.61</rating>
<name>Nina Drango</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88023" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-04">
<rating votes="7">1.36</rating>
<name>Alessand Visponti</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88024" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-04">
<rating votes="10">4.71</rating>
<name>Sofiel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88025" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-04">
<rating votes="2">2.68</rating>
<name>Dias Bardolomew</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88026" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-04">
<rating votes="4">6.68</rating>
<name>Mugaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199151.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="88849" type="appears in" update="2017-04-16">
<rating votes="2">1.77</rating>
<name>Shikkoku Hei Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2573" picture="240892.jpg">Shirokuma Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93066" type="appears in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Rita</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch70193 [Rita] 10 years later works in the capital as a shadowy doctor, accepting any patient whether divine or demonic.</description>
<picture>211386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93067" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="3">4.86</rating>
<name>Favaro Leone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch69470 [Favaro] after his encounter with Bahamut. He still calls himself a bounty hunter. Although he was knighted, he has cast off his title and set off for a meandering journey. His right leg is prosthetic.</description>
<picture>211399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93068" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="2">1.29</rating>
<name>Kaisar Lidfard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch69469 [Kaisar] after the Bahamut incident. Once the disgrace of a long lineage of knights, he recovered his noble title and his honor by helping to seal away Bahamut. Ten years later he serves King Charioce as captain of the Orleans Knights. Kaisar is honest to a fault and serious as well. His left hand is prosthetic.</description>
<picture>211401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93069" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="1">3.48</rating>
<name>Azazel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch70019 [Azazel] ten years later. He lives in the Royal Capital Anatae and works for the demon funeral home. He loathes humans for oppressing his demonic brethren. He only has two horns, not four, and his wings are retracted by default.</description>
<picture>211404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93070" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="4">4.51</rating>
<name>Jeanne d`Arc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch69811 [Jeanne] ten years later. She is no longer a knight or the leader of the Orleans Knights. Lives as a simple farmer until imprisoned by King Charioce XVII.</description>
<picture>211409.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93074" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="1">2.24</rating>
<name>El</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>El is http://anidb.net/ch88026 [Mugaro] after Gabriel awakened him as a god.</description>
<picture>211420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93077" type="appears in" update="2017-12-30">
<name>Nina Drango</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93078" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-30">
<name>Nina Drango</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211427.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93079" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Jeanne d`Arc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch93070 [Jeanne] after blessed by http://anidb.net/ch88024 [Sofiel] gains god-like powers.</description>
<picture>211437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93080" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Houtai Akuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Ragged Demon is http://anidb.net/ch93069 [Azazel] hiding his identity, fighting for the oppressed demons.</description>
<picture>211438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93081" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Chris</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211439.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93082" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Rocky</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rocky is http://anidb.net/ch93068 [Kaisar]`s severed left hand zombified by http://anidb.net/ch70193 [Rita]. It acts as Rita`s assistant.</description>
<picture>211440.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93083" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Nina no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93084" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Nina no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211442.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93085" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Kaisar Lidfard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch93068 [Kaisar] turned into a zombie after his death by http://anidb.net/ch70193 [Rita].</description>
<picture>211443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93087" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Ridwan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93091" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Ryuuzoku Zokuchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93093" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Ryuuzoku Zokuchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93094" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Ryuujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93095" type="appears in" update="2017-12-31">
<name>Ryuujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211456.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="186394" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Firestarter</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Firestarter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Firestarter</title>
<summary>The rag demon (Azazel) faces Charioce XVII`s forces alone in order to save the demons that are being held hostage.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="186395" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Close Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Close Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Close Encounter</title>
<summary>A god has infiltrated the capital following the trail of Mugaro`s recently unleashed power. Nina is enjoying life in the capital as if nothing happened, and she has a chance meeting with an attractive, young man. Back at the palace, Charioce XVII takes up command and sets out to capture the rag demon (Azazel) himself.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="186396" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Miserables</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Miserables</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Miserables</title>
<summary>After waking up in Rita`s clinic, Nina continues to work hard in the capital. Azazel approaches her in hopes of using her red dragon powers to get revenge against the humans. Meanwhile in the palace, Charioce XVII questions Kaisar on his responsibility for failing to capture the rag demon, spurring Kaisar to attempt to contact the rag demon on his own.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="186397" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Red Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Red Dragon</title>
<summary>There are rumors of a mysterious rag demon that has been massacring humans in the capital. Hearing this, Nina decides to try to catch this wanted criminal. Nina is a young girl who has come to the capital to work hard and earn money to send back to her mother in her rural village.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="186994" update="2017-04-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186995" update="2017-04-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187237" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Day of Defeat</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day of Defeat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Day of Defeat</title>
<summary>Burning with rage, the demon Azazel engages King Charoice XVII in combat, and the Orleans Knight captain Kaisar takes action to do what he believes is right.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187238" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Day of Victory</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day of Victory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Day of Victory</title>
<summary>The Orleans Knights captain Kaisar becomes uneasy as he spots demons led by Azazel acting suspiciously, so Kaisar attempts to advise Charioce XVII against participating in the upcoming victory parade. Meanwhile, Nina has no idea that any of this is going on as she helps run the food stand with Rita in the city.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187239" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Anatean Holiday</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anatean Holiday</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anatean Holiday</title>
<summary>Nina is out shopping for supplies to prepare for the evening festival of the war commemoration. She bumps into the handsomely disguised Charioce in the city once again, and invites him to the food stand she is helping to run.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187240" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Those Who Won`t Give Up</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Won`t Give Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Those Who Won`t Give Up</title>
<summary>After Azazel was saved by Nina, he now wants to use Nina in his revolt against mankind. Being completely unaware of all this, Nina is enjoying shopping with Mugaro in the city. At the same time, Kaisar and Rita are having lunch together.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187862" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Great Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Escape</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Great Escape</title>
<summary>After failing to break out of the dungeon once, Nina and Jeanne are helped by Rita in their second escape attempt. Meanwhile, Gabriel leads the gods` advance on the royal capital, where Charioce is waiting. Forces on each side are about to open fire.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187863" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Declaration of War</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Declaration of War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Declaration of War</title>
<summary>Hoping to see Mugaro again, Jeanne and Nina decide to break out of the prison where they`re being imprisoned. In the capital, the gods have gotten hold of El`s power, and they demand that Charioce return the power that he took from them.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187864" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Way She Was</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Way She Was</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Way She Was</title>
<summary>Captain of the Orleans Knights, Jeanne D`Arc, is ejected from the capital following differences with Charioce XVII, which costs her everything.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187865" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Same Old, Same Old</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Same Old, Same Old</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Same Old, Same Old</title>
<summary>Even while she`s imprisoned, Nina is still her energetic self, working away tirelessly. On the other side of the prison, Kaisar finds out that his old friend Favaro has also been imprisoned and discovers that Favaro already knows Nina. Kaisar sits and listens as Favaro tells him the story of how he met Nina.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188395" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">City of the Gods, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">City of the Gods, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">City of the Gods, Part 2</title>
<summary>El attempts to evade Nina and Bacchus in order to flee from captivity in the palace of the gods. Meanwhile, in the capital of Anatae, Kaisar is taken from prison to the coliseum, where he`s forced to battle one-on-one against a demon.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188396" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">City of the Gods, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">City of the Gods, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">City of the Gods, Part 1</title>
<summary>Nina and Jeanne soar through a storm to reach the land of the gods. Once there, Jeanne is reunited with her son, El. Meanwhile Azazel, now a captive of the humans, is forced to battle other demons to the death in the capital`s coliseum.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188397" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Homecoming</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homecoming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Homecoming</title>
<summary>Nina and Jeanne leave behind the battlefield and head toward Nina`s home in search of a way to enter the land of the gods. There they meet the village elder and are warmly welcomed by the villagers, including Nina`s mother.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188398" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">A Farewell to Arms</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Farewell to Arms</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Farewell to Arms</title>
<summary>War erupts between humans and gods. To get the upper hand against the fast-advancing gods, Charioce XVII activates a weapon that was slumbering deep underground. Just when Nina and the others are escaping from the dungeon, they`re thrown into the heat of battle.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189087" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">From Heaven to Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Heaven to Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">From Heaven to Hell</title>
<summary>After fleeing from Charioce XVII`s ball, Nina and the others are pursued by the Onyx Knights, who make an attempt on their lives. Mugaro acts together with Azazel, and Jeanne encourages him to return to the land of the gods.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189088" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Shall We Dance?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shall We Dance?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shall We Dance?</title>
<summary>Jeanne and Sofiel leave the land of the gods in search of El, but they aren`t able to get any information. As part of a plan to snatch Charioce XVII`s bracelet, Nina and Alessand lead an effort to sneak into a ball at the palace.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189089" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Invictus</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invictus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Invictus</title>
<summary>By meeting Charioce XVII again, Nina gains the ability to transform into a red dragon at will. Azazel has escaped the coliseum and is filled with bitterness when learning of Nina`s new ability. El gazes on at Azazel, and the group plans how to snatch the bracelet that Charioce is wearing.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189090" update="2019-03-17">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Virgin Souls</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Virgin Souls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Virgin Souls</title>
<summary>Nina and El flee from the land of the gods and return to the capital. There they are reunited with Rita and Favaro, who have rescued Kaisar. While searching around town for information, Nina once again encounters Charioce XVII in disguise.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190498" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Run, Nina, Run</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run, Nina, Run</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Run, Nina, Run</title>
<summary>Kaisar looks death in the eyes when protecting Charioce XVII from Jeanne and Azazel. Meanwhile, Bahamut unleashes a torrent of destruction across the world. As the end draws near, difficult decisions become inevitable.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190499" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Rise of the Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rise of the Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rise of the Nightmare</title>
<summary>While Charioce XVII is leading Bahamut to the capital, demonic forces jointly commanded by Azazel and Lucifer besiege the city. Jeanne`s rebel army enters the fray, which results in a free-for-all battle of men, gods, and demons. Amidst the chaos, Dias finds Alessand wandering the battlefield.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190500" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Which Way Is the Wind Blowing?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Which Way Is the Wind Blowing?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Which Way Is the Wind Blowing?</title>
<summary>Charioce XVII brings unrest to the land of Eibos, where Bahamut was revived a decade ago. Nina follows the king to Eibos in order to put an end to his violent acts. Having lost her son El to a stabbing, Jeanne leads her allies to make an assault on the capital and slay Charioce.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190501" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Vengeance</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vengeance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Vengeance</title>
<summary>Rita frantically attempts to save El after he`s stabbed by Alessand. El`s mother Jeanne is powerless to do anything but watch. Azazel makes his ire known and then vanishes into the rain. Alessand pleads with the head of the Onyx Knights to allow him entry into the force as a reward for stabbing El.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191243" update="2017-09-25">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191244" update="2017-09-25">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
