<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1125" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>15</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-05-17</startdate>
<enddate>2007-01-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gundam Evolve</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ガンダム イボルブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gundam Evolve</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">กันดั้มอีโวลฟ์</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="229" type="Other">Shin Kidou Senki Gundam Wing</anime>
<anime id="252" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam SEED</anime>
<anime id="596" type="Other">Kidou Senshi SD Gundam</anime>
<anime id="715" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam</anime>
<anime id="719" type="Other">Kidou Senshi Gundam ZZ</anime>
<anime id="915" type="Other">Kidou Butouden G Gundam</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.gundam-evolve.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="726" type="Animation Production">Sunrise</name>
<name id="4526" type="Direction">Momose Keiichi</name>
<name id="1531" type="Direction">Yonetani Yoshitomo</name>
<name id="4410" type="Music">Ike Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="12357" type="Direction">Suzuki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="1761" type="Direction">Murase Shuukou</name>
<name id="1639" type="Direction">Kitamura Masaki</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="659" type="Direction">Imanishi Takashi</name>
<name id="3637" type="Music">Watanabe Takeo</name>
<name id="12362" type="Direction">Abe Yuuichi</name>
<name id="34071" type="Direction">Kawada Shigehito</name>
<name id="147" type="Story Composition">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="47839" type="Direction">Matsuki Yasuaki</name>
<name id="48037" type="Direction">Masuo Takayuki</name>
<name id="53880" type="Direction">Horii Shin`ya</name>
</creators>
<description>A series of short films packaged with certain model kits and aired at conventions, the Gundam Evolve series chronicles a number of side-stories, alternative scenes, and even bonus omake from all around the Gundam canon. Featuring a mix of animation media—from traditional cels to 3-D CG rendering to even cel-shaded 2-D animation—these often 3-5 minute shorts cover such events as Domon Kasshu`s training (and a bit of a romantic tift with Rain Mikamura) from G Gundam, Amuro Ray battling Quess Paraya from Char`s Counterattack, Kamille Bidan training in the Gundam Mk.II from Zeta Gundam, and Canard Pars dueling Prayer Reverie from the Gundam SEED X Astray manga.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="390">3.88</permanent>
<temporary count="399">6.28</temporary>
<review count="1">5.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>18357.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2980</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3288</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1283</identifier>
<identifier>ruxkiq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gundam-evolve.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327361</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7168</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3216" parentid="2626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>Universal Century</name>
<description>Refers to the Universal Century timeline in Gundam anime. Gundam anime with this tag all belong in the same universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2422" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="85">8.42</rating>
<name>Principality of Zeon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Republic of Zeon was initially founded by Zeon Zum Deikun, who declared the colony located at the second Earth-Luna Lagrangian Point, named Side 3, independent from the Earth Federation in U.C.0058. For the next several years, Zeon Zum Deikun and his followers dealt with diplomatic issues surrounding their independence, chiefly the economic pressure applied to Side 3 by the Earth Federation, in their efforts to force Side 3 back into the Federation. During this time, Side 3 formed its first national guard unit. Unfortunately, for the Republic of Zeon, Zeon Zum Deikun unexpectedly died (almost certainly assassinated by the Zabis) in UC 0068, leaving Side 3 without a leader. After the end of the One Year War, the Republic was re-established with a pro-Earth Federation puppet government.</description>
<picture>17677.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2441" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Earth Federation</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The unified world government that launched the space settlement program and now rules over both Earth and the space colonies. Its main decision-making body is the Earth Federation Assembly, which meets occasionally to pass new legislation.
Though not as cruel and aggressive as the Principality of Zeon`s leaders, the bureaucrats who rule over the Earth Federation are corrupt, weak-willed, and insensitive to the space colonists` desire for independence. After the One Year War, the Federation decides to concentrate its energies on reconstructing Earth instead of the space colonies, further increasing political tensions.</description>
<picture>17701.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2452" type="appears in" update="2009-01-15">
<name>Earth Federation Forces</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The military arm of the Earth Federation. The Federation Forces are divided into several branches, including land, sea, air, and space forces. Until mass production of the RGM-79 GM begins in the final weeks of the One Year War, the Federation Forces are forced to battle the Principality of Zeon`s mobile suits using conventional tanks, planes, and space fighters. Even in the postwar years, the Federation Forces are usually inferior to their opponents in terms of skill, morale, and equipment.</description>
<picture>1824.gif</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="11958" update="2008-08-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2001-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">RX-78</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11959" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2001-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">RX-178 Gundam MK II</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11960" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2001-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">GF 13-017 NJ II</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11961" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2001-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Dendrobium RX-78GP03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11962" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2001-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">RX-93 Nu Gundam</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38075" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2006-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">YMF-X000A Dreadnought Gundam</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38078" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2006-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">XXXG-00W0 Wing Gundam Zero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38079" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2006-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">GAT-X105 Strike Gundam</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38082" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2006-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">MSZ-010 ZZ Gundam</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38083" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">RB-79 Ball</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38084" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">RMS-099 Rick Dias</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38085" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">RMS-108 Marasai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38086" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">SD Musha Gundam</title>
</episode>
<episode id="38087" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2006-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">MSZ-006 Zeta Gundam</title>
</episode>
<episode id="62435" update="2010-05-07">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2007-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">RX-78 Gundam</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
