<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1129" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1996-03-02</startdate>
<enddate>1996-03-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dragon Ball: Saikyou e no Michi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ドラゴンボール 最強への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Movie 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dragon Ball: The Path to Ultimate Strength</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Dragon Ball 10th Anniversary Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Dragon Ball Z: Sposób, by stać się silniejszym</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Dragon Ball: Droga ku potędze</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="synonym">Dragon Ball: The Way To The Strongest</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">DB Movie 4</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">DRAGON BALL 最強への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dragon Ball: The Path to Power</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Dragon Ball 4 - L`armée du Ruban Rouge</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Dragon Ball - Il cammino dell`eroe</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Dragon Ball: El camino hacia el Poder</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Dragon Ball: A Lei do Mais Forte</title>
<title xml:lang="ca" type="official">Bola de Drac: El Camí cap a el més fort</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">ดราก้อนบอล มูฟวี่ 4 ตอน วิถีแห่งเจ้ายุทธจักร</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="231" type="Alternative Setting">Dragon Ball</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<creators>
<name id="1902" type="Original Work">Toriyama Akira</name>
<name id="2706" type="Direction">Yamauchi Shigeyasu</name>
<name id="4077" type="Music">Tokunaga Akihito</name>
</creators>
<description>This is the famous 10th Anniversary movie that was released in 1996. Done in GT-style animation, the movie re-told Goku`s meeting with his original friends (Bulma, Oolong, Yamcha, Kame-Sen`nin, etc.) and his battle against the Red Ribbon Army.
Source: kanzenshuu.com/newbie/</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="958">5.35</permanent>
<temporary count="974">6.81</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>153791.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2400</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>893</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2450</identifier>
<identifier>vdiecf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dragon_Ball:_The_Path_to_Power</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドラゴンボール_最強への道</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>152792</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2085" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="689">8.50</rating>
<name>Kame Sennin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kame Sennin is an ancient and wise martial arts master and the first Earthling to wield the Kamehameha. Though he seems frail, he is a mighty warrior, having trained Grandpa Gohan, Gyuumaou, Son Gokuu, and others.</description>
<picture>135368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1935" picture="21204.jpg">Aikawa Kin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2104" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-31">
<rating votes="11">7.28</rating>
<name>Bulma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16933.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2116" type="main character in" update="2009-09-08">
<rating votes="262">8.88</rating>
<name>Son Gokuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6465" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="9">4.17</rating>
<name>Red Sousui</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6879" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-30">
<rating votes="62">5.32</rating>
<name>Kame</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch2085 [Kame Sennin]`s turtle.
He`s celebrating his 1000th birthday in http://anidb.net/e16565 [episode 117] of http://anidb.net/a1530 [Dragon Ball Z]</description>
<picture>24911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6881" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="128">4.59</rating>
<name>Oolong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oolong is a shapeshifting, anthropomorphic pig that uses his abilities for his own greedy desires. He was expelled from shapeshifting training for stealing the teacher`s underwear, so he lacks the ability to change his form for more than five minutes at a time without a break. He joins with Goku to search for the Dragon Balls and eventually steal them, but he abandons his plans. In Dragon Ball Z, he is often in the company of Roshi.</description>
<picture>135369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="368" picture="25838.jpg">Tatsuta Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6917" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="56">4.03</rating>
<name>Puar</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Puar is a soft-spoken shapeshifting blue creature and the constant companion of Yamcha. He uses his abilities to shapeshift into anything to help Yamcha rob passersby in the desert. Afterwards, he travels with Yamcha and Goku during Dragon Ball, and continues to live with Yamcha afterwards.</description>
<picture>135370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3057" picture="23959.jpg">Watanabe Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6966" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-08">
<rating votes="33">6.56</rating>
<name>Yamucha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7015" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="63">5.25</rating>
<name>Shenlong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shenron is the dragon that appears when someone collects all seven of Earth`s Dragon Balls and calls him forth. He will grant one wish and then vanish, scattering the 7 Dragon Balls throughout the Earth once again.</description>
<picture>25280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23" picture="188505.jpg">Utsumi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8999" type="appears in" update="2009-06-11">
<rating votes="10">3.47</rating>
<name>Metallic Gunsou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>28464.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22167" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="26">6.44</rating>
<name>Jinzouningen 8 Gou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of http://anidb.net/ch18381 [Dr. Gero]`s early creations. He refuses to fight http://anidb.net/ch2116 [Gokuu] when told to, and instead helps him. The two quickly become friends.</description>
<picture>56095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56031" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-22">
<rating votes="9">3.03</rating>
<name>Blue Shougun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56086" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="4">4.51</rating>
<name>Black Sanbou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56087" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-23">
<rating votes="4">4.51</rating>
<name>White Shogun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3099" picture="24698.jpg">Kakegawa Hirohiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="12030" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1996-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12031" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1996-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13474" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>75</length>
<airdate>1996-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
