<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11290" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-01-22</startdate>
<enddate>2018-09-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Toshidensetsu Series</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Urban Legend Series</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">도시전설 시리즈</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Toshi Densetsu Series</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">都市伝説シリーズ</title>
</titles>
<url>http://mary-jane.biz/mysite1/toshiden01top.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="25377" type="Character Design">Nakamori Koutarou</name>
<name id="43957" type="Direction">Kinomoto Natsumi</name>
<name id="52749" type="Work">New Generation</name>
<name id="52751" type="Character Design">Ema20</name>
<name id="43756" type="Original Work">Satsuki Imonet</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="249">5.93</permanent>
<temporary count="254">6.72</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>185351.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32355</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mary-jane.biz/mysite1/toshiden01top.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://mary-jane.biz/mysite1/toshiden02top.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://mary-jane.biz/mysite1/toshiden03top.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://mary-jane.biz/mysite1/toshiden04top.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://mary-jane.biz/mysite1/toshiden05top.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://mary-jane.biz/mysite1/toshiden06top.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-04">
<name>shota</name>
<description>Shotacon, sometimes shortened to shota, is a Japanese slang portmanteau of the phrase Shoutarou complex and describes an attraction to young boys, or an individual with such an attraction. Outside Japan, the term is less common and most often refers to a genre of manga and anime wherein pre-pubescent or pubescent male characters are depicted in a suggestive or erotic manner.
In a general sense, this is the same as http://anidb.net/t2566 [loli], just replace young girls with young boys.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>35399.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2491" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-09">
<name>nurse</name>
<description>For hentai shows, it`s enough if a http://anidb.net/t884 [nurse costume] is worn without the female character actually working as a nurse.
For ecchi shows, the nurse profession must play a big enough part in the overall setting.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
<picurl>160445.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2693" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-10">
<name>handjob</name>
<description>A handjob is the manual stimulation of the penis by another person`s hand. The female equivalent is http://anidb.net/t7229 [fingering].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2702" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-16">
<name>mammary intercourse</name>
<description>Mammary intercourse is a sex act, performed as foreplay or as non-penetrative sex, that involves the stimulation of the male penis by the female breasts. Commonly, this sex act involves the man placing his penis in the woman`s cleavage and thrusting between her breasts, while the breasts are squeezed around the penis for additional stimulation, and fellatio may also be performed in combination. Mammary intercourse is also commonly known as titty-fucking or titfuck in the United States, as well as tit wank or French fuck in the United Kingdom. The Japanese term, paizuri (from oppai, breasts, and the verb suru, used in this context to describe the sexual act), is commonly used in the anime fandom. A variant term is "naizuri" (a pun on nai, the negative of the verb aru, indicating existence/presence), which describes an attempt to do a paizuri, but with insufficient cleavage.</description>
<picurl>174692.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2705" parentid="2848" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>creampie</name>
<description>The act of a man ejaculating inside a girl`s vagina, leaving the semen oozing out of her.</description>
<picurl>160720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2707" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-20">
<name>internal shots</name>
<description>Internal shots are pictures that display the interior of the body of a living being, either through the skin, kind of as an "x-ray" of sorts, or from the inside, as if the camera was also inside. This is generally used during sex scenes to display the inside of any area being penetrated. Those shots may happen either by making an area of the body transparent or by displaying the same area again, but from the inside; the latter method is shown in the picture.</description>
<picurl>213307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2722" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>doggy style</name>
<description>Bang her from behind and use her boobies as a steering wheel!</description>
<picurl>161394.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2787" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-28">
<name>teacher x student</name>
<description>Suggests a relationship involving a teacher and their student, often times sexual in nature.</description>
<picurl>206646.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3027" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-10">
<name>sex tape</name>
<description>A sex tape is a camera recording of sexual acts, regardless of the actual storage medium. Such recordings are sometimes made against the will or even knowledge of the depicted persons.
While most of them are made solely for personal use, a sex tape may be released (or threatened to be released) to damage the reputation of the depicted, to blackmail them or merely to make a profit.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3299" parentid="6268" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>double fellatio</name>
<description>Double fellatio is when oral sex is performed on the penis simultaneously by two individuals.</description>
<picurl>168623.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3854" parentid="2891" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-13">
<name>breast expansion</name>
<description>When the breasts grow in size, right before the viewers eyes!
The breasts will slowly grow larger, either stretching clothing to its limit or bursting free completely!</description>
<picurl>184159.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4049" parentid="2721" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>outdoor sex</name>
<description>Popular place for sex in visual novels and manga.</description>
<picurl>175405.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6355" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-06">
<name>water sex</name>
<description>Sexual acts taking place in water: i.e. sea, pool, bath, shower, etc.</description>
<picurl>178296.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6389" parentid="2707" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-19">
<name>cervix penetration</name>
<description>The cervix/womb of a female is visibly penetrated. Very likely invoked in conjunction with the http://anidb.net/t2707 [internal shots] tag.
Source: EHWiki</description>
<picurl>213277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7004" parentid="7403" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-02">
<name>prostate massage</name>
<description>Prostate massage is the massage or stimulation of the male prostate gland for sexual stimulation or medical purposes.</description>
<picurl>211545.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7403" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>anal fingering</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="79459" type="main character in" update="2018-06-16">
<rating votes="1">4.70</rating>
<name>Okuda-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211909.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20502" picture="201023.jpg">Natsumura Isuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79460" type="main character in" update="2016-01-14">
<rating votes="13">8.29</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Hanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>179452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42805" picture="171542.jpg">Yatsuhashi Kinako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81180" type="main character in" update="2017-08-05">
<rating votes="13">9.33</rating>
<name>Sadako (Shou)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5846" picture="210569.jpg">Oonami Konami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81181" type="main character in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="1">4.70</rating>
<name>Eguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20502" picture="201023.jpg">Natsumura Isuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84822" type="main character in" update="2018-09-11">
<rating votes="13">6.92</rating>
<name>Hasshaku-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A tall woman from a Japanese urban legend said to abduct children and makes a "po... po... po..." sound.</description>
<picture>223592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="58125" picture="172018.jpg">Uzui Yukino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84823" type="main character in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="1">4.70</rating>
<name>Suehiro Kakeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47939" picture="244981.jpg">Akai Ria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87111" type="main character in" update="2017-01-18">
<rating votes="10">6.60</rating>
<name>Mary-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28385" picture="41280.jpg">Shirayuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87112" type="main character in" update="2018-01-14">
<rating votes="1">2.42</rating>
<name>Hitsuji Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20502" picture="201023.jpg">Natsumura Isuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90813" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-16">
<name>Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211907.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="90814" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-14">
<rating votes="1">4.70</rating>
<name>Gara Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211908.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="90815" type="main character in" update="2017-08-05">
<rating votes="10">9.10</rating>
<name>Sadako (Dai)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46117" picture="223516.jpg">Manome Ruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96170" type="main character in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="1">4.70</rating>
<name>Ryouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28385" picture="41280.jpg">Shirayuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="171150" update="2016-02-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トイレのHanakoさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hanako of the Toilet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toile no Hanako-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174703" update="2016-03-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2016-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ェ呪いのビデオ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cursed Video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">E Noroi no Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179420" update="2016-12-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2017-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メリーちゃんの電話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Call from Mary-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mary-chan no Denwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179421" update="2016-09-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2016-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">八尺さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hasshaku-san</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hachishaku-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192276" update="2018-06-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">集結! エロカワ怪異</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuketsu! Erokawa Kaii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192277" update="2018-03-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ェ呪いのVR</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cursed VR</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">E Noroi no VR</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
