<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11370" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2016-09-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Re:ゼロから始める異世界生活 新編集版</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Re: Life in a Different World from Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">Re: 제로부터 시작하는 이세계 생활</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu	Shin Henshuu-ban</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">从零开始的异世界</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">リゼロ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">Re:Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Re Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">rezero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">rizero</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Re:ゼロから始める異世界生活</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Re:Zero - Starting Life in Another World</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">بدء الحياة من الصفر في عالم آخر</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">Re: 从零开始的异世界生活</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14792" type="Sequel">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu 2</anime>
<anime id="13430" type="Side Story">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu (2018)</anime>
<anime id="14435" type="Other">Isekai Quartet</anime>
<anime id="14964" type="Other">Isekai Quartet 2</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7729" approval="53" total="106">Steins;Gate</anime>
<anime id="11261" approval="38" total="84">Kono Subarashii Sekai ni Shukufuku o!</anime>
<anime id="11292" approval="36" total="70">Boku dake ga Inai Machi</anime>
<anime id="3574" approval="25" total="51">Higurashi no Naku Koro ni</anime>
<anime id="6051" approval="10" total="22">Umineko no Naku Koro ni</anime>
<anime id="10894" approval="8" total="28">Dungeon ni Deai o Motomeru no wa Machigatte Iru Darouka: Familia Myth</anime>
<anime id="9332" approval="6" total="32">Mondaiji-tachi ga Isekai kara Kurusou Desu yo?</anime>
<anime id="4151" approval="5" total="31">Toki o Kakeru Shoujo</anime>
<anime id="4940" approval="2" total="6">Kaibutsu Oujo</anime>
<anime id="11712" approval="1" total="7">Hai to Gensou no Grimgar</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="34">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="347478">this is just a bait for the B-male teenagers, starts interesting but turn to bad scripting and bad character in a couple of episodes, most people wont stop to understand that MC power has the only feature to let him not take responsibility for his own mistakes and it kills every bit of tension, just like Boku ga Inai Machi. this anime is only for people who can cope with turning off their brain to watch a loli/moe fest.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="430272">The animation tells you one thing then all of a sudden everything gets bloody. Sometimes you won`t like the main character because, let`s be honest, he is stupid most of the time. However, if you think of where he is coming from and his mental state through the entire thing you can see where he would be coming from. It is a great watch with he art style and story line.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="117590">The anime is grim and at times gory, the plot is however interesting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="778565">Re:Zero is nicer isekai anime than other isekai anime, it was  roseate and not classic like other ones I`d recommend it anime lover that loves isekai.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="255559">u could start watching this series after episode 10 (brace urself with amateur work up to episode 8)
recommended to marathon watch up to episode 10 (complete 2 arc, leaving arc 3 for rest of the show)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="423685">The pacing is a mess in this, otherwise, quite glorious flash/rollback fiesta of numerous resets. Drama is sometimes forced, sometimes right where it should be - in teh feelz. The tragedy part can be overwhelming at times, the comedy - peculiar and offbeat or oversimplistic, the dialogs - cheezy. Yet it manages to entertain, attract and hold your attention. Not bad for chaotic clusterf.ck of ideas and anime tropes. Some episodes are true masterpieces - not many but enough to maybe even warrant a re-watch. If in a mood for chaotic action-thriller with a rather dark ambiance, set in a fantasy setting - well look no further!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="558965">Recommended to watch. I can`t express it well. So much twists, sweetness, cuteness, sadness, depressions, confuses, and believe it or not, imo this series is the most realistic than other "thrown-to-other-dimension" set as the story background.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="667661">In the beginning its like every other sci-fi anime, boy meets girl in another universe and so and so. But after the first episode you want more, because it may be similar to every other sci-fi anime but it has his charm.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="491381">i was relucantly started this series. but it has a charm that pulls you in. recommended for those who likes bloody fantasy animes .</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="97929">Starts well and ends well, but the middle part stretches credulity to the maximum. A lot of anime will have a section where the MC goes into a funk and boy does this series do that. But the issue is not only does he go into a funk he loses about 15 points of IQ and that`s not to say he was very smart to begin with. He constantly misses glaringly obvious connections and repeatedly makes the same mistakes over and over, needless to say the middle part is exasperating.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="527839">Surprisingly good!  The main character starts off as carefree and self-centered, but great tragedy and despair help shape his character.  First season built up a good world, but left many plot threads hanging.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="712992">I did not expect to enjoy this series at first. Its Time-travel fantasy mystery series. I don`t particularly like how anime handle fantasy genre, so I was reluctant to give it a try.

This particular anime however is not really about the fantastical universe the protagonist is transported into. Its about a NEET finding purpose in life after being transported to completely unknown universe. its about his self discovery and his relationship with people from this universe.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="307712">As of episode 18, I have understood the essence of Rem`s presence. She is `best` girl, way better than Emilia. She always believes in Subaru no matter what and is always with him. Her love for him doesn`t stop her, even when all her bones broken and neck twisted 180 degrees, she always gives him a path and courage to give him an edge in the paths he chooses.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="466811">It took me a very long time to start watching this anime, as it`s not dubbed yet, and I prefer dubbed over subbed, since I often have difficulties keeping up with the conversations in subbed anime.
However, regardless of my difficulties to keep up at some points, I found myself growing more and more into this anime, and felt a strong need to discuss it with others.
I won`t go into too many details, as I feel the others have already summed it up fairly well already.
But I`ll add this, even if you prefer dubbed over subbed like I do, I still strongly recommend watching it, and don`t quit before 6 episodes if you start feeling tired of it, it`s after these that things really get going and it gets good.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="491503">10 PLAIN &amp; SIMPLE
The show is great coz the story dealt with how the pro is reacting/dealing into his situations. Despair. Hopelesness. Fear. Anger. Selfishness. The pro is reacting like a real human with emotions unlike other show chars who seems to have limited emotions. Putting myself into the pro`s shoes was a great ride.
Also, this show doesn`t suffer from almost all adapted anime I`ve seen which is crunching a story into very short episodes coz "MONEY" concerns. Now imagine this show crunched into 12/13 episodes. IMAGINE THE GOLDEN EP. 18 CRUNCHED TO HALF. NO, A 1/3 OF IT`S LENGTH. Brings me to tears how it would`ve been a waste

JUST WATCH IT!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="471611">Ahh my weekly dose of suffering, good times :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="547633">Been watching this weekly since it started.  Unfortunately over time I`ve learned that this was a mistake, because every episode I watch my chest aches.
I honestly don`t know what`s worse, having to see all this terrible bullshit, or having to relive it over and over again with the glimmer of hope that it might change.
What a grim series.
10/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="797979">this show is truly entertaining and i enjoyed it all. good story, good art, good OST.
Recommended 8/10</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="212957">This show is half OK and half amazing. Usually I would not recommend a show that had so many episodes I would not like to re-watch, but the other episodes were that good! If you like time-loop shows this is definitely for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="157231">This series may look like many other `parallel world` stories. But it has great mystery dramatic plot where each episode quite unpredictable and gives You new questions. Plus protagonist looks too average and realistic (maybe too kind), like it came from some `slice of life` series that makes him closer to viewer.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="307450">Episode 15. Nothing More to Say. One Time Life Event. You shouldn`t miss it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="288423">i agree
Episode 15 is  unique and masterpiece
may be best anime episode ever</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="661364">at first i thought that it`s like other " parallel universe " crap but it wasn`t . it`s definitely one of the best shows i`ve seen in a while , the Script is powerful , Characters are Amazing , Animation is Fantastic and music/voice acting is Brilliant as well . Don`t Miss it . it will rock your world .</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://re-zero-anime.jp/tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="43464" type="Original Work">Nagatsuki Tappei</name>
<name id="1555" type="Animation Work">White Fox</name>
<name id="3519" type="Character Design">Sakai Kyuuta</name>
<name id="3527" type="Series Composition">Yokotani Masahiro</name>
<name id="572" type="Direction">Watanabe Masaharu</name>
<name id="3519" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakai Kyuuta</name>
<name id="2435" type="Music">Suehiro Ken`ichirou</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch78944 [Natsuki Subaru] is an ordinary high school student who is lost in an alternate world, where he is rescued by http://anidb.net/ch78943 [a beautiful, silver-haired girl]. He stays near her to return the favour, but the destiny she is burdened with is more than Subaru can imagine. Enemies attack one by one, and both of them are killed. He then finds out he has the power to rewind death, back to the time he first came to this world. But only he remembers what has happened since.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4527">7.82</permanent>
<temporary count="4577">7.90</temporary>
<review count="6">6.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>233421.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17360</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31240</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>33142</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>33569</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/re-zero/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://re-zero-anime.jp/tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Re:Zero_−_Starting_Life_in_Another_World</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Re:ゼロから始める異世界生活</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5560</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>4114</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>353552</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19043</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rezero_official</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=IvhgOe9BY5A</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=vFfXjuVA1Jk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20141</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20142</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>20120</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07DGKL4BM</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2391" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>bishoujo</name>
<description>In Japanese, a bishoujo is any pretty female from toddlerhood to late adolescence. In the West, the word specifically refers to attractive girls generally from late childhood or early adolescence, especially those that appeal to males, and particularly to fictional characters designed in a way traditionally associated to shoujo manga. Fictional bishoujo tend to be cute, pastel-coloured teenagers; they lack the sophistication of older women, instead having detailed eye and hair design, fluttery costumes often including ribbons, and all sorts of generally sparkly fluff.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5384" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-15">
<name>put right what once went wrong</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5651" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-06-22">
<name>against destiny</name>
<description>Screw destiny and all the others who try to discourage them; they`re not going to fulfill the prophecy of world destruction because they`re the Big Bad`s descendant, or become a sacrificial magician. They`re going to become who they want to be. (source: TV Tropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5789" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-02">
<name>back to square one</name>
<description>The story returns to its starting point (or another situation) once or even multiple times. Possible causes for this might be amnesia or time travel.
This sometimes leads to the repetition of certain events (like in the "Endless Eight" episodes in Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuutsu (2009)).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="78943" type="main character in" update="2016-03-02">
<rating votes="587">8.22</rating>
<name>Emilia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78944" type="main character in" update="2017-05-03">
<rating votes="192">3.76</rating>
<name>Natsuki Subaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183639.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78945" type="main character in" update="2016-03-02">
<rating votes="86">7.51</rating>
<name>Pack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78946" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-12">
<rating votes="63">6.84</rating>
<name>Felt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78947" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-02">
<rating votes="102">7.58</rating>
<name>Beatrice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78948" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-08">
<rating votes="31">5.05</rating>
<name>Reinhard van Astrea</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78949" type="main character in" update="2017-02-01">
<rating votes="153">6.33</rating>
<name>Ram</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32020" picture="127735.jpg">Murakawa Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78950" type="main character in" update="2017-02-01">
<rating votes="522">5.01</rating>
<name>Rem</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81522" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-05">
<rating votes="28">3.11</rating>
<name>Roswaal L Mathers</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81576" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-08">
<rating votes="63">4.76</rating>
<name>Elsa Granhilte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81577" type="appears in" update="2016-04-08">
<rating votes="1">3.92</rating>
<name>Kan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81578" type="appears in" update="2016-04-08">
<rating votes="2">1.58</rating>
<name>Chin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29668" picture="239507.jpg">Muro Genki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81579" type="appears in" update="2016-04-08">
<rating votes="1">3.92</rating>
<name>Ton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28471" picture="57632.jpg">Yamamoto Itaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81580" type="appears in" update="2016-04-08">
<rating votes="5">4.99</rating>
<name>Romjii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81869" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">1.71</rating>
<name>Kadomon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81870" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">8.96</rating>
<name>Kadomon no Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36618" picture="175524.jpg">Tanaka Aimi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81871" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kadomon no Yome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17149" picture="174125.jpg">Yamamura Hibiku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81881" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">2.20</rating>
<name>Roten no Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12640" picture="226055.jpg">Souma Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82451" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="28">3.46</rating>
<name>Anastasia Hoshin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64054.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82452" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="13">3.31</rating>
<name>Aldebaran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64059.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="211227.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82453" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="69">7.04</rating>
<name>Crusch Karsten</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64050.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82454" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-01">
<rating votes="44">5.40</rating>
<name>Felix Argyle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82455" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="37">2.40</rating>
<name>Priscilla Barielle</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64057.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82456" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="27">4.75</rating>
<name>Julius Juukulius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64062.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82457" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="37">7.45</rating>
<name>Wilhelm van Astrea</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64058.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84469" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Cain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40098" picture="228293.jpg">Shinoda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84470" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Dain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84471" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="3">4.70</rating>
<name>Petra Leyte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39199" picture="242466.jpg">Kouno Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84472" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Mild</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84473" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Meili</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84474" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Meina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84475" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Lucas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42648" picture="207956.jpg">Yoshino Yuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84476" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Wakagaeri Babaa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41981" picture="170979.jpg">Izawa Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84477" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Seinendan Danchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20273" picture="175422.jpg">Kijima Ryuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84478" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="2">4.90</rating>
<name>Frederica Baumann</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84479" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Temae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="188" picture="1804.gif">Kimura Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84480" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Quark</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84481" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Kizoku no Zokuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11025" picture="43745.jpg">Tezuka Hideaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84482" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Miklotov McMahon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84483" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Marcos Gildark</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84484" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Bordeaux Zellgef</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="324" picture="223539.jpg">Saitou Jirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84485" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Rickert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190815.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84486" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="11">2.37</rating>
<name>Otto Suwen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40642" picture="62085.png">Amasaki Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84487" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="36">3.32</rating>
<name>Petelgeuse Romanee-Conti</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84488" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="15">7.28</rating>
<name>Mimi Pearlbaton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12783" picture="225340.jpg">Fujii Yukiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84489" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<name>Russell Fellow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84851" type="appears in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<name>Hetaro Pearlbaton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191390.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84852" type="appears in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="1">5.48</rating>
<name>Ricardo Welkin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84853" type="appears in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<name>Conwood Melahau</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191392.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84854" type="appears in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="5">8.19</rating>
<name>Thearesia van Astrea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33633" picture="151771.jpg">Takahashi Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84855" type="appears in" update="2016-09-17">
<name>Wilhelm (Seinenki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84856" type="appears in" update="2016-09-17">
<rating votes="1">1.36</rating>
<name>Tivey Pearlbaton</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18131" picture="223909.jpg">Shimowada Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84857" type="appears in" update="2016-09-17">
<name>Ketty</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84858" type="appears in" update="2016-09-17">
<name>Muraosa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32216" picture="223331.jpg">Sasa Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="176267" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロズワール邸の団欒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Happy Roswaal Mansion Family</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans l`intimité du manoir Roswaal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roswaal-tei no Danran</title>
<summary>After being badly wounded by Elsa, Subaru somehow survived and awoke in the mansion of Margrave Mathers, in the Kingdom of Lugunica.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702407</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176268" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="32">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼロから始まる異世界生活</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starting Life from Zero in Another World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une vie qui commence de zéro dans un autre monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zero kara Hajimaru Isekai Seikatsu</title>
<summary>Subaru attempts to buy the insignia from Felt and return it to Satella before Elsa arrives at the loot house... but Satella arrives before the negotiations are complete, and Elsa still attacks them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702405</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176269" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会の魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion with the Witch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retrouvailles avec la sorcière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai no Majo</title>
<summary>After being attacked by someone the first time, sliced open by Elsa the second time, and stabbed in the back by punks the third time, Subaru should have been dead, but found himself back where he started in the same parallel world every time. He finally realizes he`s acquired the power to go back to the time and place he started from, which he calls "Return by Death." In hopes of changing the fate awaiting Felt, Satella, Old Man Rom, and himself, Subaru takes off for the fourth time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702403</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176270" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2016-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="38">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">始まりの終わりと終わりの始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of the Beginning and the Beginning of the End</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin du commencement et le début de la fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Owari to Owari no Hajimari</title>
<summary>Natsuki Subaru is summoned to a parallel world on his way home from the convenience store. He`s entranced at first by the fantasy world suddenly stretching before his eyes, but the cute girl he believes summoned him is nowhere to be found, and soon enough he`s utterly lost. Then a gang of punks surrounds him, but he quickly learns that he doesn`t have any of the powers that he thought all people transported to a parellel world should have. Just when he`s about to be beaten senseless, a girl appears...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702401</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>709019</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176694" update="2017-10-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める異世界体験</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pre Air Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Taiken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176838" update="2016-04-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176980" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="27">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">泣いて泣き喚いて泣き止んだから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Cried, Cried My Lungs Out, and Stopped Crying</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sèche tes larmes après avoir pleuré sans répit</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naite Nakiwameite Nakiyanda kara</title>
<summary>Subaru`s first day in Roswaal`s mansion begins for the fifth time. Determined to save everyone this time, he makes it a point to keep his best smile on his face in order to earn the trust of the mansion`s staff. But although he works his hardest to make them like him, his body begins to have trouble keeping up with his heart`s intentions. Soon Emilia is unable to bear the sight of him struggling any longer and takes an unexpected action...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702415</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176981" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="33">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナツキ・スバルのリスタート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Natsuki Subaru`s Restart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour à la case départ pour Subaru Natsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuki Subaru no Restart</title>
<summary>Standing before Subaru is someone he never expected. The truth of the attacker`s identity leaves him bewildered, and he feels everything crumbling around him as he dies yet again. Then, for the fourth time, he awakes on his first day at the Roswaal mansion. This time, the night of the fourth day passes without incident, and Subaru is stunned as he greets the morning of the fifth day... but then the situation takes an unexpected turn.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702413</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176982" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="26">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鎖の音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sound of Chains</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cliquetis de la chaîne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kusari no Oto</title>
<summary>Subaru`s first day at the Roswaal mansion begins for the third time. The first time, he grew weak and died of unknown reasons in his sleep, and the second time, he was killed by an attacker. The sound of chains that he heard as he died the second time replays in his mind, waking him in a terrified, cold sweat. He has no idea what the killer is after, let alone who it is, so he makes a plan to leave the mansion on the fourth night and watch for the attack to happen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702411</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176983" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束した朝は遠く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Morning of Our Promise Is Still Distant</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au loin, le matin promis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku Shita Asa wa Tooku</title>
<summary>Subaru now lives and works in Roswaal`s mansion, working with Ram and Rem, and finally getting Emilia to agree to a date with him. But the day of their promised date never comes as Subaru keeps going back to the day he first awoke in the mansion. He`s confused at the thought that he Returned by Death despite having no memory of experiencing anything deadly, but he`s determined to repeat his previous actions up to the point of fulfilling his promise with Emilia.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702409</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177108" update="2017-07-05">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 02</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 02</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 02</title>
<summary>Felt teaches Subaru how time works in her world.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716489</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177109" update="2017-07-05">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 01</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 01</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 01</title>
<summary>Subaru learns that objects in this new world are named very similarly to the ones in his own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716487</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177318" update="2017-07-05">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 03</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 03</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 03</title>
<summary>Emilia and Puck discuss Reinhard, the Master Swordsman, and his many divine protections.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716491</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177455" update="2017-07-05">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 04</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 04</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 04</title>
<summary>After being hired at Roswaal`s mansion, Subaru has a chat with the maid sisters Ram and Rem.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716493</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177533" update="2017-07-05">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 05</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 05</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 05</title>
<summary>Roswaal and Subaru have a chat while sharing the mansion`s luxurious bath.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716495</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177613" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="30">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再来の王都</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return to the Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour à la capitale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sairai no Outo</title>
<summary>At the order of the council of elders that manages Lugunica in the king`s absence, Wilhelm and Felis visit Roswaal`s mansion as emissaries. Emilia is required in the imperial capital right away, so Subaru asks her to take him along. Emilia tells him this won`t be a pleasure trip, but a push from Rem and Roswaal ends in her agreement, so Emilia and Subaru head to the capital. Now all of the candidates to be Lugunica`s next king are gathered, and the royal selection is underway.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702423</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177614" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="37">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rem</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rem</title>
<summary>Knocked unconscious by Subaru`s attack, Rem dreams of an event in her past that she and Ram would rather forget... a sin for which Rem feels she can never be forgiven. After waking up, she tells Subaru that she`s just committed the same sin again. When the three of them are moments from being cornered by the Ulgarm pack, Subaru takes off to draw their attention so Ram and Rem can escape.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702421</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177615" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="29">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼がかったやり方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fanatical Methods Like a Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une méthode d`ogre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oni ga Katta Yarikata</title>
<summary>Subaru risked his life to save the children from a pack of Ulgarm, but he was so powerfully cursed that there could be no saving him. Even Beatrice is unable to undo the complex web of curses on him, and says he`ll grow weak and die within half a day. The only way he can survive is if the entire Ulgarm pack is defeated, but time is not on his side. Subaru is ready to give up when he learns that Rem has gone into the forest by herself...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702419</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177616" update="2018-02-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="29">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勇気の意味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Meaning of Courage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sens du courage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuki no Imi</title>
<summary>The scattered pieces of the puzzle finally come together, and Subaru realizes for certain that the shaman who cursed him is in the village at the foot of the mountains. He heads there with Ram and Rem and makes sure all the villagers touch him so that he can find out, with Beatrice`s help, who cast the curse. But the truth he finds is not what he expected, and he finds himself rushing toward the village again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702417</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177674" update="2017-07-05">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 06</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 06</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 06</title>
<summary>Emilia continues to insist on doing something to thank Subaru for saving her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716497</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177803" update="2017-07-05">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 07</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 07</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 07</title>
<summary>Subaru asks Beatrice about the library she maintains for Roswaal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716499</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177992" update="2017-04-15">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 09</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 09</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 09</title>
<summary>Subaru learns just how kind and considerate Ram can be.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716503</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177993" update="2017-04-15">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 08</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 08</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 08</title>
<summary>Subaru is still embarrassed about resting his head in Emilia`s lap, and the maid sisters aren`t about to let him forget it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716501</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178054" update="2017-04-15">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 10</title>
<summary>Subaru tells Ram about the promises he made to Rem while they track the mabeasts through the forest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716505</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178105" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="28">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">豚の欲望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greed of a Pig</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les désirs d`un porc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Buta no Yokubou</title>
<summary>Subaru awakens in front of the fruit stand in Lugunica`s capital yet again. Realizing that he`s in a hopeless situation, he desperately seeks help from Crusch, Priscilla, and Anastasia, but his limited time continues to tick away...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702431</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178106" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="54">8.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂気の外側</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Outside of Madness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au bord de la folie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouki no Sotogawa</title>
<summary>Upon returning to Roswaal`s mansion, Subaru is greeted by an unbelievable sight and wails that this was not what he wanted to happen. Stricken with despair, everything before Subaru starts to go white as, finally, he hears a voice: "You were too late."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702429</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178107" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="29">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望という病</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sickness Called Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La maladie du désespoir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou to Iu Yamai</title>
<summary>"I just wanted to protect her. That feeling wasn`t a lie. Where did I go wrong?" Rejected by the one who meant more to him than anything, Subaru is still unable to recognize that he may have done something irreversible. He then finds out that some disturbing movement has been detected within Roswaal`s domain, where Emilia and the others are. He`s certain that he can save them somehow, so in spite of Rem and Crusch`s opposition, Subaru makes his way back to Emilia...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702427</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178108" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="32">4.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自称騎士ナツキ・スバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Self-Proclaimed Knight Natsuki Subaru</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Subaru Natsuki, chevalier autoproclamé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jishou Kishi Natsuki Subaru</title>
<summary>As Emilia joins Priscilla, Crusch, and Anastasia in a meeting of the royal selection participants, Reinhard enters the hall with Felt. According to a new prophecy seen on the Dragon Stone, there are five priestesses with the potential to be the kingdom`s next ruler. Reinhard announces that Felt is the fifth priestess, meaning it`s time to formally begin the royal selection, but Felt refuses to have any part in it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702425</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178115" update="2017-04-15">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ゼロから始める休憩時間[ブレイクタイム] - 11</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Zero - Starting Break Time from Zero - 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Break Time - 11</title>
<summary>Subaru and Emilia reunite after the mabeasts are defeated and his curses erased.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716507</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178217" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち1 再来の学校</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 1 - Return to School</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 1 - Sairai no Gakkou</title>
<summary>Subaru awakens to find himself in a classroom... with Emilia as the homeroom teacher?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717629</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178555" update="2018-02-05">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178556" update="2016-07-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178557" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち2 自称先生, ベアトリス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 2 - Beatrice, Self-Proclaimed Teacher</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 2 - Jishou Sensei, Beatrice</title>
<summary>Subaru meets another teacher at the mysterious school he`s awakened in...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717631</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178625" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち3 ご主人様と, そのメイドたち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 3 - The Master and His Maids</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 3 - Goshujin-sama to, Sono Maid-tachi</title>
<summary>Subaru finds himself in a maid café with two very familiar maids serving him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717685</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178700" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴィルヘルム・ヴァン・アストレア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wilhelm van Astrea</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Wilhelm van Astrea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wilhelm van Astrea</title>
<summary>Subaru has devoted everything he had, and done all he could do. His passion has captured Crusch`s heart, as well as Anastasia`s cooperation, and they all enter into the battle against the White Whale together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702439</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178701" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="30">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白鯨攻略戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle Against the White Whale</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chasse à la baleine blanche</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakugei Kouryakusen</title>
<summary>To save Emilia, Subaru approaches Crusch to negotiate the formation of an alliance. His terms are a bit difficult for Crusch to believe, but she can see that Subaru isn`t lying.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702437</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178702" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="39">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼロから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De zéro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zero kara</title>
<summary>Subaru laments that he could not do anything or save anyone, and has no options left. Exhausted, he suddenly takes off running at full speed as if he`s made a decision...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702435</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178703" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="30">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">醜態の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disgrace in the Extreme</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Couvert de honte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuutai no Hate ni</title>
<summary>A mysterious figure appears before Subaru and his traveling companions. As the looming beast attacks with a deafening bellow amidst the darkness and fog, Rem determines that it will be too difficult to escape...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702433</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178827" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち4 そのメニューは――</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 4 - That Menu Item Is...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 4 - Sono Menu wa...</title>
<summary>Subaru is in yet another unique café whose theme is a mystery, though the staff is familiar...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717633</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179110" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち5 天然</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 5 - Ditz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 5 - Tennen</title>
<summary>Subaru runs into Felt and Emilia in an arcade, where Felt is having some kind of competition with Reinhard.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717635</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179233" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち6 豚でない欲望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 6 - Greed That Isn`t a Pig`s</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 6 - Buta de Nai Yokubou</title>
<summary>Felt`s arcade competition with Reinhard continues, with a little help from an unexpected visitor...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717871</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179377" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち7 ゼロから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 7 - From Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 7 - Zero kara</title>
<summary>Subaru visits a certain doujinshi expo and finds Rem sitting at a booth, selling a book she wrote.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717873</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179427" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自称騎士と最優の騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Self-Proclaimed Knight and the Greatest Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chevalier autoproclamé et le chevalier modèle</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">O Cavaleiro Autoproclamado e o Cavaleiro da Piedade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jijou Kishi to Saiyuu no Kishi</title>
<summary>Emilia tried to warn the villagers of Arlam that danger was coming and they should evacuate, but was not well-received. As she`s pondering what more she can do, Wilhelm arrives at the mansion with a message...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702447</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179428" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪辣なる怠惰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nefarious Sloth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Diabolique paresse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuratsunaru Taida</title>
<summary>Subaru and his companions head toward Roswaal`s mansion to evacuate Emilia and all the others there, stopping at the nearby village on the way and beginning to evacuate its residents as well. However, the situation takes a turn that nobody expected...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702445</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179429" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怠惰一閃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Flash of Sloth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Éclair de paresse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taida Issen</title>
<summary>The half of the mercenary army that had been blocking the road during the White Whale subjugation returns to join the main force. Subaru then leads the way into the forest of the Mathers domain, hoping to find and destroy the Witch`s Cult before they can learn of the subjugating army`s movements.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702443</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179430" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="27">9.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望に抗う賭け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Wager That Defies Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un pari contre le désespoir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou ni Aragau Kake</title>
<summary>Subaru and Rem lose all words at the sight unfolding above them. Just when it seemed they would soon have the White Whale cornered, despite the sacrifices it took to reach that point, the battle takes a turn that no one expected.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702441</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179617" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち8 決戦当日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 8 - The Day of the Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 8 - Kessen Toujitsu</title>
<summary>Subaru continues to explore the doujinshi expo and bumps into two other unexpected attendees, Crusch and Priscilla.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717875</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179707" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ただそれだけの物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s All This Story Is About</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une simple histoire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tada Sore dake no Monogatari</title>
<summary>Subaru and Julius face off against Betelgeuse`s Unseen Hand. However, as one Unseen Hand after another is launched their way, the two heroes find themselves completely on the defensive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702449</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179793" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち9 スイカ攻略戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 9 - Conquering the Watermelon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 9 - Suika Kouryakusen</title>
<summary>Subaru finds himself on the beach, greeted by the sight of Crusch and Rem in swimsuits. Is this some kind of reward?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717877</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179909" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち10 煩悩に抗うだけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 10 - Just Resisting Desires of the Flesh</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 10 - Bonnou ni Aragau dake</title>
<summary>Subaru awakens on the beach again... but this time he`s buried in the sand. Who could have done this?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717879</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180009" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち11 アレとアレと(以下略)の精算</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 11 - That and That and (Omitted) at Checkout</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 11 - Are to Are to (Ikaryaku) no Seisan</title>
<summary>Subaru visits a convenience store to buy a drink, but its owner is a very shrewd business woman...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717881</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180081" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち12 ——買え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 12 - Buy It</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 12 - --Kae</title>
<summary>Subaru returns to the convenience store... and this time Emilia stands behind the counter! It`s the situation he`s been waiting for!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717883</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180211" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち13 獅子王のみた本</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 13 - The Book the Lion King Saw</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 13 - Shishi-ou no Mita Hon</title>
<summary>Subaru visits a bookstore to buy a copy of a favorite book, but the employee at the register doesn`t trust his motives...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717885</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180463" update="2018-02-05">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180471" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Re:ぷち Re:プチから始める異世界生活 ぷち14 ただそれだけの宣伝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Re:Petit - Re: Starting Life in Another World from Petit - Petit 14 - That`s All This Promotion Is About</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Re: Petit - Re: Petit kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu - Petit 14 - Tada Sore dake no Senden</title>
<summary>Subaru and Emilia wait at the bookstore for the rest of the gang`s arrival to take advantage of an exciting new release!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>717887</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-shorts</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194273" update="2018-02-05">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-05-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195832" update="2018-02-06">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">第2弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 2 Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195833" update="2018-02-06">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225905" update="2020-02-26">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2020-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">始まりの終わりと終わりの始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: The End of the Beginning and the Beginning of the End</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Owari to Owari no Hajimari</title>
<summary>Natsuki Subaru is summoned to a parallel world on his way home from the convenience store. He`s entranced at first by the fantasy world suddenly stretching before his eyes, but the cute girl he believes summoned him is nowhere to be found, and soon enough he`s utterly lost. Then a gang of punks surrounds him, but he quickly learns that he doesn`t have any of the powers that he thought all people transported to a parellel world should have. Just when he`s about to be beaten senseless, a girl appears...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792278</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225906" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2020-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会の魔女 / ゼロから始まる異世界生活</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: Reunion with the Witch / Starting Life from Zero in Another World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai no Majo / Zero kara Hajimaru Isekai Seikatsu</title>
<summary>After being attacked by someone the first time, sliced open by Elsa the second time, and stabbed in the back by punks the third time, Subaru should have been dead, but found himself back where he started in the same parallel world every time. He finally realizes he`s acquired the power to go back to the time and place he started from, which he calls "Return by Death." In hopes of changing the fate awaiting Felt, Satella, Old Man Rom, and himself, Subaru takes off for the fourth time.
Subaru attempts to buy the insignia from Felt and return it to Satella before Elsa arrives at the loot house... but Satella arrives before the negotiations are complete, and Elsa still attacks them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792279</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225907" update="2020-03-30">
<epno type="6">O3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2020-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロズワール邸の団欒 / 約束した朝は遠く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: The Happy Roswaal Mansion Family / The Morning of Our Promise Is Still Distant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roswaal-tei no Danran / Yakusoku Shita Asa wa Tooku</title>
<summary>"After being badly wounded by Elsa, Subaru somehow survived and awoke in the mansion of Margrave Mathers, in the Kingdom of Lugunica.
Subaru now lives and works in Roswaal`s mansion, working with Ram and Rem, and finally getting Emilia to agree to a date with him. But the day of their promised date never comes as Subaru keeps going back to the day he first awoke in the mansion. He`s confused at the thought that he Returned by Death despite having no memory of experiencing anything deadly, but he`s determined to repeat his previous actions up to the point of fulfilling his promise with Emilia."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792280</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226245" update="2020-03-30">
<epno type="6">O4</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2020-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鎖の音 / ナツキ・スバルのリスタート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: The Sound of Chains / Natsuki Subaru`s Restart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kusari no Oto / Natsuki Subaru no Restart</title>
<summary>"Subaru`s first day at the Roswaal mansion begins for the third time. The first time, he grew weak and died of unknown reasons in his sleep, and the second time, he was killed by an attacker. The sound of chains that he heard as he died the second time replays in his mind, waking him in a terrified, cold sweat. He has no idea what the killer is after, let alone who it is, so he makes a plan to leave the mansion on the fourth night and watch for the attack to happen.
Standing before Subaru is someone he never expected. The truth of the attacker`s identity leaves him bewildered, and he feels everything crumbling around him as he dies yet again. Then, for the fourth time, he awakes on his first day at the Roswaal mansion. This time, the night of the fourth day passes without incident, and Subaru is stunned as he greets the morning of the fifth day... but then the situation takes an unexpected turn."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792281</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226310" update="2020-01-30">
<epno type="6">O5</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2020-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">泣いて泣き喚いて泣き止んだから / 勇気の意味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: I Cried, Cried My Lungs Out, and Stopped Crying / The Meaning of Courage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Naite Nakiwameite Nakiyanda kara / Yuuki no Imi</title>
<summary>Subaru`s first day in Roswaal`s mansion begins for the fifth time. Determined to save everyone this time, he makes it a point to keep his best smile on his face in order to earn the trust of the mansion`s staff. But although he works his hardest to make them like him, his body begins to have trouble keeping up with his heart`s intentions. Soon Emilia is unable to bear the sight of him struggling any longer and takes an unexpected action...  The scattered pieces of the puzzle finally come together, and Subaru realizes for certain that the shaman who cursed him is in the village at the foot of the mountains. He heads there with Ram and Rem and makes sure all the villagers touch him so that he can find out, with Beatrice`s help, who cast the curse. But the truth he finds is not what he expected, and he finds himself rushing toward the village again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792282</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226311" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="6">O6</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2020-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼がかったやり方 / レム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: Demonically Inspired Methods / Rem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oni ga Katta Yarikata / Rem</title>
<summary>Subaru risked his life to save the children from a pack of Ulgarm, but he was so powerfully cursed that there could be no saving him. Even Beatrice is unable to undo the complex web of curses on him, and says he`ll grow weak and die within half a day. The only way he can survive is if the entire Ulgarm pack is defeated, but time is not on his side. Subaru is ready to give up when he learns that Rem has gone into the forest by herself...  Knocked unconscious by Subaru`s attack, Rem dreams of an event in her past that she and Ram would rather forget... a sin for which Rem feels she can never be forgiven. After waking up, she tells Subaru that she`s just committed the same sin again. When the three of them are moments from being cornered by the Ulgarm pack, Subaru takes off to draw their attention so Ram and Rem can escape.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792283</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226312" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="6">O7</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2020-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再来の王都 / 自称騎士ナツキ・スバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: Return to the Capital / Self-Proclaimed Knight Natsuki Subaru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sairai no Outo / Jishou Kishi Natsuki Subaru</title>
<summary>At the order of the council of elders that manages Lugunica in the king`s absence, Wilhelm and Felis visit Roswaal`s mansion as emissaries. Emilia is required in the imperial capital right away, so Subaru asks her to take him along. Emilia tells him this won`t be a pleasure trip, but a push from Rem and Roswaal ends in her agreement, so Emilia and Subaru head to the capital. Now all of the candidates to be Lugunica`s next king are gathered, and the royal selection is underway.
As Emilia joins Priscilla, Crusch, and Anastasia in a meeting of the royal selection participants, Reinhard enters the hall with Felt. According to a new prophecy seen on the Dragon Stone, there are five priestesses with the potential to be the kingdom`s next ruler. Reinhard announces that Felt is the fifth priestess, meaning it`s time to formally begin the royal selection, but Felt refuses to have any part in it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793677</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226313" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="6">O8</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2020-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望という病 / 狂気の外側</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: The Sickness Called Despair / The Outside of Madness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou to Iu Yamai / Kyouki no Sotogawa</title>
<summary>I just wanted to protect her. That feeling wasn`t a lie. Where did I go wrong?" Rejected by the one who meant more to him than anything, Subaru is still unable to recognize that he may have done something irreversible. He then finds out that some disturbing movement has been detected within Roswaal`s domain, where Emilia and the others are. He`s certain that he can save them somehow, so in spite of Rem and Crusch`s opposition, Subaru makes his way back to Emilia... Upon returning to Roswaal`s mansion, Subaru is greeted by an unbelievable sight and wails that this was not what he wanted to happen. Stricken with despair, everything before Subaru starts to go white as, finally, he hears a voice: "You were too late."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793678</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226314" update="2020-03-04">
<epno type="6">O9</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2020-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">豚の欲望 / 醜態の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: A Pig`s Greed / Disgrace in the Extreme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Buta no Yokubou / Shuutai no Hate ni</title>
<summary>Subaru awakens in front of the fruit stand in Lugunica`s capital yet again. Realizing that he`s in a hopeless situation, he desperately seeks help from Crusch, Priscilla, and Anastasia, but his limited time continues to tick away...  A mysterious figure appears before Subaru and his traveling companions. As the looming beast attacks with a deafening bellow amidst the darkness and fog, Rem determines that it will be too difficult to escape...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793679</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226315" update="2020-03-13">
<epno type="6">O10</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2020-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゼロから / 白鯨攻略戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: From Zero / Battle Against the White Whale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zero kara / Hakugei Kouryakusen</title>
<summary>Subaru laments that he could not do anything or save anyone, and has no options left. Exhausted, he suddenly takes off running at full speed as if he`s made a decision... To save Emilia, Subaru approaches Crusch to negotiate the formation of an alliance. His terms are a bit difficult for Crusch to believe, but she can see that Subaru isn`t lying.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793680</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226316" update="2020-03-18">
<epno type="6">O11</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2020-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴィルヘルム・ヴァン・アストレア / 絶望に抗う賭け</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: Wilhelm van Astrea / A Wager That Defies Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wilhelm van Astrea / Zetsubou ni Aragau Kake</title>
<summary>Subaru has devoted everything he had, and done all he could do. His passion has captured Crusch`s heart, as well as Anastasia`s cooperation, and they all enter into the battle against the White Whale together. Subaru and Rem lose all words at the sight unfolding above them. Just when it seemed they would soon have the White Whale cornered, despite the sacrifices it took to reach that point, the battle takes a turn that no one expected.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793681</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226317" update="2020-03-25">
<epno type="6">O12</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2020-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怠惰一閃 /  悪辣なる怠惰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: A Flash of Sloth / Nefarious Sloth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taida Issen / Akuratsunaru Taida</title>
<summary>The half of the mercenary army that had been blocking the road during the White Whale subjugation returns to join the main force. Subaru then leads the way into the forest of the Mathers domain, hoping to find and destroy the Witch`s Cult before they can learn of the subjugating army`s movements. 
Subaru and his companions head toward Roswaal`s mansion to evacuate Emilia and all the others there, stopping at the nearby village on the way and beginning to evacuate its residents as well. However, the situation takes a turn that nobody expected...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793682</identifier>
<identifier>rezero-starting-life-in-another-world-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226318" update="2020-02-18">
<epno type="6">O13</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2020-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Director`s Cut: Episode 13</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
