<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11376" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-23</startdate>
<enddate>2016-04-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Zutto Mae kara Suki Deshita. Kokuhaku Jikkouiinkai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">I Want to Let You Know That I Love You.</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ずっと前から好きでした. ~告白実行委員会~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">I`ve Always Liked You: Confess Your Love Committee</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12041" type="Sequel">Suki ni Naru Sono Shunkan o. Kokuhaku Jikkouiinkai</anime>
<anime id="13038" type="Sequel">Itsudatte Bokura no Koi wa 10 Centi Datta.</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.honeyworks-movie.jp/1st/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6242" type="Character Design">Fujii Maki</name>
<name id="38009" type="Original Work">HoneyWorks</name>
<name id="6445" type="Direction">Yanagisawa Tetsuya</name>
<name id="38009" type="Music">HoneyWorks</name>
<name id="6242" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujii Maki</name>
</creators>
<description>This is the last time I`m going to practice...
http://anidb.net/ch76335 [Enomoto Natsuki], a third-year student at Sakuragaoka High School, has feelings of unrequited love for her childhood friend, http://anidb.net/ch76336 [Setoguchi Yuu]. Unable to be true to her own feelings, Natsuki tells Yuu that she is merely using him as a stand-in to practice confessing her love to. As Natsuki continues to pretend not having any feelings for Yuu, her classmate http://anidb.net/ch78251 [Ayase Koyuki] asks her out on a date. Will Natsuki ever be able to stop practicing and actually confess her love to Yuu?
Source: Aniplex USA</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="542">5.20</permanent>
<temporary count="542">6.58</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>184229.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17342</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31245</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>36305</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.honeyworks-movie.jp/1st/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.aniplexusa.com/honeyworks/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zutto_Mae_Kara_Suki_Deshita</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>告白実行委員会〜恋愛シリーズ〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354767</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18864</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ive-always-liked-you</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="76332" type="main character in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="8">6.29</rating>
<name>Aida Miou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76333" type="main character in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="10">5.44</rating>
<name>Hayasaka Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76334" type="main character in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="4">3.99</rating>
<name>Mochizuki Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76335" type="main character in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="15">7.04</rating>
<name>Enomoto Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76336" type="main character in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="5">3.89</rating>
<name>Setoguchi Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="76337" type="main character in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="5">4.97</rating>
<name>Serizawa Haruki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="191" picture="17006.jpg">Suzumura Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78247" type="appears in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Narumi Sena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78248" type="appears in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="2">7.24</rating>
<name>Akechi Saki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78249" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="1">7.36</rating>
<name>Enomoto Kotarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78250" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="4">6.01</rating>
<name>Setoguchi Hina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37985" picture="175206.jpg">Asakura Momo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78251" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="3">2.37</rating>
<name>Ayase Koyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="586" picture="171556.jpg">Yonaga Tsubasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82990" type="appears in" update="2016-10-16">
<name>Hamanaka Midori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38008" picture="139434.jpg">Gero</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="173240" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>2016-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Will Natsuki be able to confess her love to her long-time crush, Yu?  From HoneyWorks songs to movie, the long-awaited romantic comedy is here!  Follow three potential couples as tensions between them rise.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721425</identifier>
<identifier>ive-always-liked-you</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181668" update="2016-11-05">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">HoneyWorksヤマコ描き下ろしミュージックムービー 「日曜日の秘密」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">HoneyWorks Music Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">HoneyWorks Yamako Kaki Oroshi Music Movie: Nichiyoubi no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181669" update="2016-11-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメピクチャードラマ 「金曜日のおはよう」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anime Picture Drama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime Picture Drama: Kinyoubi no Ohayou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
