<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11466" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-10</startdate>
<enddate>2016-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tonkatsu DJ Agetarou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Tonkatsu DJ Age-Taro</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">とんかつDJアゲ太郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tonkatsu DJ Agetaro</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">炸猪排DJ扬太郎</title>
</titles>
<url>http://tonkatsudj.tokyo/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1423" type="Direction">Daichi Akitarou</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="49643" type="Music">Fujiwara Daisuke</name>
<name id="49644" type="Original Work">Koyama Yuujirou</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch80389 [Katsumata Agetarou] works at his family`s tonkatsu restaurant in Shibuya, but he doesn`t find his work exciting. One day, he takes a delivery to the staff of a night club, and the worker lets him in to enjoy the club for a while. Agetarou finds that he loves the club, with its relaxed people and beautiful girls, all enjoying the music supplied by the DJ. He continues going to the club, until http://anidb.net/ch80387 [DJ Big Master Fly], an American guest DJ, puts on a show one night. Inspired by Big Master Fly, Agetarou realizes that the groove of being a DJ is very similar to the one of being a tonkatsu chef; thus, he becomes determined to master both disciplines, though the one he is truly most excited about is becoming a DJ!
Source: MangaHelpers</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="195">5.74</permanent>
<temporary count="196">6.26</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>184724.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17798</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31370</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tonkatsudj.tokyo/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>とんかつDJアゲ太郎</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4131</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>353682</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19099</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="80386" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-02">
<name>DJ Oily</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80387" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-02">
<name>DJ Big Master Fly</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="173" picture="150067.jpg">Chafuurin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80388" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-02">
<name>Katsumata Agesaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80389" type="main character in" update="2016-03-02">
<name>Katsumata Agetarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80390" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-02">
<name>Oshibori Shuugo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80391" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-02">
<name>Hattori Sonoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80392" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-02">
<name>Mizokuro Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="176443" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い込んだらオイリーハウス! 1000本カットin!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoikondara Oily House! 1000-pon Cut In!</title>
<summary>It`s time for Agetarou`s first DJ session! But can he master Scratchin` and Poppin`, the final secrets of the DJ`s art?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712247</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176444" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お前も見とくか, リアルってやつを</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omae mo Mitoku ka, Rival-tte Yatsu o</title>
<summary>Agetarou makes a weird deal with DJ Oily to learn the secrets of the Quick Mix.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712245</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176445" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">若者よ レコードをdigれ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakamono yo Record o Dig re!</title>
<summary>Agetarou learns the sacred art of diggin` for records at his local shop, gathers up some equipment and hosts his first party.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712243</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176446" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">昼も夜もアゲてやる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiru mo Yoru mo Agete Yaru!</title>
<summary>Agetarou would rather go clubbing than work at his family`s tonkatsu restaurant. But his tonkatsu-making skills might be the key to making him the greatest DJ of all time!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712241</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177264" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">EDMの貴公子降臨!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">EDM no Kikoushi Kourin!</title>
<summary>Agetarou learns about EDM when a Korean DJ heats up one cold dance floor. When a whole crowd wants yakiniku, what`s a tonkatsu DJ to do?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712255</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177265" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">藤井頼太</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fujii Raita</title>
<summary>Japan`s coolest freelance writer is moved by Agetarou`s funkiness. Will his words inspire the young man to lead the new generation of DJ talent?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712253</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177266" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Chill Out</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chill Out</title>
<summary>Agetarou`s next lesson opens his eyes to the world of chillin`. But his quest for the ideal chill might spell the end to his DJ career!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712251</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177267" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">豚々[トントン]拍子で初DJ...!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonton Hyoushi de Hatsu DJ...!?</title>
<summary>Agetarou`s first real audience is hungry for both tonkatsu and beats. Can he sail through smoothly, or will he fall prey to the DJ demons?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712249</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177705" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱くとけろ!! ラードシティ!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atsuku Tokero!! Lard City!!!</title>
<summary>DJ Oily`s Lard City event is ready to heat up! But will the biggest snow in a century force the guests to cancel and leave the party cold?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712263</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177706" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラードシティ(前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lard City (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>Despondent over his mentor`s lack of popularity, Agetarou plots a way to throw Oily into the DJ spotlight!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712261</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177707" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イルでイケズなIKENOSUKE!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iru de Ikezu na Ikenosuke!!!</title>
<summary>The "Newcomer Killer" is out to kill his Agetarou`s career! Lured from the safety of his home turf in Shibuya, can he handle Ikebukuro`s hip-hop heat?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712259</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177708" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2016-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマス苑子と正月AMAKALA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas Sonoko to Shougatsu Amakala</title>
<summary>Agetarou gets some sweet and spicy inspiration from a pair of cute girl DJs... but his own flavor mix still has a long way to go!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712257</identifier>
<identifier>tonkatsu-dj-agetaro</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
