<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11467" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-08-06</startdate>
<enddate>2016-08-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Rudolf to Ippaiattena</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rudolf the Black Cat</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ルドルフとイッパイアッテナ</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Rudolf der schwarze Kater</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Rudolfo, O Gatinho Preto</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5801" approval="1" total="1">Chii`s Sweet Home</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.rudolf-ippaiattena.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="32346" type="Work">OLM Digital</name>
<name id="727" type="Work">OLM</name>
<name id="41513" type="Work">Sprite Animation Studios</name>
<name id="4235" type="Direction">Yuyama Kunihiko</name>
<name id="41510" type="Direction">Sakakibara Motonori</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="13">6.18</permanent>
<temporary count="13">6.19</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>175838.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19417</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31373</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.rudolf-ippaiattena.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rudolf_the_Black_Cat</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ルドルフとイッパイアッテナ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>353665</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1846" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>kodomo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word kodomo refers to a children`s audience roughly for the ages 12 and younger. In Japanese, the word means simply "child", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3968" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>animal protagonist</name>
<description>The anime revolves around an animal, usually only communicating with typical onomatopoeia. The animal mostly lives in a human family and has adventures on a regular base. This can be the discovery of a new room, or being lost by having taken a wrong turn in the outside world.
Typical example: http://anidb.net/a5801 [Chii`s Sweet Home].
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t4259 [animal world], where the whole world is composed of animals.</description>
<picurl>10255.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="79024" type="main character in" update="2015-12-22">
<name>Ippaiattena</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44331" picture="10334.jpeg">Suzuki Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79025" type="main character in" update="2015-12-22">
<name>Rudolf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40419" picture="158221.jpg">Inoue Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108693" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-14">
<name>Butchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20423" picture="53731.jpg">Yashima Norito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108694" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-14">
<name>Devil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36066" picture="220265.jpg">Furuta Arata</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108695" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-14">
<name>Misha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="171128" update="2016-08-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2016-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
