<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11478" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2008-04-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mononoke Dance</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">電気グルーヴ モノノケダンス</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Denki Groove: Mononoke Dance</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">モノノケダンス</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5614" type="Other">Hakaba Kitarou</anime>
</relatedanime>
<description>An animated music video for Denki Groove`s song "Mononoke Dance".</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="70">3.58</permanent>
<temporary count="71">4.67</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>176019.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10584</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>モノノケダンス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>puppetmation</name>
<description>A puppet is an inanimate object or representational figure animated or manipulated by a puppeteer. It is usually (but by no means always) a depiction of a human character, and is used in puppetry, a play or a presentation that is a very ancient form of theatre. The puppet undergoes a process of transformation through being animated, and is normally manipulated by at least one puppeteer.
There are many different varieties of puppets, and they are made of a wide range of materials, depending on their form and intended use. They can be extremely complex or very simple in their construction. They may even be found objects. As Oscar Wilde wrote, "There are many advantages in puppets. They never argue. They have no crude views about art. They have no private lives".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="170480" update="2015-08-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2008-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
