<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11489" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-11-26</startdate>
<enddate>2016-11-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban KanColle</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">劇場版 艦隊これくしょん</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版 艦これ</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">극장판 칸코레</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10161" type="Prequel">Kantai Collection: KanColle</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://kancolle-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1789" type="Animation Work">Diomedea</name>
<name id="19801" type="Character Design">Ide Naomi</name>
<name id="19898" type="Character Design">Matsumoto Mayuko</name>
<name id="3422" type="Direction">Kusakawa Keizou</name>
<name id="46673" type="Original Plan">Tanaka Kensuke</name>
<name id="7791" type="Character Design">Kohara Makoto</name>
<name id="46671" type="Original Work">DMM.com</name>
<name id="19898" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsumoto Mayuko</name>
<name id="7791" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kohara Makoto</name>
<name id="19801" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ide Naomi</name>
<name id="31217" type="Music">Kameoka Natsumi</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="243">5.14</permanent>
<temporary count="244">6.66</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>225538.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18245</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31418</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kancolle-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kadokawa-pictures.jp/official/gekijoban_kancolle/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4752</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355321</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3635" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-01">
<name>sea battles</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="65836" type="main character in" update="2014-03-22">
<rating votes="29">5.20</rating>
<name>Fubuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65837" type="main character in" update="2014-03-22">
<rating votes="31">7.36</rating>
<name>Akagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65838" type="main character in" update="2014-03-22">
<rating votes="37">7.90</rating>
<name>Kaga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69133" type="appears in" update="2014-08-03">
<rating votes="26">6.54</rating>
<name>Shimakaze</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159045.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69134" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-03">
<rating votes="52">9.20</rating>
<name>Kongou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69135" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-03">
<rating votes="38">8.91</rating>
<name>Yamato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69479" type="main character in" update="2014-08-15">
<rating votes="21">4.90</rating>
<name>Mutsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="129542.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69481" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-15">
<rating votes="32">8.89</rating>
<name>Nagato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69753" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-01">
<rating votes="24">6.31</rating>
<name>Sendai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69754" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-01">
<rating votes="17">6.86</rating>
<name>Jintsuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69755" type="appears in" update="2014-09-01">
<rating votes="21">4.92</rating>
<name>Naka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160297.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69946" type="appears in" update="2014-09-13">
<rating votes="19">6.88</rating>
<name>Akatsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160823.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69947" type="appears in" update="2014-09-13">
<rating votes="24">6.97</rating>
<name>Hibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160824.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69948" type="appears in" update="2014-09-13">
<rating votes="17">6.59</rating>
<name>Ikazuchi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160825.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69949" type="appears in" update="2014-09-13">
<rating votes="19">6.75</rating>
<name>Inazuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160826.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="69950" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-13">
<rating votes="26">7.69</rating>
<name>Mutsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70243" type="appears in" update="2014-09-25">
<rating votes="21">8.07</rating>
<name>Atago</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161651.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="70955" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-27">
<rating votes="21">5.66</rating>
<name>Kitakami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70956" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-27">
<rating votes="26">4.09</rating>
<name>Ooi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70957" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-27">
<rating votes="15">7.79</rating>
<name>Ooyodo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70958" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-10-27">
<rating votes="19">7.00</rating>
<name>Hiei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72409" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-29">
<rating votes="24">6.99</rating>
<name>Zuikaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72596" type="main character in" update="2015-02-05">
<rating votes="14">5.38</rating>
<name>Kisaragi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="129542.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72598" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-05">
<rating votes="19">8.09</rating>
<name>Haruna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72600" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-05">
<rating votes="18">7.66</rating>
<name>Shoukaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72601" type="appears in" update="2015-02-05">
<rating votes="13">6.28</rating>
<name>Mamiya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72602" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-05">
<rating votes="15">7.98</rating>
<name>Kirishima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="72788" type="appears in" update="2015-02-05">
<rating votes="10">7.38</rating>
<name>Takao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>168428.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="73684" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-06">
<rating votes="14">5.86</rating>
<name>Souryuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73685" type="main character in" update="2015-03-06">
<rating votes="23">7.33</rating>
<name>Yuudachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>169738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41943" picture="166787.jpg">Tanibe Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74107" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-27">
<rating votes="11">4.89</rating>
<name>Hiryuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>170850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91382" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="3">5.69</rating>
<name>Aoba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aoba is 6th Division`s Heavy Cruiser.</description>
<picture>207054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91383" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="3">5.69</rating>
<name>Kako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kako is 6th Division`s Heavy Cruiser.</description>
<picture>207055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91384" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="3">5.69</rating>
<name>Furutaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Furutaka is 6th Division`s Heavy Cruiser.</description>
<picture>207056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91385" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="3">5.69</rating>
<name>Kinugasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinugasa is 6th Division`s Heavy Cruiser.</description>
<picture>207057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="423" picture="37799.jpg">Nakajima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91386" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="3">5.69</rating>
<name>Choukai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Choukai is 8th Fleet`s Flagship Heavy Cruiser.</description>
<picture>207058.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91398" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Kaga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaga, as an Abyssal Vessel.
The night before the battle of Ironbottom Sound, http://anidb.net/ch65838 [Kaga] revealed that she was sunk once and became Abyssal Vessel shortly after that. Her memories of the time when she was Abyssal Vessel still remained even after she was sunk for the second time, but as a Abyssal Vessel instead, just to be recreated into Fleet Girl again.</description>
<picture>207102.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91399" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Kisaragi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kisaragi, as an Abyssal Vessel.</description>
<picture>207103.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="129542.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91400" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="3">5.69</rating>
<name>Ryuujou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="129542.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91401" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="3">5.69</rating>
<name>Tatsuta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91402" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="4">4.78</rating>
<name>Tokitsukaze</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91403" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="3">5.69</rating>
<name>Amatsukaze</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="178043" update="2016-11-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2016-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
