<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11529" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-07-23</startdate>
<enddate>2016-07-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">One Piece Film: Gold</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">One Piece Movie 13</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ONE PIECE FILM GOLD</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">One Piece Film: Gold</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="69" type="Parent Story">One Piece</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://one-piece.com/movie/film/13</url>
<creators>
<name id="4013" type="Original Work">Oda Eiichirou</name>
<name id="3516" type="Character Design">Satou Masayuki</name>
<name id="27421" type="Direction">Miyamoto Hiroaki</name>
<name id="3516" type="Chief Animation Direction">Satou Masayuki</name>
<name id="27786" type="Music">Hayashi Yuuki</name>
<name id="1834" type="Work">Toei Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>Set in Grantesoro, an independent country chartered by the World Government, home of the world`s greatest entertainment city where well-known pirates, Marines, and millionaires gather in an "absolute sanctuary" that even the World Government can`t touch.
There, http://anidb.net/ch474 [Luffy] and the others meet the ruler of the country, the golden emperor http://anidb.net/ch83090 [Gild Tesoro] who easily wins pirates, the Marines, and even the World Government over to his side with money. He is about to take action to satisfy his bottomless ambition which may result in major changes in power relationships in the New World.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="414">6.84</permanent>
<temporary count="418">7.35</temporary>
<review count="2">6.41</review>
</ratings>
<picture>216847.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36240</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>36241</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>31490</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>36242</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>33606</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://one-piece.com/movie/film/13</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.onepiece-film2016.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>One_Piece_Film:_Gold</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ONE_PIECE_FILM_GOLD</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>353896</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19252</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20198</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="474" type="main character in" update="2019-03-01">
<rating votes="4175">8.53</rating>
<name>Monkey D. Luffy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Monkey D. Luffy is a fictional character and the main protagonist in the anime and manga series http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece] created by http://anidb.net/cr4013 [Oda Eiichiro]. He is a boy whose body is made of rubber after he ate a http://anidb.net/t2518 [devil`s fruit] and acquired the accursed ability.
In the anime and manga, Luffy is captain of the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates], a group of pirates he assembles himself as he quests to find the "One Piece" and become the King of the Pirates. His primary motivation throughout the series is to reach the goal with all of his comrades, a task he pursues no matter what stands in his way. While he is goofy and reckless, he gets quite serious when anyone is in serious danger, notably his crew, whom he considers his friends. Luffy has additionally appeared in all of the featured movies in the series and other media relating to the series, including several video games and specials.
His blood type is F in XFS blood group system used in his world. It is equivalent to B in ABO blood group system.</description>
<picture>77294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="475" type="main character in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="3991">8.67</rating>
<name>Roronoa Zoro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roronoa Zoro is a pirate, former bounty hunter and one of the main protagonists of http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece]. He was the first member to join the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates], and to date is widely acknowledged as the largest threat and the most dangerous member in the crew after http://anidb.net/ch474 [Luffy]. He is famed as a master swordsman, user of the Santouryuu style, and his great strength sometimes leads others to believe he must be the true captain. Being labeled as one of the "Monster Trio", he`s one of the top three fighters in the crew. Zoro is currently one of eleven pirates who have been referred to as "The Eleven Supernovas", having a bounty of 120,000,000 beli.</description>
<picture>80181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="476" type="main character in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="2401">7.24</rating>
<name>Nami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nami, nicknamed Thief-Cat Nami, is the crew`s 18-year-old navigator and thief. She has the ability to recognize and analyze even the slightest changes in the weather up to the point of sheer intuition. She is also an excellent pickpocket. Her dream is to draw a complete map of the world. Throughout the series, Nami fights using a bou-like staff that is made up of three connectable segments. http://anidb.net/ch478 [Usopp] later provides her with a version of this weapon capable of controlling weather, called the Clima-Takt ("Climate Baton" in the English manga and as "Weather Forcer" in the 4Kids dub). Even later, Usopp augments the Clima-Takt with dials, making it more powerful. Nami ranked in the Top 10 of all three Shounen Jump character popularity polls. Her backstory has been found to be a "touching story" as it "unfolds with a lot of emotion" by Mania Entertainment writer, Jarred Pine. Pine also mentioned Nami was his favorite character from the series, and satisfied with how the manga showed her past. While reviewing the 8th DVD from Viz Media, Activeanime mentioned Nami is one of the best characters from the series as "She`s got guts, smarts, and can heft a mean punch when needed". Like Pined, Activeanime liked Nami`s background and added that his "itty bitty heart went out to her".
When a reader asked http://anidb.net/cr4013 [Oda] who Nami is in romantic love with, Oda answered that there will not likely be any romance among the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates]. Oda explained that he does not portray romance in http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece] as the series is a shounen comic, and the young boys who read the comic are not interested in romance.</description>
<picture>80179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="478" type="main character in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="1329">4.40</rating>
<name>Usopp</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Usopp, nicknamed "Sogeking", "King of Snipers Sogeking" (Sogeki no Ou-sama; "Sniperking" (Viz manga) is the 17-year old marksman of the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates]. His name comes from Uso, which means liar in Japanese, and Aesop, the author of The Boy Who Cried Wolf. He is a liar, talented inventor, as well as a skilled painter and sculptor. His primary weapon is a slingshot, which he uses to fire various kinds of ammunition, ranging from rotten eggs and shuriken to hot sauce, flaming, and exploding projectiles. Later, he creates himself a large, dial-powered slingshot he calls Kabuto, with which he is able to out range even guns. Usopp`s father, http://anidb.net/ch688 [Yasopp], left his family to become a pirate when Usopp was still very young. Some time after this, Usopp`s mother, http://anidb.net/ch648 [Banchina], fell ill. Usopp started telling lies, stating that his father had returned and would be taking them with him. His mother eventually died, but Usopp, in his sadness, continued to lie. Despite all this, he does not blame his father for leaving him, but takes pride in his heritage. He is inspired by http://anidb.net/ch474 [Luffy], http://anidb.net/ch475 [Zoro], and http://anidb.net/ch476 [Nami] and decides to go out to sea, following his dream of becoming a "brave warrior of the sea". His weakness as a fighter weighs heavily upon him and when after the crew is defeated and almost destroyed by http://anidb.net/ch3168 [Admiral Aokiji], Luffy decides to replace the badly damaged http://anidb.net/ch2028 [Going Merry], the Straw Hats` first ship, which is given to them by Usopp`s friend http://anidb.net/ch643 [Kaya], a girl from his village that he used to cheer up with his lies, Usopp goes so far as to temporarily leave the crew.
Usopp ranked in the Top 10 of all three Shounen Jump character popularity polls. In a 2007 Oricon poll, Usopp was voted the 10th most wanted character to receive a spin off amongst all respondents, and the 5th most popular amongst males. In a review of Funimation Entertainment`s second DVD release for Mania Entertainment, Bryce Coulter notes that Usopp "brings lots of comic relief to the series", but also comments that he "can be down right annoying at times".</description>
<picture>80183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="479" type="main character in" update="2017-08-18">
<rating votes="1397">6.86</rating>
<name>Vinsmoke Sanji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanji is a pirate and the chef of the Straw Hat Pirates. He is the fifth member of the crew and the fourth to join. Since he was born in North Blue, he is the first Straw Hat not to originate from East Blue. His dream is to find the rumoured All Blue, which is where East Blue, West Blue, North Blue, and South Blue meet along with their wildlife; a chef`s paradise. He has a bounty of 77,000,000 Berry.
Source: onepiece.wikia.com</description>
<picture>80184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="487" type="main character in" update="2012-01-18">
<rating votes="889">5.23</rating>
<name>Tony Tony Chopper</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tony Tony Chopper is the doctor of the Straw Hat Pirates. Chopper is a reindeer that consumed the Devil fruit, Hito Hito no Mi. He comes from Drum Island, which makes him the only member of the Straw Hat Pirate Crew who was born on the Grand Line. He is the sixth member of the crew and the fifth to join, as well as being the youngest member on board. He has a bounty of 50 Berry, due to being mistaken for the crew`s pet.</description>
<picture>80146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="488" type="main character in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="1489">7.47</rating>
<name>Nico Robin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nico Robin, nicknamed "Demon Child" (悪魔の子, Akuma no Ko) by the http://anidb.net/ch1974 [World Government] is the 28 years old archeologist of the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates] Growing up alone on the island Ohara, home of the world`s largest and oldest library, she became an archeologist at age eight and learned how to decipher the writings on the ancient stones called Poneglyph, which are scattered around the world. After the World Government destroyed Ohara for housing archeologists along with her returning mother, http://anidb.net/ch2887 [Nico Olivia], researching these stones, Robin spent twenty years on the run, cooperating with various pirates and other outlaws and became a member of http://anidb.net/ch2939 [Baroque Works] nicknamed as "Ms. All-Sunday"; Ms. Sunday (4Kids dub) at the time, being briefly an antagonist to the Straw Hat Pirates before joining them. Like the scholars of Ohara before her, it is her dream to find and decipher the Rio Poneglyph, which is said to tell the world`s lost history. Her devotion to history and its preservation goes so far that she will even risk her life to protect ancient artefacts and buildings. She ate the Flower-Flower Fruit, allowing her to create copies of any of her body parts on any surface that she can see. However, if her replicated parts are hurt, she feels the pain on her actual body.</description>
<picture>80187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="490" type="main character in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="461">6.17</rating>
<name>Franky</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Franky is the shipwright for the http://anidb.net/ch1954 [Straw Hat Pirates]. He is a 34 year old cyborg from Water 7, and was introduced in the story as the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch3252 [Franky Family], a group of ship dismantlers. He is also so far one of the two "true" cyborgs so far shown in the series, with the other being the http://anidb.net/ch2135 [Shichibukai], http://anidb.net/ch3841 [Bartholomew Kuma], and was the first one to be introduced. He was originally named Cutty Flam until he threw away his original name for his nickname per the request by http://anidb.net/ch3264 [Iceburg] to hide his identity. Franky and followers were originally introduced as antagonists of the Water 7 Arc against the Straw Hats until circumstances forced them to become allies. Per the request of the Franky Family, Franky was allowed to join the Straw Hats to fulfill his dream. He is the eighth member of the Straw Hat crew and the seventh to join http://anidb.net/ch474 [Luffy]`s crew. He is also the second member to have been a former villain (the first being http://anidb.net/ch488 [Nico Robin]).</description>
<picture>80182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="491" type="main character in" update="2012-01-19">
<rating votes="404">5.60</rating>
<name>Brook</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Brook is the musician of the Straw Hat Pirates. He is a skeleton the Straw Hats found on board a ghost ship after drifting into the Florian Triangle. He is a Devil Fruit user who ate the Yomi Yomi no Mi and is an undead being brought back into a pseudo-immortal state because of its powers. He is the ninth member of the Straw Hat crew and the eighth to join Luffy`s crew. He is also one of the two swordsmen onboard their current ship with the other being Zoro. He fills the role of the long awaited musician that Luffy wanted for his crew since his journey began. He has a bounty of 33,000,000 Berry.</description>
<picture>80188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2937" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-23">
<rating votes="69">2.06</rating>
<name>Akainu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Admiral Akainu is an Admiral of the Marines. His real name is Sakazuki, he was originally introduced as a Vice Admiral. Because of his actions, Akainu can be considered the main antagonist of the Marineford arc.</description>
<picture>188596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3270" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-08">
<rating votes="41">4.98</rating>
<name>Rob Lucci</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rob Lucci is one of the main antagonists of the CP9 Saga, specifically the Water 7 and Enies Lobby Arcs. Introduced as one of the five foremen of Galley-La Company`s Dock One, he was a sawyer, treenail, and bolt specialist. He was later revealed to be the strongest member of the CP9 operating undercover to obtain the Pluton blueprint from Iceburg.</description>
<picture>73021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3289" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-28">
<rating votes="13">1.62</rating>
<name>Spandam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Spandam is the chief of CP9 and the main antagonist of the Enies Lobby Arc.
Source: One Piece Wikia</description>
<picture>213755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69660" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-27">
<rating votes="7">6.76</rating>
<name>Koala</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43275" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69929" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-12-20">
<rating votes="4">7.55</rating>
<name>Sabo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>166188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83069" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Tanaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42514" picture="169500.jpg">Hamada Gaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83072" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Alba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46342" picture="188651.jpg">Nishino Nanase</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83073" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Long Long Senchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83074" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Curve</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46339" picture="188649.jpg">Narita Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83075" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Kiruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46343" picture="188652.jpg">Satou Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83076" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Kent Beef Jr.</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36066" picture="220265.jpg">Furuta Arata</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83077" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Jimmy Myers</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41701" picture="166029.jpg">Croket</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83078" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Bit</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46334" picture="188644.jpg">Miyoshi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83079" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Morkin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188618.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46338" picture="188648.jpg">Nadal</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83080" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Repre</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46335" picture="188645.jpg">Takeda Rena</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83081" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Akame Fukurou A~P</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>188617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41701" picture="166029.jpg">Croket</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83082" type="main character in" update="2016-07-17">
<rating votes="4">4.46</rating>
<name>Carina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46330" picture="188640.jpg">Mitsushima Hikari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83084" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-17">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Dice</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29623" picture="78236.jpg">Kendou Kobayashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83085" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Baccarat</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46333" picture="188643.jpg">Nanao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83086" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Raise Max</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34374" picture="127853.jpg">Kitaooji Kin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83090" type="main character in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Gild Tesoro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="245665.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83094" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Pork</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36066" picture="220265.jpg">Furuta Arata</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83096" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Narushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83097" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Tesoro (Seinen)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83098" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Rikka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="548" picture="186185.jpg">Sakamoto Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83099" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Tenpo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3057" picture="23959.jpg">Watanabe Naoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83100" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Stella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188632.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19415" picture="50423.jpg">Gi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83101" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Double Down</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188633.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4038" picture="25985.jpg">Takenaka Naoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83102" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>White Jack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4038" picture="25985.jpg">Takenaka Naoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83103" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Kamael Sei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46329" picture="188639.jpg">Mimura Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83104" type="appears in" update="2016-07-17">
<name>Mad Treasure</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1984" picture="21284.jpg">Oguri Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103243" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-06-04">
<name>Gion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234302.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="103244" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-06-04">
<name>Tokikake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234303.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="173604" update="2016-07-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>120</length>
<airdate>2016-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179109" update="2016-07-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2016-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">~episode 0~ 711ver.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 0: 711 Ver.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">~Episode 0~ 711ver.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191493" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-02-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ONE PIECE FILM GOLD×TOHOシネマズ 特別映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TOHO Cinemas x One Piece Film: Gold Special Video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TOHO Cinemas x One Piece Film: Gold - Tokubetsu Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191494" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">「ONE PIECE FILM GOLD」シネマイクポップコーン告知</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Piece Film: Gold - Cine Mike Popcorn Annoucement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">One Piece Film: Gold - Cine Mike Popcorn Kokuchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200330" update="2018-05-26">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">SCRATCH × ONE PIECE FILM GOLD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scratch x One Piece Film: Gold</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Scratch x One Piece Film Gold</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
