<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11535" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-10-09</startdate>
<enddate>2014-10-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hatsune Miku x Tetsuya Nomura</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">HATSUNE MIKU × TETSUYA NOMURA</title>
</titles>
<description>A collaboration video of HATSUNE MIKU x TETSUYA NOMURA (SQUARE ENIX) that was screened at Hatsune Miku Art Exhibition "Universal Positivity"@Wallplay (Oct.9th-Oct.19th), as a part of HATSUNE MIKU EXPO 2014 in New York.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="91">3.43</permanent>
<temporary count="92">4.93</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>176722.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>28439</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4542" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>no dialogue</name>
<description>The anime either has no spoken dialogue or no dialogue at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29077" type="main character in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="407">7.44</rating>
<name>Hatsune Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatsune Miku is a singing synthesizer application and its female character, developed by Crypton Future Media. It uses Yamaha Corporation`s Vocaloid 2 synthesizing technology. The name of the character comes from a fusion of the Japanese for first (初 hatsu), sound (音 ne) and future (Miku (ミク) sounds like a nanori reading of future, 未来, normally read as mirai), referring to her position as the first of Crypton`s Character Vocal Series. She was the second Vocaloid to be sold using the Vocaloid 2 engine and the first Japanese Vocaloid to use the Japanese version of the Vocaloid 2 engine. Her voice is sampled from Japanese voice actress, http://anidb.net/cr1673 [Fujita Saki]. Hatsune Miku has performed onstage as a projection.
Miku`s popularity has seen various references to her in anime. During an episode of http://anidb.net/a5576 [Zoku Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei], Miku is seen auditioning for the voice of http://anidb.net/ch13125 [Otonashi Meru] (Kagamine Rin and Len are referenced in the same episode). Miku`s voice is used in the last http://anidb.net/s10696 [ending theme] for the anime series http://anidb.net/a6182 [Akikan!]. In the http://anidb.net/a5932 [Lucky Star OVA], http://anidb.net/ch32 [Hiiragi Kagami] gets magically transformed into Miku cosplay. http://anidb.net/ch11062 [Kondou Mikoto] in the anime http://anidb.net/a6685 [Kampfer] appears dressed as Miku in episode seven. Miku also makes a cameo appearance in the anime http://anidb.net/a6176 [Sora o Kakeru Shoujo] as well as getting cosplayed by http://anidb.net/ch2254 [Kannagi Itsuki] in the second picture drama.</description>
<picture>84342.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="171929" update="2015-09-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2015-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
