<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11551" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-01-04</startdate>
<enddate>2016-01-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nisekoi: (2016)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">マジカルパティシエ小咲ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">니세코이: (2016)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Magical Patissier Kosaki-chan!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ニセコイ: (2016)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9903" type="Alternative Setting">Nisekoi</anime>
<anime id="10859" type="Alternative Setting">Nisekoi:</anime>
<anime id="10638" type="Other">Nisekoi OAD</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.nisekoi.jp/info/?article_id=35185</url>
<creators>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="59" type="Chief Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="3399" type="Music">Kikuya Tomoki</name>
<name id="37305" type="Original Work">Komi Naoshi</name>
<name id="7770" type="Character Design">Sugiyama Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="59" type="Series Composition">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="26229" type="Series Composition">Tou Fuyashi</name>
<name id="1512" type="Chief Direction">Miyamoto Yukihiro</name>
<name id="10608" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takano Akihisa</name>
<name id="7770" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sugiyama Nobuhiro</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
</creators>
<description>Based on Magical Patissier Kosaki-chan spinoff manga shorts of Nisekoi manga. Bundled with the 21st volume of the Nisekoi manga.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="475">4.73</permanent>
<temporary count="478">6.45</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>178750.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16607</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32553</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nisekoi.jp/info/?article_id=35185</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="57797" type="main character in" update="2014-06-07">
<rating votes="101">4.13</rating>
<name>Ichijou Raku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Raku is the son of a Yakuza family leader. He refuses to take over the family`s duties as the next leader, and prefers to pursue a normal career when he graduates. In the story, he is placed in a fake relationship with Chitoge to prevent a war from starting between their families. The relationship often leads to misunderstandings and difficulties for him as he pursues his crush, Kosaki Onodera. Raku is shown to be very kind and caring even to the people he is supposed to hate, as shown when he helps Chitoge numerous times in the series. As the story progresses, he grows closer to Chitoge, and he even stated that he no longer hates her, although he has yet to sort out his true feelings.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>142256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57798" type="main character in" update="2015-12-02">
<rating votes="303">5.76</rating>
<name>Kirisaki Chitoge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The daughter of the leader of the Bee Hive Gangsters, Chitoge transfers from America to Raku`s high school at the start of the series. She and Raku pretend to be in a relationship in order to prevent their families` factions from feuding. She is half-Japanese with long blonde hair that is tied with a ribbon. She is good at sports and academics, but clueless when it comes to cooking. Despite not getting along with Raku from the start, she makes an effort to find his lost pendant. Ten years before, Chitoge makes a promise with a boy; when she looks through her diary from that time, she stumbles upon a key that could potentially unlock Raku`s locket. Later she develops feelings for Raku without realizing it, and tends to get jealous whenever other girls such as Marika try to get close to him. During their Romeo and Juliet class play, she eventually realizes that she is genuinely in love with him. Her mother, Hana, is a powerful CEO in America.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>142255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57799" type="main character in" update="2014-06-07">
<rating votes="290">7.13</rating>
<name>Onodera Kosaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Onodera Kosaki is a kind and sweet classmate of Raku. She has a shoulder length dark brown hair and chestnut brown eyes. Although Raku has a major crush on her, she does not reveal that she has a similar crush on him. When Raku mentions his lost locket of his first love, she shows some interest as she secretly carries a potential key, however, when confronted about the key or being the first love, she lies and denies it in embarrassment. Although she works with her mother at a dessert shop, she turns out to be a terrible cook on her own. Surprisingly, whatever food she fashions looks good on the outside.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>142254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57905" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-28">
<rating votes="118">6.89</rating>
<name>Tsugumi Seishirou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsugumi is a hitwoman who was raised and trained by Claude of the Beehive Gangsters. Tsugumi is originally introduced as a guy who transfers to Chitoge`s class, and has orders to protect her from Raku, whom she thinks forced Chitoge into the relationship. She and Chitoge are childhood friends; she tries to keep a ten year old promise of becoming strong to protect Chitoge. However, after Raku treats her nicely, she begins to develop feelings for him, even though she is too stubborn and embarrassed to admit it. In America, her assassin code name is "Black Tiger", who had a rivalry with "White Fang" Paula McCoy. She does well academically, having ranked next to Chitoge on a yearly exam. Raku has occasionally confided with her as a good friend and also for romance advice.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>146655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58637" type="appears in" update="2015-08-31">
<rating votes="59">5.50</rating>
<name>Maiko Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shuu is Raku`s best friend; they have known each other since pre-school. He is the kind of person that would do anything for a laugh, and often makes perverted passes or comments without shame to his friends. He is also very perceptive, knowing immediately that Raku was not really dating Chitoge, that Raku and Onodera have secret crushes on each other, and that Tsugumi develops feelings for Raku. He uses this knowledge for his enjoyment. On academic rankings, he places next to his "glasses buddy" Ruri, much to the latter`s chagrin. He has not expressed romantic interest in Raku`s friends, but has expressed interest in their homeroom teacher Kyouko.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>177029.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="60162" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-12-02">
<rating votes="128">6.30</rating>
<name>Tachibana Marika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marika transfers to Raku`s class and is introduced as his fiancée; she bears a key that she thinks will unlock Raku`s pendant, and is the most vocal about expressing her love to Raku. She is the daughter of the police chief, and has been in love with Raku for the past ten years. She does not get along with Chitoge; she states she hates girls with long hair despite the fact that she also has long hair. She has a frail constitution; ten years prior, she was frequently visited by a young Raku, who brought her gifts and sparked a friendship with her. She used to speak in a rather vulgar manner, but has attempted to correct her language after Raku had told her that he likes a girly girl with long hair. However, when flustered, she reverts to her old speaking habits.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>146654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67819" type="appears in" update="2014-06-05">
<rating votes="4">5.94</rating>
<name>Tachibana Gen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marika`s father. He is a police commissioner.</description>
<picture>156354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75506" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-01">
<rating votes="9">6.21</rating>
<name>Magical Patissier Kosaki-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75507" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-01">
<rating votes="3">4.61</rating>
<name>Magical Police Marika-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75510" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-01">
<rating votes="6">6.72</rating>
<name>Magical Gorilla Chitoge-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75514" type="appears in" update="2016-01-07">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Ruurin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75518" type="appears in" update="2015-06-01">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Dr. Maiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77515" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-07">
<rating votes="3">5.67</rating>
<name>Magical Teacher Kanakura Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79424" type="appears in" update="2016-01-07">
<rating votes="2">5.86</rating>
<name>Togechii</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79426" type="appears in" update="2016-01-07">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Magical Chocolatier Haru-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79427" type="appears in" update="2016-01-07">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79428" type="appears in" update="2016-01-07">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Windoll</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32588" picture="87531.jpg">Koiwai Kotori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79429" type="appears in" update="2016-01-07">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ruurin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="171153" update="2016-01-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シンコン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Newlyweds</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">신혼</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinkon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174290" update="2016-01-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マジカルパティシエ小咲ちゃん!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magical Patissier Kosaki-chan!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">매지컬 파티셰 코사키짱</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magical Patissier Kosaki-chan!!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
