<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11557" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-09-12</startdate>
<enddate>2014-09-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ball yo Doko e Yuku</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ボールよどこへゆく</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11114" type="Other">I`m Stuck!!: Life of the Dead</anime>
<anime id="11558" type="Other">Majin Sentai Death Ranger: Ubawareta Pudding!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Fb9mLr_Aqc</url>
<description>Collaboration between Studio Binzo and J-toys Channel.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="24">2.18</permanent>
<temporary count="24">3.10</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>177160.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>30093</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=7Fb9mLr_Aqc</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3206" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-06">
<name>stop motion</name>
<description>Stop motion (also known as stop-action or frame-by-frame) is an animation technique to make a physically manipulated object appear to move on its own. The object is moved in small increments between individually photographed frames, creating the illusion of movement when the series of frames is played as a continuous sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="171961" update="2015-09-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2015-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
