<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11595" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2016-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ooya-san wa Shishunki!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">大家さんは思春期!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ooya-san wa Shishunki!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">房东妹子青春期</title>
</titles>
<url>http://ooyasan-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="36055" type="Work">Seven Arcs Pictures</name>
<name id="32756" type="Direction">Ogawa Yuuki</name>
<name id="31541" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shimizu Atsuki</name>
<name id="38590" type="Music">Arte Refact</name>
<name id="44215" type="Original Work">Minase Ruruu</name>
<name id="31541" type="Character Design">Shimizu Atsuki</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch79443 [Maeda-san] is living alone in rented accommodations for the first time after finding employment. In his tiny, no-bath apartment he is visited by http://anidb.net/ch78343 [Satonaka Chie], who looks like the little sister he never had, but turns out to be the landlord of this apartment building. Chie`s high degree of competence when it comes to cooking and housework, sometimes makes her appear very much older than the middle school girl she actually is. Maeda-san`s other neighbour, http://anidb.net/ch79445 [Shirai Reiko], quite jealously tries to guard the cute landlord for herself though. And so Maeda-san`s otherwise uneventful life, supposedly living alone, suddenly becomes quite lively...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="718">4.50</permanent>
<temporary count="721">6.24</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221964.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17795</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31621</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ooyasan-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ooya-san_wa_Shishunki!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>大家さんは思春期!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4046</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354142</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18826</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="77102" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-10-27">
<rating votes="20">7.13</rating>
<name>Komori Shuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178960.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77103" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-10-27">
<rating votes="13">6.93</rating>
<name>Negishi Masako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178961.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77104" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-10-27">
<rating votes="13">5.42</rating>
<name>Nishitori Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178962.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77811" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-10-13">
<rating votes="8">6.21</rating>
<name>Ootani Kurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178513.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="78343" type="main character in" update="2016-01-13">
<rating votes="13">7.52</rating>
<name>Satonaka Chie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78698" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-13">
<rating votes="2">4.42</rating>
<name>Miyamura Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37227" picture="195131.jpg">Yamazaki Erii</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78699" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-13">
<rating votes="2">4.42</rating>
<name>Ueno Mayu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79443" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-13">
<rating votes="4">3.90</rating>
<name>Maeda-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79444" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-13">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Mori Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43849" picture="228703.jpg">Nakashima Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79445" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-13">
<rating votes="9">5.86</rating>
<name>Shirai Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79446" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-13">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Kanemoto Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>181419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40101" picture="156237.jpg">Wada Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80919" type="appears in" update="2018-08-31">
<name>Sasaki Kengo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80920" type="appears in" update="2016-03-14">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="174233" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんは世話焼き!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Is Neighborly!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio s`incruste</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Sewayaki!</title>
<summary>Coming home from work, I smell curry from my room!? I envision us being a domestic couple or a newlywed as Chie-chan greets me at the door, but she’s more like a mom!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691999</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174234" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんは無自覚?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Is Oblivious?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio est une ingénue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Mujikaku?</title>
<summary>Chie-chan is frightened when she feels someone is following her. 
Reiko-san can keep an eye on her during the afternoon, but since she has to work at night, Chie-chan is coming to spend a night at my place.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691997</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174235" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんは家庭的!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Is Domesticated!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio est un cordon bleu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Kateiteki!</title>
<summary>I’m going to learn how to cook with the very cute Chie-chan wearing her aprons over her school uniform and the beautiful next door neighbor, Reiko-san, in the tiny 1 room kitchen. Isn’t this the pinnacle of my life!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691995</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174236" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんは女の子!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Is a Little Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon propriétaire est une ado</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Onnanoko!</title>
<summary>The middle school girl waiting in my new 1 room apartment(with no bath) is my landlord!?
Plus, the beautiful next door neighbor raises my anticipation for the new chapter in my life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>691993</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174443" update="2019-09-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174723" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんは銭湯通い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Goes to the Public Baths!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio va aux bains publics</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Sentou Kayoi!</title>
<summary>Maeda goes to public bath along with Chie-chan and Reiko. 
The bath is filled with old men even though it just opened. It seems they are there for Chie-chan. 
They are able to hear Chie-chan and Reiko’s conversation next door if they listen carefully...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692007</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174724" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんは料理人!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Is a Chef!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio est un cuistot !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Ryourinin!</title>
<summary>Chie was able to make friends thanks to Reiko’s kyaraben and even made a cooking club.
With the free ingredients provided by the local grocery store, they begin making pork soup on the 1st day...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692005</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174725" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんは注目の的!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Is the Center of Attention!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio est le centre d`attention</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Chuumoku no Mato!</title>
<summary>Reiko accepted Chie-chan’s request to make a “cute bento,” but she rarely cooks.
She somehow finished making a kyaraben, but the end result is...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692003</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="174726" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんはひとり好き?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Likes to Be Alone?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio aime la solitude ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Hitori Suki?</title>
<summary>Chie-chan goes straight home after school, so she doesn’t belong in any afterschool club activities. Maeda and Reiko want her to enjoy her school life. Feeling their passion, Chie-chan finds the courage to take the first step…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692001</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175523" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんはやっぱり...!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Is Just So...!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio est vraiment...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Yappari...!</title>
<summary>It’s the summer festival. Wearing a yukata, Chie meets up with her friends.
Maeda is tagging along as a bodyguard. Protecting the girls from the crowd, Maeda turns into an event security. Maeda loses the girls, but Chie comes calling...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692015</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175524" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんはお目が高い!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Has a Good Eye!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio a du goût !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Ome ga Takai!</title>
<summary>Maeda and Reiko take Chie clothes shopping since she wears her school uniform every day. The two enjoy watching Chie try out different clothes like a model, but Chie is interested in something else...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692013</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175525" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんは成長中?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Is Growing?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio est en pleine croissance ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Seichouchuu?</title>
<summary>Reiko runs into Mayu and Yuki who came over to study with Chie and notices something unusual with Yuki’s body. Yuki, who is still developing, is not wearing the correct size bra.
Chie and Mayu watch indifferently as the two share their pain of having a large chest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692011</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="175526" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大家さんは変わり者?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Landlord Is an Oddball?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma proprio est étrange ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooya-san wa Kawarimono?</title>
<summary>Chie is enjoying looking at grocery ads during recess. 
The worried classmates watch her and are surprised when they realize something...
The mysterious Chie becomes the talk of the class.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>692009</identifier>
<identifier>ooya-san-wa-shishunki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="220004" update="2019-09-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="220005" update="2019-09-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
