<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1163" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>9</episodecount>
<startdate>1987-07-21</startdate>
<enddate>1987-07-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Robot Carnival</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ロボット・カーニバル</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Robotų Karnavalas</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ロボットカーニバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Robot Carnival</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Robot Carnival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Robot Carnival</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="262" approval="5" total="5">Memories</anime>
<anime id="812" approval="3" total="6">Roujin Z</anime>
<anime id="3544" approval="1" total="1">Megazone 23 Part II: Himitsu Kudasai</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="132589">Lots of short stories about mechs. Not verbal, completely visual. Kinda boring. Only a few of the stories really moved me. I didn`t get most of it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="505867">For those who watched anime before Toonami. Sci Fi channels Saturday Anime time slot showing some anime like Project Ako, Lilly CAT, Vampire Hunter D (85), Eye Of Mars, Green Legend Ran, Tank Police, Venus Wars and many others. This movie showed some of the best artist at the time. To tell you the truth it was short....too short. If the some of the short movies were a bit longer....it would have showed great potential. Stick with what you like this movie will only disappoint those who watched Toonami and claim it was the first.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="253095">Compilation of showcase short stories.
Excellent animation quality and high artistic value in several of the segments.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.b-ch.com/ttl/index.php?ttl_c=206</url>
<creators>
<name id="1947" type="Music">Hisaishi Joe</name>
<name id="6497" type="Music">Takeichi Masahisa</name>
<name id="5090" type="Character Design">Oomori Hidetoshi</name>
<name id="5090" type="Direction">Oomori Hidetoshi</name>
<name id="1953" type="Character Design">Umetsu Yasuomi</name>
<name id="1953" type="Direction">Umetsu Yasuomi</name>
<name id="9508" type="Character Design">Fukushima Atsuko</name>
<name id="149" type="Direction">Ootomo Katsuhiro</name>
<name id="276" type="Character Design">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="276" type="Direction">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="4374" type="Character Design">Kitazume Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="4374" type="Direction">Kitazume Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="1601" type="Character Design">Nakamura Takashi</name>
<name id="1601" type="Direction">Nakamura Takashi</name>
<name id="1389" type="Character Design">Sadamoto Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="3670" type="Direction">Kitakubo Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="25723" type="Character Design">Mao Lamdo</name>
<name id="25723" type="Direction">Mao Lamdo</name>
<name id="49309" type="Music">Fujita Isaku</name>
</creators>
<description>8 of Japan`s leading animators were asked to create a short segment that followed the theme of Robots, for their inclusion in this film. Essentially, this movie is 9 short films, all independent of one another. The common element is human interaction with robots, namely the consequences of creating life with one`s own hands, played in nine very different ways.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="626">6.27</permanent>
<temporary count="630">6.89</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>17942.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>828</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2182</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3367</identifier>
<identifier>lbgnlh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.b-ch.com/ttl/index.php?ttl_c=206</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Robot_Carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ロボットカーニバル</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88757</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07DNKFS54</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3277" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-28">
<name>bendy lasers</name>
<description>Lasers — of all things — bend at strange angles, are profusely in effect in this anime. Usually seen in a space setting, as part of a weapon system on spaceships.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5793" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-13">
<name>Asimov`s Three Laws of Robotics</name>
<description>The SF author Isaac Asimov developed (1942) a set of laws he used to govern the behaviour of robots:
1. A robot may not injure a human being or, through inaction, allow a human being to come to harm.
2. A robot must obey any orders given to it by human beings, except where such orders would conflict with the First Law.
3. A robot must protect its own existence as long as such protection does not conflict with the First or Second Law.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="32281" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Fukusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4915" picture="48429.jpg">Miwa Katsue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32282" type="main character in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Sankichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3252" picture="24231.jpg">Tomiyama Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32283" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="491" picture="38232.jpg">Yokoyama Chisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32284" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Jean-Jacques Walkerson III</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71556.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32285" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Daimaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9290">Nishio Toku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32286" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Genjirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32287" type="main character in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Shujinkou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32746" picture="88317.jpg">Moritsugu Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32289" type="main character in" update="2011-05-15">
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71561.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="12509" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>1987-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オープニング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Opening</title>
<summary>A visual treat for the eyes as well as the mind, Robot Carnival is an anthology collection of nine short films, many done by animators before they got their feet wet in directing. From funny to dramatic, artistic to entertaining, each story reaches towards the furthest corners of time and space to bring you a tale of robots, and the people who make them. Whether you have a love for great hand-drawn animation, an appreciation for fine storytelling, or just like robots, this anthology is a must!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742733</identifier>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130162" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>1987-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンディング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ending</title>
<summary>A visual treat for the eyes as well as the mind, Robot Carnival is an anthology collection of nine short films, many done by animators before they got their feet wet in directing. From funny to dramatic, artistic to entertaining, each story reaches towards the furthest corners of time and space to bring you a tale of robots, and the people who make them. Whether you have a love for great hand-drawn animation, an appreciation for fine storytelling, or just like robots, this anthology is a must!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742733</identifier>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130163" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1987-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニワトリ男と赤い首</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niwatori Otoko to Akai Kubi</title>
<summary>A visual treat for the eyes as well as the mind, Robot Carnival is an anthology collection of nine short films, many done by animators before they got their feet wet in directing. From funny to dramatic, artistic to entertaining, each story reaches towards the furthest corners of time and space to bring you a tale of robots, and the people who make them. Whether you have a love for great hand-drawn animation, an appreciation for fine storytelling, or just like robots, this anthology is a must!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742733</identifier>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130164" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1987-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明治からくり文明奇譚~紅毛人襲来之巻~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Tale of Two Robots: Chapter 3 - Foreign Invasion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meiji Karakuri Bunmei Kitan: Koumoujin Shuurai no Maki</title>
<summary>A visual treat for the eyes as well as the mind, Robot Carnival is an anthology collection of nine short films, many done by animators before they got their feet wet in directing. From funny to dramatic, artistic to entertaining, each story reaches towards the furthest corners of time and space to bring you a tale of robots, and the people who make them. Whether you have a love for great hand-drawn animation, an appreciation for fine storytelling, or just like robots, this anthology is a must!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742733</identifier>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130165" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1987-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">2.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">CLOUD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cloud</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cloud</title>
<summary>A visual treat for the eyes as well as the mind, Robot Carnival is an anthology collection of nine short films, many done by animators before they got their feet wet in directing. From funny to dramatic, artistic to entertaining, each story reaches towards the furthest corners of time and space to bring you a tale of robots, and the people who make them. Whether you have a love for great hand-drawn animation, an appreciation for fine storytelling, or just like robots, this anthology is a must!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742733</identifier>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130166" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>1987-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">STARLIGHT ANGEL</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starlight Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Starlight Angel</title>
<summary>A visual treat for the eyes as well as the mind, Robot Carnival is an anthology collection of nine short films, many done by animators before they got their feet wet in directing. From funny to dramatic, artistic to entertaining, each story reaches towards the furthest corners of time and space to bring you a tale of robots, and the people who make them. Whether you have a love for great hand-drawn animation, an appreciation for fine storytelling, or just like robots, this anthology is a must!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742733</identifier>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130167" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>1987-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレゼンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Presence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Presence</title>
<summary>A visual treat for the eyes as well as the mind, Robot Carnival is an anthology collection of nine short films, many done by animators before they got their feet wet in directing. From funny to dramatic, artistic to entertaining, each story reaches towards the furthest corners of time and space to bring you a tale of robots, and the people who make them. Whether you have a love for great hand-drawn animation, an appreciation for fine storytelling, or just like robots, this anthology is a must!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742733</identifier>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130168" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>1987-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="8">2.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DEPRIVE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deprive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deprive</title>
<summary>A visual treat for the eyes as well as the mind, Robot Carnival is an anthology collection of nine short films, many done by animators before they got their feet wet in directing. From funny to dramatic, artistic to entertaining, each story reaches towards the furthest corners of time and space to bring you a tale of robots, and the people who make them. Whether you have a love for great hand-drawn animation, an appreciation for fine storytelling, or just like robots, this anthology is a must!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742733</identifier>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="130169" update="2017-09-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>1987-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フランケンの歯車</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Franken`s Gears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Franken no Haguruma</title>
<summary>A visual treat for the eyes as well as the mind, Robot Carnival is an anthology collection of nine short films, many done by animators before they got their feet wet in directing. From funny to dramatic, artistic to entertaining, each story reaches towards the furthest corners of time and space to bring you a tale of robots, and the people who make them. Whether you have a love for great hand-drawn animation, an appreciation for fine storytelling, or just like robots, this anthology is a must!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742733</identifier>
<identifier>robot-carnival</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197975" update="2018-04-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Memory of Robot Carnival: A Look Back at the History of the Classic Anthology</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
