<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1165" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1997-11-22</startdate>
<enddate>1997-11-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Onkyou Seimeitai Noiseman</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Звукоед Нойзмен</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Dźwiękowy insekt - Noiseman</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">noiseman</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">音響生命体ノイズマン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Noiseman Sound Insect</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.studio4c.co.jp/works/noiseman/</url>
<creators>
<name id="276" type="Direction">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="241" type="Music">Kanno Youko</name>
<name id="276" type="Character Design">Morimoto Kouji</name>
<name id="49" type="Character Design">Yuasa Masaaki</name>
<name id="738" type="Animation Work">Studio 4C</name>
<name id="1280" type="Original Plan">Beyond City</name>
</creators>
<description>In a city called, "Champon", a scientist created a synthetic life form called "Noiseman", who erase Hertzian waves of music by transforming it into crystals. A group of street "biker" kids rebel against Noiseman to release their town from his control.
Produced by beyond c and Bandai Visual, this 1997 short film is one of Koji Morimoto`s major works. He is currently well-known for Beyond, as part of the Animatrix. Another noteworthy credit in this film is Yoko Kanno, who skillfully turns noise and Hertzian waves into music.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="791">5.04</permanent>
<temporary count="792">6.56</temporary>
<review count="1">7.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>2455.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3118</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1978</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3537</identifier>
<identifier>vhgcol</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://studio4c.co.jp/works/pages/03.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://studio4c.co.jp/works/en/pages/03.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Noiseman_Sound_Insect</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>音響生命体ノイズマン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1276</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>153397</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="47278" type="main character in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="1">4.42</rating>
<name>Noiseman</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2046" picture="186581.jpg">Kozakura Etsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47279" type="main character in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="1">7.27</rating>
<name>Tobio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3295" picture="38451.jpg">Ogihara Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47280" type="main character in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="1">7.27</rating>
<name>Reina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="489" picture="43165.jpg">Okamoto Maya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="12780" update="2005-09-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>1997-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43431" update="2005-11-08">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Jet TV (DVD Extra)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="43432" update="2005-11-08">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">MTV Japan Top20 (DVD Extra)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
