<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11679" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-07-09</startdate>
<enddate>2016-10-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nejimaki Seirei Senki: Tenkyou no Alderamin</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ねじ巻き精霊戦記 天鏡のアルデラミン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Alderamin on the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Alderamin on the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">태엽 감는 정령전기 천경의 알데라민</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">发条精灵战记 天镜的极北之星</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6244" approval="29" total="36">Senjou no Valkyria: Valkyria Chronicles</anime>
<anime id="10744" approval="20" total="30">Madan no Ou to Vanadis</anime>
<anime id="7315" approval="13" total="16">Densetsu no Yuusha no Densetsu</anime>
<anime id="6408" approval="6" total="8">Souten Kouro</anime>
<anime id="10445" approval="5" total="13">Aldnoah.Zero</anime>
<anime id="10864" approval="4" total="13">Heavy Object</anime>
<anime id="584" approval="4" total="9">Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu</anime>
<anime id="6005" approval="3" total="8">Tytania</anime>
<anime id="4521" approval="1" total="7">Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="272780">Simply the best. We are all waiting for the moment. After watching you will wait for it too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="521848">My favorite show from summer 2016.
Surprisingly good both on characters and plot.
War themed with a bit of magic, the only thing i dislike is to wait for season 2.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="432674">I`m surprised no one has yet to recommend this. This is for you guys who usually read at recommend section to see if its worth watching especially those looking out for sammy321 must sees like me :D.

Anyway this series is good. There were about 3 arcs that was each entertaining and kept you wanting to watch the next episode after each. There are a lot of blood spurting scene. No annoying characters. Magic/fantasy isn`t really a major element to those who stay away from those tags. Hoping for a next season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="430272">Very intriguing and a use of your brain. Very enjoyable!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="576556">I rarely write a recommendation but Alderamin on the Sky really deserves it. The MC is awesome, he is using his brain to solve problems and is aware that some times because of your position you are unable to solve everything but is still doing what he can for the current situation taking in account his limitations. The main heroine that is supporting him is also a great character. She is also well aware of her pros and cons and the bond between them is making them overcome bad situations. 
The story is also great and has so much more potential to grow if they decide to make more seasons but even if they don`t the ending is still satisfying.

Ending words: just give it a try if you are into well-thought-out characters without arse-pulled hidden powers and be amazed :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="624023">It`s surprising to see so little recommandations for this series, the main character is more than lazy and even more interresting. I have seen more than my fair share of anime but this does count as one off the better ones. It`s a good story with very interresting and fassinating characters. Definitely hoping for a second season as this is just the beginning!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="331199">Really like this series and follows a pretty cool MC who`s goal is to be the laziest person in the world. I came from reading the manga to this and it`s a pretty good adaptation with the characters drawn a little better in the manga. but overall this series is great and the plot line really develops as they unveil little by little the characters past.

Definitely hoping for a second season as the story is just starting.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://alderamin.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="44032" type="Original Work">Uno Bokuto</name>
<name id="11674" type="Character Design">Katsuki Kunio</name>
<name id="19696" type="Series Composition">Yasukawa Shougo</name>
<name id="731" type="Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="2156" type="Direction">Ichimura Tetsuo</name>
<name id="27275" type="Music">Inai Keiji</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="11674" type="Chief Animation Direction">Katsuki Kunio</name>
<name id="43388" type="Chief Animation Direction">Maebara Momoko</name>
<name id="17928" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirano Yuuichi</name>
</creators>
<description>In the "military history fantasy" series, the Katvarna Empire is at war with the neighboring Republic of Kioka. In the Katvarna Empire, the lazy, woman-admiring Ikuta hates war, but due to certain circumstances, he grudgingly takes the High Grade Military Officer Exam. No one would have expected that this 17-year-old young man would eventually become a soldier called a great commander by others. Ikuta survives this world engulfed in war with his superior intellect.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1677">6.84</permanent>
<temporary count="1681">7.38</temporary>
<review count="3">5.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>184119.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17755</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31764</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://alderamin.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tenkyō_no_Alderamin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ねじ巻き精霊戦記_天鏡のアルデラミン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4250</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354346</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19238</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B076B5JDY9</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1032" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-10">
<name>fishing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2635" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>jungle</name>
<description>This show features jungle(s) as one of its settings.
This can either involve jungle adventures or shady business revolving around deforesting of jungles or forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2756" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>board games</name>
<description>People here play a board game. It can vary from chess and Go, to Monopoly, to Dungeons and Dragons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2917" parentid="2756" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>chess</name>
<description>Chess is a game for two players. It is played on a square board, made of 64 smaller squares, with eight squares on each side. Each player starts with sixteen pieces (eight pawns, two each of knights, bishops, and rooks, and one king and queen). One player`s pieces are a light color, he is called "White", and the other player`s pieces are a dark color, he is called "Black".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3374" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>civil war</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3581" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>tactics</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4274" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>hidden agenda</name>
<description>Someone or some organization/government/etc. is misrepresenting themselves by doing/saying one thing while hoping/striving for something else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="78826" type="main character in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="32">6.89</rating>
<name>Ikuta Soroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78827" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="44">6.50</rating>
<name>Shamiyu Kitra Katjvanmaninik</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78828" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="14">5.39</rating>
<name>Truway Remion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32333" picture="131863.jpg">Kanemoto Ryousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78829" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="33">6.08</rating>
<name>Haroma Becker</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35415" picture="146334.jpg">Chisuga Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78830" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="14">3.77</rating>
<name>Matthew Tetojirichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78831" type="main character in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="52">6.20</rating>
<name>Yatorishino Igsem</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83040" type="appears in" update="2016-07-19">
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<name>Arshankrut Kitra Katjvanmaninik</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emperor of the Katjvarna Empire.</description>
<picture>188840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="688" picture="18295.jpg">Tanaka Kan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83041" type="appears in" update="2016-07-19">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hazaaf Rikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lieutenant General of the Katjvarna Empire.</description>
<picture>188841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83308" type="appears in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Iriq Bauza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43746" picture="240127.jpg">Kumagai Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83309" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="7">3.88</rating>
<name>Kus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83310" type="appears in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hardearka Ogory</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83311" type="appears in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Nihad Hiu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39260" picture="150015.jpg">Ishiya Haruki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83312" type="appears in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Nejif Harurum</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36770" picture="151722.jpg">Nose Ikuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83313" type="appears in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ison Ho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83314" type="appears in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="2">1.50</rating>
<name>Sarihaslag Remion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83315" type="appears in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Sushuraf Remion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42164" picture="176249.jpg">Takeuchi Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83316" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-27">
<rating votes="21">5.31</rating>
<name>Suya Mitcalif</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46468" picture="189248.jpg">Akikawa Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83707" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="2">3.96</rating>
<name>Aigi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45234" picture="186846.jpg">Sugawara Shinsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83708" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Ikuta Sankrei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83709" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Gwemp</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34417" picture="128012.jpg">Motohashi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83710" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Shishindi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42006" picture="232274.jpg">Mizunaka Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83711" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Tobai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189926.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39791" picture="153557.jpg">Kagura Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83712" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Ninika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83714" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Yatorishino Igsem (Shoujo Jidai)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83715" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="3">4.98</rating>
<name>Anarai Khan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83716" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Guihan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40504" picture="158574.jpg">Watanuki Ryuunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83717" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Shia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29353" picture="186153.jpg">Yamazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83718" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Solvenares Igsem</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83719" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Nazuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83720" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Badin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40096" picture="207906.jpg">Nogami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83721" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Bada Sankrei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83722" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Mariban Susa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83723" type="appears in" update="2016-08-10">
<rating votes="2">5.07</rating>
<name>Yuuka Sankrei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189931.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85248" type="appears in" update="2016-10-01">
<rating votes="14">7.12</rating>
<name>Kanna Temari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9124" picture="186845.jpg">Hayama Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85285" type="appears in" update="2016-10-03">
<rating votes="10">6.44</rating>
<name>Nanaku Daru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85286" type="appears in" update="2016-10-03">
<rating votes="5">3.48</rating>
<name>Miara Gin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85287" type="appears in" update="2016-10-03">
<rating votes="3">3.76</rating>
<name>Jean Arkinex</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85664" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Senpa Sazaluf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85665" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="3">1.07</rating>
<name>Tamtooktsk Safida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2603" picture="22591.jpg">Sakurai Toshiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85666" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Deinkun Hargunska</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28471" picture="57632.jpg">Yamamoto Itaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85667" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Meraize</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85668" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Yuskshiram Toakk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="196332.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85671" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Azan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24335" picture="192864.jpg">Chiba Shouya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85672" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">1.31</rating>
<name>Amuse Sulkatta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12640" picture="226055.jpg">Souma Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85673" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Nirva Gin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17523" picture="223264.jpg">Yamamoto Kanehira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85674" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Hilmish Nikafarma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85675" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Manubans Najiru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32216" picture="223331.jpg">Sasa Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85676" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Niki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85677" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hisha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193247.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85678" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Akugalpa Sa Domeisha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85679" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Mishuri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10906" picture="200861.jpg">Yanagita Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85684" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Taznyado Harrah</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5632" picture="158531.jpg">Sugisaki Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85690" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="3">5.77</rating>
<name>Mita Kenshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85698" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">1.05</rating>
<name>Talca</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34774" picture="129969.jpg">Obana Kanji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85699" type="appears in" update="2016-10-18">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Nanaku Daru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="178345" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永霊樹の番犬たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Watchdogs of the Spirit Tree</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les chiens de garde de l’esprit éternel</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">영령수의 파수견들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eireijuu no Banken-tachi</title>
<summary>Ikta leads his troops to grand victory over the forces led by the higher ranking officers.  But what was supposed to be a simple training exercise turns deadly serious when a force of men loyal to a betrayed commander kidnaps the princess.  Can Ikta lead his exhausted troops to track down and defeat a squad of experienced soldiers?  And can he do it without letting them hurt the princess?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715607</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178346" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高等士官学校の騎士団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Knights of the High-Level Officer`s School</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’ordre de chevalerie de l’Académie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">고등 사관학교의 기사단</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutou Shikangakkou no Kishidan</title>
<summary>Ikta has been appointed an Imperial Knight, and his new life at the High-Level Officer`s School begins.  The easily-bored Ikta has difficulty fitting in, and its not long before he`s picking fights and making enemies among the upper ranks.  He`s set up in a trap to be humiliated during a mock exercise, and to make matters worse, his platoon commander won`t listen to a word he says.  The reason: because he slept with her mother!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715605</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178347" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不本意なる褒賞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Unwanted Medal of Honor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Indésirable récompense</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">의도치 않은 포상</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuhon`i Naru Houshou</title>
<summary>Ikta succeeds in a daring plan to cross the Kioka border and return the princess home.  But this means he gets a reward, and his reward is the title of Imperial Knight.  Now he finds himself dragged into a war he hates, serving a government that doesn`t want to win, and despising the princess he rescued.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715603</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178348" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐の邂逅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Stormy Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rencontre orageuse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">폭풍의 해후</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Kaikou</title>
<summary>Ikta is a brilliant, but lazy and unmotivated boy.  His childhood friend, a high-ranking daughter of a noble, offers him an easy position at a library if he can help he get the top score on a military exam.  But their lives take a sudden turn when the boat carrying them to the exam runs aground, and Ikta rescues a mysterious girl on board.  When she turns out to be a princess, and they all find themselves behind enemy lines, Ikta is going to start having to work hard for real...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715601</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178656" update="2016-07-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178895" update="2016-07-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179100" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつか, 三度目に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Someday, for the Third Time</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Troisième rencontre</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">언젠가 세 번째로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuka, Sandome ni</title>
<summary>Ikta and his soldiers are sent to deliver supplies to the struggling imperial armies as the war continues. Unused to fighting in the high mountains, and led by incompetent leaders the imperial soldiers suffer heavy casualties.  Ikta devises a brilliant stratagem to retake an enemy fortress, but when a messenger begs him for help in saving his allies, he`s forced to choose between risking his own soldiers life, and bringing another imperial force to certain doom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715615</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179101" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カトヴァーナ北域動乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Northern Katjvarna Rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Révolte dans la province septentrionale</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">카트바나 북역 동란</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katjvarna Hoku Iki Douran</title>
<summary>War breaks out in the far north, as the Empire`s oppression of the mountain people results in a terrifying backlash. With the one competent leader in the Northern Garrison assassinated, the ignorant garrison commander flings the troops headlong into a highly defended, mountainous position, with disastrous results.  Ikta and his friends are kept as part of the reserves for now, but it won`t be long until they`re thrust into the war as well.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715613</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179102" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神の階の麓にて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the Base of the Stairs of God</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aux pieds de l’escalier de Dieu</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">신의 계단 아래 기슭에서</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami no Kai no Fumoto nite</title>
<summary>Ikta and crew are assigned to a garrison in the far northern region of the empire: a lonely, desolate place at the foot of a massive mountain range. The garrison staff are petty and corrupt, and don`t like it when Ikta slacks off and defies orders.  But when they try to throw him in the garrison prison, he stumbles across a secret that they want desperately to keep hidden.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715611</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179103" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人でひとつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two in One</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux en un</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">둘이 하나</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari de Hitotsu</title>
<summary>"Welcome to the world of science!"  When Yatori was 9 years old, she was sent to study with the general Bada Sankrein, and met a young boy her age, Ikta.  The world he shows her is new and exciting, like nothing she`s ever seen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715609</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179794" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亡霊を狩るもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ghost Hunter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chasseurs de fantômes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">망령을 사냥하는 자</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bourei o Karu Mono</title>
<summary>The Imperial army is continuing its retreat from the numerically superior Aldera forces at the base of the Alafatra mountain range.  They`ve set fire to the forest to buy themselves more time, but after a few days the fire is beginning to burn out.  To buy the time they need to finish the retreat, Ikta is forced to mountain a proactive mobile defense and keep the flames burning.  But the enemy general is breaking all the rules, and Ikta can`t figure out his game.  By the time Ikta realizes what`s happened, it`s too late, and the enemy battering down his walls with a new weapon and sending their cavalry straight through the flames!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715623</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179795" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">常怠VS不眠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lazy vs. Unsleeping</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Flegmatique contre insomniaque</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">상태 vs 불면</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joutai VS Nemurazu</title>
<summary>The Imperial Army is pushed back, and Ikta is forced to use every trick at his disposal to keep his numerically inferior force from being overwhelmed.  The Alderamin army has 12,000 troops, and his unit has only a little over 600.  When he`s forced to make a tough call to sacrifice his own men and save the Sinack, Suya confronts him angrily.  She wants to know why he was willing to sacrifice his own men for the people he was fighting yesterday, and she says he owes her an answer.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715621</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179796" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラ・サイア・アルデラミン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">La Saia Alderamin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Saia Alderamin</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">라 사이아 알데라민</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">La Saia Alderamin</title>
<summary>The Sinack have been subdued, but the Imperial Army finds that it`s been caught in a trap!  A huge army from the Aldera nation has crossed the supposedly-impassable northern mountains, and threatens to overwhelm the exhausted Imperial forces.  Ikta`s only way out is to force a peace treaty with the Sinack and ask for their help, which means going to their defeated leader and abasing himself.  Will she respond to his pleas, after the Imperials burned her village and killed her people?  How far is he willing to go earn her forgiveness?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715619</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179797" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ささやかな面目の行方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fate of a Small Honor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Début d’un modeste prestige</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">변변치 않은 면목의 행방</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasayaka na Menboku no Yukue</title>
<summary>The war against the mountain people continues, and the imperial forces are about to make one last march to their final staging ground. The incompetent imperial commanders pick a route that leaves their flanks exposed to an attack, but fortunately Ikta persuades them to dismount and use their shields.  In the midst of the Sinack attack, a group of unknown assassins appears out of nowhere and heads straight for the Lieutenant General!  They`re heavily armed and highly trained, but can Yatori stop them in time?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715617</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180070" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たそがれの帝国にて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In a Twilight Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le crépuscule de l’Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">황혼의 제국에</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tasogare no Teikoku nite</title>
<summary>Ikta suffers a serious setback at the hands of the unsleeping, shining officer from the Kioka republic.  His lines have been broken and the retreat is in disarray.  To salvage an increasingly desperate situation, he leads a small, handpicked force to lure Jean into a trap.  But Jean`s proven himself for than a match for Ikta already, and the Alderan military outnumbers his own forces by over a dozen times.  How can he handle such overwhelming numbers when his opponent has shown to be his equal?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715625</identifier>
<identifier>alderamin-on-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
