<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11672" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-17</startdate>
<enddate>2016-07-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Magi: Sindbad no Bouken (2016)</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Le avventure di Sinbad</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Magi: Sinbad`ın Macerası</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Маги: Приключенията на Синбад (2016)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マギ シンドバッドの冒険 (2016)</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Magi: Adventure of Sinbad</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">天方魔谭MAGI 辛巴达的冒险</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9268" type="Sequel">Magi: The Labyrinth of Magic</anime>
<anime id="10392" type="Summary">Magi: Sindbad no Bouken</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5406" approval="1" total="5">Ookami to Koushinryou</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://urasunday.com/magi/tv_anime.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="42709" type="Animation Work">Lay-duce</name>
<name id="8733" type="Character Design">Sako Souichirou</name>
<name id="14270" type="Original Work">Ootaka Shinobu</name>
<name id="3691" type="Direction">Miyao Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="31573" type="Music">Ookubo Tomohiro</name>
<name id="43962" type="Original Work">Ootera Yoshifumi</name>
</creators>
<description>Thirty years before the events of Magi, a brave and handsome young man named Sinbad set sail and started his adventure. The future High King of Seven Seas gradually matured through various encounters and farewells, taking him towards kingship step by step.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="802">6.82</permanent>
<temporary count="809">7.41</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>183439.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17687</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31741</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://urasunday.com/magi/tv_anime.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.project-magi.com/sinbad/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Magi:_The_Labyrinth_of_Magic#Adventure_of_Sinbad</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マギ_(漫画)#.E3.83.9E.E3.82.AE_.E3.82.B7.E3.83.B3.E3.83.89.E3.83.90.E3.83.83.E3.83.89.E3.81.AE.E5.86.92.E9.99.BA.EF.BC.88.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.EF.BC.89</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4111</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354288</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19048</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6614" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-12">
<name>Animeism</name>
<description>Animeism is a late-night Japanese programming block established in April 2012. It is devoted to anime and broadcast each Thursday night on MBS, in a fashion similar to Fuji TV`s http://anidb.net/t3865 [noitaminA] that also airs on Thursdays. Just like noitaminA, the block airs two series back to back. From April 2015 onwards, the block was moved to Friday nights.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>63625.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6743" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-21">
<name>One Thousand and One Nights</name>
<description>One Thousand and One Nights is a collection of Middle Eastern and South Asian stories and folk tales compiled in Arabic during the Islamic Golden Age. The work was collected over many centuries by various authors, translators, and scholars across West, Central, and South Asia and North Africa. The tales themselves trace their roots back to ancient and medieval Arabic, Persian, Mesopotamian, Indian, Jewish and Egyptian folklore and literature. Some of the stories very widely associated with The Nights, in particular Aladdin`s Wonderful Lamp, Ali Baba and the Forty Thieves, and The Seven Voyages of Sinbad the Sailor were not part of The Nights in its original Arabic versions, but were added to the collection by Antoine Galland and other European translators.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>191584.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="59997" type="appears in" update="2014-05-16">
<rating votes="15">6.40</rating>
<name>Scheherazade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143445.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="62750" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="16">5.83</rating>
<name>Yunan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yunan is one of the four Magi in the current era, known as the Wandering Magi, and is the Guardian of the Great Rift. He was the one that advised http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] to clear the 1st dungeon, http://anidb.net/ch80566 [Baal], stating it would give him the power he sought.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63160" type="main character in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="22">8.12</rating>
<name>Sinbad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sinbad was born and raised in Tison Village of the Parthevia Empire. When Sinbad was 14, he captured his first and the world`s first Dungeon, http://anidb.net/ch80566 [Baal], which was summoned by http://anidb.net/ch62750 [Yunan]. During his journeys, he recruited all of his future http://anidb.net/ch63616 [Kingdom]`s Generals.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>148637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63161" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="8">8.39</rating>
<name>Esra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Esra was the mother of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] and wife of http://anidb.net/ch63164 [Badr].
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>183773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63162" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-09">
<rating votes="11">3.50</rating>
<name>Seredine Dikumenowlz Du Parthevia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63163" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="5">4.89</rating>
<name>Dragul Nol Henrius Gobias Medias Partenvonmias Dumid Os Koltanon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dragul is a former general of the Parthevia Empire. He is part of Parthevia`s Dragul Family, and son of the Parthevian General Draguliel Pertegomidus.
When 1st Dungeon, http://anidb.net/ch80566 [Baal], appeared in Parthevia, the Emperor wanted to obtain its power, since Parthevia was in war against Reim Empire. All the soldiers who were sent to the Dungeon died, and the Emperor decided to send Dragul as well. He recruited more people among the population, with Sinbad among them. Only Dragul and Sinbad managed to reach the Baal`s throne room, where they had a duel in order to decide who will take Baal`s power for himself. In the end, Sinbad won.
He was the first of the Eight Generals to meet http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] and the first member of Sinbad`s Household.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>156526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="63164" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="4">6.10</rating>
<name>Badr</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Badr was the father of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] and a former soldier of the Parthevia Empire.
Badr was a cheerful, fun-loving guy. He cared a lot about his family, just like how Sinbad cares for the people of his country like they were family. He had a serious side too, since when everybody in Parthevia was delirious with the war he asked himself if it was alright to continue like this. He and his son`s personalities are very similar.
Source: Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>183772.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66049" type="appears in" update="2014-03-25">
<rating votes="2">2.54</rating>
<name>Rametoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66051" type="appears in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="6">8.67</rating>
<name>Sinbad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sinbad, while using Baal Djinn Equip.
In this form, Sinbad takes on the appearance of a dragon and gets two horns and a jewel on his forehead and an elaborate necklace along with blue scale-like armor over parts of his body and a long tail. In this equip, Sinbad gains the sword of http://anidb.net/ch80566 [Baal], Bararaq Saiqa. The sword has a guard around the hilt similar to that of the claw of Baal with blue scales.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70828" type="appears in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="5">6.03</rating>
<name>Pipirika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pipirika is a member of the Imuchakk Tribe. She is the daughter of one of the Patriarchs and the sister of http://anidb.net/ch84285 [Hinahoho]. She accompanied her brother when he challenged the Rampaging Unicorn in order to complete his coming of age ceremony.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>164249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71398" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="5">3.88</rating>
<name>Ja`far</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ja`far was born into Parthevia`s undercover unit, the assassins http://anidb.net/ch84317 [Sham Lash], and at one point became its leader. At the age of six, he was forced into killing both of his parents.
Source: Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>164245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71399" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-16">
<rating votes="6">1.91</rating>
<name>Falan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71400" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-22">
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<name>Mahad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mahad, along with http://anidb.net/ch84320 [Vittel] and http://anidb.net/ch71398 [Ja`far], was formerly an assassin of http://anidb.net/ch84317 [Sham Lash]. After http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] conquered the 6th Dungeon, http://anidb.net/ch84270 [Valefor], he became a merchant of Sindria Company and joined Sinbad in his travels. He`s a quiet person and good at observing people as well as taking care of his employees.
Mahad grew up with Vittel and they stuck together as they both shared the common fate as war orphans. They both started to steal for survival and eventually both were picked up by Sham Lash.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>164247.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="80566" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-26">
<rating votes="4">5.66</rating>
<name>Baal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baal is the lightning Djinn, also known as the Djinn of Wrath and Heroes, who ruled over the 1st Dungeon.
He`s is one of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad]`s seven Djinn.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80567" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="3">1.28</rating>
<name>Barbarossa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Barbarossa is a lieutenant of the Parthevia Empire, head of the Dragul family and http://anidb.net/ch63163 [Drakon]`s elder brother. He is one of http://anidb.net/ch47594 [Judal]`s King Vessels and a Dungeon Capturer, capturing one Dungeon.
Source: Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>190525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84270" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-26">
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<name>Valefor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Valefor is the water Djinn, also known as the Djinn of Falsehood and Prestige, who ruled over the 6th Dungeon.
He`s is one of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad]`s seven Djinn.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84271" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-26">
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<name>Valefor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Valefor is the water Djinn, also known as the Djinn of Falsehood and Prestige, who ruled over the 6th Dungeon.
He`s is one of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad]`s seven Djinn.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84285" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="4">6.33</rating>
<name>Hinahoho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinahoho comes from Imuchakk, and is the son of one of its Patriarchs. He used to be very timid, lacked courage and often a crybaby, until he met http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad]. After they cleared the dungeon http://anidb.net/ch84270 [Valefor], he joined Sinbad in his travels.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84317" type="appears in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="2">1.56</rating>
<name>Sham Lash</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Sham Lash is an assassins`s guild and Parthevia`s undercover unit.</description>
<picture>190546.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84318" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="2">6.51</rating>
<name>Rurumu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rurumu is the wife of http://anidb.net/ch84285 [Hinahoho] and the daughter of the Chief of the Imuchakk Tribe, Rametoto. Among the Imuchakk Tribe girls, she is noted to be the most beautiful.
Before Hinahoho went to conquer the dungeon, she seemed to like him and happily accepted his hand in marriage. Although Hinahoho loves his wife dearly, there are times when she frightens him.
Rurumu made it her job to teach http://anidb.net/ch71398 [Ja`far] and http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] how to read, write, and use mathematics as they sailed to Reim. Although she is a little rough with Ja`far, she stated she treated him as if he were her own son.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84320" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="2">6.65</rating>
<name>Vittel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vittel was a part of the Assassin`s Guild http://anidb.net/ch84317 [Sham Lash] from the Parthevia Empire before his defection to join http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] as one of the founders of Sindria Trading Company and eventually the nation of Sindria.
Source: Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>190549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84321" type="appears in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Masrur (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Masrur is a Fanalis, who once was a slave and a gladiator in the Reim Colosseum that tried to kill http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad], but failed and became his subordinate.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190551.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84323" type="appears in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Sinbad</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sinbad, while using Valefor Djinn Equip.
In this form, Sinbad takes the form of a nine-tails fox with white fur. His hair changes to white in color and lengthens. His ears also elongates and look like ears of a fox. He also gains eyes on his palms which allows him to use http://anidb.net/ch84270 [Valefor]`s true ability by releasing some sort of waves.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84324" type="appears in" update="2016-08-27">
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<name>Sinbad (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190556.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84423" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-01">
<rating votes="2">5.66</rating>
<name>Ja`far</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ja`far is a former member of Parthevia`s undercover unit, the assassins http://anidb.net/ch84317 [Sham Lash]. After the 6th Dungeon, http://anidb.net/ch84270 [Valefor], was conquered by http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad], he decided to serve him as a vassal and joined him in his travels.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84465" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Pisti (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pisti is the youngest daughter of the Queen of Artemyra, http://anidb.net/ch66048 [Mira Dianos Artemina].
Source: Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>190788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84466" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Mystras Leoxses</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mystras Leoxses is the older son of Darius Leoxses. He was a candidate for the next Knight-King of Sasan. He activated his Household Vessel of the Djinn http://anidb.net/ch80566 [Baal] during a fight with http://anidb.net/ch84285 [Hinahoho], and became one of http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad]`s Household Members.
He was replaced by his younger brother http://anidb.net/ch49494 [Spartos] as one of Sinbad`s Eight Generals following his death.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84467" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="2">3.79</rating>
<name>Darios Leoxses</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darius Leoxses is the Knight-King of Sasan, one of the countries that forms the Seven Seas Alliance. He has conquered the 52nd Dungeon and obtained his Djinn, Alloces.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84468" type="appears in" update="2016-09-02">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Spartos Leoxses (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Spartos Leoxses is the younger brother of http://anidb.net/ch84466 [Mystras Leoxses] and youngest son of http://anidb.net/ch84467 [Darius Leoxses], the Knight-King of Sasan.
Source: Magi Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84509" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-03">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Rashid Saluja</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rashid Saluja is the 22nd King of Balbadd. He taught http://anidb.net/ch63160 [Sinbad] a lot about trade and helped him start his Sindria Trading Company.</description>
<picture>190839.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2585" picture="22579.jpg">Tsuchida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84510" type="appears in" update="2016-09-03">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Barukaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84511" type="appears in" update="2016-09-03">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Darius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darius was the Reim Empire`s Army Intelligence Officer. He was on the run, spying for Reim in the Parthevia Empire.
Source: Magi Wiki</description>
<picture>190845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2573" picture="240892.jpg">Shirokuma Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84512" type="appears in" update="2016-09-03">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Judal (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190847.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="176755" update="2016-06-24">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マギ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magi</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Magi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Magi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176756" update="2016-04-07">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔装vs魔装</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Djinn Equip vs Djinn Equip</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Cin Donanımı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masou vs Masou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176757" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天空都市アルテミュラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Artemyra, the City in the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Gökyüzünde Bir Şehir, Artemyra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkuu Toshi Artemyra</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176758" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界を変える力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Power to Change the World</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Dünyayı Değiştirme Gücü</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai o Kaeru Chikara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176759" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">清浄の地ササン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Land of Purity: Sasan</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Saflığın Diyarı, Sasan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seijou no Chi Sazan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176760" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眷属器</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Household Vessel</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Birlik Taşıyıcı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kenzoku Utsuwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176761" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">商人シンドバッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sinbad the Trader</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Tüccar Sinbad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounin Sinbad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176762" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">居場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Place Where You Belong</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ait Olduğun Yer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ibasho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176763" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">王の資質</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Qualities of a King</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bir Kralın Özellikleri</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ou no Shishitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176764" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとつめの海</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İlk Deniz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitotsume no Umi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176765" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷宮バアル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dungeon Baal</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Baal Zindanı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meikyuu Baal</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176766" update="2016-04-06">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">船乗りシンドバッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sinbad the Sailor</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Denizci Sinbad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Funanori Sinbad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176767" update="2016-04-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Child of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Doğru Kader</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Ko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177061" update="2016-04-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177062" update="2016-04-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
