<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11696" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-01-21</startdate>
<enddate>2017-01-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kuroshitsuji: Book of the Atlantic</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Black Butler: Book of the Atlantic</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Black Butler the Movie: Book of Atlantic</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">黒執事 Book of the Atlantic</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10548" type="Prequel">Kuroshitsuji: Book of Murder</anime>
<anime id="6048" type="Other">Kuroshitsuji</anime>
<anime id="10402" type="Other">Kuroshitsuji: Book of Circus</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.kuroshitsuji-movie.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2459" type="Character Design">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="8740" type="Original Work">Toboso Yana</name>
<name id="4566" type="Direction">Abe Noriyuki</name>
<name id="2459" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="20907" type="Music">Mitsuda Yasunori</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch11141 [Ciel] is tasked with investigating the Aurora Society, who is rumored to be reviving the dead. http://anidb.net/ch11140 [Sebastian] discovers the society`s next meeting will be held aboard the ship Campania, on its maiden voyage across the Atlantic Ocean.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="244">7.54</permanent>
<temporary count="248">7.56</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224675.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18077</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31812</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kuroshitsuji-movie.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Black_Butler:_Book_of_the_Atlantic</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>黒執事_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355734</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19696</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kuroshitsuji2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20988</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07D5MKJ7K</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11140" type="main character in" update="2014-07-12">
<rating votes="267">8.08</rating>
<name>Sebastian Michaelis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sebastian appears to be a youthful male with red-orange eyes and dark brown hair (black in the anime). He is typically dressed in a distinguished outfit consisting of black trousers, tailcoat, vest, tie and shoes with a white botton-down shirt. He wears white gloves that cover up the sign of his Faustian contract with Ciel Phantomhive, which is on his left hand. When they are off, it is shown that he has black fingernails, although it is unknown if this is their natural colour. He frequently carries a pocket watch as well. When in tutor mode, he also wears glasses, although it`s unknown if he actually needs them or not. He slightly resembles Ciel`s father, and has had his attractiveness commented on before.
Sebastian`s demonic form has never fully been shown. Details including high-heeled boots, longer fingernails, slitted pupils and sharper, longer teeth are all that have been revealed. In the anime, he has the ability to transform into a crow, although this has never been said or implied in the manga.
Source: kuroshitsuji.wikia.com</description>
<picture>157980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11141" type="main character in" update="2017-12-31">
<rating votes="109">7.16</rating>
<name>Ciel Phantomhive</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ciel is a young male, whose age is from 12 to 13 throughout the series, with blue eyes and black hair. As the head of the noble Phantomhive family, he typically dresses in a way that suits his standing, including a long jacket, button-down shirt, tie, shorts, knee-high socks and boots. Occasionally, he carries other accessories such as a top hat, white or black gloves and a cane. He also has his ears pierced and frequently wears a one-of-a kind family ring that has been passed down through his family for generations. He nearly always wears an eye patch over his left eye, not because he is missing it, but because that`s where the sign of his Faustian contract with Sebastian Michaelis is hidden.
Occasionally, he wears other outfits, typically because he is undercover, investigating something at Queen Victoria`s request. These outfits have included a dress, when he invaded Aleister Chamber`s home, and pauper`s clothes, when he posed as a servant when joining the Noah`s Ark Circus.
Source: kuroshitsuji.wikia.com</description>
<picture>33143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11142" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="67">6.84</rating>
<name>Grelle Sutcliff</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grelle initially appears as a meek man with long, brown hair tied back with a red ribbon, yellow eyes and round glasses. He dresses in simple clothes to match his appearance.
However, it is later revealed that this is not his true appearance is that of a Shinigami. In his Shinigami form, he has long, red hair, yellow eyes, false eyelashes, razor-esque teeth and red-framed glasses with skulls dangling from chains on the frames. He also wears a suit including gloves and a tie, like the other Shinigami, high-heeled shoes, and a red coat, which he slings off his shoulders and wears around his elbows. Occasionally, his tie is replaced with a red-striped bow.
He seems to think highly of his appearance, as he is upset when Sebastian Michaelis attempts to hit him in the face, and he is distressed that he has to appear in his human form with the "out of vogue" brown hair and without make-up in front of others.
(from http://kuroshitsuji.wikia.com/wiki/Grelle_Sutcliffe)</description>
<picture>198168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11143" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="51">8.26</rating>
<name>Undertaker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Undertaker has long, grey hair with a few braids throughout, which is worn so as to hide his eyes. He has a noticeable scar across his face, although how he acquired it is unknown, and has long, black fingernails. He also wears all black, including an incredibly long, black top hat, and a he wears a long, grey scarf across his chest, with it knotted by his hips.
Source: kuroshitsuji.wikia.com</description>
<picture>198167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11228" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="10">5.28</rating>
<name>William T. Spears</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>William has short, neatly combed hair and wears rectangle-shaped glasses that have decorative lines on the sides of the frames. He dresses in a nice black suit, tie and dress shoes, similar to Ronald Knox and wears black gloves. When he infiltrates the Noah`s Ark Circus as Suit, he wears a white suit and spotted tie.
He almost always displays a near-frown on his face.
Source: kuroshitsuji.wikia.com</description>
<picture>63959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18402" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="28">5.44</rating>
<name>Baldroy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baldroy, usually referred to as Bard, is the household cook of American descent. Bard gruffly treats everything as though it`s a military exercise, often referring to troops, enemies, and weaponry when he goes off into one of his many long-winded speeches about what it truly means to appreciate the culinary arts. He rarely produces anything edible as he uses weaponry such as a series of flamethrowers, each more extravagant than the last to cook and believes cooking is an art requiring explosions. Sebastian believes anything he creates is made up of charcoal and carcinogens. It`s unknown if the food he produces is actually edible.</description>
<picture>168999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="451" picture="17347.jpg">Touchi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18403" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="17">4.75</rating>
<name>Finnian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Finnian, often called Finny, is the Phantomhive household gardener. However, it seems every time he tends to the garden, it is killed through an accident caused by his clumsiness and overenthusiastic pruning or not noticing that the pesticide container is leaking. In fact, if left to his own devices, he`s stated that he`d like to make the garden into the shape of a giant robot.</description>
<picture>168997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18404" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-20">
<rating votes="40">6.94</rating>
<name>Mey Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maylene is a clumsy maid whose cracked glasses do nothing to improve her clumsiness. However, she refuses to purchase a new pair as they are the first thing Ciel bought for her. Sebastian believes her main problem is her intelligence and not her poor eyesight. She has a crush on Sebastian as blushes when ever she is in his presence and is even clumsier when Sebastian is watching. In the anime she fantasizes about being close to him in episode 1. She is rather superstitious but admits to having a soft spot for scary stories. Maylene used to be a sniper who did not use a scope, due to her sharp far-sighted vision caused by her ill-fitting glasses. She is also physically fit as she can use a sniper rifle like a hand gun and keeps hundreds loaded at once to decrease reload time. At the anime`s conclusion, it is unknown whether she is alive or dead, although it is noted she was breathing before she collapsed.</description>
<picture>168998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18407" type="appears in" update="2015-02-22">
<rating votes="18">6.76</rating>
<name>Angelina Durless</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madame Red, born Angelina Durless, is Ciel`s aunt. As her title suggests, she is known for her red appearance and clothing. Initially she hated her red hair, which she inherited from her father, until Ciel`s father stated he liked it. Angelina fell in love with him and became distraught when she found her sister was marrying him. Madame Red later married Baron Barnett, who treats her lovingly and gently, stating that he does not mind that she harbors feelings for another. She obtained a medical license against the wishes of her parents and practices at the Royal London Hospital. After a carriage accident in which her husband was killed, her womb and unborn child had to be removed. This causes her great strife as a doctor because she regularly performs abortions on prostitutes as they believe having a child is troublesome. She later kills her patients with Grelle Sutcliffe and the two become known as Jack the Ripper. However, she cannot kill Ciel as she holds him as dear as her own son and because of this, she is killed by Grelle.</description>
<picture>169084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18411" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-31">
<rating votes="48">5.44</rating>
<name>Elizabeth Midford</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elizabeth Midford is the daughter of Marchioness Frances Midford and is both Ciel`s cousin and fiancée. She is a very happy and upbeat girl. She has known Ciel for a long time and cares deeply for him, trying her best to see him smile again. Elizabeth would always tell Ciel to call her "Lizzy". She also loves cute things. Ciel sees her as an important friend and a girl that he needs to protect because he says that he does not want to lose anything important again. It has been shown a few times on how much Ciel cares for her, such as throwing himself in front of her to protect her from a bear in the manga, how he tried his best to save Elizabeth from Drocell, and also drying her tears after she broke his ring despite how upset he had been.</description>
<picture>198166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18412" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="13">4.09</rating>
<name>Aleister Chamber</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Viscount of Druitt, Lord Aleister Chamber, is a noble who is known for his taste in fine art, wine and food. He becoms a main suspect in the Jack the Ripper murder case. During the investigation, he is found kidnapping women and selling their body parts on the black market. He is later arrested by Scotland Yard, although he is suspected to have bribed his way out of prison when he is again seen in public. He graduated from medical school, but does not practice medicine. He relates anything he sees as beautiful to a woman, and is particularly infatuated with a mysterious girl he met at a ball, who was in fact Ciel in disguise. He was most probably based from Montague John Druitt who was suspected of being Jack the Ripper.</description>
<picture>49026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="22106" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-10-05">
<rating votes="3">3.90</rating>
<name>Ronald Knox</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ronald Knox is a Shinigami sent to work with William Spears as extra personnel.
Ronald appears to be a rather laid back, easy-going Shinigami, who apparently has problems with arriving on time. He seems interested in finding a way to accomplish his job quickly, as shown when he says he has never been one for overtime, and with ease, as shown when he wistfully tells William that Grell Sutcliff got to do an easier job. He also seems interested in partying, as he shares with William that he would like to finish a job quickly because he has a party to attend to afterward. His lackadaisical attitude seems to annoy William, but he does seem willing to work hard, as he states he will try his best. He also comes across as respectful, as he uses the senpai honorific when talking about Grell. He is also shown to be a ladies man, commenting he got his scythe legally modified by flirting with the receptionist.
Like the other Shinigami, Ronald has a death scythe used in his job. It has been modified to look like a lawnmower, which he states was done on the principle of avoiding overtime work.</description>
<picture>55939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65844" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-12">
<rating votes="3">7.36</rating>
<name>Snake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67237" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="7">6.09</rating>
<name>Charles Grey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67238" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="5">6.16</rating>
<name>Charles Phips</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87692" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<name>Edward Midford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37882" picture="173035.jpg">Yamashita Seiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87693" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<name>Francis Midford</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87694" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<name>Alexis Midford</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87695" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<name>Ryan Stoker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="179536" update="2017-01-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2017-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
