<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11734" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>39</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Diamond wa Kudakenai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Jojo`s Bizarre Adventure Part 4: Diamond is Unbreakable</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Diamond Is Not Crash</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Невероятните приключения на Джо-Джо: Вечен диамант</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">JJBADU</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">JJBA 2016</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">jojo4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">jojodk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">JoJo 2016</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ジョジョの奇妙な冒険 ダイヤモンドは砕けない</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Diamond Is Unbreakable</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">JoJo`s Bizarre Adventure: Diamond Is Unbreakable</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">JOJO 的奇妙冒險 不滅鑽石</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">JOJO的奇妙冒险 不灭钻石</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14173" type="Sequel">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Ougon no Kaze</anime>
<anime id="10835" type="Prequel">JoJo no Kimyou na Bouken: Stardust Crusaders (2015)</anime>
<anime id="13812" type="Side Story">Kishibe Rohan wa Ugokanai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="123101">It`s JoJo but starts really really weak so be aware of it. This doesn`t mean that it`s bad, it`s just weaker compared to previous seasons.
Many won`t give it a chance but tbh, the last episodes are of an amazing quality in terms of plot and the little twist makes it worth the time wasted on a weaker starting plot.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="422217">I loved Stardust Crusaders but this sequel feels more like a poorly written filler with Stands. There`s very little in terms of continuous plot or tension.
Some of the Stand fights are decent though, but not on the same level as Stardusts. Only for fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="740913">Highly recommended Duwang.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://jojo-animation.com/du/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2213" type="Character Design">Nishii Terumi</name>
<name id="2702" type="Series Composition">Kobayashi Yasuko</name>
<name id="981" type="Original Work">Araki Hirohiko</name>
<name id="16061" type="Direction">Tsuda Naokatsu</name>
<name id="2887" type="Animation Work">David Production</name>
<name id="6306" type="Music">Kanno Yuugo</name>
<name id="1477" type="Direction">Katou Toshiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>It is 1999 (10 years after http://anidb.net/ch81467 [Kuujou Joutarou] defeated http://anidb.net/ch75409 [DIO] in Egypt), and high schooler http://anidb.net/ch81463 [Higashikata Jousuke] (illegitimate son of http://anidb.net/ch1742 [Joseph Joestar]) lives in the small and peaceful town of Morioh, Japan.
The Arrow, manifesting latent Stand abilities, travels throughout Morioh; as Jousuke and his friends seek out the culprits of a series of homicides.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1233">8.52</permanent>
<temporary count="1243">7.98</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>226412.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17832</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31933</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://jojo-animation.com/du/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>JoJo's_Bizarre_Adventure:_Diamond_Is_Unbreakable</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ジョジョの奇妙な冒険_(テレビアニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4100</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354618</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19039</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=gagUdy3AY14</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Q3TiTxP0N5w</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=t3AHvHNpb18</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=sPtetc-7jx4</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=q1pOiJHpWd8</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=aV1YlhjpPsU</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=IZd3H6qC1Gc</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=S0XOsNhl1OM</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=cS4yXFTj9Mc</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=8XLSrPm_S6g</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=zKosVCNaskU</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=NAKf3GRqveo</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=NLZP_z2PxCw</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=ofoOFCP6TTY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5962" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>rural town</name>
<description>The rural town is one that is either isolated from what is considered "normal" society or it is so far away from the city centre that there are not a lot of buildings. Some rural towns do not have the technology of the city (and some want it that way), while others just seem to be behind the times. Most of these towns have some sort of farming culture or inn culture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1720" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="18">7.38</rating>
<name>Star Platinum</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the strongest stands in the JoJo universe; Star Platinum possesses super human senses, strength, stamina, accuracy and speed. It can see for great distances and at great magnifications. As an added bonus, it has a "Star Finger" attack in which it extends its finger to attack.
It is similar to Dio`s The World stand, and, it turns out, can likewise be used to stop time, but that ability is only revealed in Jotaro`s epic battle with Dio Brando when Dio was about to drop a lorry on him.
The Star card symbolises, above all, hope. This is very appropriate, since Jotaro is very much the young new hope of the series. Like other physically powerful stands, Star Platinum suffers from a narrow range of activity. It can only be active within a 2-3 metre radius from Jotaro.</description>
<picture>153555.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81463" type="main character in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="21">8.21</rating>
<name>Higashikata Jousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Higashikata Jousuke is the main protagonist of http://anidb.net/a11734 [Diamond Is Unbreakable].
Jousuke is a high school freshman residing in the town of Morioh. Part IV begins as Joutarou Kuujou searches for him on behalf of Joseph Joestar, Jousuke`s aging, absent father.</description>
<picture>63677.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81464" type="main character in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="20">2.83</rating>
<name>Hirose Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hirose Kouichi is a central character and ally featured primarily in Diamond Is Unbreakable.</description>
<picture>63678.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81465" type="main character in" update="2016-04-03">
<rating votes="10">6.17</rating>
<name>Nijimura Okuyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Okuyasu Nijimura (虹村 億泰 Nijimura Okuyasu) is a central character and core ally in Diamond Is Unbreakable.
Introduced as an antagonist, Okuyasu soon becomes Josuke Higashikata`s best friend.</description>
<picture>185171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81466" type="main character in" update="2016-04-03">
<rating votes="22">8.74</rating>
<name>Kishibe Rohan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rohan Kishibe (岸辺 露伴 Kishibe Rohan) is a character introduced in Diamond Is Unbreakable.
A successful professional mangaka, Rohan is often roped into paranormal events while conducting research for his latest manga.</description>
<picture>185172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81467" type="main character in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="23">8.99</rating>
<name>Kuujou Joutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuujou Joutarou is the protagonist of Stardust Crusaders. He appears prominently in Diamond Is Unbreakable, and is the nephew of Higashikata Jousuke despite being born first.</description>
<picture>185173.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82059" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-14">
<rating votes="6">4.57</rating>
<name>Hazamada Toshikazu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63792.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="18131" picture="223909.jpg">Shimowada Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82060" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-14">
<rating votes="7">2.53</rating>
<name>Kobayashi Tamami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63793.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82061" type="appears in" update="2016-05-14">
<rating votes="3">5.59</rating>
<name>Higashikata Tomoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63794.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82062" type="appears in" update="2016-05-14">
<rating votes="2">5.53</rating>
<name>Higashikata Ryouhei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63795.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="282" picture="223615.jpg">Houki Katsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82063" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-14">
<rating votes="6">4.17</rating>
<name>Katagiri Anjuuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63796.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82064" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-14">
<rating votes="6">8.24</rating>
<name>Nijimura Keichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63797.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82173" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-23">
<rating votes="24">4.04</rating>
<name>Yamagishi Yukako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63826.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82364" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-04">
<rating votes="11">6.82</rating>
<name>Tonio Trussardi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63852.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2248" picture="170362.jpg">Kawashima Tokuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82566" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-06-15">
<rating votes="5">6.85</rating>
<name>Joseph Joestar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63895.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82694" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-18">
<rating votes="5">3.22</rating>
<name>Otoishi Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Plays the guitar, his stand represents Red Hot Chilli Pepper.</description>
<picture>63915.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82912" type="appears in" update="2016-07-08">
<rating votes="2">1.97</rating>
<name>Shizuka Joestar</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63943.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2792" picture="26717.jpg">Kawata Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83420" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-05">
<rating votes="20">8.75</rating>
<name>Sugimoto Reimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64019.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="10951" picture="222825.jpg">Hara Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83421" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="11">5.11</rating>
<name>Yanguu Shigekiyo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>64020.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83680" type="main character in" update="2017-05-18">
<rating votes="25">8.97</rating>
<name>Kira Yoshikage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89368" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-18">
<rating votes="6">9.25</rating>
<name>Hazekura Mikitaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>It is unclear whether he is a space alien or a stand user. Claims to be 216 years old.</description>
<picture>202594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89369" type="appears in" update="2019-01-20">
<rating votes="2">2.80</rating>
<name>Kawajiri Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3198" picture="160468.jpg">Shimamura Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89370" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-18">
<rating votes="5">6.33</rating>
<name>Tsuji Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89371" type="appears in" update="2017-05-18">
<rating votes="2">5.53</rating>
<name>Arnold</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202597.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89372" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-18">
<rating votes="4">5.54</rating>
<name>Kira Yoshihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89373" type="appears in" update="2019-01-20">
<rating votes="3">8.68</rating>
<name>Kawajiri Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92153" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-05">
<rating votes="3">9.63</rating>
<name>Crazy Diamond</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch81463 [Josuke Higashikata`s] Crazy Diamond is a short range stand enhanced by physical might, super speed and the ability of repairing broken items.</description>
<picture>209306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92154" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-05">
<rating votes="2">7.48</rating>
<name>The Hand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch81465 [Okuyasu Nijimura`s] The Hand is a powerful short-range stand able to to erase anything it touches with its palm from the universe.</description>
<picture>209308.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92155" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-05">
<rating votes="3">7.81</rating>
<name>Echoes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Echoes is the stand of http://anidb.net/ch81464 [Koichi Hirose].</description>
<picture>209310.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98061" type="appears in" update="2018-09-19">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Heaven`s Door</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224107.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="100409" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-20">
<name>Kawajiri Kousaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kira Yoshikage after he assumed the identity and appearance of http://anidb.net/ch100416 [Kawajiri Kousaku] at the end of episode 24 by forcing http://anidb.net/ch89370 [Tsuji Aya] to use her Stand, Cinderella.</description>
<picture>229337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100416" type="appears in" update="2019-01-20">
<name>Kawajiri Kousaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229344.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="100752" type="appears in" update="2019-02-10">
<name>Killer Queen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230042.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="173951" update="2018-09-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第1弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1 (2:24)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 1 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176207" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虹村兄弟 その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nijimura Brothers, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nijimura Kyoudai: Sono 2</title>
<summary>In order to save Koichi, Josuke goes further into the Nijimura household. Suddenly, he`s attacked from many tiny beams of light. Josuke manages to dodge the attack, but it hits Okuyasu right in the face. Josuke tells Okuyasu that he`ll heal his wounds if he tells him what the identity of his brother`s Stand is. Okuyasu says he has no itention of telling him, and Josuke does something surprising...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702303</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176208" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虹村兄弟 その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nijimura Brothers, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nijimura Kyoudai: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Angelo`s Stand ability was brought forth by the mysterious bow and arrow, and apparently they`re also connected to DIO. After defeating Angelo, Jotaro thought that the danger had left the city, and tries to find the whereabouts of the bow and arrow. A few days later, Koichi is walking home with Josuke, and they pass a house that should be empty...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702301</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176209" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東方仗助! アンジェロに会う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Josuke Higashikata! Meets Angelo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Higashikata Jousuke! Angelo ni Au</title>
<summary>Josuke spots the terrible and violent villain Angelo`s Stand, and tells Jotaro about that incident. Jotaro figures it`s a Stand that can somehow enter people, so he warns Josuke to not eat or drink anything until he can get to him. Right when he`s told that, Josuke witnesses the Stand go into his mother, and then does the unthinkable.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702299</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176210" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空条承太郎! 東方仗助に会う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jotaro Kujo! Meets Josuke Higashikata</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuujou Joutarou! Higashikata Jousuke ni Au</title>
<summary>April 1999. Jotaro Kujo arrives to Morioh Town in search of someone named Higashikata, and ends up running into a young man surrounded by delinquents. Jotaro then finds out that his name is Josuke Higashikata, and was exactly the person he was looking for.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702297</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176281" update="2018-09-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第2弾(康一ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2 (Kouichi Ver.) (2:00)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 2 Dan (Kouichi Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176282" update="2018-09-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第2弾(承太郎ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2 (Joutarou Ver.) (2:00)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 2 Dan (Joutarou Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176283" update="2018-09-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第2弾(仗助ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2 (Jousuke Ver.) (2:00)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 2 Dan (Jousuke Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176802" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176803" update="2018-09-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176904" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">山岸由花子は恋をする その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukako Yamagishi Falls in Love, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamagishi Yukako wa Koi o Suru: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Koichi is asked out by another student in his grade named Yukako Yamagishi. At first, he couldn`t hide his joy from being asked out, but quickly has second thoughts when she suddenly loses her temper with him. The next day, she knitted him a sweater, made him lunch, and did other things for him that makes Koichi start to wonder about her. Yukako obssession worsens, and she does the unthinkable.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702311</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176905" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">間田敏和 (サーフィス)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toshikazu Hazamada (Show Off)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hazamada Toshikazu (Surface)</title>
<summary>Josuke and Koichi hear from Tamami that a high school student named Hazamada might also be a Stand user, so the two go to the school and investigate. Josuke checks inside Hazamada`s locker, and finds a strange wooden doll inside, but nothing else out of the ordinary. However, as Josuke is inspecting the doll, it suddenly turns into Josuke, and attacks him and Koichi...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702309</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176906" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">広瀬康一 (エコーズ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koichi Hirose (Reverb)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hirose Kouichi (Echoes)</title>
<summary>Riding his bike to school, Koichi accidentally runs over a bag that was in the road that had a cat inside. Koichi is instantly overwhelmed by what happend. Then suddenly, a man named Tamami Kobayashi appears. Despite it being an accident, he demands money from Koichi, saying that he`ll use it to bury the cat. Koichi can`t process what`s going on, but Tamami keeps pushing that he can`t just leave after what happened. Koichi is filled with guilt, and then suddenly, a giant lock pops out of his chest...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702307</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176907" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虹村兄弟 その3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nijimura Brothers, Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nijimura Kyoudai: Sono 3</title>
<summary>Josuke and Koichi defeat Keicho. They go further into the Nijimura house, in order to destroy the bow and arrow to make sure there will be no more victims. However, they end up hearing strange noises in the dark room they happen upon. As soon as Josuke tries to jump into the room, a monster-like hand grabs Koichi`s leg...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702305</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177564" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レッド・ホット・チリ・ペッパー その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chili Pepper, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Red Hot Chili Pepper: Sono 2</title>
<summary>In order to defeat Chili Pepper, who intends on killing Joseph Joestar, Josuke and the others head to the harbor. Jotaro believes that Chili Pepper will try to get to Joseph`s boat with something that requires a battery, so he leaves Josuke and Koichi at the harbor, telling them to attack the user if he shows himself. As Josuke is dealing with his conflicting feelings towards Joseph, the very confident user of Chili Pepper shows himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702319</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177565" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レッド・ホット・チリ・ペッパー その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chili Pepper, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Red Hot Chili Pepper: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Chili Pepper shows himself in front of Josuke. He seems to be more powerful than Jotaro, and is able to travel anywhere where electricity flows. Jotaro summons Josuke, Okuyasu, and Koichi and tells them that a certain someone is heading toward Morioh...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702317</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177566" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イタリア料理を食べに行こう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go Eat Some Italian Food</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Italia Ryouri o Tabe ni Ikou</title>
<summary>Josuke and Okuyasu visit a brand new Italian restaurant in Morioh. Rather than customers choosing items from a menu, the chef, Tonio, decides what the customer will eat after he looks at them. Tonio wants Okuyasu to feel better, and first, offers him water. Okuyasu is moved at how wonderful it tastes. He`s actually moved to tears at how delicious the water is, but then starts showing even weirder symptoms...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702315</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177567" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">山岸由花子は恋をする その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukako Yamagishi Falls in Love, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamagishi Yukako wa Koi o Suru: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Koichi can`t handle living in captivity any longer and tries to plan his escape. While talking to Yukako, Koichi finds out that there`s a payphone nearby, and has Reverb go find it. He tries to contact Josuke and Okuyasu, but Yukako already figured out what he was planning. Koichi loses hope. Yukako then goes to the phone to order some ingredients but then something unexpected happens...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702313</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178004" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「狩り[ハンティング]」に行こう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go Hunting!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Hunting" ni Ikou!</title>
<summary>Josuke suddenly gets invited to go hunting by Jotaro. The purpose of this hunting trip was to hunt down the rat that gained Stand abilities after Akira Otoishi shot it with the bow and arrow. As they trace the rat to a drainage canal, they see a clump of fourteen rat corpses fused together. They realize it`s probably the work of the rat that they`re after and follow it to a farm, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715143</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178005" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">漫画家のうちへ遊びに行こう その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go to the Manga Artist`s House, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mangaka no Uchi e Asobi ni Ikou: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Koichi suddenly arrives at Rohan`s house. Koichi carefully goes inside and finds Rohan drawing manga at an incredible speed. Apparently he can`t stop himself from drawing after reading about Koichi`s experiences. Rohan attempts to tear another page from Koichi by using Heaven`s Door, when someone unexpected shows up at his door...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715141</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178006" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">漫画家のうちへ遊びに行こう その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go to the Manga Artist`s House, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mangaka no Uchi e Asobi ni Ikou: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Koichi and Hazamada find out that the famous manga artist, Rohan Kishibe, who draws "Pink Dark Boy," lives in Morioh and they go to his house to get an autograph. Not only did Rohan promise them autographs, but invited them inside to see his work space, and the boys are thrilled. Though Koichi gradually becomes frightened when he sees just how far Rohan will go to achieve reality...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715139</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178007" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やばいものを拾ったっス!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Picked Up Something Crazy!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yabai Mono o Hirottassu!</title>
<summary>Josuke and the others successfully capture Akira Otoishi and safely retrieve the bow and arrow. Peace is back in Morioh, but Josuke still faces a big problem... He still can`t seem to get closer to his father he just met, Joseph. He agrees to let Joseph look upon his mother from a distance and they head toward his house, but Joseph accidentally gets onto the wrong bus. He manages to catch up to Joseph, but then Joseph tells him that there`s a Stand user nearby...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702321</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178643" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">山岸由花子はシンデレラに憧れる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukako Yamagishi Dreams of Cinderella</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamagishi Yukako wa Cinderella ni Akogareru</title>
<summary>Yukako, who was depressed because Koichi wouldn`t look her way, sees a mysterious shop one day called Salon Cinderella. Unlike other salons, apparently this was a salon that created faces to bring people fortune. The esthetician, Aya Tsuji, gives Yukako a face that allows her to encounter love. Yukako goes out and immediately runs into Koichi, and he seems different than usual. Yukako had never felt happier in her life, but the effects only lasted 30 minutes...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715151</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178644" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「重ちー」の収穫[ハーヴェスト] その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shigechi`s Harvest, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Shigechii" no Harvest: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Josuke and the others head to the bank with their lottery ticket, but the bank is suspicious if that ticket really belongs to them. Josuke insists that they bought the ticket, but they find out that someeone else`s name and phone number are written on the back of the ticket, and the bank clerk decides to call the number. Seeing that they can`t get out of this situation, Josuke takes action...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715149</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178645" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「重ちー」の収穫[ハーヴェスト] その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shigechi`s Harvest, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Shigechii" no Harvest: Sono 1</title>
<summary>As Josuke was worrying about not having any money, a tiny little Stand holding a 1-yen coin appeared in front of him. A surprised Josuke follows it and encounters a new Stand user name Shigekiyo Yangyu (Shigechi)! Josuke is moved by the fact that Shigechi uses his Stand, Harvest, to pick up all of the forgotten coins around the town and figures out an even better idea using Harvest...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715147</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178646" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">岸辺露伴の冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rohan Kishibe`s Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kishibe Rohan no Bouken</title>
<summary>Koichi and Rohan discover a bizarre sight. Before them lies an alley that`s not listed on any map. They decide to go down the alley and find only empty houses that are also not listed on the map. While wandering they realize that no matter which way they turn, they keep ending back where they started. Rohan believes that they`re under a Stand`s attack, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715145</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179201" update="2019-11-20">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179382" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シアーハートアタック その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Attack, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sheer Heart Attack: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Koichi manages to survive because Reverb Act 3 made Heart Attack heavy, but then the murderer, Yoshikage Kira shows up! Feeling intense anger against the murderer, Koichi fights Kira with Act 3, but doesn`t stand a chance. Kira is infuriated by the fact that Koichi made a fool of him in public, and lets loose on him, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715159</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179383" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シアーハートアタック その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Attack, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sheer Heart Attack: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Jotaro and Koichi try to track down the owner of the button and run into the murderer, Yoshikage Kira and his Stand, Deadly Queen`s bomb, Heart Attack at Centipede Shoes. Koichi wants to go after Kira, but Jotaro tells him not to. However, Koichi isn`t satisfied with Jotaro`s decision and decides to act on his own, right when Heart Attack attacks again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715157</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179384" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吉良吉影は静かに暮らしたい その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoshikage Kira Just Wants to Live Quietly, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kira Yoshikage wa Shizuka ni Kurashitai: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Yoshikage Kira was the killer hiding in Morioh and is also a Stand user. Shigechi finds out this secret, so Kira tries to dispose of him, but Shigechi fights back with Harvest. However, because of Kira`s Stand, Deadly Queen, he suffers a mortal wound and loses. Shigechi manages to get away from Kira and tries to find Josuke so he can tell him about Kira and be fixed by Shining Diamond.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715155</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179385" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吉良吉影は静かに暮らしたい その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoshikage Kira Just Wants to Live Quietly, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kira Yoshikage wa Shizuka ni Kurashitai: Sono 1</title>
<summary>As Yoshikage walked through the town at lunchtime, declined the offer to eat lunch with his female coworkers, and heads to a bakery to buy lunch. While enjoying his lunch outdoors, Shigechi walks by and accidentally takes Kira`s sandwich bag by mistake, thinking it was his own. Realizing this, Kira quickly goes after Shigechi, because the contents of that bag definitely did not contain a sandwich...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715153</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179924" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャンケン小僧がやって来る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Janken Boy Is Coming!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Janken Kozou ga Yattekuru!</title>
<summary>Yoshihiro successfully steals the bow and arrow from Josuke and the others and is on the run to try to find other people to make into potential Stand users to protect his son, Yoshikage. He tells the arrow to choose someone, and shoots them. Meanwhile, Rohan was at Morioh Station taking pictures of various men going to work, trying to locate Yoshikage. He tells Joseph that he wants to find him before Kira tries to kill off his new family. Then suddenly, a boy walks up to him and challenges him to janken.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715163</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179925" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アトム・ハート・ファーザー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart Father</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atom Heart Father</title>
<summary>Josuke and the others head to the house that Yoshikage Kira used to live to try to find some clues on him. Kira had very few unique characteristics, but Jotaro comes to the conclusion that he hid all of his potential on purpose so he wouldn`t stand out. They also find jars of nail clippings as well as their data in the room. Josuke is rather creeped out by this. Suddenly, the hear the Polaroid camera on the desk suddenly take a picture...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715161</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180214" update="2019-01-19">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">猫は吉良吉影が好き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cats Love Yoshikage Kira</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neko wa Kira Yoshikage ga Suki</title>
<summary>Kawajiri hears from Shinobu that there is a British Blue cat in the basement with a hole in its neck. Kawajiri wonders if it was shot with the arrow, and goes down to check, however all he finds is a dead cat. Shinobu, frightened by the cat, started to swing around a broom frantically and knocks over a glass bottle. Some of the glass fragments pierced the cat, killing it. Kawajiri buries the cat in their yard, but the next day, a strange plant grew in the place where the cat was buried...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720843</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180215" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハイウェイ・スター その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Highway Go Go, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Highway Star: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Jotaro tries to track down the mysterious foot print Stand`s user. He manages to outrun the Stand with a motorcycle, and thinks to call Koichi and ask him to find the user by using Reverb. Meanwhile, the mysterious Stand keeps chasing Jotaro. Jotaro manages to get his hands on a cellphone and manages to call Koichi, but then he realizes that the ocean i right in front of him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720841</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180216" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハイウェイ・スター その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Highway Go Go, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Highway Star: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Rohan has a feeling that Josuke is cheating at cee-lo, and cuts off his own pinky. If he is unable to figure out Josuke`s trick in the next round, he says he will pay him 2 million yen to have him use Shining Diamond to fix his finger. But if Rohan does figure it out, he says he`ll take Josuke`s pinky instead. He even calls Tamami to act as a mediator, having him use his Stand ability so Josuke can`t play fairly the next round, either.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720839</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180217" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくは宇宙人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m an Alien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku wa Uchuujin</title>
<summary>Kira had been living as Kosaku Kawajiri ever since he stole his face, but he starts to realize just how hard it is to live controlling his urge to kill. Kira sees a woman pass by and he wants to show her his true self and strangle her slender neck. He tries to hold in his urges, but when he sees Shinobu`s neck, and loses control... Meanwhile, Josuke and Okuyasu encounter a strange person in the middle of a crop circle...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720837</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180868" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">7月15日(木) その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">July 15th (Thurs), Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">7-gatsu 15-nichi (Moku): Sono 2</title>
<summary>In order to get estimates for the fire damage and restoration costs to Rohan`s house, the architect, Masazo Kinoto comes by. Rohan invites him into his house, but Rohan can`t help but wonder about Kinoto`s odd obsession... Meanwhile, in order to save Mikitaka, who was trapped inside the pylon, Josuke fights Kanedaichi one more time. But Kanedaichi knows everything about the pylon, and has no problem dodging all of Josuke`s attacks...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720847</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180869" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">7月15日(木) その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">July 15th (Thurs), Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">7-gatsu 15-nichi (Moku): Sono 1</title>
<summary>Yoshihiro looks for his missing son, Yoshikage Kira, when he spots Kosaku Kawajiri. He is convinced that he is his son, Yoshikage, and tries to get close, but the he spots Hayato taking video of him. Seeing that Rohan and Jotaro are also looking for Yoshikage, Yoshihiro fears that they`ll find him, so he takes action. Meanwhile, Josuke and Okuyasu are walking to school and find a pair of binoculars on the road, which happens to be Mikitaka. He asks them to look up at an unused pylon through the binoculars and they find a man living up there!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720845</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181583" update="2016-12-07">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アナザーワン バイツァ・ダスト その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bites the Dust, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Another One Bites the Dust: Sono 2</title>
<summary>After blowing up Rohan Kishibe with Deadly Queen`s third ability, Bites the Dust, Hayato is told by Kira as to what happened and returns to the same morning. He then thinks that the only people who could defeat Kira are people with abilities like Rohan, and tries to tell Rohan about Kira without getting him killed. However, Rohan blows up, even without meeting Hayato. Hayato is distraught, thinking that there`s no one else who can defeat Kira when he runs into...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720855</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181584" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アナザーワン バイツァ・ダスト その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bites the Dust, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Another One Bites the Dust: Sono 1</title>
<summary>After being cornered, Kosaku Kawajiri gets rid of Hayato. Though he made it look like an accident, Rohan and the others have spotted Hayato, and were coming to the Kawajiri household the next day to ask him some questions. At this rate, he`s going to be found out and caught... Kawajiri fell into despair when suddenly, Yoshihiro`s arrow suddenly stabs him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720853</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181585" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">7月15日(木) その4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">July 15th (Thurs), Part 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">7-gatsu 15-nichi (Moku): Sono 4</title>
<summary>At his wit`s end with Cheap Trap, Rohan calls Koichi over to his house and asks him for help. Rohan does everything in his power not to show Koichi the Stand that`s on his back, which just makes Koichi believe that he`s just playing a trick on him, and Koichi leaves. Enraged by Cheap Trap, Rohan decides to finally leave his house and head for the Morioh Grand Hotel. However, the danger of having someone see his back is almost too much for him to bear...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720851</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181586" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">7月15日(木) その3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">July 15th (Thurs), Part 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">7-gatsu 15-nichi (Moku): Sono 3</title>
<summary>Rohan ends up looking at Masazo Kinoto`s back, and becomes possessed by the Stand Cheap Trap. Because any attack on Cheap Trap would just come back to Rohan, he can`t attack it, which puts him into a dilemma. Meanwhile, Josuke and Fungami are looking for Koichi when are approached by a young man who has a Stand who can trap anyone inside pieces of paper. He pulls out a piece of paper from his pocket, which happens to have something hidden inside...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720849</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182550" update="2017-01-09">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら杜王町-黄金の心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Morioh: The Heart of Gold</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Moriou-chou: Ougon no Kokoro</title>
<summary>Josuke and the others finally corner Kira. Jotaro also arrives but Kira uses Bites the Dust on a paramedic who came to help and tries to blow away time gain. He tells the woman his true identity, causing Bites the Dust to activate. The final battle in Morioh is finally reaching its end!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720861</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182551" update="2016-12-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クレージー・D[ダイヤモンド]は砕けない その2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining D (Diamond) Is Unbreakable, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Crazy D (Diamond) wa Kudakenai: Sono 2</title>
<summary>Josuke and Hayato try to force Deadly Queen and Stray Cat into close-quarters combat by going into a nearby house. However, air bullets start to show up in the house. Josuke tries to dodge them by throwing around ash from an ashtray so he can see where they are going, but for some reasons, the air bullets keep chasing after Josuke. There`s no way that Kira should be able to see them from the outside, so Josuke and Hayato start panicking...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720859</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182552" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クレージー・D[ダイヤモンド]は砕けない その1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining D (Diamond) Is Unbreakable, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Crazy D (Diamond) wa Kudakenai: Sono 1</title>
<summary>Hayato`s plan to kill Kira with Stray Cat`s air bullets failed. Kira realizes that Hayato has repeated the same morning numerous times, and realizes that it`s becoming dangerous for Hayato to repeat the same morning any longer, and considers undoing Bites the Dust. Kira truly believed that fate was on his side, and then he showed up...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720857</identifier>
<identifier>jojos-bizarre-adventure</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189476" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189477" update="2018-09-07">
<epno type="3">C15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189478" update="2018-09-07">
<epno type="3">C14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189479" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189480" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189481" update="2019-11-20">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189482" update="2019-11-20">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189483" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189484" update="2019-11-20">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 4a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189485" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189486" update="2019-11-20">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189487" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206320" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">CM (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206321" update="2018-09-07">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">最終回直前 ジャンプフェスタ2017 スペシャルPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Episode Jump Festa 2017 Special PV (1:31)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saishuukai Chokuzen Jump Festa 2017 Special PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206322" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Vol. 1 CM 1 (CM 1; 0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206323" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM第2弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Vol. 1 CM 2 (CM 2; 0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM Dai 2 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206324" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM第3弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Vol. 2 CM (CM 3; 0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM Dai 3 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206325" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM第4弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Vol. 3 CM (CM 4; 0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM Dai 4 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206326" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM第5弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Vol. 4 CM (CM 5; 0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM Dai 5 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206327" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM第6弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Vol. 5 CM (CM 6; 0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM Dai 6 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206328" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM第8弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Vol. 6 CM (CM 8; 0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM Dai 8 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206329" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM第9弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Vol. 7 CM (CM 9; 0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM Dai 9 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206330" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD Sales Hit CM (0:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="206331" update="2018-09-06">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM第7弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">BD&amp;DVD + Special Event CM (CM 7; 0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blu-ray &amp; DVD CM Dai 7 Dan</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
