<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11795" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-01-25</startdate>
<enddate>2007-01-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Happiness! De:Lucks: Watarase Jun no Karei Naru Ichinichi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">はぴねす! でらっくす 渡良瀬準の華麗なる一日</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">はぴねす! でらっくす 渡良瀬 準の華麗なる1日</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Happiness! Jun Watarase`s Magnificent Day</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4594" type="Parent Story">Happiness!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4003" approval="2" total="3">Otome wa Boku ni Koishiteru</anime>
</similaranime>
<description>By mixing several different magic spells, http://anidb.net/ch1149 [Watarase Jun] is turned into an actual girl and starts to experience an unusual spike in popularity from the guys at school. Due to Jun`s transformation, she has more charm than any other normal girl has, which makes all the boys lose their senses and they start chasing after Jun asking for a kiss.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Bundled with the limited edition of the PS2 game Happiness! De:Lucks.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="108">3.50</permanent>
<temporary count="108">5.68</temporary>
<review count="1">7.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>179975.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1902</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>362</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1149" type="main character in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="19">6.02</rating>
<name>Watarase Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite his feminine appearance, he is in fact an androgynous okama boy who crossdresses like a girl. He himself says he does this because the female school uniform suits him better and does make him popular among male students. Also, he has the desire to date Yuuma himself, but Yuuma being entirely heterosexual strongly refuses. He often says or does things that would be seen as ironic, such as saying how perverted men are, when he himself is male. Jun`s signature attack, the Patriot Missile Kick, is a flying side kick, normally used as a means to keep Hachi under control.</description>
<picture>2889.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="243" picture="17061.jpg">Yuimoto Michiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5727" type="main character in" update="2016-08-01">
<rating votes="6">3.95</rating>
<name>Kohinata Yuuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main protagonist in the story. He has a nice, helping personality and is not afraid to help girls in need. His two close friends are Takamizo Hachisuke, and Watarase Jun, who seems to have a crush on him. When he was younger he was able to do some magic in order to help Haruhi who was being bullied, but now he professes that he cannot use magic (though in reality he still can). Additionally, he seems to be put off by the notion of using magic whatsoever, even if it is able to help people. Eventually, he realizes that magic can bring happiness if used in the right way and transfers to the magic section.
In the end, he learned that his real mother is Minagi Suzuri (a teacher in the magic section). He is actually one of a kind and one of the most powerful and quickest of learners when it comes to magic, although he doesn`t use it because of a few accidents when he was younger and because his mother taught him not to use magic since he was young.</description>
<picture>22735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5728" type="main character in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="8">4.74</rating>
<name>Kamisaka Haruhi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main heroine in the story. She is a mage in training and is seen as very skilled amongst her peers, who have been known to think of her as a genius when it comes to using magic. When she was younger, Yuuma was able to use some magic in order to help her from some bullies which made her want to become a mage herself. She harbours feelings for Kohinata Yuuma.</description>
<picture>22736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1666" picture="54036.jpg">Sakakibara Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5729" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="9">4.01</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Anri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruhi`s close friend and also her a fellow mage in training. She tends to have a very strong-willed type of personality which she uses to try to get the things she wants. It can also make her reckless when it comes to her using magic, due to her being overconfident and under skilled compared to Haruhi.</description>
<picture>22737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1920" picture="21113.jpg">Naruse Mia</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5730" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="6">8.50</rating>
<name>Takamine Koyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend of Haruhi and Anri who is one year above them and is also in the magic section.</description>
<picture>22738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="459" picture="45036.jpg">Hinata Yura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5731" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="8">3.59</rating>
<name>Shikimori Ibuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young girl and powerful mage who transfers into Sumomo`s class. Most of the time, she is very standoffish and will push people away from her either figuratively or literally, so as to be left alone. Her family is known for being well-advanced in terms of magic, and even at such a young age Ibuki has shown herself to be well skilled as she uses her magic wand named Bisaim which takes the form of an umbrella.</description>
<picture>22740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2204" picture="23065.jpg">Ichimura Oma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5732" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="8">3.39</rating>
<name>Kohinata Sumomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuma`s younger sister who seems to have an energetic personality. She has known Haruhi since childhood and they used to play together. Due to family circumstances, Sumomo didn`t become Yuuma`s sister until after she had entered elementary school. She has amazing skills in cooking.</description>
<picture>22739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1671" picture="19766.jpg">Gotou Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5733" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="5">4.13</rating>
<name>Kamijou Saya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young girl who transfers into Yuuma`s class along with her twin brother Shinya, who is also a mage. She was initially mistaken for a ghost by Hachisuke after he met up with her one night by chance at school.</description>
<picture>22741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5734" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="4">4.71</rating>
<name>Kamijou Shinya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The twin brother of Kamijou Saya. His family has served Shikimori for every generations. He has a wooden, katana-like magic wand though the name is unknown. One of his defining traits is that he has a horrible sense of direction where he even gets lost walking to school with his sister as they manage to get separated constantly. However, if Saya is in any danger, he instantly knows where she is and runs to her in seconds.</description>
<picture>22742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5735" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-24">
<rating votes="3">4.25</rating>
<name>Takamizo Hachisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Otherwise known simply as Hachi, is one of Yuuma`s close friends and hangs out with him and Watarase Jun constantly. He seems to be desperate for any affection from girls, as the closest chance he has at getting a girl is with his friend Jun, who, despite his feminine appearance, is in fact male. He is often very perverted as well.</description>
<picture>22743.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2880" picture="23064.jpg">Kawamura Takuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77701" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="2">5.01</rating>
<name>Kohinata Otoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Otoha is the unorthodox mother of Yuuma and Sumomo. She runs the school cafeteria called Oasis. Otoha often does not act her age, but rather she acts closer to her daughter`s age. She is close friends with Minagi Suzuri. This is why Suzuri entrusts her to take care of Yuuma.</description>
<picture>178309.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10025" picture="37214.jpg">Hoshino Chizuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77702" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-26">
<rating votes="4">9.48</rating>
<name>Minagi Suzuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the biological mother of Kohinata Yuuma. She is a teacher in the magical section. She was forced to entrust her son, Yuuma, to her close friend, Otoha, because of many tragic things that had happened. She erased Yuma`s memory of her before going separate ways. She revealed the whole story to Haruhi and Anri of what had happened in the past.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>178310.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="461" picture="188441.jpg">Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81921" type="appears in" update="2016-04-29">
<name>Kuroki-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>186238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13802" picture="65373.jpg">Hasu Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="67108" update="2015-11-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
