<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11840" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-03-31</startdate>
<enddate>2017-06-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gin no Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ぎんのがーでぃあん</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Gümüş Koruyucu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">銀の墓守り[ガーディアン]</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Silver Guardian</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">은의 묘지기</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">银之守墓人</title>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="official">Yin Zhi Shoumuren</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13237" type="Sequel">Gin no Guardian II</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="725935">TLDR: If you have other things to "waste" your time on, then do that instead, otherwise you can give this a go.
---
IMO, the major problems with the show are:
- Plot Drops/Continuity
- Story pacing is too fast
- Cliff Hanger Ending

- I think this show could/should have been A LOT better if the episode length were normal, It feels like, they tried to jam 24 mins of content into 13 min episodes, as if they`re trying to tell the "hobbit+lotr" worth of content in ~160 mins. 
- The plot twists were entry level/weak, but fantastic and interesting at the same time. The storyscape/characters/abilities are interesting, but the 12eps was really just the "intro" into what seems like the main plot.
- Other thoughts: For some reason, it feels very similar to "Monster Strike", but with an interesting story (imo),  and "Phi Brian".</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="255705">Don`t waste your time with this. It is a mess. :&amp;lt;</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://ginno-guardian.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2463" type="Character Design">Tsubata Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="1732" type="Series Composition">Kimura Hidefumi</name>
<name id="6530" type="Series Composition">Ookura Masahiko</name>
<name id="6530" type="Direction">Ookura Masahiko</name>
<name id="2463" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tsubata Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="32762" type="Music">Seki Minako</name>
<name id="44379" type="Animation Work">Haoliners Huimeng Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>The protagonist, Riku Suigin is a pro-level gamer. The heroine, Riku Rei, knows of this and is the most beautiful girl in school and also loves video games. Suigin receives a device to play a net game called "Grave Buster" from Rei, but Rei is suddenly kidnapped. When Suigin puts his hand on the device, he`s sucked into the world of the game. And in that world, a battle between the tomb raiders and tomb protectors for the tomb of the mother goddess Bango`s tomb has been going on for 1000 years.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="392">2.30</permanent>
<temporary count="396">5.10</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>198776.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19661</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32936</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ginno-guardian.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yín_Zhī_Shǒu_Mù_Rén</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>銀の墓守り</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4557</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356171</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>銀之守墓人</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ginno_guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07KMMB657</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>http://v.qq.com/detail/c/co1rct64uxcugab.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6493" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manhua</name>
<description>The Chinese equivalent of the Japanese manga, produced in Mainland China, Hong Kong, and Taiwan.
See also http://anidb.net/t2798 [manga] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6690" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-07-12">
<name>Sino-Japanese co-production</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="88080" type="main character in" update="2017-03-05">
<name>Riku Suigin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88081" type="main character in" update="2017-03-05">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Riku Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4006" picture="25936.jpg">Saitou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88252" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-16">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Farin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40590" picture="159151.jpg">Nishida Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88253" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-16">
<rating votes="1">6.53</rating>
<name>Phoebe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88254" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-30">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Twin Star</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88850" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-16">
<name>Wanchoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44509" picture="237813.jpg">Matsumoto Sara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88851" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-16">
<name>Ran Shou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11275" picture="65394.jpg">Suzuki Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88852" type="appears in" update="2017-04-16">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Elu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88853" type="appears in" update="2017-04-16">
<name>Ring</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88854" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-16">
<name>Riku Yuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89355" type="appears in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Bashida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89356" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Eeyuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89357" type="appears in" update="2017-05-16">
<rating votes="2">4.91</rating>
<name>Shostia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1876" picture="66007.jpg">Asakura Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89358" type="appears in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Shirikon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2501" picture="191381.jpg">Yoshikai Kiyohito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89359" type="appears in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Koshiriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89360" type="appears in" update="2017-05-16">
<rating votes="1">2.80</rating>
<name>Collector</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202529.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89361" type="appears in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Temujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6854" picture="216700.jpg">Tani Atsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89362" type="appears in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Wild Wolf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202531.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89363" type="appears in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Dark Tiger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202532.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105179" type="appears in" update="2019-08-25">
<name>Gwin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237677.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105180" type="appears in" update="2019-08-25">
<name>Ray</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4006" picture="25936.jpg">Saitou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105181" type="appears in" update="2019-08-27">
<name>Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105199" type="appears in" update="2019-08-26">
<name>God Grave Tech Company</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>237700.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105209" type="appears in" update="2019-08-27">
<name>Collector</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50468" picture="226248.jpg">Fukuhara Katsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105225" type="appears in" update="2019-08-29">
<name>Shin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105226" type="appears in" update="2019-08-29">
<name>Wei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237815.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105227" type="appears in" update="2019-08-30">
<name>Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105228" type="appears in" update="2019-08-30">
<name>Mikan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44509" picture="237813.jpg">Matsumoto Sara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105229" type="appears in" update="2019-08-30">
<name>Lao Long</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4688" picture="29259.jpg">Hirota Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105230" type="appears in" update="2019-08-30">
<name>Mammoth Viking</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5576" picture="224283.jpg">Sasaki Hiroo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105231" type="appears in" update="2019-08-30">
<name>Ruo Long</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105232" type="appears in" update="2019-08-30">
<name>Dragon</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237845.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105247" type="appears in" update="2019-08-31">
<name>Gold Hunters</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An in-game tomb raider group, led by http://anidb.net/character/89362 [Wild Wolf], that tricks newbies to steal their money, forcibly logging them out of the game Grave Buster.</description>
<picture>237871.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105248" type="appears in" update="2019-08-31">
<name>Totems</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Organization within the game Grave Buster that gathers ability users. They are interested in http://anidb.net/character/88080 [Suigin] and http://anidb.net/character/88081 [Rei].</description>
</character>
<character id="105249" type="appears in" update="2019-08-31">
<name>Precious</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="186169" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 敗北を喫する!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Receives a Loss!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin connaît la défaite !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Haiboku o Kissuru!</title>
<summary>On the last day of services for “Dungeon Century,” many of the players had gathered online to enjoy some last-minute festivities. Riku Rei waits for Suigin to arrive, but ends up going to find the flower herself because he’s taking so long. Suigin ends up late to meet up with her because of his job, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>735029</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186170" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 終末を憂える!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Regrets the End!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin est triste que ça s`arrête !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Shuumatsu o Ureeru!</title>
<summary>Suigin finds out that his only way of interacting with Riku Rei was about to end. The game, “Dungeon Century,” was about to end all of its services. Suigin ends up in utter shock. However, in the game, Suigin promises Riku Rei to do everything he can to find the flower she is looking for in the game. As “Dungeon Century” is about to come to an end, the same company announces that Riku Rei’s father, Riku Yuuki’s new game, “Grave Buster” will start its services soon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733279</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186171" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 陸怜と近づく!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Gets Closer to Riku Rei!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin et Lei Riku se rapprochent !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Riku Rei to Chikazuku!</title>
<summary>The poor student, Suigin, spent most of his days working various part-time jobs, and his only skill was video games. Suigin then meets the Madonna of the school, Riku Rei, through an online game. However, since Suigin is playing the game for free, their correspondence is limited. However, they continue to play online together whenever they can, and their bond deepens.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733277</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186172" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 陸怜と出会う!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Meets Riku Rei!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin rencontre Lei Riku !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Riku Rei to Deau!</title>
<summary>The children of the wealthy go to Shinryou Private Academy. The most beautiful and popular girl at school, Riku Rei, can’t seem to hide her melancholy every night. One day, she encounters the protagonist of this story, Suigin, who is a poor boy with no family.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733275</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186598" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186599" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187017" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 最後の墓守りとなる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Becomes the Last Tomb Guardian!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin devient le dernier gardien de la tombe !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Saigo no Hakamori to Naru!</title>
<summary>Riku Yuuki explains the game of Grave Buster to Suigin. In the game of tomb raiding and tomb guarding that has gone on for years, Riku Yuuki ended up being the one and final guardian to guard the Goddess’s tomb. Suigin finds out that guarding the Goddess’s tomb is connected to protecting Riku Rei, as well, and tells Yuuki as he is fading away that he will become the last guardian.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733289</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187018" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 祖父と邂逅する!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin`s Chance Encounter with His Grandfather!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin rencontre son grand-père !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Sofu to Kaikou Suru!</title>
<summary>Suigin is pulled into the world of “Grave Buster” by a woman named Twin Star. Surprisingly, Suigin ends up meeting his grandfather, Riku Yuuki, who should’ve been dead, and he can’t hide his doubts about this whole situation. Then a woman named Shostia performs a ritual that reawakens Suigin’s childhood memories. Before they can enjoy their reunion, they are attacked by someone...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733287</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187019" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 陸怜に誓う!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Pledges Himself to Riku Rei!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin prête serment à Lei Riku !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Riku Rei ni Chikau!</title>
<summary>Riku Rei is taken by some debt collectors, and Suigin follows them. However, Riku Rei’s captors immediately get away by car. Suigin somehow manages to catch up on a bike, but she is then taken away by a mysterious man who magically disappears.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733285</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187020" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 遺産を相続する!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Inherits a Legacy!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin prend la succession !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Isan o Souzoku Suru!</title>
<summary>Riku Rei summons Suigin after her father, Riku Yuuki dies, and hands him something that Yuuki apparently left for him. Though he is hesitant, Suigin accepts the item, which happens to be a specialized console to play the new game “Grave Buster.” On the console, Riku Yuuki left Suigin a message and one billion in inheritance and tells him to protect Riku Rei.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733283</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187615" update="2017-08-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 新たなる旅立ち!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin`s New Journey!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin commence un nouveau voyage !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Aratanaru Tabidachi!</title>
<summary>Suigin takes Takeshi’s place and fights in the tournament. However, he ends up facing a penalty, and ends up having a difficult battle against his enemy. It’s then that Twin Star reveals their true form and powers, and the path to Suigin’s desired destination opens up...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733297</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187616" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, タケシと出会う!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Meets Takeshi!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin rencontre Takeshi !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Takeshi to Deau!</title>
<summary>Riku Rei undergoes a certain ritual and joins Temujin’s group. Meanwhile, Suigin encounters a young boy named Takeshi. Apparently he is travelling to get money to help his ailing friend, Mikan, who’s like his older sister. He ends up crashing a martial arts tournament and accidentally drags Suigin and Twin Star with him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733295</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187617" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 再び起つ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Stands Once Again!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin se relève une nouvelle fois !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Futatabi Tatsu!</title>
<summary>Temujin sees something special in Riku Rei, and gets her something special while he’s holding her captive. Meanwhile, A woman that has been single-handedly defeating tomb raiders has become the buzz of the town. That woman was another billion player, just like Suigin, and her name was the Collector.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733293</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187618" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水銀, 盗掘ゲームを学ぶ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suigin Learns to Play the Grave Robbing Game!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Suigin étudie les pilleurs de tombes !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suigin, Toukutsu Game o Manabu!</title>
<summary>Suigin receives a message from Temujin, the man who kidnapped Riku Rei, who tells him to come to Grave Buster. Suigin starts gathering information and tries to come up with a plan. Money is everything in the lawless world of Grave Buster. Suigin decides that he needs to hurry and save Riku Rei as soon as possible...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733291</identifier>
<identifier>the-silver-guardian</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188662" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Chinese Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188686" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Chinese Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188687" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Chinese Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188688" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Chinese Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188689" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Chinese Episode 6</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
