<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1184" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>8</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-05-12</startdate>
<enddate>1997-09-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Injuu Seisen: Twin Angels</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">淫獣聖戦XX</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">음수성전: 트윈 엔젤</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Injuu Seisen XX</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">淫獣聖戦 ツインエンジェル</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Twin Angels</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Δίδυμοι Άγγελοι</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1278" type="Prequel">Seijuuden: Twin Dolls</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="875" approval="2" total="2">Dragon Rider</anime>
<anime id="663" approval="2" total="2">Injuu Gakuen La Blue Girl</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://twinangels.rdy.jp/main.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1183" type="Unknown Relation">Daiei Eizou</name>
<name id="3063" type="Character Design">Rin Sin</name>
<name id="3110" type="Direction">Fukumoto Kan</name>
<name id="7648" type="Music">Takahama Teruo</name>
<name id="849" type="Work">Dandelion</name>
</creators>
<description>In 723 AD, eight celestial maidens ascended to bath in Lake Yogo, there http://anidb.net/ch102328 [one of those maidens] lost her raiment and was unable to return to heaven, thus she married a http://anidb.net/ch102329 [man] and gave birth to three children. The only male of those demigod children was adopted by the historical figure, http://anidb.net/ch102332 [Sugawara Koreyoshi], and thus became known as http://anidb.net/ch102335 [Sugawara Michizane]. Sugawara served the http://anidb.net/ch102326 [Heavenly Sovereign] well, but was ousted from the court by the schemes of his rival, http://anidb.net/ch102323 [Fujiwara Tokihira]. In exile, Sugiwara was poisoned by his rival, and but because he was a half-deity he became a powerful spirit, known as Tenjin-sama. Fujiwara Tokihira used the dark side of Teijin-sama becoming a power demon named http://anidb.net/ch102323 [Oniyasha Doui] the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch102408 [Demon Beasts]. However, the sisters of Sugawara were able to conceal the Demon Beast into the Demon World. In order to keep them trapped, the siblings formed an organization of the http://anidb.net/ch102338 [Tenjin Watchers].
A millennium later, the Demon Beasts have finally found a way to escape their prison and seek to recruit Sugawara`s heir, http://anidb.net/ch102342 [Onimaro] into their ranks and terminate the Tenjin Watchers. Alas, the head of the Tenjin Watchers, Amatsu Genshu is too old to protect Onimaro effectively, thus she trust the family`s heavenly raiment into the hands of her granddaughters, http://anidb.net/ch102304 [Ai] and http://anidb.net/ch102303 [Mai]. With the power of the raiment, the twins are able to transform into magical girls and slay the Demon Beasts with ease. However, the Demon Beasts are aware of their power, and thus use indirect approaches in order to defeat their enemies...
Note: In Japan, all 8 episodes were released as Injuu Seisen. Episodes 1-4 were released as numbered episodes of the Injuu Seisen arc. Episodes 5-8 were released as named episodes of Injuu Seisen XX[i] arc.
All the US releases of this title have been edited (Central Park Media/Anime 18`s original release as well as the DVD release by Nutech). The editing consists of the deletion of all the scenes that involved sexual situations (including nudity) with a young-looking character (Lord Onimaro). It should be noted that the R1 release of the prequel, http://anidb.net/a1278 [Seijuuden: Twin Dolls], by ADV`s Soft Cel Pictures, did not have any sexual scenes involving Onimaro deleted or otherwise edited.[/i]</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="275">3.33</permanent>
<temporary count="281">5.58</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>233020.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14161</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>968</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12061</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3569</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>405</identifier>
<identifier>ojkwwk</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2760</identifier>
<identifier>dsxlmd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://twinangels.rdy.jp/main.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="893" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>dominatrix</name>
<description>A dominatrix is a woman, typically a paid professional, who takes the dominant role in BDSM activities. A dominatrix may be of any sexual orientation, which does not necessarily limit the genders of her submissive partners. The role of a dominatrix may not even involve physical pain toward the submissive; her domination can be verbal, involving humiliating tasks, or servitude. The umbrella term for BDSM activities involving a dominatrix is female dominance, female domination, or simply femdom.
Source: Wikipedia.</description>
<picurl>230370.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2699" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>sixty-nine</name>
<description>At least one sex position from a group generically called sixty-nine or 69 is featured, characterised by a mutually inverted alignment of two people of any sex in which both perform oral sex simultaneously. Putting it another way, the top of the head of one person points more or less towards the feet of the other, and the head of each is at the height of the other`s genitals, and both perform cunnilingus or fellatio, whichever is appropriate in each case. The name stems from this mutual inversion, which resembles the numbers 6 and 9.</description>
<picurl>162104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2708" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>uncensored version available</name>
<description>There`s an uncensored version available of the porn anime this tag is added to, which in most cases means, that there was a region 1 DVD (R1 DVD = North America) release.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2717" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>anal</name>
<description>Sodomy, buggery, buttsex, cornholing, or the poop-chute polka. Call it whatever you like, but somebody is getting something stuck where the sun does not shine.</description>
<picurl>173755.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2720" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-04">
<name>bestiality</name>
<description>Is the practice of sex between humans and animals, or a preference or fixation on such practice.</description>
<picurl>161795.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2724" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-15">
<name>double penetration</name>
<description>Double penetration is a situation during which someone is simultaneously penetrated by two penises or strap-ons.</description>
<picurl>172771.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4318" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-28">
<name>plot with porn</name>
<description>Any adult-rated work where porn is not the only point to it. As in, it has a plot that is not merely an excuse for having sex on screen. Even better if the sex is actually plausibly worked into said plot or used for characterization.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="102303" type="main character in" update="2020-01-08">
<name>Amatsu Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amatsu Mai is the twin sister of Amatsu Ai.
She belongs to the "Samurai club", mastering anything from naginata to kodachi, but she also takes interest in baseball.
Her favorite color is red; which is highlighted in her transformation.
She is gentle and friendly soul but has a tendency to fall for pretty boys.</description>
<picture>232912.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102304" type="main character in" update="2019-05-18">
<name>Amatsu Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amatsu Ai is the twin sister of Amatsu Mai.
She practices archery and her favorite color is blue. She is far stricter than her sister.</description>
<picture>232860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8097" picture="170361.jpg">Kumagaya Niina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102321" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-20">
<name>Amatsu Genshuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232848.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102323" type="appears in" update="2019-04-22">
<name>Fujiwara Tokihira</name>
<gender>intersexual</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232849.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102340" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-23">
<name>Dekunobou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232862.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102342" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-21">
<name>Onimaro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102394" type="appears in" update="2019-04-21">
<name>Sugi Kotomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232922.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102396" type="appears in" update="2019-04-21">
<name>Arisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4962" picture="60945.jpg">Toyoshima Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102408" type="appears in" update="2019-04-22">
<name>Oni-juu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Oni-juu (lit. "the demon beasts") are the main enemies of the series.</description>
<picture>232954.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102409" type="appears in" update="2019-04-22">
<name>Oniyasha Douji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232946.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102428" type="appears in" update="2019-04-26">
<name>Daigo Utako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2362" picture="22137.jpg">Andou Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102496" type="appears in" update="2019-04-24">
<name>Matsukasaboshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233043.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102497" type="appears in" update="2019-04-24">
<name>Iijima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="102498" type="appears in" update="2019-05-05">
<name>Kama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102499" type="appears in" update="2019-05-05">
<name>Sakurai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102543" type="appears in" update="2019-04-26">
<name>Kurodama-Hoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurodama-Hoshi was "the most heinous sorcerer of the Carnal Underworld".</description>
<picture>233083.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102544" type="appears in" update="2019-04-26">
<name>Oniyasha Douji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233086.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102545" type="appears in" update="2019-05-05">
<name>Mayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233280.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102546" type="appears in" update="2019-05-05">
<name>Emi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233278.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102547" type="appears in" update="2019-05-05">
<name>Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233279.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="12878" update="2009-08-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">淫獣聖戦1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13675" update="2009-08-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">淫獣聖戦2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14609" update="2009-08-07">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">淫獣聖戦3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14610" update="2009-08-07">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">淫獣聖戦4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106116" update="2018-09-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">羽衣飛翔篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hagoromo Hishou Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106117" update="2018-09-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">姉妹奈落篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shimai Naraku Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106118" update="2018-09-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼畜都市篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kichiku Toshi Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106119" update="2018-09-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1997-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔王新生篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou Shinsei Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="205925" recap="true" update="2018-09-03">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>80</length>
<airdate>2002-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">淫獣聖戦: ツインエンジェル♥快楽大全</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Injuu Seisen: Twin Angels Kairaku Taizen</title>
<summary>Digest version of eps 1-2 of http://anidb.net/a1278 [Seijuuden: Twin Dolls] and eps 1-4 of Injuu Seisen.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="205926" recap="true" update="2018-09-03">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2002-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">淫獣聖戦XX: ツインエロス大全</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Injuu Seisen XX: Twin Eros Taizen</title>
<summary>Digest version of eps 5-8 of Injuu Seisen.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
