<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11848" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-07-05</startdate>
<enddate>2016-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">D.Gray-man Hallow</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ディー・グレイマン (2016)</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Akuma`nın Gri Çocuğu: Azizlerin Gecesi</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Сивият: Светията</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Сивият (2016)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">D.Gray-man HALLOW</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">D.Gray-man Hallow</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">驱魔少年 HALLOW</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4549" type="Prequel">D.Gray-man</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="243082">I put off watching this for so long as the first couple of episodes didn`t really grab me. Allen Walker was always what drew me to the original series, a tragic story that created a truly interesting character with the ability to see the shades of grey between the black and white driving a need to save both humans and the souls bound to Akuma. If you persevere Hallow advances Allen`s character and starts to unravel some of the mysteries left by the original series. 

Hallow also spends a decent amount of time on Kanda advancing his character and giving him some real depth. Well worth the watch but make no mistake, this is just a fillerless 13 part addition to the series. I truly hope they continue making the anime when the author has made enough material. Fleshing it out to 26 episodes wouldn`t have diluted it in my opinion.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://dgrayman-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1493" type="Original Work">Hoshino Katsura</name>
<name id="917" type="Animation Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="7583" type="Direction">Ashino Yoshiharu</name>
<name id="1766" type="Character Design">Kabashima Yousuke</name>
<name id="1766" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kabashima Yousuke</name>
<name id="2703" type="Music">Wada Kaoru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr1493 [Hoshino Katsura].
From the studio behind D.Gray-man comes the highly anticipated continuation to the popular series. http://anidb.net/ch7347 [Allen Walker] is an exorcist working for the Black Order whose mission is to protect mankind from the evil http://anidb.net/ch9471 [Millennium Earl] and his deadly Akuma. Allen and his comrades must recover lost Innocence while defending against the Earl`s terrifying army. But if they fail, Innocence will be lost forever.
Source: Crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="687">5.59</permanent>
<temporary count="697">6.85</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>188137.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18193</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32370</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/dgrayman/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tms-e.co.jp/search/introduction.php?pdt_no=536</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://dgrayman-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>D.Gray-man#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>D.Gray-man#.E7.AC.AC2.E4.BD.9C</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4213</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355170</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19231</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>dgrayman_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5863" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Weekly Shounen Jump</name>
<description>The Weekly Shounen Jump is a Japanese manga magazine released on a weekly basis. Its main target audience consists of young males and it features several manga titles. The magazine was created by http://anidb.net/cr780 [Shueisha] in July, 1968, and was originally only called Shounen Jump, because it was not published every week at the time. A number of very famous shounen manga were or are published in it, such as http://anidb.net/a386 [Hokuto no Ken], http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], http://anidb.net/a942 [City Hunter], http://anidb.net/a826 [Saint Seiya], http://anidb.net/a590 [Slam Dunk], http://anidb.net/a312 [Yuu Yuu Hakushou], http://anidb.net/a69 [One Piece], http://anidb.net/a239 [Naruto], http://anidb.net/a2369 [Bleach], http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], http://anidb.net/a3468 [Gintama], to name a few of the most well-known.</description>
<picurl>66685.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7367" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="15">4.23</rating>
<name>Bookman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Teacher of Lavi, Bookman Senior follows the same `code` as his apprentice, travelling to record history from a neutral standpoint. Uses the Equipmanet-type Innocence Heaven`s Compass, which is a scroll filled with needles that pierce enemies.</description>
<picture>189332.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9409" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<rating votes="28">7.56</rating>
<name>Cross Marian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cross Marian is an Exorcist and General of the religious organization, the Black Order. He is the master of Allen Walker, and one of the only people who knew of Mana Walker`s true intentions concerning the boy. He can be very demanding, disrespectful, and temperamental. However, despite his flaws, he shows that he does have a softer side, though it`s usually only seen with Allen or women, like Anita and Lenalee. The latter even managing to keep him from running away from The Order again.</description>
<picture>189341.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9471" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-10">
<rating votes="21">6.82</rating>
<name>Sennen Hakushaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Millenium Earl is the First Disciple of the http://anidb.net/ch10022 [Noah Family], and is truly named Adam. He is the story`s main antagonist.
The Earl resembles a grotesque caricature of a Victorian gentleman: a rotund figure in cape and top hat, with a perpetual enormous grin, a pair of pince-nez spectacles, and horns hidden under the hat. Despite his intentions he often displays a cheerful attitude, but is quick to reveal his more intimidating and malicious side. He is often seeing holding a small living being known as http://anidb.net/ch32940 [Lero] as a regular umbrella, but is also seen using it to summon Akuma.
He has a sword, nearly identical to http://anidb.net/ch7347 [Allen Walker]`s sword of exorcism which amazes him when the two briefly clash in Noah`s Ark. He distributes playing cards with the details of people he wants killed to his collaborators also containing Cell Roron who is the keeper of the list.
He has existed for 7000 years. He tricks people who mourn for their dead friends or relatives into resurrecting them, turning them into http://anidb.net/t6684 [Akuma], weapons that consume people`s bodies and follow all his orders. The only person known to have escaped this fate is a child name http://anidb.net/ch83367 [Allen Walker], who destroyed the Akuma of his guardian, http://anidb.net/ch32514 [Mana Walker], before it had a chance to take over his body. In the series` beginning, the Earl attempts to kill a young boy whose best friend was killed by his late mother`s Akuma, but is stopped by http://anidb.net/ch7347 [Allen]. Afterwards, the Earl orders his followers, the Noah Family, to kill all of the Generals of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order], an organization of exorcists opposing them. This starts another fight against his enemies, the Black Orders` supporting exorcists. Upon learning that one of them, http://anidb.net/ch7123 [Lenalee Lee], might have the Innocence known as the Heart that might give them victory to either side, the Earl traps a group of them into a dimension known as the Noah`s Ark. However, the Ark starts being destroyed, and the Earl escapes the area with Noah http://anidb.net/ch7370 [Tyki Mikk] who was about to be killed by the General http://anidb.net/ch9409 [Cross Marian].
Shortly afterwards, the Earl orders the Noah to send multiple http://anidb.net/ch32723 [Level 3 Akuma] to attack the Black Order`s http://anidb.net/ch32499 [Headquarters] and kill all exorcists. As the exorcists manage to defeat the invaders, the Earl reminisces about why he did not kill Allen in their first meeting and curses himself for it.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>71804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10022" type="appears in" update="2016-07-10">
<rating votes="10">7.38</rating>
<name>Noa no Ichizoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Noah Family consists of thirteen human descendants of Noah who have inherited his genes. A Noah can be identified by a gray skin tone, yellow/gold eyes, and a horizontal line of seven cross-shaped stigmata referred to as holy marks. Like http://anidb.net/t6684 [Akuma] creatures, they base their powers off dark matter, the opposite of Innocence, and as such are vulnerable to Innocence. The Noah share an inborn drive to kill Exorcists, but otherwise possess unique will and mindsets. "Carved" on their genes is a memory of Noah different from any member in their generation and possess a supernatural ability. They claim to be immortal, but this is proven to be an exaggeration after Yu Kanda kills the Noah Skin Bolic.</description>
<picture>30219.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32498" type="appears in" update="2011-05-22">
<rating votes="2">1.97</rating>
<name>Kuro no Kyoudan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Kuro no Kyoudan is a religious organization that works to defeat the Millennium Earl and his army of Akuma.</description>
<picture>71884.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32499" type="appears in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="3">7.89</rating>
<name>Honbu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The European Branch (or simply Headquarters), located in England, is one of the seven branches of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] and is the main branch, overseen by Branch Chief and Chief Officer http://anidb.net/ch7365 [Komui Lee] and his sister, Chief Assistant http://anidb.net/ch7123 [Lenalee Lee]. Recently, Lenalee was replaced as the Chief Assistant by http://anidb.net/ch83417 [Bridget Faye].
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>191031.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32500" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="2">5.68</rating>
<name>Asia Shibu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Ajia shibu, located in China, is one of the seven branches of the Black Order, overseen by Branch Chief Bak Chang and Chief Assistant Sammo Han Won.</description>
<picture>71886.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32501" type="appears in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Hokubei Honbu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The North American Branch, located in the United States, is one of the seven branches of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order], overseen by http://anidb.net/ch84693 [Renny Epstain].
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>191033.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32502" type="appears in" update="2011-05-20">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Central</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A facility located in the Vatican, Central acts as the liaison between His Holiness The Pope and the Black Order. Central is said to have ties with the Great Generals, though the extent of this relationship is unknown.</description>
<picture>71888.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="32722" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="5">1.91</rating>
<name>Akuma Level 4</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Level 4 is the most powerful and destructive Akuma known to the Exorcists so far, surpassing even the strength of the Noahs. Despite its immense strength, like all other levels of Akuma, the Level 4 still has to obey the Noah clan, though they no longer have to obey the Skulls, unlike the Level 3.</description>
<picture>189376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="44365" picture="180996.jpg">Kawashima Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32723" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="5">3.36</rating>
<name>Akuma Level 3</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>72254.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46388" picture="200800.jpg">Iwanaka Mutsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32790" type="appears in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Kie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kie is one of three surviving crew members of http://anidb.net/ch32776 [Anita]`s ship after it was attacked by http://anidb.net/t6684 [Akuma] at sea. He joined the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] as Finder afterwards.</description>
<picture>199411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34508" picture="211755.jpg">Tokuishi Katsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32795" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="3">2.01</rating>
<name>Malcolm C. Lvellie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Malcolm C. Lvellie is a high-ranking Inspector of of the Central Agency, a subsection of the Vatican that oversees the Black Order.</description>
<picture>189333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32938" type="appears in" update="2016-07-28">
<rating votes="8">6.55</rating>
<name>Rohfa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rohfa is a member of the Black Order`s Science Division in the Asian Branch.</description>
<picture>189317.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81263" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="4">3.93</rating>
<name>Alma Karma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alma Karma is a former Exorcist of http://anidb.net/ch32498 [the Black Order], a Second Exorcist, and the "First Womb" of the Third Exorcist Program.
Because of the shard of Dark Matter from the Akuma Egg that was placed into his body, he later became an Akuma before he fought and died from injuries sustained at the hands of his best friend and the incarnation of his previous incarnation`s lover, http://anidb.net/ch7366 [Kanda Yuu].
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17705" picture="188509.jpg">Asari Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81264" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-07">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Wisely Kamelot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wisely is the Fifth Disciple of the http://anidb.net/ch10022 [Noah Family], representing the "Wisdom" of Noah. Now inhabiting the body originally that of a homeless man, he is the most recently fully reborn Noah.
Beyond a long bandanna wrapped around his forehead, his most distinguishing characteristic is a series of eye-shaped emblems decorating his forehead, the largest of which he refers to as the "Demon Eye". Using this, he can peer into the hearts and minds of others; any who look into it fall under his influence, and should he wish, risk having their minds blown apart.
Among the Noah, he is the only one of those killed by http://anidb.net/ch84602 [the 14th] in his previous incarnation to still retain his old memories. Fairly laid-back, he is remarked by his siblings as being rather haplessly imprecise, and speaks in an old-fashioned form of Japanese.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>190974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82006" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Tewaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tewaku is a Third Exorcist, a human/Akuma hybrid. She is the younger sister of fellow Third Exorcist http://anidb.net/ch82008 [Madarao] and a former member of the European Branch of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] and http://anidb.net/ch84585 [CROW].</description>
<picture>190934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38248" picture="140190.jpg">Suegara Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82007" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Tokusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tokusa is a Third Exorcist, a human/Akuma hybrid. He is a former member of the European Branch of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] and http://anidb.net/ch84585 [CROW].</description>
<picture>190953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82008" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-07">
<rating votes="2">1.26</rating>
<name>Madarao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madarao is a Third Exorcist, a human/Akuma hybrid. He is the older brother of fellow Third Exorcist http://anidb.net/ch82006 [Tewaku] and a former member of the European Branch of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] and http://anidb.net/ch84585 [CROW].</description>
<picture>191000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82892" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Emilia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82893" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Timothy Hearst</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82913" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Sheril Kamelot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sheril Kamelot is the Fourth Disciple of the http://anidb.net/ch10022 [Noah Family], representing the "Desire" of Noah and is truly named Desires. He is the adoptive father of http://anidb.net/ch82914 [Road Kamelot] and the elder brother of http://anidb.net/ch84615 [Tyki Mikk].
His power seems to be a form of telekinesis, as he is seen crushing his target`s limbs without touching them, and manipulating the movements of the Science Department team. He is also seen to manipulate objects, as he did with the pipes that bound http://anidb.net/ch81263 [Alma Karma].
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>192684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82914" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-09">
<rating votes="4">2.68</rating>
<name>Road Kamelot</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34378" picture="127861.jpg">Kondou Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82915" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="2">7.28</rating>
<name>Miranda Lotto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miranda Lotto is a 25-year-old German woman whose clock caused time to rewind in her town after she unknowingly activated the Innocence inside it. She often feels inferior and useless, but with the help of http://anidb.net/ch7347 [Allen] and http://anidb.net/ch7123 [Lenalee], she became determined to be a useful Exorcist, and has become more self-confident and capable; she is still, however, a very nervous and jittery person.
Her Equipment-type anti-Akuma weapon, the Time Record, is located on her right arm. It allows her to stop or reverse time in an area for a short while, causing any object to revert to its original status; however, any damage the object suffered before and during the reversed time will affect the object once the technique is stopped. She is also unable to resurrect the dead, due to the fact that her Innocence cannot erase time.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>190938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83357" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Aleister Crowley Sansei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83358" type="appears in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Maosa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maosa is one of three surviving crew members of http://anidb.net/ch32776 [Anita]`s ship after it was attacked by http://anidb.net/t6684 [Akuma] at sea. He joined the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] as Finder afterwards.</description>
<picture>199412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44365" picture="180996.jpg">Kawashima Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83359" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Roufujin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189350.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83360" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="5">5.90</rating>
<name>Lenalee Lee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lenalee Lee is a 17-year-old Exorcist from Hong Kong and member of the European Branch of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order].
After a Level 4 Akuma attacks the HQ, and many people were injured or killed, her anti-Akuma weapon, The Dark Boots, changed from Equipment to Crystal-type weapon, taking the form of two blood-red anklets. These new boots are made up of Lenalee`s blood and will repair themselves as long as she has blood in her body.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>190932.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83363" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-07">
<rating votes="3">5.13</rating>
<name>Howard Link</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Howard Link is a subordinate of Central Inspector http://anidb.net/ch32795 [Malcolm C. Lvellie]. A former member of http://anidb.net/ch84585 [CROW], he was assigned to act as Allen Walker`s observer/guardian after Allen fell under suspicion for being connected to the Fourteenth Noah.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki</description>
<picture>190928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83364" type="appears in" update="2016-09-07">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Johnny Gill</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Johnny Gill is a member of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] and a scientist in the http://anidb.net/ch32499 [European Branch]`s Science Division. He is often identified by the black skull on his shirt and his big glasses.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="71" picture="171537.jpg">Ichiki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83365" type="appears in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="2">2.50</rating>
<name>Mana Walker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mana Walker is a traveling clown who adopted http://anidb.net/ch83367 [Allen] on Christmas Day. Over time, Allen formed a very strong bond with Mana, though had initially been annoyed with him. Eventually, Mana died of a carriage accident and Allen turned him into an http://anidb.net/t6684 [Akuma]. Mana sliced through Allen`s left eye, cursing him and marking it with a pentacle. He was quickly destroyed by Allen`s awakened anti-Akuma weapon, but not before his original self forced its way to the surface to tell Allen that he loved him.
He is allegedly the older brother of the http://anidb.net/ch84636 [14th Noah], http://anidb.net/ch84602 [Nea D. Campbell]. Mana also taught Allen the "notes" on the 14th`s music score. According to http://anidb.net/ch9409 [Cross], Mana began to lose his grip on reality by the time Allen was adopted, undermining Allen`s belief that Mana truly loved him, instead of loving the Noah that Allen possessed. His name was later revealed to be Mana D. Campbell, and he was actually a personality of the Millennium Earl himself subconsciously created to approach Allen.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>189347.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83366" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="3">4.66</rating>
<name>Komui Lee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2888" picture="200816.jpg">Inoue Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83367" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="2">4.99</rating>
<name>Allen Walker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83410" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<name>Noise Marie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83412" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Galmar-keibu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83413" type="appears in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Gigi Lujun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gigi Lujun is a member of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] and a scientist of the http://anidb.net/ch32499 [European Branch]`s Science Division.</description>
<picture>191044.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83414" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Timothy Hearst</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83415" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Inchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83416" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Tsukikami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83417" type="appears in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Bridget Faye</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bridget Faye is a member of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] and the Assistant Branch Head of the http://anidb.net/ch32499 [European Branch], under Branch Head and Chief Officer http://anidb.net/ch83366 [Komui Lee]. A former secretary from http://anidb.net/ch32502 [Central], she was transferred to the European Branch after it was moved to its new location and expanded with other Central personnel.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki</description>
<picture>191043.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36619" picture="134996.jpg">Nitta Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83418" type="appears in" update="2016-07-29">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Reever Wenhamm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84585" type="appears in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>CROW</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>CROW, the Central Office Battle Corps, is an elite group of humans from http://anidb.net/ch32502 [Central] who act as special enforcers. Though they are not endowed with Innocence, they possess unique skills and the ability to cast powerful spells to bind their enemies. Regular members of CROW are capable of temporarily hindering Akuma and preventing Exorcists from using their Innocence.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki</description>
<picture>190927.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84586" type="appears in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Kanda Yuu (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanda Yuu is one of two Second Exorcists successfully created during the Artificial Disciple Program carried out by the Chan and Epstein families nine years ago.
Kanda was originally an Accommodator and Exorcist of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order], but he was killed by an Akuma about thirty years before the start of the story. There was also a woman in his previous life whom he loved, a fellow Exorcist who died alongside him.
After their deaths, the bodies of Kanda and his lover were taken to http://anidb.net/ch32500 [Asian Branch], where their brains were harvested and implanted into new bodies as part of the Second Exorcist Program. About twenty years later, Kanda awoke in the Sixth Laboratory of the Asian Branch.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190931.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84587" type="appears in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Alma Karma (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alma Karma is one of two Second Exorcists successfully created during the Artificial Disciple Program carried out by the Chan and Epstein families nine years ago. Alma was an upbeat but emotional child and was good friends with http://anidb.net/ch84586 [Kanda Yuu], although Kanda was initially hostile towards him.
Upon learning that Kanda was to be "terminated" for regaining his memories, he knocked out the attendants and escaped with Kanda. He was able to truly bond with his Innocence in an attempt to save Kanda; however, he learns that as a Second Exorcists, he possesses the brain of an Exorcist killed in battle and his brain is that of the female Exorcist Kanda loved. After learning the truth about himself, he kills the scientists working on the project. He also attacks Kanda, hoping to die with him and end their suffering as Second Exorcists. However, Kanda refuses and cuts Alma to pieces. Alma is later sewn back together and kept barely alive somewhere in the North American branch of http://anidb.net/ch32498 [the Black Order]. http://anidb.net/ch32502 [The Central] uses him to house the shard of the Akuma egg recovered by http://anidb.net/ch32788 [Howard Link] and creates Third Exorcists from special cells produced by his body.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>190930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84596" type="appears in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Noise Marie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noise Marie has been with the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] for a long time. During http://anidb.net/ch7366 [Kanda]`s memory flashback to around nine years ago, Marie was seen at the http://anidb.net/ch32500 [Asian Branch] with blood stained bandages around his eyes, having received the injury that blinded him during a mission in which the entire rest of his team was killed.
Not long after, while on a mission, Marie sustained a serious head wound that left him in critical condition for over an hour in the field. http://anidb.net/ch32795 [Malcolm C. Lvellie] gave the order to make Marie part of the Second Exorcist Program, and Marie was taken to Laboratory 6 soon after.
While unconscious in the lab, Marie was found again by http://anidb.net/ch84586 [Kanda], who accidentally healed Marie when some of his blood fell into Marie`s head wound. Kanda then took the blind Marie with him, carrying him on his back as he crawled through a ventilation duct.
When Kanda found his friend, http://anidb.net/ch84587 [Alma Karma], and they began fighting, Kanda ran with Marie, but Alma lashed out at Marie and set him crashing through a wall. Both Kanda and Marie survived Alma`s slaughter of the staff of Laboratory 6, and both later became apprentices of General http://anidb.net/ch32784 [Froi Tiedoll].
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84602" type="appears in" update="2016-09-21">
<rating votes="2">6.30</rating>
<name>Nea D. Campbell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nea, often referred to as "The 14th", was the extra member of the http://anidb.net/ch10022 [Noah Family]. He was the only member, other than http://anidb.net/ch82914 [Road] and the http://anidb.net/ch9471 [Earl], who was able to control the Ark. Before the story`s timeline, he gave this power away to a human and ran, betraying the Earl and the Clan of Noah.
He attempted to kill the Earl in order to become the new Earl himself, but was killed in return by the Earl, an ending which greatly depressed the Earl.
Later, it was revealed that the 14th had chosen http://anidb.net/ch7347 [Allen Walker] as his next host. Some time before his death, he told http://anidb.net/ch9409 [Cross Marian] that if http://anidb.net/ch83365 [Mana] was looked after, he would return to him one day. He briefly appears in Allen`s mind to name himself "Nea", the Noah of Destruction. Soon after, Nea fully possesses Allen for brief moments and wonders about the current situation. It is also revealed that his name is Nea Campbell, not Walker as it is said by the Earl who calls his older brother, Mana D. Campbell rather than Nea Walker.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>190954.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84613" type="appears in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Kanda Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Male Exorcist of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] that appeared in http://anidb.net/ch7366 [Kanda Yuu]`s flashbacks.
He`s actually Kanda`s previous incarnation, who was killed by an Akuma about thirty years before the start of the story. There was also a woman in his previous life whom he loved, a fellow Exorcist who died alongside him.
After their deaths, the bodies of Kanda and his lover were taken to http://anidb.net/ch32500 [Asian Branch], where their brains were harvested and implanted into new bodies as part of the Second Exorcist Program. About twenty years later, http://anidb.net/ch84586 [Kanda] awoke in the Sixth Laboratory of the Asian Branch to his fellow Second Exorcist, http://anidb.net/ch84587 [Alma Karma], hovering over his birthing pit.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190967.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84614" type="appears in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Alma Karma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Female Exorcist of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] that appeared in http://anidb.net/ch7366 [Kanda Yuu]`s flashbacks.
She`s actually http://anidb.net/ch81263 [Alma Karma]`s previous incarnation, who was a female Exorcist who had died in battle. She and Kanda`s previous incarnation, http://anidb.net/ch84613 [another Exorcist], had been lovers.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190940.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84615" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-06">
<rating votes="2">6.30</rating>
<name>Tyki Mikk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tyki Mikk, as he appears in D.Gray-man Hallow.
Since his battle with http://anidb.net/ch7347 [Allen Walker] in Noah`s Ark and his subsequent transformation, Tyki`s complexion has become darker, even in his human form. His hair has grown past shoulder length and is now worn in a ponytail. His chest is marred with deep scar wounds that still ache from the battle in which he received them. As a Noah, an additional, large stigmata has appeared on his neck.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16886" picture="151720.jpg">Nishida Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84620" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-21">
<rating votes="6">8.30</rating>
<name>Kanda Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanda Yuu is an Exorcist and member of the http://anidb.net/ch32499 [European Branch] of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order], formerly of the http://anidb.net/ch32500 [Asian Branch].
He is a Second Exorcist, an Exorcist raised in a test tube and artificially modified to bear the Innocence of the previous Exorcist his brain formerly belonged to. He is also the second incarnation of the http://anidb.net/ch84613 [lover] of fellow Second Exorcist http://anidb.net/ch81263 [Alma Karma]`s http://anidb.net/ch84614 [former incarnation].
Mugen, his Equipment-type anti-Akuma weapon, is a sword with supernatural powers. The shape of the sword has changed throughout the story: during his childhood, it takes the form of a small butcher blade with multiple small wings on the hilt; upon Kanda`s introduction in the beginning of the series, it took the form of a chokuto with a black cross-emblazoned hilt and sheath; after his battle with http://anidb.net/ch9411 [Skin Boric], it was reforged into a traditional http://anidb.net/t1640 [katana].
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>190979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2328" picture="171565.jpg">Satou Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84637" type="main character in" update="2016-09-21">
<rating votes="6">6.70</rating>
<name>Allen Walker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Allen Walker is now a former Exorcist and a member of the http://anidb.net/ch32499 [European Branch] of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] which he is now seen and classified by them as a Noah, http://anidb.net/ch84636 [the 14th]. He is also currently the current host of the former Noah, http://anidb.net/ch84602 [Nea Walker]. He is the adoptive son of http://anidb.net/ch83365 [Mana Walker], the elder brother of Nea Walker. Allen was also the former apprentice of the Exorcist General, http://anidb.net/ch9409 [Cross Marian]. Allen has mostly been seen with http://anidb.net/ch32939 [Timcanpy] on his side.
The Crown Clown, his Parasitic-type anti-Akuma weapon, takes the form of a type of fur cape and a giant claw. Later on, it is able to additionally produce a large sword from Allen`s left arm, resembling the sword the http://anidb.net/ch9471 [Earl] uses. Shortly after his anti-Akuma weapon takes the form of the Crown Clown, his synchronization rate exceeded the percentage required for General level. When the Crown Clown was created, Allen claimed his right hand was for the human race and his left for the Akuma.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>190998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84694" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Renny Epstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Renny Epstain is a member of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] and the Chief of the http://anidb.net/ch32501 [North American Branch].
After the relocation of the http://anidb.net/ch32499 [Headquarters], Renny appears before Bak to deliver the news to http://anidb.net/ch83366 [Komui Lee] about a new type of Exorcist: members of http://anidb.net/ch84585 [CROW] that have been implanted with the Akuma cells of http://anidb.net/ch81263 [Alma Karma]. While talking to Komui, she explains that the half-Akuma are Third Exorcists and have stationed five of them of them at the Black Order, by the orders of the http://anidb.net/ch32502 [Central].
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>191034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9365" picture="34581.jpg">Kokuryuu Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84695" type="appears in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Renny Epstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In her younger days, Renny had worked as the assistant to her father on the Second Exorcist Project at the http://anidb.net/ch32500 [Asian Branch], 6th laboratory. Back then, her job mainly was to monitor http://anidb.net/ch84586 [Yu] and http://anidb.net/ch84587 [Alma], and to report on any abnormalities.
Later, along with her father and Twi Chang, she helped seal up Yu when he started to regain his old memories. When Alma went on a killing rampage, she was the only survivor of the massacre as Twi Chang helped her escape before being killed herself.
After the massacre and tragedy, she and Bak Chang sealed off the human experiments as taboos. However, in the recent times, she had a change of heart after the invasion of http://anidb.net/ch32720 [Lulu Bell] and attack of the Level 4 at the http://anidb.net/ch32499 [Headquarters], as she willingly headed the Third Exorcist project after receiving the Akuma egg fragment from http://anidb.net/ch32795 [Malcolm C. Lvellie].
Source: D.Gray-Man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>191037.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84696" type="appears in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Sahlins Epstain</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sahlins Epstain was the head of the Epstain Family and a member of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order,] where he served the http://anidb.net/ch32500 [Asian Branch] as the head of the Science Council. He, along with his daughter http://anidb.net/ch84695 [Renny Epstain], served as the representative of the Epstain Family`s efforts in the Second Exorcist Project, where he offered both his scientific prowess and his skills in his family`s magic.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>191038.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="84703" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Zuu Mei Chang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zuu Mei Chang is a metallurgist and anti-Akuma weapon manufacturer, as well as Head Chef of the http://anidb.net/ch32500 [Asian Branch] of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order]. He is Bak Chang`s great-uncle.
Zuu Mei was once the greatest sorcerer of the Chang family and worked at http://anidb.net/ch32502 [Central] as a powerful official, where http://anidb.net/ch32795 [Malcolm C. Lvellie] was one of his students. It was during his time at Central, when he was a darker, more power-hungry person who only cared about the status of the Chang Clan, that he proposed the basic idea of the Second Exorcist Project. He was the smith who forged http://anidb.net/ch84620 [Kanda]`s Mugen, and he also taught http://anidb.net/ch32507 [Jeryy] how to cook. During Kanda`s childhood, Zuu Mei was frequently his confidant, assuring Kanda that the lotus blooms he was seeing were only illusions.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>191039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84704" type="appears in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Twi Chang</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Twi Chang was a member of the Black Order and the former Head of http://anidb.net/ch32500 [Asian Branch] and Chang clan. She is Edgar Chang Martin`s wife, Bak Chang`s mother, and http://anidb.net/ch84703 [Zuu Mei Chang]`s niece, and was also the overseer of the Second Exorcist Project.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki</description>
<picture>191040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2015" picture="224313.jpg">Kouda Kaho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84705" type="appears in" update="2016-09-08">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Edgar Chang Martin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Edgar Chang Martin was the Assistant Chief of the http://anidb.net/ch32500 [Asia Branch] of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order], husband of http://anidb.net/ch84704 [Twi Chang], nephew of http://anidb.net/ch84703 [Zuu Mei Chang] and father of Bak Chang. He, like his wife, played a large role in the Second Exorcist Program until his death.
Source: D.Gray-man Wiki</description>
<picture>191041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2585" picture="22579.jpg">Tsuchida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84793" type="appears in" update="2016-09-15">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Cardinal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Unnamed Cardinal, who appeared amiable and friendly and was seen comforting http://anidb.net/ch84637 [Allen Walker]`s friends when they were harassed in the cafeteria by those who thought Allen should be executed. The Cardinal assured the group otherwise.</description>
<picture>191294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3337" picture="211147.jpg">Ogino Seirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84794" type="appears in" update="2016-09-21">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Apocryphos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Apocryphos is an autonomous, sentient Innocence that possesses a humanoid form. It is the guardian of the Heart, the central Innocence whose existence maintains the others. It also refers to itself as the "Grim Reaper of the Noah" because its body and powers are the polar opposite of those of the http://anidb.net/ch10022 [Noah].
Because it is the Heart`s guardian, the Noah have been searching for the Apocryphos for 7000 years because it is known to stay close to the Heart, the Noah`s target.
The Apocryphos can appear as a normal human being and is disguised as an unnamed http://anidb.net/ch84793 [Cardinal] of the Church visiting the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order]. It can assimilate other Innocence and use the Innocence to locate Exorcists. It also seems to possess telepathic abilities and can render people unconscious and erase their memories. Many of its abilities have a feather-like motif. It is also very quick and powerful and can easily outmaneuver http://anidb.net/ch84585 [CROW] member http://anidb.net/ch83363 [Howard Link] and Noah http://anidb.net/ch84615 [Tyki Mikk].
The Apocryphos seems to have murdered http://anidb.net/ch9409 [Cross Marian] with the General`s own anti-Akuma weapon and later attempts to assimilate http://anidb.net/ch84637 [Allen Walker]. However, Allen managed to escape.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>191296.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="85458" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="4">4.88</rating>
<name>Lavi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lavi is a cheerful 18-year-old red-haired Exorcist of mixed heritage. He aims to become a Bookman, a person who records the hidden history of the world, and has been trained from a young age to achieve that goal. He travels extensively with the http://anidb.net/ch7367 [Bookman Senior], archiving various instances of history from a supposedly non-interferative standpoint. He is later shown to possess heightened combat and intuitive skills, and extremely photographic memorization abilities.
Lavi is the 49th alias he assumed after casting away his real name to reach that goal. He works alongside the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] just to be close to the events that must be seen, but slowly becomes more attached to his friends in Black Order, and his original Bookman self is constantly being clouded by his growing care for them.
His Equipment-type anti-Akuma weapon, Iron Hammer, often referred to as "Big Hammer, Little Hammer", is capable of growing and extending to undefined sizes and lengths. The weapon allows him to use "Seals" that control several elements of nature.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>189342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85459" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="2">1.26</rating>
<name>Chaozii Han</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chaozii Han is an Exorcist and member of the http://anidb.net/ch32498 [Black Order] http://anidb.net/ch32499 [European Branch]. Before joining the Order, he worked for Black Order supporter http://anidb.net/ch32776 [Anita], along with his friends http://anidb.net/ch83358 [Maosa] and http://anidb.net/ch32790 [Kie], who also joined the Order as Finders after Anita died.
His Equipment-type anti-Akuma, the Arm of Baptism, grants him superhuman strength. It appears as a pair of gloves with buttons on each knuckle and cloth-like extensions at the wrists. When revoked, it takes the form of two linked bracelets on his left wrist.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>192682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4032" picture="77662.jpg">Okamoto Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="178080" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖戦ブラッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blood Crusade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seisen Blood</title>
<summary>North American Branch Chief Renny Epstain pays a visit to Komui to let him know that, by order of the Pope, she is activating the Black Order’s new fighting power, the Third Exorcists. Meanwhile, the last Noah member awakens.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="178081" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">顔を洗えば大丈夫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`ll Be Fine If I Wash My Face</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kao o Araeba Daijoubu</title>
<summary>While Allen, Kanda, and Marie are fighting Akuma inside Hearst Orphanage, Timothy awakens as a new Innocence Accommodator. Meanwhile, Reever and the others try to enter the building, but they are hindered by an enveloping barrier.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="178082" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロンリーボーイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lonely Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lonely Boy</title>
<summary>Allen and the others are sent to Paris to investigate Phantom Thief G, who is believed to have something to do with Innocence. Once there, they find the thief, whom they discover is also being sought by another party.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="178083" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">14番目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fourteenth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">14 Banme</title>
<summary>After collecting Innocence, Allen and the other Exorcists are headed to the Black Order’s new Headquarters, where Director Lvellie and Allen’s Master, Cross Marian, await Allen’s arrival.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="178573" update="2016-07-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178574" update="2016-07-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178972" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚醒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusei</title>
<summary>As Alma Karma finally wakes, the Alma cells that were implanted in the Third Exorcists start to go out of control. When the situation becomes desperate, the Millennium Earl makes Allen an offer.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="178973" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">徒花の真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth About a Sterile Flower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Adabana no Shinjitsu</title>
<summary>While in Kanda’s memories, Allen sees what the Black Order was doing to Kanda and Alma Karma in the name of the Second Exorcist Plan nine years ago, and how Kanda ended up killing Alma Karma.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="178974" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">friend</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Friend</title>
<summary>The Millennium Earl, along with some Noah members, pays a visit to the Black Order’s North American Branch where Alma Karma has been sleeping. In order to awaken him, Wisely uses Kanda’s brain, which ends up dragging Allen into his memories.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="178975" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルマ=カルマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alma Karma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alma Karma</title>
<summary>Some of the Black Order’s staff are brought into the North American Branch to observe Alma Karma, the parent body of the Third apostles. However, during the meeting, the branch is attacked and comes under the Noah clan’s control.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="179714" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">My Home</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Home</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">My Home</title>
<summary>Now that the Order considers Allen a Noah, Komui issues an order for Exorcists and CROWS to capture him. However, Lenalee believes that Allen won’t betray them and goes after him on her own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="179715" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">隠されたもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hidden One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakusareta Mono</title>
<summary>When the Cardinal attacks Link, Allen, still in a daze and fearing for Link`s life, instinctively uses his Innocence on the Cardinal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="179716" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望の罪人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sinner in Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zetsubou no Zainin</title>
<summary>Allen is confined for disobeying Director Lvellie’s orders. Since he does not eat anything as he’s afraid of the food possibly having truth serum in it, Link gets worried and brings some food for him. Then they receive a visitor in Allen’s cell.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="179717" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リトル・グッバイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Good-Bye</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Little Goodbye</title>
<summary>After the Hekiji barrier placed on the North American Branch is canceled, Allen sees the soul of Alma Karma, who became an Akuma, and learns why Alma has been trying to kill Kanda.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180178" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウォーカー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Walker</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Walker</title>
<summary>Three months after Allen`s desertion from the Order, some still believe in him and others harbor doubts. When Lenalee expresses disappointment at being unable to help Allen, Marie reassures her that their bond with him remains intact.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="181683" update="2016-11-06">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
