<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11851" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-07-01</startdate>
<enddate>2016-09-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Berserk</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Берсерк (2016)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="short">剑风传奇</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ベルセルク</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Berserk (2016)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Berserk (Saison 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Берсерк (2016)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12414" type="Sequel">Berserk (2017)</anime>
<anime id="7991" type="Prequel">Berserk: Ougon Jidai Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="707755">I`ve watched all the forms/versions previous so was really looking forward to watching this. It took a bit of getting used too seeing the different style of animation. 

Other than this, this was pretty good. Not quite what I expected but good to see a continuation of the story line rather than another rehash.

Looking forward to another. If you have seen the previous renditions then you`ll definitely want to see this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="142179">horrible 3d Animation, shameful, otherwise berserk is berserk even if the original is the best</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="726539">If you can get past the CGI its really good oh and  also ignore the hating snobs.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="672527">Nice berserk series with awesome action. Unlike many I don`t dislike CGI, however in this series the animation work can be pretty messy. I don`t know how closely it follows the manga, but there are so many frustratingly stupid and selfish people that I really don`t care about anyone, except guts (pfff casca is also so annoying).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="136978">This series is actually a sequel to the 2012-2013 movie trilogy, so it`s better to watch those movie before starting with Berserk (2016). Even if you`ve already watched the original series from the 90`s, there are some changes in the plot that can confuse you.
As for the series itself, I rather enjoyed it, because I didn`t have any prejudice.
I am not a big fan of CG in anime in general, but, as it was in the case of Ajin, I don`t mind that they use computer graphics, if the plot is good and the characters are interesting.
Besides we get excellent soundtrack composed by Sagisu Shirou (Evangelion) as a bonus.
I don`t see many reasons to complain.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="274570">Despite the shitty cgi the rest is worth watching compare to 80% of the newer ones.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="248668">This is a page by page manga adaption and continuation to the previous series. Honestly i really enjoy the CGI, i don`t know why people find it hard to adapt to this. The full Berserk experience don`t miss out !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="540059">the cgi is not as nice as Bubuki Baranki, in general i do not enjoy it. That apart i love this. that grotesque ero contrast thing was quite surprisingly well done. The direction pacing and character development i thought were 10/10. in ep 9-11, the epic battle was not so amazingly done. Final chapter was nice</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="430272">If you were a fan of the manga then watch this. It follows the manga step by step. The only problem with it is the art style they used. It makes it slightly different to watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="549212">Shit man....
This is the stuff of legends.
I just wished they would make more episodes.
S3 anyone ?</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://berserk-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="666" type="Original Work">Miura Kentarou</name>
<name id="34196" type="Series Composition">Fukami Makoto</name>
<name id="35233" type="Work">Liden Films</name>
<name id="2338" type="Direction">Itagaki Shin</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="3729" type="Main Character Design">Abe Hisashi</name>
<name id="40269" type="Animation Work">Millepensee</name>
<name id="45278" type="Animation Work">Gemba</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the manga by http://anidb.net/cr666 [Miura Kentarou] serialised in the seinen magazine http://anidb.net/cr30430 [Young Animal].
Spurred by the flame raging in his heart, the Black Swordsman http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] continues his seemingly endless quest for revenge. Standing in his path are heinous outlaws, delusional evil spirits, and a devout child of god. Even as it chips away at his life, Guts continues to fight his enemies, who wield repulsive and inhumane power, with nary but his body and sword - his strength as a human. What lies at the end of his travels? The answer is shrouded in the "night."
Source: Crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1562">4.17</permanent>
<temporary count="1598">6.18</temporary>
<review count="7">4.64</review>
</ratings>
<picture>222151.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18160</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35009</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>32379</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://berserk-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Berserk_(2016_TV_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ベルセルク_(漫画)#.E3.83.86.E3.83.AC.E3.83.93.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E7.AC.AC2.E4.BD.9C</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4244</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355237</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19214</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=D1O5us-PLc0</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B078TM58HB</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5890" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>medieval</name>
<description>Setting is placed in the so called "dark ages". It can be either European style, oriental style or Chinese/Japanese style of castles, armour, ways of fighting etc.. 
Also the average education is weak, superstition is high and fights are settled on foot or horseback. Furthermore the level to technology is rather low.
Note: The perceived low level of cultural and technological evolution may be offset by an influx of magic (fantasy stories) or very sophisticated technology that the inhabitants choose to make less obvious to the viewer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6614" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-12">
<name>Animeism</name>
<description>Animeism is a late-night Japanese programming block established in April 2012. It is devoted to anime and broadcast each Thursday night on MBS, in a fashion similar to Fuji TV`s http://anidb.net/t3865 [noitaminA] that also airs on Thursdays. Just like noitaminA, the block airs two series back to back. From April 2015 onwards, the block was moved to Friday nights.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>63625.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6730" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>torture</name>
<description>Torture involves the deliberate act of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or apply coercion to compel action from the victim. Torture, by definition, is a knowing and intentional act; deeds which unknowingly or negligently inflict pain without a specific intent to do so are not typically considered torture.
This is distinct from http://anidb.net/t2905 [erotic torture], which is generally for the purpose of using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="650" type="main character in" update="2015-05-04">
<rating votes="828">9.33</rating>
<name>Guts</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Guts is the primary protagonist of the story. He is a tall, muscular man who wields the Dragon Slayer, a zweihänder or 2 handed sword about 7` long and 12" wide at its base. Described in the manga as more of a table-sized slab of iron than a blade, the Dragon Slayer`s massive size makes it the ideal weapon for slaying apostles of the God Hand. Guts` left hand is prosthetic, a replacement for the one he lost when Griffith attempted to sacrifice him to the forces of hell; it folds back to expose a hidden cannon within the wrist. Guts also carries throwing knives, miniature bombs, a dagger, and even a repeating crossbow that can be mounted onto his prosthetic arm.</description>
<picture>14962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28214" picture="49071.jpg">Iwanaga Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="654" type="main character in" update="2008-12-11">
<rating votes="228">7.64</rating>
<name>Casca</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Casca was the only female soldier in the original Band of the Hawk and is behind only Griffith and Guts in swordsmanship. Her ambivalent relationship to both of them makes her moody and capricious. Casca joins the Band of the Hawk after Griffith empowers her to save herself from a sexual assault by a nobleman.</description>
<picture>14964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20501" picture="186150.jpg">Yukinari Toa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="660" type="main character in" update="2009-06-10">
<rating votes="227">7.07</rating>
<name>Griffith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Griffith is the founder and leader of the mercenary unit known as the Band of the Hawk. Extraordinarily charismatic, intelligent, and handsome, his skill with his sabre and tactics gives him and his band the reputation of invincibility, making him the favoured choice of the Midland King, who was locked in a century long war with the Empire of Tudor. Griffith is willing to sacrifice everything for his dream of his own kingdom and believes that he is destined for things greater than the average man.</description>
<picture>14967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2002" type="appears in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="32">5.44</rating>
<name>Rickert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rickert was the youngest in the old Band of the Hawk; he was just a child.
He is one of the few surviving members of the original Band of the Hawk. After the Eclipse, which he wasn`t present at, he lived with Godo, the smith who created Guts` Dragon Slayer, and became his smith apprentice. For the next two years, Rickert`s talents as a smith grew. He tweaked Guts`s armour and replaced his old crossbow with a repeating crossbow. During his stay with Godo, Rickert had remained completely unaware of what transpired at the Eclipse. He was thus able to put the past behind him. It wasn`t until after Guts, Griffith and Casca were reunited at the Hill of Swords that he learned of the original Band of the Hawk`s fate. Even still, Griffith offered Rickert a position in the new Band of the Hawk. After the death of Godo and the destruction of his mine by Zodd, Rickert travels with Godo`s adopted granddaughter, Erica.</description>
<picture>16792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2003" type="appears in" update="2009-01-07">
<rating votes="74">7.81</rating>
<name>Judeau</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Judeau was part of the original Band of the Hawk and was a former circus performer, which was the background for his prowess in knife-throwing. He was one of Griffith`s most valued fighters, but his greatest strength came from his ability to read the emotions of other people, as shown by him being the first to notice the growing bond between Guts and Casca, even before the two themselves. Quiet, calm, and practical, Judeau was often the voice of reason when handling the more volatile Hawks like Corkus. Noble and generous, Judeau usually put his companions in the band above him, showing himself to be at ease with understanding matters of the heart and inquiring the true intentions of those who surround him. Judeau himself admitted that he was pretty good at a lot of things but was not a stand-out in any of them. His honesty and down-to-earth personality made him a kind of "average joe" character that people could easily identify with. Throughout his tenure with the Band of the Hawk, he was secretly in love with Casca, but he never acted on it out of respect for Guts and Casca`s feelings for each other.
He died during the Eclipse, sacrificing himself for Casca in order to keep her, the leader of the Hawks, alive. In his final moments, Judeau questions what his last words should be, and settles with telling Casca she cried a lot. As he falls down he mourns over the fact that Casca never saw him as anything other than useful.</description>
<picture>16793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2007" type="appears in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="37">2.55</rating>
<name>Corkus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A loud-mouthed ex-thief, Corkus, was fond of delusions of grandeur and was constantly at odds with Guts. He was the leader of his own band of thieves before he joined the old Band of the Hawk, being one of the longest running members. He was the one who first tried to assault Guts in order to rob him of the money earned defeating Bazuso, but failed miserably, making Casca, followed by Griffith, step in. Because of that, he always held a grudge against Guts and never fully accepted him as a Hawk. Surprisingly, when Casca and Rickert blamed Guts for Griffith`s capture, Corkus refused to agree with them due to his belief that they overestimated Guts` importance to the Band.
Despite his unappealing nature, he was one of the most loyal members of the Band of the Hawk, staying with them until his death during the Eclipse, where he convinces himself that everything had been a dream, since it had been just too good to be true.</description>
<picture>89132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56088" picture="223094.jpg">Matsumoto Yoshiroo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2012" type="appears in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="18">2.09</rating>
<name>Midland no Kokuou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The elderly ruler of Midland who had been fighting a century long war with the neighbouring kingdom of Tudor. Burdened by the demands and responsibilities of his throne, the King`s only comfort was his daughter Charlotte whom to him was the sole source of warmth in his existence. Due to the Band of the White Hawk`s victories on the battlefield, the King supported Griffith despite his common heritage and the disapproval of the nobility and eventually bestowed upon him command over all of Midland`s armies.
However, after Griffith slept with Charlotte, the king became enraged and ordered that Griffith be imprisoned and tortured. He also ordered an attack on the leaderless Band of the Hawk, resulting in the Band`s numbers being drastically reduced over the following two years. Driven to the brink of insanity by the fear of losing his only comfort, the king then proceeded to attempt to rape Charlotte who barely managed to fight him off. Afterwards, the guilt over what he had nearly done caused the King`s health to slowly degrade to the point that his hair turned white and his body wasted away to skin and bones. When Griffith was rescued a year later by Guts and the surviving members of the Hawks; the king sent first a group of five Bakiraka, and then the Black Dog Knights led by Wyald to kill Griffith. Shortly before Griffith was reincarnated on Earth, the King`s health had further faded to the point that he was unable to leave his bed anymore. In his final moments, he demanded to see his daughter, but Charlotte no longer recognised him as her father and refused to see him. Before he died, the King had a final vision of Griffith being reunited with Charlotte whereupon he realised the real reason he had supported Griffith was his hope that Griffith would take his place and free him from the cold loneliness of the throne.</description>
<picture>89126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3379" picture="24407.jpg">Katsube Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2014" type="appears in" update="2012-06-06">
<rating votes="29">4.33</rating>
<name>Charlotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The princess of Midland, Charlotte fell in love with Griffith almost at first sight.
After Guts defeated Griffith in their duel, Griffith slept with Charlotte and was imprisoned and tortured for a year as a result. During that time, Charlotte continued to pine over Griffith and eventually was the one who provided the route for the Hawks to rescue him from prison.</description>
<picture>89131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2015" type="appears in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="9">2.41</rating>
<name>Foss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Minister Foss is a master of court intrigue. He conceived of plots with both Julius and the queen to kill Griffith.
However, after the death of Julius, Griffith discovered Foss` involvement with the queen because he detected a hint of fear in the look of the minister`s eyes.</description>
<picture>16823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2017" type="appears in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="7">2.94</rating>
<name>Laban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Laban was a high-ranking noble in Midland`s Court. During the One Hundred Year War, Laban led some of the Midland`s forces and was an early supporter of http://anidb.net/ch660 [Griffith]. He agreed with http://anidb.net/ch2012 [the king] that Griffith should be judged on battlefield merit.
Source: Berserk Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>208559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2042" type="appears in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="14">3.88</rating>
<name>Erica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2043" type="appears in" update="2009-01-08">
<rating votes="10">5.02</rating>
<name>Godo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Blacksmith and creator of Guts` Dragonslayer and foster father of Erica.</description>
<picture>16849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19172" picture="189066.jpg">Inagaki Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2050" type="appears in" update="2011-04-08">
<rating votes="39">3.99</rating>
<name>Femto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Femto is the incarnation of Griffith as a member of the God Hand. During the Incarnation Ceremony, he is reincarnated with a human body but given the gift of supernatural charisma and yet other unknown powers, continuing to chase his dream of a kingdom backed up by his new Band of the Hawk. Femto`s body appears as dark armour with cape-like wings on the back, with a demonic version of Griffith`s familiar hawk-beak helmet.
His currently displayed powers are flight via his dark, cape-like wings, a spherical energy shield that protects his body from attacks such as Guts` arm-cannon, and a powerful blast of dark energy that can rip apart even an Apostle in one hit. His first act as a member of the God Hand is to rape Casca, tainting the child she is bearing, which is Guts`.</description>
<picture>16856.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45688" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="3">2.59</rating>
<name>Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anna is the faithful and loyal servant of http://anidb.net/ch2014 [Charlotte].</description>
<picture>208560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32886" picture="182081.jpg">Takeuchi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49432" type="appears in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="6">5.85</rating>
<name>Silat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Silat is a highly skilled and agile Kushan fighter first encountered by http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] in the Golden Age Arc. He is the leader of the Bakiraka clan and the impressive http://anidb.net/ch82448 [Tapasa] group are his bodyguards.
He claims to be a man with a "bird`s eye view of things". Though he says that his clan abandoned self esteem when they chose to be assassins, he is shown to be proud of his abilities and also of his clan.
His combat style is similar to Kalarippayattu (a martial arts form existing in South India) and uses many Indian weapons used by Rajput warriors, though Guts has referred to him as a circus performer due to Silat`s exotic appearance, acrobatics and his almost theatrical tendency to call out his attacks. Despite Guts` mockery, Silat is one of the strongest human warriors in Midland and among his race the Kushans too, as he defeated many knights in the tournament and overpowered http://anidb.net/ch654 [Casca] later as well as killing a few trained Hawk members. Silat`s skill only fell short when faced with the overwhelming strength of Guts, who he now considers his rival.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49433" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="40">7.96</rating>
<name>Dokuro no Kishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Skull Knight is an enigmatic figure and a self-proclaimed foe of the inhumans, having waged war against demonkind for a millennium.
An ancient being, the Skull Knight is aloof and mysterious with great understanding of the deterministic nature of the world and foreknowledge of the predestined. As such, he possesses a brutally realistic worldview, oftentimes citing the inevitability of causality`s flow. Despite this outlook, he has proven to be quite heroic, saving http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] and his comrades on multiple occasions. However, http://anidb.net/ch87815 [Flora] has questioned whether his actions are out of genuine care or merely a means of furthering his own agenda, a query which the Skull Knight turns a deaf ear to. He ultimately values the human will to survive and defy fate, encouraging Guts to contend against causality and aptly naming him "struggler". He is also quite insightful, warning Guts that http://anidb.net/ch654 [Casca]`s true desire might differ from the Black Swordsman`s own.
The Skull Knight has a long-spanning rivalry with Nosferatu http://anidb.net/ch2009 [Zodd], who is always excited to fight the knight, calling him "old friend". He is normally indifferent to Zodd, only showing irritation at the apostle`s efforts to impede him, though he does openly acknowledge their history and rivalry. He has also known and apparently had a close relationship with the witch Flora for at least several hundred years.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81092" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="8">2.07</rating>
<name>Azan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azan is an old-fashioned knight who practices a code of honor and loyalty. Formerly a devout Vice-Commander of the Holy Iron Chain Knights, he leaves to become a supporting companion to http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] and a member of his party.
Azan is an elder man who is notorious for almost always wearing armor. He`s balding and has a thick mustache. His helmet is reminiscent of a samurai warrior`s kabuto, and his constitution is muscular, but stout. Recently, he was shown to be a bit taller than dwarves.
Since Azan follows old fashioned code of honor. when he fought Guts one on one he ordered the others to stand down. He is shown to care for his fellow knights as shown when he felt ashamed when he fainted and trapped under the rappels and was unable to save them. He is shown to help others whenever he can as when he helped http://anidb.net/ch87813 [Schierke] and her friends against the pirates without being asked.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81093" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="11">5.07</rating>
<name>Isidro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Isidro is a young runaway thief who joins http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] in his travels as a member of the swordsman`s traveling party.
He has always dreamed to be, if not a soldier, the best mercenary warrior of his time. The inspiration for his ambitions is the legend of a once formidable captain - the great "Hundred Man Slayer" - who fought in the original http://anidb.net/ch2063 [Band of the Hawk]. Although Guts has never revealed to Isidro that he is in fact the young boy`s idol, he has supported his dream nonetheless. Being a younger member of the group, Isidro looks up to Guts as a father figure, despite his insistence to the contrary. Currently, he is training under Guts, hoping to achieve his dream of becoming the greatest swordsman in the world. Rather than teaching Isidro his moves, Guts instructs him to learn to fight using his own style, as each person has a different strength, speed, height, and arm-reach. Isidro develops his spinning move using a cutlass, passed down to him by Morgan, and the Salamander Dagger, given by http://anidb.net/ch87815 [Flora].
When receiving compliments individually or as part of the group Isidro and http://anidb.net/ch81095 [Puck] normally brag about how they can manage things themselves. However, both vastly exaggerate their own aptitude for combat. The two are extremely close friends and Puck often sits on the young boy`s head, seeing himself as a mentor of such to the boy. Puck attempts to teach him in the ways of the "Elf Dimension Style", to little success.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>189404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81094" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="19">7.28</rating>
<name>Serpico</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Serpico is one of the main characters of the series. He is a servant and illegitimate son of the noble Vandimion family who would join http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts]` Traveling Party along with his half-sister http://anidb.net/ch81096 [Farnese]. He is polite in manner, and very loyal, sincere, and protective of Farnese.
He is a slender young man with blond hair. His most notable feature is that his eyes are closed at almost all times, except for when he is very serious. He is often compared to a fox because of this. While a member of the Holy Iron Chain Knights, Serpico wore silvery-white armor around a green shirt with matching scarf and skirt. After leaving the Iron Chain Knights, Serpico wears traveler`s garbs prior to receiving the Sylph Cloak. In combat, Serpico is a deft fencer, very clever and cunning.
From his terrible life on the streets, he has grown to show very little emotion, often hiding his true feelings behind a facade of incompetence or sarcasm. He is scared of fire and dislikes the sight of blood, which makes him an unlikely warrior. He learned from growing up poor that revenge only brings more revenge, and avoids creating these situations. Farnese would sometimes force him into duels with other nobles that insulted his honor, but, though he was always far better than his opponent, he chose to purposefully end it in a draw, as he was well aware that the nobles would want revenge. Serpico views Farnese as his guardian angel for saving him from his miserable life on the streets, and does not hate her, despite that she condemned his demented mother for being a heretic (when she, quite obviously, was not), and forced him to burn her himself. 
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81095" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="21">5.47</rating>
<name>Puck</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Puck is the first of the companions that http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] makes during the latter`s days as the Black Swordsman. He is an elf of the pisky race, descendants of the ancient spirits of wind.
As an elf, Puck is, at first glance, similar to a miniature naked human. Upon closer inspection, Puck`s features as an elf become more distinct; his ears are elongated and pointed, he has insect-like wings on his back, and he lacks any kind of visible genitals. Puck sports blue hair that grows out in all directions at the front (similar to a tomato stem) and uniformly points backward in the back. Puck`s eyes are the same color as his hair, and he has a feminine facial structure, with large eyes and a soft jawline. He often holds a burdock, the closest thing to a weapon the elf possesses.
Puck is a whimsical and lighthearted presence that stands out in the dark and unforgiving world he lives in. Not one to take people`s behavior at face value, Puck prefers to find the inherent good in those he meets rather than dismiss them for what he initially sees. As such, Puck displays a great deal of patience when dealing with less-than-reputable characters, and in some cases (like Guts`) Puck does eventually come to find that they do possess some manner of morality and a reason for their brash actions.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81096" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="22">4.56</rating>
<name>Farnese</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Farnese is a noblewoman from the Vandimion family who led the Holy See`s ceremonial guard, the Holy Iron Chain Knights. She later becomes a member of http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts]` traveling party.
Due to her upbringing and subsequent events, Farnese has a very complex but developing personality. Whenever she wanted she would whip, bite, and otherwise abuse http://anidb.net/ch81094 [Serpico] and even drink his blood. She does not know that he is her half-brother. As a child, she treated him as a possession, and she reminded him frequently of this status. Her lack of empathy due to her poor upbringing along with the praise she received in joining in a witch burning provoked her to hunt down and burn supposed witches and pagans at the stake. This fueled a secret sadistic pleasure that she constantly tried to deny.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82447" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="5">5.82</rating>
<name>Jerome</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jerome is a member of the Holy Iron Chain Knights. Originally loyal to the Holy See, he becomes a temporary ally to http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] and his party after witnessing the horrors of the Incarnation Ceremony.
Although being a member of the Holy Iron Chain Knights, he was a fairly decent person and in private admitted to disliking his job. He was known to enjoy sex, and spent many of his breaks and much of his money on prostitutes, though he held a special place for http://anidb.net/ch91824 [Luca] in his heart. Though he enjoyed his life`s comfort and was shocked and scared by the happenings at Albion, he resolved to defy the Knights in order to protect Luca.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82448" type="appears in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="2">3.41</rating>
<name>Tapasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Tapasa are the four Bakiraka that serve as the personal bodyguards of http://anidb.net/ch49432 [Silat]. Each of these four men have knots on their knuckles and mysterious markings on their foreheads. Their bodies are muscular and their skin colour is brown, like all Kushan. The clothes they wear are small and light, minimal so as to not interfere during battles.
The Tapasa have a strong monk-like mentality and as such don`t show much characteristics besides undying loyalty to Silat. However unlike other Bakiraka assassins, they don`t exhibit a cruel nature and even try to appear friendly while disguising in Falconia, but the sight of their huge grinning smiles terrified http://anidb.net/ch91824 [Luca].
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82449" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="4">1.74</rating>
<name>Nina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nina is a member of Luca`s group of traveling prostitutes. She`s a relatively selfish and cowardly person. While she means well, she is too afraid to stand up for others for fear of punishment. On a few occasions, she lashes out at both Luca and Casca, but she is quick to cry and apologize for it.
She suffers from an undefined infection. One several occasions she had persistent vaginal bleeding along with purulent discharge. This suggested a sexually transmitted disease; however, there was no evidence that Joachim or any of her other customers suffered from it, nor that Luca prevented her from continuing to work when she could. Due to that, she is ever worried that she will die soon. She has very little hope for a long future, and many of her decisions are based on immediate results.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82450" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="2">3.41</rating>
<name>Mozgus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mozgus was one of the Chief Inquisitors of the Holy See, traveling the world with his group of torturers, having been sent to root out a violent cult of heretics in the city of Albion. He is the main antagonist of the Conviction Arc, hindering http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts]` efforts in saving http://anidb.net/ch654 [Casca] with his excessive religious zeal. His symbol is four breaking wheels, embodying his willingness to use torture as a way to "cleanse people from evil".
Mozgus is a tall, muscular and strong man with pale skin and blue eyes. His most distinguishing feature is his smooth, almost flat face that is the result of years of prostration, where he harshly kneels and slams his face into the floor. During his prayers, and whenever he is angry, his face becomes swelled with veins and he takes on a much more intimidating appearance. He wears a traditional pontiff`s garb, white with gold trimming and a red cloth that has the insignia of the Holy See. Lastly, he wears a red, wide-brimmed hat with ear covers.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87812" type="appears in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="5">4.67</rating>
<name>Ivalera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ivalera is an elf of the Pisky race and descendant of the ancient Spirits of the Wind. She is a member of http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts]` Traveling Party and a lifelong friend to http://anidb.net/ch87813 [Schierke].
Just like the others of her race, she is an empath, able to feel the emotions of others. In time, Ivalera learned how to "finetune" this ability with the feelings of Schierke, acting in a protective, almost motherly way to protect her from distress, and counseling the other members of the party on what to do when Schierke, overexerting herself, falls in a state of trance too deep to awaken alone. Outwardly more serious and reliable than http://anidb.net/ch81095 [Puck], Ivalera often share with him moments of bickering and fighting, enhancing their value of the "comic relief" characters.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208537.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="87813" type="appears in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="12">6.59</rating>
<name>Schierke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Schierke is http://anidb.net/ch87815 [Flora]`s disciple and a witch. She is a member of http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts]` Traveling Party. She is mature for her age, quiet, and withdrawn.
As a disciple, she was very respectful towards her mistress and was deeply saddened upon her demise. Presently, she gets along well with most of Guts` party, as well as with total strangers such as http://anidb.net/ch87814 [Sonia] and Isma. As a result of being rather sheltered throughout her childhood, she is disdainful towards the human world and the Holy See`s religion, but finds life outside of the forest bearable while traveling with her companions.
Although kind and usually friendly, she sees http://anidb.net/ch81093 [Isidro] as an incompetent monkey and regularly mocks his intelligence, causing some friction between the two which frequently lends itself to comical situations. Initially, Schierke held a disliking for Guts, however this was largely due to her not understanding him. She has since developed an infatuation with him akin to a schoolgirl crush, although their relationship more closely resembles that of a father and daughter.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208536.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91820" type="appears in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Adolf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32216" picture="223331.jpg">Sasa Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91821" type="appears in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<name>Collette</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37377" picture="188508.jpg">Aikawa Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91823" type="appears in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Joachim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joachim is a refugee in the city of Albion, having become smitten with the prostitute http://anidb.net/ch82449 [Nina] upon seeing her for the first time.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34408" picture="127934.jpg">Oonishi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91824" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="9">5.52</rating>
<name>Luca</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Luca is a former Albion prostitute and refugee who currently runs an inn in Falconia. She is a kindhearted and playful person who, due to the positions and environments that she places and finds herself in, is forced to put on a serious air to the benefit of both herself those around her.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91831" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-18">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Kanpeki na Sekai no Tamago</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Egg of the Perfect World is a deformed outcast of society who became an apostle, watching over the city of Albion. He ultimately acts as the key needed to reconstitute http://anidb.net/ch660 [Griffith] into a corporal form by means of self-sacrifice.
The apostle believes in purpose and faith; he admires those who show great passion for their beliefs, such as the cult leader and lord http://anidb.net/ch82450 [Mozgus], to whom he grants great powers. He himself does not like killing and avoids it whenever possible. As a human, he was an outcast who lived on the fringes of society, keeping himself out of sight in an underground tunnel. Hence, he is kind and sympathetic to the misshapen and downtrodden, granting the Demon Child peace by ingesting it and allowing the child to play a part in the birth of the Perfect World. Unlike many apostles, the Egg of the Perfect World is selfless and believes in creating a better world, not for himself, but for the betterment of others.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91837" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Pepe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pepe is an apprentice prostitute serving under http://anidb.net/ch91824 [Luca]. She usually assists in helping her and the other girls.
She is eventually targeted by Hunters of the Holy See while in Albion. They bind her wrists and drag her along by their horses, and when she begs them to let her go, she is whipped across the waist and face. Luckily, Pepe is saved by http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts]` intervention.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34378" picture="127861.jpg">Kondou Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91838" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Fouquet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pepe is an apprentice prostitute serving under http://anidb.net/ch91824 [Luca]. She usually assists in helping her and the other girls. She`s almost always seen smiling and often acts childish.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33628" picture="92051.jpg">Hamasaki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91839" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Lucie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lucie is an apprentice prostitute serving under http://anidb.net/ch91824 [Luca]. She usually assists in helping Luca and the other girls. She is more reserved than the other girls.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39730" picture="223599.jpg">Miki Mii</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91857" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="3">5.35</rating>
<name>Karasu Fukumen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Crow is http://anidb.net/ch82450 [Mozgus]` second in command and one of two members of the group who speaks, recruited by the inquisitor as a child when left to die by his family who could no longer afford his treatment.
While the most normal-looking of the disciples, the Crow suffers from both a weak immune system and photo-sensitivity to the point that his skin festers from being in prolonged sunlight. Because of this, he wears a complete black bodysuit that covers his entire body. He covers his face with a crow-like plague-mask, with dark-toned glasses and a copper beak for respiratory means.
His torture device of choice is a man catcher, a spiked collar on a pole intended for removing a mounted soldier from his horse, and used against heretics with great efficiency.
During the start of the Incarnation Ceremony, the Crow pleaded for Mozgus to escape while he and the others hold the door to chantry. He also was the only one in the room to see http://anidb.net/ch91831 [the Egg of the Perfect World] before becoming an Apostle spawn along with his comrades.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37719" picture="138626.jpg">Fukuda Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91858" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="3">4.19</rating>
<name>Mozgus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mozgus, in his Apostle form.
After http://anidb.net/ch91831 [the Egg of The Perfect World] turns him into an apostle spawn, his transformed state being a reflection of his religious ideals. He gains large, white-feathered wings that he is able to use in his human form. In his transformed state his feathers turn grey and harden giving a similar appearance to closed fists. His body becomes completely encased in the hardened feathers giving him an armored, scaly appearance.
Source: Berserk Wiki</description>
<picture>208596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91859" type="appears in" update="2017-10-19">
<rating votes="3">5.35</rating>
<name>The Bubblehead</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Bubblehead is the tallest of the group and seemingly oldest, a strong man with a misshapen skull. His weapon of choice is a chain with a set of razor sharp jaws on the end. Turned like the others into a spawn.
As an apostle spawn, he gained the common feature of enhanced strength, speed, stamina and angelic wings. He also gained an increased stamina beyond his comrades, evident when http://anidb.net/ch650 [Guts] cuts his right arm off and he did not seem to notice or care.
He was seen one last time as http://anidb.net/ch33056 [God Hand] http://anidb.net/ch2046 [Slan]`s shadow vessel.</description>
<picture>208597.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="97343" type="appears in" update="2018-08-11">
<name>Inchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3362" picture="69121.jpg">Fukuda Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="178341" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">啓示</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Epiphany</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La révélation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keiji</title>
<summary>Guts returns to a place he`d left two years ago to reconnect with old friends, but finds that someone he holds most dear has vanished. Guts tries to lay blame, but he is not entirely innocent...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714987</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178342" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡の夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night of Miracles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La nuit du miracle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki no Yoru</title>
<summary>Guts and Puck are taken aback by Farnese`s inability to see the elf. However, Farnese`s refusal to accept anything beyond what she considers to be real in her world is about to be sorely tested...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714985</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178343" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖鉄鎖騎士団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Holy Iron Chain Knights</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les chevaliers de l`Ordre des chaînes sacrées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sei Tessa Kishidan</title>
<summary>Guts is still coming to terms with his fateful encounter with the monk and his daughter when he is confronted by the Holy Iron Chain Knights. Their commander berates him about his many sins is declares he is to be brought to the Holy See...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714983</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178344" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜殺しの大剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Branded Swordsman</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La pourfendeuse de dragons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuu Koroshi no Daiken</title>
<summary>Into a tavern walks a man with a massive sword, where he encounters a caged elf being bullied by grown men. Thus begins the strange partnership between the elf, Puck, and the swordsman, Guts.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714981</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178465" update="2016-07-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178466" update="2016-07-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178488" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔窟の再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion in the Den of Evil</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retrouvailles dans le repaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Makutsu no Saikai</title>
<summary>As Guts fights his way to Casca, his way is barred by the possessed leader of the heretics. Little does he know that a far more formidable human opponent lies in wait up ahead...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714995</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178489" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒き魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Witch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La sorcière noire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroki Majo</title>
<summary>Guts is finally close to finding Casca, but Casca has caught the heretics` eye, and the Holy Iron Chain Knights are also homing in on the heretics` location...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714993</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178490" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火あぶりの夜宴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Nighttime Feast: Burning at the Stake</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le banquet nocturne des supplices</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiaburi no Yaen</title>
<summary>As Mozgus and his men continue their witchhunt for heretics, Farnese can`t help but feel a twinge of doubt. Meanwhile, Guts unexpectedly encounters a familiar face, who brings ill tidings.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714991</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178491" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">断罪の塔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tower of Conviction</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La tour des châtiments</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Danzai no Tou</title>
<summary>Intent on finding Casca, Guts continues his journey toward the Tower of Conviction. Meanwhile, Farnese is already there, witnessing unspeakable horrors committed by those who serve the Holy See.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714989</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179297" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すがるもの, もがくもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Cling, Those Who Struggle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ceux qui s`accrochent et ceux qui se débattent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugaru Mono, Mogaku Mono</title>
<summary>As people struggle to survive the onslaught of demonic forces, the eclipse reaches its zenith. What will happen when the prophesied God materializes among mortal men?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715003</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179298" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イデアの影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadows of Ideas</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ombre d`Idea</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idea no Kage</title>
<summary>Guts faces off with Mozgus, who has transformed into a giant monster, while trying to save Caska from being burned at the stake. Guts has trouble defeating Mozgus in his current form, due to his body being so hard that even his sword cannot break through. Meanwhile, the Egg has a fateful encounter...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715001</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179299" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘルス・エンジェルス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hell`s Angels</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les anges de l`enfer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hell`s Angels</title>
<summary>Mozgus and his disciples have been turned, and Guts must work fast to keep them from taking Casca. Meanwhile, Luca finds herself face to face with a strange entity who begins to tell her a story...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714999</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179300" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亡者の血流</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blood Flow of the Dead</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sang des morts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mouja no Ketsuryuu</title>
<summary>As Luca leads Guts, Ishidro, and Puck into the tower, Casca is brought to the torture chamber. Just as Mozgus attempts to torture her, however, there is an unexpected turn of events...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714997</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182120" update="2016-11-16">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714957</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="185157" recap="true" update="2018-11-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Recap</title>
<summary>Listed as episode 12.5. Recap episode of the first season.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>732609</identifier>
<identifier>berserk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
