<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11865" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>2016-06-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Usakame</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">うさかめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Usakame</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">兔龟</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9367" type="Same Setting">Teekyuu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://nemumi.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="40269" type="Animation Work">Millepensee</name>
<name id="2338" type="Direction">Itagaki Shin</name>
<name id="2338" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itagaki Shin</name>
<name id="30935" type="Original Work">Roots</name>
<name id="44887" type="Character Design">Miyamura Akira</name>
<name id="44888" type="Character Design">Sugawara Miyuki</name>
<name id="45678" type="Chief Direction">Murata Hikaru</name>
<name id="2338" type="Series Composition">Itagaki Shin</name>
</creators>
<description>The girls of the Usakame High tennis club, Tanaka Kinako, Suzuki Ayako, Sato Kurumi, and Nishiarai-Taishi Nishi, pursue their various dreams... This high school comedy kind of thing starts now.
"Usakame", the official rival of the high intensity comedy "Tekyu", depicts the mostly ordinary but slightly strange daily lives of four girls who devote themselves to practice.
All members of Earth Star Dream, an Earth Star Entertainment idol unit of nationally famous voice actors, appear in the show!
Sit back, relax, and enjoy Tekyu`s rival Usakame.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="290">3.22</permanent>
<temporary count="291">5.20</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>185722.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17972</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34615</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>32454</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://smiral-label.com/usakame/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Teekyu#Usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>てーきゅう#.E3.81.86.E3.81.95.E3.81.8B.E3.82.81</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355308</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19118</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2752" parentid="2881" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tennis</name>
<description>Tennis is yet another sport involving hitting a ball. Were it not for the copious amounts of grass involved in certain varieties, it seems hard to imagine that people would pay it any attention at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4199" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-20">
<name>live-action closing -- TO BE MOVED AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be removed. For each tagged anime, please tag the corresponding ending/credits episodes with the http://anidb.net/t6679 [live-action episode] tag (adding them and their relation to the ending songs if necessary) and then remove this tag from it. Please do not apply this credit to the main episode that has the live-action ending, only to the corresponding credits episode. For example, if episode 22 has a live-action ending, and that ending is also credits episode C7, tag episode C7, not episode 22.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="47679" type="appears in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="43">6.90</rating>
<name>Bandou Marimo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47680" type="appears in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="37">4.67</rating>
<name>Oshimoto Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24615" picture="73810.jpg">Watanabe Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47681" type="appears in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="41">6.41</rating>
<name>Shinjou Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47682" type="appears in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="46">5.74</rating>
<name>Takamiya Nasuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34225" picture="127053.jpg">Narumi Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79292" type="main character in" update="2016-04-05">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Satou Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44383" picture="181062.jpg">Koide Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79293" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-22">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Furubira Tasuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43732" picture="177230.jpg">Takao Kanon</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79294" type="main character in" update="2016-04-05">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Tanaka Kinako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185229.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43849" picture="228703.jpg">Nakashima Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79295" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-22">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Irohani Hoheto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44381" picture="181060.jpg">Aihara Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79296" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-22">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Shibakusa Sora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185991.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79297" type="main character in" update="2016-04-05">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Nishiaraidaishi Nishi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44382" picture="181061.jpg">Tanijiri Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79298" type="main character in" update="2016-04-05">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Suzuki Ayako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44384" picture="181063.jpg">Araida Izumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79299" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-22">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Baba Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>185993.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44380" picture="181055.jpg">Sogabe Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="176705" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と 芙蓉したたる 音すなり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Faint Sound of the Dripping Dew from the Lotus Blossoms with Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Fuyou Shitataru Oto Sunari</title>
<summary>Shibakusa-sensei, the tennis club advisor, shows up to school hungover. She relunctantly agrees to attend practice when the team begs her to come.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712273</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176706" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と ひょろりと猫の 影法師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spindly, Long and Thin, Just as the Silhouette of a Cat, with Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Hyorori to Neko no Kageboushi</title>
<summary>Ayako desperately attempts to befriend a stray cat, but the cat seems determined to hate her. Meanwhile, the other club members seem to have no trouble making friends with the cat and even a strange man named Sekiguchi-san.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712271</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176707" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と そこのけそこのけ お馬が通る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Get Out of the Way, Horse Coming Through, with Kouhai, Get Out of the Way</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Soko no Ke Soko no Ke Oba ga Tooru</title>
<summary>Nishi and Ayako run into each other as they arrive at school. Ayako`s musings about Nishi`s scooter are interrupted when they run into another member of the tennis club doing something rather strange on the stairs.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712269</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176708" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と 隣は何を もらい水</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Does Someone Ask for Water That Is from the Neighbor with Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Tonari wa Nani o Morai Mizu</title>
<summary>Introducing the Usakame High School tennis club! To prepare for the national tournament, the girls practice their super killer moves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712267</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176853" update="2016-04-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177059" update="2016-04-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177276" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と 水がとろりと 春の風</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Viscous Water and Gently Blowing Springtime Zephyrs with Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Mizu ga Torori to Haru no Kaze</title>
<summary>With summer approaching, the girls decide to go shopping for swimsuits. As the weather is still too cold to go to the beach, the girls decide to show off their new suits at the mall`s rooftop pool.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712281</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177277" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と いつか出てある 昼の月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Afternoon Moon, Appearing Up in the Sky One Day, with Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Itsuka Dete Aru Hiru no Tsuki</title>
<summary>Kinako suddenly wakes up in the middle of class. Has everything that`s happened until now been a dream? And who are Bamyan and Tasuku?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712279</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177278" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と 野辺につれ立つ 日永哉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh, How I Spent the Long Spring Days Together in the Fields with Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Nobe Nitsure Tatsu Hinaga Kana</title>
<summary>The girls decide to go to Kurumi`s house after their practice match to discuss the game. When they enter the door, they`re greeted by Kurumi`s panicked father who screams that there`s an emergency in progress!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712277</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177279" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と 春風鳴って 白羽の矢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spring Breeze Blows Through the Feathers on White-Feathered Arrows with Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Harukaze Natte Shiraha no Ya</title>
<summary>A group of familiar faces arrive at Usakame High for a practice match. Can the Usakame tennis club beat their old rivals?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712275</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177778" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と 黄なるてふてふ 一つ見し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Gaze Upon an Aureolin Butterfly Alongside Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Ki Naru Tefutefu Hitotsu Mishi</title>
<summary>With their own graduation approaching, Kurumi and Ayako think back to when their seniors graduated from the tennis club. Will their memories send them spiraling into depression or inspire them to play better at the upcoming tournament?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712289</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177779" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と 我名よばれん 初しぐれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oh, to Hear My Name Spoken as the First Rain Starts to Fall with Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Waga Na Yobaren Hashigure</title>
<summary>With their final tournament as a team approaching, it`s time to get serious. Who will be chosen to play doubles with Ayako?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712287</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177780" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と 明けゆく春の 嵐かな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Could This Truly Be the Dawning of a Springtime Tempest with Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Ake Yuku Haru no Arashi ka na</title>
<summary>Ayako and Kinako are busy with their respective committee meetings, leaving Nishi and Kurumi to hang out and practice alone together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712285</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177781" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">後輩と 奥商人と つれたちて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Constitutionals Alongside the Shopkeeper as Well as Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouhai to Oku Shounin to Tsuredachite</title>
<summary>Kinako is stuck running the family candy shop for the day. As her friends from school come to visit one after another, she attempts to keep herself entertained, sometimes at their expense.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>712283</identifier>
<identifier>usakame</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196942" update="2018-03-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
