<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11915" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-02-04</startdate>
<enddate>2016-02-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Noblesse: Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">NOBLESSE: Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Noblesse: Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Noblesse: Awakening</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11935" type="Prequel">Noblesse: Pamyeol-ui Sijak</anime>
<anime id="15409" type="Other">Noblesse</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="158613">What an anime, if you like vampire hunter D you will love this. I hope they make into a anime series 24+ episodes cause it`s absolutely fantastic</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="555927">Too fast-paced, so if someone didn`t read the original manhwa, he might not be able to understand what`s going on. 
Still, it`s a "must-see" for fans of original series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="298967">Must see for fans
I hope this get a full season.
One of the best manwas on korea</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="12213" type="Direction">Matsuzawa Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="2136" type="Chief Direction">Tada Shunsuke</name>
<name id="39770" type="Character Design">Umishima Senbon</name>
<name id="3573" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Akiharu</name>
<name id="4410" type="Music">Ike Yoshihiro</name>
</creators>
<description>A long time ago, there were those with superhuman strength and longevity, who used their powers to protect humanity from catastrophes. They chose to live in the shadows, quietly and in solitude. Worshipped by humans, they were sometimes known as nobles, sometimes as rulers, and sometimes as gods. But little is known of the strongest among them, who protected the other nobles. The guardian of nobles... he was called the Noblesse. — intro
A powerful noble, Cadis Etrama di Raizel, has been asleep for 820 years with no knowledge of mankind`s advancement or scientific progress. Rai wakes up in an abandoned building in South Korea, and starts to get used to the modern world. He visits the Ye Ran High School, where he reunites with his loyal servant Frankenstein, principal of that school. With the latter`s help, Rai enrols into high school and inadvertently befriends athletic teenager Shinwu Han, computer geek Ikhan Woo, and Shinwoo`s crush Yuna Suh. The group henceforth has to confront a very dangerous secret organization while uncovering Rai`s past.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="560">6.37</permanent>
<temporary count="563">7.05</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>182198.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18051</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32668</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.webtoons.com/en/promotion/noblesse-ova</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Noblesse_(manhwa)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>노블레스_(만화)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>noblesse-awakening</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2673" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Korea</name>
<description>Korea is a historical country in East Asia; since 1945, it has been divided into two distinct sovereign states: North Korea (officially the "Democratic People`s Republic of Korea") and South Korea (officially the "Republic of Korea"). Located on the Korean Peninsula, Korea is bordered by China to the northwest and Russia to the northeast. It is separated from Japan to the east by the Korea Strait and the Sea of Japan.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214324.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5010" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manhwa</name>
<description>The Korean equivalent of the Japanese manga (has the look of a manga, but you read it like a Western comic).
See also http://anidb.net/t2798 [manga] and http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6166" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-23">
<name>South Korean production</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/t6762 [North Korean production]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="108586" type="main character in" update="2020-03-06">
<name>Cadis Etrama Di Raizel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Age: 3000+
Race: Noble
Occupation: The Noblesse, Student
Eye colour: Red
Hair colour: Black
Rai is a very elegant and mysterious Noble. He has no knowledge whatsoever of the 21st century, and will often become lost and confused especially with regards to modern day technology (such as using a cell phone). He is often used as the manhwa`s comic relief with his love of ramen and the errors he makes with technology. He has fallen into a deep slumber for 820 years, and had woken up in an abandoned building in South Korea. After seeing what most of the humans on the streets were wearing, Rai took on the uniform of a student from Ye Ran High School, which is under the administration of Frankenstein, and inadvertently followed the students there.</description>
<picture>68627.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="108587" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-06">
<name>Woo Ik-Han</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Woo Ik-Han is a regular human and best friends to Shinwoo, Yuna and Suyi, in addition to Regis, Seira and Rai. He spends most of his free time on his computer. He wears spectacles.
A running gag throughout the Manhwa is Ikhan`s worry about his relatively short height. Initially, when Regis and Seira joined his class at school, Ikhan showed extreme interest in the new students, which others supposed was Ikhan developing a crush on Seira. However, it is later revealed that Ikhan was rather enraptured by Regis, for Ikhan stated that he always wanted a fellow `short` friend. Throughout his adventures, Ikhan is seen giving Regis foods and candies that are long and thin (such as Pocky) stating that he and Regis must eat them to grow taller (a pun on the stature of the food).
His hacking and computing skills are extremely proficient. He was able to match Tao`s speeds when Tao tried to hack into Ikhan`s uncle`s police databases. He is also the best when it comes to computer games as it is mentioned by Shinwoo that Ikhan defeated him every time. Ikhan also shows to be quite brainy rather than brawny, taking school very seriously compared to Shinwoo.</description>
</character>
<character id="108588" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-06">
<name>M-21 "Number Four"</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>M-21 is one of the first one hundred humans that was experimented on by the Union. He is designated as the 21st human in that batch. He was classified as a failed experiment, and took the lowest raking agent position in the Union along with M-24.</description>
</character>
<character id="108589" type="appears in" update="2020-03-06">
<name>M-24</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Age: Unknown (&gt;25)
Race: Human (modified)
Occupation: (deceased)
Eye Color: White
Hair Color: (bald)
M-24 is a large, bulky and muscular guy with a purplish-tinted skin, who wears a black fedora with a gray turtleneck sweater, black jacket and dark pants. Though he appears to be cruel and cold-hearted at first, it is later revealed that he can be very compassionate and caring towards others. He shares a very close relationship with M-21 because they were the only 2 remaining from their group. Together, they try to find out their comrades’ names. He even wished for M-21 to call him ‘older brother’ because he thinks that previously in his life, he had younger siblings.
M-24 was one of the first 100 humans (M-1 to M-100) that were experimented on by the Union. He is considered a failed experiment, like M-21, and he is dependent on pills from the union that prevent his body from deteriorating. In time he has developed the ability of minor mind-control as side effect of the experiments done on him. He helped M-21 to learn how he could withstand mind control by launching several attempts of mind control on him. He was also capable of producing ‘infected’ and control them.</description>
</character>
<character id="108590" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-06">
<name>Han Shinwoo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Han Shinwoo is a student in Ye Ran High School and is popular because of his excellent martial skills. On the day of Rai`s awakening, he happens to meet him on the way to school and gradually becomes close to Rai at school, developing a bond which can be termed as friendship. Eventually he gets involved in many strange fights against people with extra-ordinary powers. Rai and Frankenstein rescue him and others from the mess every time. Later he as well as the others are brainwashed for their own safety and so remember nothing of the strange happenings.
Shinwoo is an energetic and athletic teenager with bright red hair. He is always seen with a bandage over the bridge of his nose. He is actually pretty good looking but not that many people realize it because of his behavior.
He is well-known within the city to be skilled in martial arts and feared by gangs. Shinwoo is often shown sleeping (and drooling) in class and slacking off. Though he is shown as a lazy student, he is also very courageous and would protect his friends at all costs. He often tends to be late for school due to over sleeping.
He has liked Yuna for a long time and it is disclosed that he confessed to her in past which led to an embarrassing situation. Since then they have been just good friends although Shinwoo still has a liking for Yuna. Shinwoo is also starting to like Seira.
Shinwoo is an amazing Martial Artist excelling in Tae Kwon Do and Hapkido. He is well-known within the city to be skilled in martial arts and is feared by gangs. He is able to match the powers of M-24`s Infected, and since then has been getting stronger.
Even for normal human parameters, it`s been quoted that Shinwoo possesses an incredible amount of strength, which he has displayed during his multiple battles; including those with the Infected.
It`s been noted that one of Shinwoo`s most incredible attributes is his speed, shown as he instantly disappeared when he went to aid Yuna right after she yelled for help. Alongside his speed, his agility and reflexes have increased during the progression of the series; to the point he was able to dodge one of Shark`s attacks and counterattack at the same time.
Shinwoo`s most incredible strength relies in his durability, since he is able to endure attacks that would normally kill a human being; as shown when he took a beating from Shark and was even able to stood up against him one more time right after he threatened to kill his friends.</description>
</character>
<character id="108591" type="appears in" update="2020-03-06">
<name>Yuna Suh</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Race: Human
Occupation: student
Eye colour: brown
Hair colour: brown
Yuna is a beautiful young girl with a friendly, shy and quiet personality. Ik-Han and Shinwoo are childhood friends of her. She’s a student of Ye Ran High School and she’s in the same class as Shinwoo, Ik-Han and the others. Shinwoo had a crush on her since they were kids. She also becomes friends with Rai and visits him at Frankenstein’s home together with Shinwoo and Ik-Han. When she and Rai are introduced to video games, she appears to be quite competent despite it being her first try.</description>
</character>
<character id="108592" type="main character in" update="2020-03-06">
<name>Frankenstein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Frankenstein (Kor. 프랑켄슈타인) (commonly referred to as chairman by the children) is Rai`s devoted servant. He supports Rai whole-heartedly and calls him "Master". He had tried searching for his master after Rai`s apparent "disappearance." Frankenstein is the principal/director of Ye Ran High School. He was stunned to find Rai in his school office after Rai had woken up and dressed in his school`s uniform.
Frankenstein is a very cheerful and loyal person, especially toward his master, but can become quite serious and calculative when the situation calls for it. Although Frankenstein has shown somewhat of a sadistic side during his recurrent battles, like Rai, he is also compassionate towards human beings, especially towards the students in his school.
Frankenstein is immensely powerful but some of his powers had been sealed away by Rai due to him misusing them in the past. After 820 years of sealing, Rai has finally taken off the punishment. But whenever Frankenstein gets serious in fighting uses his full power, Rai shows a considerable amount of anxiety.</description>
</character>
<character id="108593" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-06">
<name>Jake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Age: Unknown
Race: Modified Human
Affiliation: Union
Occupation: Assassination Squad
Jake is a modified human who worked for the Union as a member of its Assassination squad, where he is partnered with Mary. He is one of the earliest modified humans and antagonists introduced in the series.
Jake is one of the most powerful successful experiments created by Dr. Crombel. He is Mary`s partner; the two of them make up the assassination unit of the Organization/Union.
Jake is usually egotistical and extremely aggressive, which gets him scolded by Mary. He thinks very little of failed experiments such as M-21 and M-24. He likes brutality shown in his elimination of everyone in the hospital.
Jake was shown to be very powerful, especially in comparison to M-24 and the minimally-transformed M-21. Jake forced the scientists to experiment on him in order to improve his transformation. In his full transformation state his powers were ten times greater than that of Mary`s powers.</description>
</character>
<character id="108594" type="appears in" update="2020-03-06">
<name>Mary</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Race: Modified Human
Affiliation: Union
Occupation: Assassination Unit
First Appearance: Chapter 30
Mary is a modified human who serves the Union as a member of its Assassination Squad where she was partnered with Jake. She was the first female modified human shown within the series as well as one of the earliest antagonists.
Mary is one of the first female experiments seen in the series. She is one of the highest ranked and most powerful of the successful experiments created by Dr. Crombel. The assassination unit of the Union is composed by her and Jake. It is implied that Mary is more powerful that her partner, which means that she holds a higher rank and commanding capability.
Mary, though quiet, is very intelligent and loyal to Dr. Crombel. She rarely displays emotion, which frequently annoys Jake, her partner. She has a very cold and cruel nature, and always strictly follows her missions. When she died, everyone in the Union, including the members of the DA-5, showed surprise. They all found it hard to believe that she could have been killed.
She has been shown to have the ability to transform her arms, and in this transformed state she gains immense speed and strength. It is implied that she is even more powerful than Jake, for he had vowed to kill her and Dr. Crombel one day, but not until he became stronger. Jake is also afraid of her, further attesting to Mary`s immense strength.</description>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="174898" update="2020-02-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2016-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Web</title>
<summary>Cadis Etrama di Raizel wakes up from 820-years long sleep and starts a new life as a high school student. His peaceful days as a student are soon interrupted as his new human friends are assaulted by mysterious attackers with superhuman abilities.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694155</identifier>
<identifier>noblesse-awakening</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182138" update="2016-11-16">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>694157</identifier>
<identifier>noblesse-awakening</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
