<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11929" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1983-12</startdate>
<enddate>1983-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kodanuki Ponpo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">こだぬき ポンポ</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www2.nhk.or.jp/minna/search/index.cgi?id=MIN198312_01</url>
<description>A music video for the song "Kodanuki Ponpo" by Atomu Shimojou. Aired as part of NHK`s Minna no Uta program.
Source: MAL</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="19">2.92</permanent>
<temporary count="20">4.37</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>182818.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32430</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www2.nhk.or.jp/minna/search/index.cgi?id=MIN198312_01</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3968" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>animal protagonist</name>
<description>The anime revolves around an animal, usually only communicating with typical onomatopoeia. The animal mostly lives in a human family and has adventures on a regular base. This can be the discovery of a new room, or being lost by having taken a wrong turn in the outside world.
Typical example: http://anidb.net/a5801 [Chii`s Sweet Home].
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t4259 [animal world], where the whole world is composed of animals.</description>
<picurl>10255.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6423" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-11">
<name>Minna no Uta</name>
<description>Minna no Uta is a five-minute music programme broadcast several times daily on NHK TV and radio since 1961. It is used to introduce new songs from popular and new singers, as well as to highlight the talents of various animators and directors.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>174524.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="176304" update="2016-03-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
