<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11931" restricted="false">
<type>unknown</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-04-16</startdate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Double Hard</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ダブル・ハード</title>
</titles>
<description>Unbeatable fist-fighter Daiki Hayami and professional knuckler Jin Takayama ram into an incredible fight against Shibaura`s craziest bike gang, the underhanded Midnight King, and its leaders, the Shinjo Brothers. Midnight King takes one of Daiki`s classmates, Mai, as a hostage, and that makes Daiki and Jin`s anger get to the high peak!
Source: Crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="6">4.38</permanent>
<temporary count="6">3.66</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>182900.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>29605</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://nextanimation.com.tw/us/tomo_detail.php?a=4</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ダブル・ハード</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="80597" type="main character in" update="2016-02-27">
<name>Hyami Daiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63590.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="80598" type="main character in" update="2016-02-28">
<name>Takayama Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63591.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="80599" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-28">
<name>Keiko Nishiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63593.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="175150" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Southpaw!! Part II</title>
<summary>For an extra caution, Shangli-la takes Kouji as its hostage. When Daiki gets to the place, he sees all Shangli-la team members beaten down and lying on the floor.
It was the Blond Lefty who beat all the men by himself. His name is now revealed and it`s Amagi.
Amagi has wanted a one-on-one fight against Daiki and he prepares a perfect stage for the fight. How does Daiki fight against this daunting fighter!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175151" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Southpaw!! Part I</title>
<summary>A blond lefty beats gang team`s leaders one after another in town and makes quick fight money. Got eyes on this, gang team Shangli-la`s Jinnai comes up with a cool idea and approaches to the Blond Lefty.
Jinnai`s idea is to knock down Two Men Army by using this Blond Lefty!
Jinnai puts 500K for the fight money. How does this play on the fate of Two Men Army?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175152" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Memory Part II</title>
<summary>Shinjo proposes a one-on-one fight against Red Skelton`s Kenmochi. However, creepy Kenmochi commands the whole gang team to attack him once.
Daiki hears about this confrontation between Shinjo and Red Skelton at Shinjo`s bike shop. Without telling Shinjo, Daiki re-assembles Midnight King.
As Two Men Army and Midnight King watch, the one-on-one fight between Shinjo and Kenmoch begins.
Their one-on-one fight plays long. No one know which one is going to win!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175153" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Memory Part I</title>
<summary>The formar leader of Midnight King Shinjo returns to the town. He was believed to be retired from the gang fights and now he works at a bike shop. So it happens, Shinjo saves Mai who get bullied by a gang team Red Skelton.
Got mad by this happening, the leader of Red Skelton Kenmochi attacks the owner of the bike shop where Shinjo works. The owner suffers a severe injury which takes 2 months to heal.
Shinjo`s inner anger starts to burn quietly but hard and red!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175154" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Brother Part II</title>
<summary>Real Daiki and Jin hear about a rumor of phony Daiki and rush to the place where the confrontation takes place.
Phony Daiki is in one-on-one fight against the leader of the rival gang team. Battered so hard by the rival leader, phony Daiki tries to protect the girl who lured him into the situation.
Feeling his true guts, real Daiki jumps into the midest of the fight to rescue the two.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175155" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Brother Part I</title>
<summary>Someone alike Daiki walks around the town and pretends to be Daiki, one of the Two Men Army. This phony Daiki happens to save a girl bullied by a gang team and get rid of them. Lured by the girl, phony Daiki gets to a hang-aorund place of the other gang team Wild Cat. He get involved in a private war against its rival team Kind Edge.
Phony Daiki is no good at fighting at all. How does this trick play on this guy`s life?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175156" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">P.S. I Love You Part II</title>
<summary>A mysterious and beautiful lady makes visit to Daiki at his gym. Her name is Ryoko. Daiki and Ryoko have something in their past. Ryoko cared Daiki. Daiki feels momentary comfort with the memory he had with Ryoko.
The past days that the two share and their lives crisscross again for a moment.
No matter how true they becomes to themselves, there are the days they cannot take back and embrace. And are separate roads lying infront of them on which each has to take a step forward.
The story about Daiki`s reminisence over his younger days. PART 2
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175157" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">P.S. I Love You Part I</title>
<summary>A mysterious and beautiful lady makes visit to Daiki at his gym. Her name is Ryoko. Daiki and Ryoko have something in their past. Ryoko cared Daiki. Daiki feels momentary comfort with the memory he had with Ryoko.
No matter how true they becomes to themselves, there are the days they cannot take back and embrace. And are separate roads lying infront of them on which each has to take a step forward.
The story about Daiki`s reminisence over his younger days. PART 1
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175158" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">White Trap 3</title>
<summary>Rescued by Captain Kuwaki, Daiki and his friends are released from the jail. They rushes to the drop-off place of Shizuka`s ransom in order to save her.
Now with Jin joining the team, they are to make the final confrontation against the gangster.
Little Shizuka`s life in danger, they must fight out and win this battle! Daiki and Jin, stop the kidnappers and ugly policemen, and kick ass their nefarious plan!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175159" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">White Trap 2 = Part 2</title>
<summary>Viciously entrapped by the local gangster and ugly policemen, Daiki and his friends get arrested and jailed.
Now sweeping the intruders, the kidnappers pressure Shizuka`s grandfather Saeki. Captain Kuwaki hurries to the site from Tokyo. Is he able to salvage the situation?
The gangster and ugly policemen`s evil deed... that ignites the fuse of Daiki`s anger!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175160" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">White Trap 2 = Part 1</title>
<summary>The gangster`s violent attack starts. Daiki and his friends hit back against the gangster`s army and its leader Kaieda, who penetrate into Keiko`s villa.
Mai ski downhills and reaches to the police station. She reports the situation at the villa to the police, but guess whom the police arrest when they get to the villa...
The double traps darkly entangles Daiki and his friends. How will they get out and overcome this danger??
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175161" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">White Trap 1 = Part 2</title>
<summary>In order to protect Shizuka, the granddaughter of a local big shot, Daiki and his friends shelter Shizuka in Keiko`s resort villa. However, Shizuka gets sick and runs high fever.
The gangsters destroy Keiko`s car. Daiki and his friends lose their transportation. Mai volunteers skies downhill to call a help from the police force as she is the only one good at skiing.
Is Mai able to find the police safely? And are Daiki and his friends able to shelter Shizuka and fend the gangster`s fierce attack?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175162" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">White Trap 1 = Part 1</title>
<summary>Keiko, Daiki and Mai are driving up to a snow mountain. Ryuzaki is on ahead, supposed to wait for them up there. It`s supposed to be a fun skiing vacation, however, up there what waits for them is a threat by a local gang group who attempt to kidnap Shizuka, a grand-daughter of a local big shot.
The gang group are to start their attack. Are Daiki and his friends able to protect Shizuka throughout this dangerous situation??
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175163" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Double Justice Part 2</title>
<summary>Daiki is recruited by Hijiri to be a member of Shinsen Gumi. But he questions the army`s idea to have a better world just by sweeping out the bad ones. Meanwhile, Daiki gets to know the truth about the cause of the death of Hijiri`s younger brother. He makes up his mind!!
Hijiri gets chased after by the police force because of Shinsen Gumi`s loss of control. The police force gets there to stop further expansion of city damages. And Daiki and JIn who get involved in that voltex more and more... Where do these fierce battles end up??
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175164" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Double Justice Part 1</title>
<summary>Daiki runs into his senior student Kengo Hijiri, whom he knows from his junior school days. And at the same time, there have been repeated cases where street gangs get busted by a militant group called Shinsen Gumi. Captain Kuwaki asks Daiki and Jin to get some information. Meanwhile, Daiki gets to know that the leader of Shinsen Gumi is none other than his senior student, Kengo Hijiri...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175165" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">A Boy Meets a Girl, Part II</title>
<summary>Having admiration to Daiki`s fighting style, Kouji follows after Daiki everyday. Meanwhile, Kouji`s girlfriend Miki is kidnapped by a street gang group.
Kouji chases after the gang desperately to rescue Miki. Hearing this happening, Daiki and Jin get on their foot and chase after Kouji and Miki...!?
How does Kouji`s first love story go? Are Daiki and Jin able to rescue the young loves? PART II
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175166" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">A Boy Meets a Girl, Part I</title>
<summary>Having admiration to Daiki`s fighting style, Kouji follows after Daiki everyday. Meanwhile, Kouji`s girlfriend Miki is kidnapped by a street gang group.
Kouji chases after the gang desperately to rescue Miki. Hearing this happening, Daiki and Jin get on their foot and chase after Kouji and Miki...!?
How does Kouji`s first love story go? Are Daiki and Jin able to rescue the young loves? PART I
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175167" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Lady Tiger!</title>
<summary>Daiki`s junior fellow Kouji gets trapped and bitterly betrayed by Maki, the leader of the up-rising gang team Mad Powers, whom Kouji admired so much. As result, Kouji is sold to the enemy team Metal Dog as a sacrifice.
Been worrying about Kouji`s recent behavior, Keiko talk his situation to Daiki. The two is heading to the place of confrontation to rescue Kouji together!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175168" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Crusade Part 4</title>
<summary>It comes to the climax of the battle at BC`s home park. Daiki is ready to face BC`s unbeatable leader Nodou.
But in all what happen, Ryuzaki`s female friend Keiko is taken as a hostage. What`s the plan, Daiki? Would they be able to take back Keiko safely, or...??
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175169" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Crusade Part 3</title>
<summary>After defeating Haryu and his men, Daiki, Jin, Ryuzaki and Shinjo go down to Black Crusader`s evil lair. Waiting for them there were BC`s eerie looking top members, Fukuo, Taira and their boss, Nodo.
BC`s top guys attack Daiki and his friends in vicious ways. Daiki and his team get back footed in BC`s home park and separated. Does Daiki`s fair fight beat up these basehearted BC bosses?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175170" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Crusade Part 2</title>
<summary>Police force ace captain Kuwaki is investigating the violent cases caused by Crusader. Meanwhile, Daiki, Jin and Ryuzaki step into the enemy territory to rescue Midnight King!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175171" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Tokyo Crusade Part 1</title>
<summary>The magnum combo Daiki and Jin double their hands again! Shibaura`s craziest bike-rider gang Midnight King gets into bloody insurrection against another violent rival gang group Black Crusader…
Yokohama`s sharp knuckle fighter Ryuzaki has joined the team, Daiki and Jin start firing in tough and hard bloody new battles!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175172" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Full-Metal Leather!!!!</title>
<summary>Having a skirmish against gangsters from Yokohama, Daiki is attacked by a hatchet man Ryuzaki who is sent by those Yokohama gangs.
Is Daiki able to stop this skilled fist fighter Ryuzaki by himself? And there again, Mai gets trapped and held as a hostage by the gangs. Can Daiki rescue her in time again?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175173" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Midnight Trap!!!</title>
<summary>Daiki gets trapped in a false charge and suspected that he had attacked the younger brother of Shinjo whose wounds and injuries are not completely healed yet. Burnt in anger, the Head of Midnight King, Shinjo`s older brother challenges Daiki a one-on-one battle!
Rescuing him from this crisis and cleared the false charge is none other than Daiki`s trustful partner Jin himself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175174" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Mariwana Night!!</title>
<summary>Junya, a son of a gang group`s boss unleashes violence in a popular dance club Mariwana. Hearing it, Daiki appears at the club and beats Junya to a pulp. Burnt with anger, Junya takes a group of militants in the gang members, trying to attack Daiki and his friends.
Under a full-scale war against the gang group, is the combo, Daiki and JIn, able to overcome this crisis?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="175175" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Double Power!</title>
<summary>Unbeatable Fist-Fighter Daiki Hayami and Professional Knuckler Jin Takayama ram into the incredible fight against Shibaura`s craziest bike gang Midnight King and its head Shinjo Brothers!!
Unfair and underhanded Midnight King takes one of Daiki`s classmates Mai as its hostage. That makes Daiki and Jin`s anger get to the high peak!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
