<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1194" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-09-15</startdate>
<enddate>1999-09-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Alexander Senki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Alexander Record of War</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Alexander`s War Chronicles</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Alexander`s Campaign</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Александр Завоеватель</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Александр [ТВ]</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Alexander</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アレクサンダー戦記</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Reign: The Conqueror</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Alexandre le grand</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Alexander - Cronache Di Guerra Di Alessandro Il Grande</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Reign: Ο Κατακτητής</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Alexandru cel Mare</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7528" type="Summary">Alexander Senki Gekijouban</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="1865" type="Direction">Kanemori Yoshinori</name>
<name id="19740" type="Character Design">Peter Chung</name>
<name id="23600" type="Original Work">Aramata Hiroshi</name>
</creators>
<description>In the 4th century B.C., a pagan shaman prophesies that Olympias, Queen of Macedonia, wife of King Phillip II will give birth to a baby who will grow up to destroy the world, and the baby named Alexander.
Years later, Alexander with many successful campaigns unifies Persia and Macedonia, so great that it makes Aristotle worry that the world can be destroyed by Alexander`s advance toward the East...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="415">3.69</permanent>
<temporary count="427">5.83</temporary>
<review count="3">8.05</review>
</ratings>
<picture>36677.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2276</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1442</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1172</identifier>
<identifier>jvxdsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Reign:_The_Conqueror</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アレクサンダー戦記</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159492</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1065" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>heterochromatic eyes</name>
<description>Heterochromia Iridis is a condition where one eye is a different color from the other, or one eye is more than one color.
Characters with different eye-colour may not necessarily have the medical condition itself, as the state of different-coloured eyes can be caused by various other reasons such as possession by spiritual entities, indication of special powers or artificial changes.</description>
<picurl>63229.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2833" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Middle East</name>
<description>The Middle East is a transcontinental region centered on Western Asia, Turkey (both Asian and European), and Egypt (which is mostly in North Africa). The corresponding adjective is Middle Eastern and the derived noun is Middle Easterner. The term has come into wider usage as a replacement of the term Near East (as opposed to the Far East) beginning in the early 20th century.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192047.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2837" parentid="2628" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>floating island</name>
<description>A floating island is an island either floating in the sky, or actually floating in the ocean (mobile). The island`s flotation can be powered either by magic or science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5091" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>India</name>
<description>India, officially the Republic of India, is a country in South Asia. It is the seventh-largest country by area, the second-most populous country, and the most populous democracy in the world. It is bounded by the Indian Ocean on the south, the Arabian Sea on the southwest, and the Bay of Bengal on the southeast. It shares land borders with Pakistan to the west; China, Nepal, and Bhutan to the northeast; and Myanmar (Burma) and Bangladesh to the east.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="55622" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="3">8.11</rating>
<name>Alexander</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alexander III of Macedon (commonly known as Alexander the Great) was a king of Macedon, a state in northern ancient Greece. Born in Pella in 356 BC, Alexander was tutored by Aristotle until the age of 16. He was undefeated in battle and is considered one of history`s most successful commanders.</description>
<picture>136295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55623" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="1">2.49</rating>
<name>Aristotle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aristotle was a Greek philosopher and polymath, a student of Plato and teacher of Alexander the Great. His writings cover many subjects, including physics, metaphysics, poetry, theater, music, logic, rhetoric, linguistics, politics, government, ethics, biology, and zoology. Together with Plato and Socrates, Aristotle is one of the most important founding figures in Western philosophy. Aristotle`s writings were the first to create a comprehensive system of Western philosophy, encompassing morality, aesthetics, logic, science, politics, and metaphysics.</description>
<picture>136296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3380" picture="187130.jpg">Nozawa Nachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55624" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">2.49</rating>
<name>Philip II</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Philip II was king of Macedon from 359 BC until his assassination in 336 BC. He was the father of Alexander the Great and Philip III.</description>
<picture>136298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4438" picture="26713.jpg">Sakaguchi Yoshisada</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55625" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">4.27</rating>
<name>Haphaestion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hephaestion, son of Amyntor, was a Macedonian nobleman and a general in the army of Alexander the Great. He was "... by far the dearest of all the king`s friends; he had been brought up with Alexander and shared all his secrets." This friendship lasted their whole lives, and was compared, by others as well as themselves, to that of Achilles and Patroclus.</description>
<picture>136300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55626" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-08">
<rating votes="2">1.56</rating>
<name>Ptolemy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ptolemy was a Macedonian general under Alexander the Great, who became ruler of Egypt (323-283 BC) and founder of both the Ptolemaic Kingdom and the Ptolemaic Dynasty. In 305/4 BC he took the title of Pharaoh.</description>
<picture>136301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55627" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">2.49</rating>
<name>Parmenion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Parmenion was a Macedonian general in the service of Philip II of Macedon and Alexander the Great, murdered on a suspected false charge of treason.</description>
<picture>136302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3266" picture="151719.jpg">Nakamura Tadashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55628" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">4.27</rating>
<name>Cleitus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cleitus was an officer of the Macedonian army led by Alexander the Great. Cleitus was son of Dropides and brother of Alexander`s nurse, Lanike.</description>
<picture>136303.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55629" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">1.51</rating>
<name>Darius III</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darius III was the last king of the Achaemenid Empire of Persia from 336 BC to 330 BC.</description>
<picture>136304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55630" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="2">4.01</rating>
<name>Olympias</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Olympias was a Greek princess of Epirus, daughter of king Neoptolemus I of Epirus, the fourth wife of the king of Macedonia, Philip II, and mother of Alexander the Great. She was a devout member of the orgiastic snake-worshiping cult of Dionysus, and it is suggested by the 1st century AD biographer, Plutarch, that she may have slept with snakes.</description>
<picture>136305.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29012" picture="76619.jpg">Mashina Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55631" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">4.27</rating>
<name>Roxanne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roxana was a Bactrian (Persian Empire) princess and a wife of Alexander the Great.</description>
<picture>136306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="352" picture="17191.jpg">Minaguchi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55632" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">2.49</rating>
<name>Cassandra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136307.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55633" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">2.49</rating>
<name>Philotas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Philotas was the eldest son of Parmenion, Alexander`s most experienced and talented general.</description>
<picture>136308.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20546" picture="2047.gif">Meguro Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55634" type="appears in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">1.51</rating>
<name>Antipater</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Antipater was a Macedonian general and a supporter of kings Philip II of Macedon and Alexander the Great. In 320 BC, he became regent of all of Alexander`s Empire. Antipater was one of the sons of a Macedonian nobleman called Iollas or Iolaus and his family were distant collateral relatives to the Argead dynasty. Antipater was originally from the Macedonian city of Paliura.</description>
<picture>136309.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55635" type="appears in" update="2013-05-14">
<rating votes="1">1.13</rating>
<name>Attalos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Attalus was an important courtier of Macedonian king Philip II of Macedonia.</description>
<picture>136311.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28" picture="23184.jpg">Aono Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55636" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="1">1.51</rating>
<name>Plato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Plato was a philosopher in Classical Greece. He was also a mathematician, student of Socrates, writer of philosophical dialogues, and founder of the Academy in Athens, the first institution of higher learning in the Western world. Along with his mentor, Socrates, and his student, Aristotle, Plato helped to lay the foundations of Western philosophy and science.</description>
<picture>136313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5165" picture="131891.jpg">Sagawa Tetsurou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55637" type="appears in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">1.51</rating>
<name>Dinocrates</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dinocrates was a Greek architect and technical adviser for Alexander the Great. He is known for his plan for the city of Alexandria, the monumental funeral pyre for Hephaestion and the reconstruction of the Temple of Artemis at Ephesus, as well as other works.</description>
<picture>136314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55638" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="1">4.27</rating>
<name>Diogenes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diogenes of Sinope was a Greek philosopher and one of the founders of Cynic philosophy. Also known as Diogenes the Cynic, he was born in Sinope (modern-day Sinop, Turkey), an Ionian colony on the Black Sea.</description>
<picture>136315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3386" picture="24413.jpg">Kumakura Kazuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55639" type="appears in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">4.27</rating>
<name>Antigonos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Antigonus, son of Philip from Elimeia, was a Macedonian nobleman, general, and satrap under Alexander the Great. During his early life he served under Philip II, and he was a major figure in the Wars of the Diadochi after Alexander`s death, declaring himself king in 306 BC and establishing the Antigonid dynasty.</description>
<picture>136316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2946" picture="23373.jpg">Gouri Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55640" type="appears in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">1.51</rating>
<name>Philippos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55645" type="appears in" update="2013-05-06">
<rating votes="1">4.27</rating>
<name>Eurydice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eurydice was a mid. 4th century BCE Macedonian noblewoman, niece of Attalus, and last of the seven wives of Philip II of Macedon.</description>
<picture>136322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="12974" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虐殺行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Vanquished Arise</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il massacro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakusatsugyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12975" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔王誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Prophecy Born This Day</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La nascita del distruttore del mondo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou Tanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12976" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔王邂逅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Failure of Diplomacy</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Incontro con l`avversario</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maou Kaikou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12977" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔都彷徨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Here Shall Stand Alexandria</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mato Houkou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12978" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ペルセポリスの炎上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unification Before Division</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Persepoli in fiamme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Persepolis no Enjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12979" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カタルシス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prophecy Come To Pass</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katharsis</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12980" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狂えるソクラテス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">God of Creation</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Colui che potrebbe far impazzire Socrate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurueru Sokrates</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12981" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガウガメラの死闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Persia Shall Fall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gaugamela no Shitou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12982" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サモトラケの魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret of Samothrace</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La strega di Samotracia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samothrace no Majo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12983" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アモンの神託</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Oracle of Ammon</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`oracolo di Ammone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amon no Shintaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12984" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">陰謀の序曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Thunder of Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inbou no Jokyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12985" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暗殺の音階</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ascension to the Throne</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Concerto per un assassinio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ansatsu no Onkai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="12986" update="2007-06-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴルディオのきびき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gordian Knot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gordio no Kibiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="172998" update="2015-11-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
