<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11979" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Watashi ga Motete Dou Sunda</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">watashimote</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">私がモテてどうすんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kiss Him, Not Me</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Bésalo a él, no a mí</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我太受欢迎了该怎么办</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4734" approval="1" total="1">Yamato Nadeshiko Shichi Henge</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="778494">If you don`t know what a fujoshi is and what problems they have, just watch this quite funny and nice series. The animation is beautiful on the one hand and ... special on the other, but its entertaining for the story. Shoud be longer `caus the ending is not a real ending.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="363469">The ending was frustrating in the way that most Harem anime endings are, and there is one guy who outshines every other guy by so much that it shouldn`t have even been a competition. That said, I enjoyed this anime quite a bit, in spite of that fact that I don`t like the genre. Recommended</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="518231">Gave me a good time ^_^
Pleasant feeling and i laughed a lot :) .
Give it a try :)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/watamote/</url>
<creators>
<name id="12920" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oosawa Mina</name>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="12518" type="Character Design">Tamura Kazuhiko</name>
<name id="3465" type="Series Composition">Yokote Michiko</name>
<name id="5865" type="Direction">Ishiodori Hiroshi</name>
<name id="45268" type="Original Work">Junko</name>
<name id="5818" type="Music">Kawada Ruka</name>
</creators>
<description>Serinuma Kae is what you`d call a "fujoshi." When she sees boys getting along with each other, she loves to indulge in wild fantasies! One day her favorite anime character dies and the shock causes her to lose a ton of weight. Then four hot guys at school ask her out, but that isn`t exciting to her at all — she`d rather see them date each other!
Source: ANN
Note: The first episode received an early screening at a special event on September 19, 2016. The regular TV broadcast started on October 7, 2016.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="615">4.89</permanent>
<temporary count="617">6.46</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>187606.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18135</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32899</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/watamote/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kiss_Him,_Not_Me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>私がモテてどうすんだ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4302</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355964</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19505</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_watamote</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B079VV9L94</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3610" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-12-19">
<name>game references</name>
<description>Be it the sound of a 1-up being grabbed, three golden triangles appearing on someones shirt or a blatant parody portraying a monkey throwing barrels down a poorly constructed facility, this anime contains characteristics dedicated to the remembrance/worship of an actual video game.</description>
<picurl>166123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="84242" type="main character in" update="2016-10-15">
<rating votes="5">3.62</rating>
<name>Nanashima Nozomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192881.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23393" picture="158026.jpg">Koumoto Keisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84243" type="main character in" update="2016-10-15">
<rating votes="7">5.98</rating>
<name>Nishina Shima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84244" type="main character in" update="2016-10-15">
<rating votes="4">5.26</rating>
<name>Igarashi Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192887.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84245" type="main character in" update="2016-10-15">
<rating votes="6">8.69</rating>
<name>Mutsumi Asuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192882.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84246" type="main character in" update="2016-10-15">
<rating votes="5">3.25</rating>
<name>Shinomiya Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84247" type="main character in" update="2017-05-27">
<rating votes="5">8.23</rating>
<name>Serinuma Kae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85512" type="appears in" update="2016-10-15">
<name>Shion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192893.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85513" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-15">
<rating votes="2">3.19</rating>
<name>Nakano Amane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85514" type="appears in" update="2016-10-15">
<name>Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192892.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29851" picture="139189.jpg">Awazu Takatsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85515" type="appears in" update="2016-10-15">
<name>Serinuma Mitsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192884.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="372" picture="141584.jpg">Sugimoto Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85516" type="appears in" update="2016-10-15">
<name>Serinuma Takurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192885.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85517" type="appears in" update="2017-05-27">
<rating votes="2">7.70</rating>
<name>Serinuma Kae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192886.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85518" type="appears in" update="2016-10-15">
<name>Tono</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192890.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85519" type="appears in" update="2017-05-27">
<name>Akane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192891.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29613" picture="78208.jpg">Aoi Shouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91834" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-18">
<name>Mutsumi Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208534.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="179816" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">できるかな? リアル乙女ゲー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Can She Do It? A Real Life Otome Game</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vais-je y arriver ? Un jeu de drague dans la vie réelle !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dekiru kana? Real Otome Game</title>
<summary>"I love seeing guys get along more than anything!" Serinuma Kae is a second year high school student who`s always entertaining such wild thoughts and pairing boys up everywhere. Everyday, she enjoys discussing her fujoshi flavored fantasies with her like-minded friend, A-chan. But one day, Kae`s favorite anime character dies, and she suddenly loses a lot of weight in shock. She becomes a head turning beauty, and because of that, gets asked out on a date by four hot guys from her school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721111</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180260" update="2016-12-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマスは聖地で♥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas in the Holy Land</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Noël en Terre sainte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas wa Seichi de</title>
<summary>With Christmas around the corner, Nanashima suggests everyone have a party. However, Kae says she can`t possibly make it because she`s going to Comiket. In the end, everyone decides to go to Comiket together, then have a Christmas party afterwards. The boys are bewildered at their first visit to Comiket, and feel as though everyone is looking at them askance. Meanwhile, Kae is busy bustling about the entire venue, until she runs into some trouble at the cosplay plaza. And then, a handsome cosplayer saves her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721117</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180261" update="2016-12-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天高く乙女萌ゆる秋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Clear and Blue Autumn Sky, and Passionate Otome</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">En automne, le ciel est haut et les fujoshis sont au taquet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ten Takaku Otome Moyuru Aki</title>
<summary>For the school cultural festival, Kae`s class decides to host a cosplay café. Kae is fired up about designing the costumes not only for her classmates Igarashi and Nanashima, but also for Shinomiya, who`s playing the role of a princess for his class which is putting on a play. But as excited as she gets about the costumes, she also has to help the history club set up its exhibition. With everyone`s help, she manages to finish everything in time for the festival. And what follows is a date with the four hot guys...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721115</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180262" update="2016-12-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議なお部屋と4人のDK[男子高校生]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strange Room and the Four High School Boys</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une étrange pièce et 4 beaux gosses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi na Oheya to 4 Nin no Danshi Koukousei</title>
<summary>After having lost weight, Kae does extremely well in PE class. Seeing that, some girls from the soccer club ask Kae to help play in a practice match. Kae has full confidence in her soccer knowledge, but she actually only knows soccer from soccer anime and has never actually played herself. And so, Igarashi from the soccer club, as well as Nanashima, Shinomiya and Mutsumi try to help her out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721113</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181075" update="2016-10-15">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181076" update="2016-10-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181356" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺はアドバンテージ・マイナス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m at a Disadvantage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`ai l`avantage ou pas ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore wa Advantage Minus</title>
<summary>After the group`s pilgrimage is over, Nanashima begins to notice there`s been a change in Kae`s relationship with others in the group. Nanashima realizes his only advantage is that he looks like Shion, and with Shion out of the picture, he`s lagging behind the rest. While dancing a dance from Puri Puri Moon with his little sister, Nanashima decides he needs to be more proactive. Meanwhile, Kae has decided to take up a part-time job at Usami Land to raise funds for upcoming Kachu Rabu events.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721125</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181357" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖地巡礼かちゅ☆らぶの旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On a Journey to the Holy Land of Kachu Rabu</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pèlerinage en Terre sainte de Kachû Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seichijunrei Kachu Love no Tabi</title>
<summary>Everyone goes together on a one night trip in order to attend the death anniversary of Hyakki Sametora, the samurai the lord in Kachu Rabu is modelled after. Both Kae and Nishina are enraptured by the real armor and helmet Akane is modelled after, and a portrait of Sametora. After, Kae and the gang decide to go to a small island in a lake where Sametora`s head is rumored to be buried. But what will happen next?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721123</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181358" update="2016-12-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カップリング戦争勃発!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let the Shipping Wars Begin!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La guerre des couples !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Coupling Sensou Bappatsu!</title>
<summary>A new anime, Katchu Ranbu, or Kachu Rabu for short, has started, and it`s hugely popular. Bot Kae and Nishina are elated about the show, until they find out that they each ship Lord x Akane and Akane x Lord respectively and get into a huge fight. Their friendship appears to be heading to a halt, so Igarashi, Nanashima, Shinomiya and Mutsumi try to help the pair out. Unfortunately, it looks like their reverse ship war is just heating up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721121</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181359" update="2016-12-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">元に戻ってどうすんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Back to My Original Self! What Should I Do?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour à la case départ ! Que faire ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moto ni Modotte Dou Sunda</title>
<summary>The anime Mirage Saga is hosting a Valentine`s event, and Kae decides to make a chocolate for Shun for the event. As Kae fusses over what chocolate to make in order to perfectly capture Shion`s beauty, Nishina suggests Kae try making a 3-D chocolate sculpture. Kae agrees, and throws herself into making one, but is unable to improve in her ability to sculpt the chocolate at all. Nishina can`t bear to see Kae saddened by her situation, so suggests Kae use the chocolate she made instead. What will Kae decide to do?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721119</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182439" update="2017-01-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私がモテてどうすんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kiss Him, Not Me</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Que voulez-vous que je fasse de cette popularité ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi ga Motete Dou Sunda</title>
<summary>After winning against Kazuma in their duel, Mutsumi tells Kae how he feels about her. Igarashi, Nanashima, Shinomiya and Nishina are shocked by this sudden move on Mutsumi`s part, and take action to prevent him from making any more advances on Kae. However, in the end, they decide to all get together and tell Kae how they honestly feel about her along with Mutsumi. Kae decides to go on a date with all of them individually to decide who`s feelings she will accept.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721133</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182440" update="2017-01-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いざ出陣!! 城ガード!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forward! Guard the Castle!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">A l`attaque ! Duel au jeu de cartes "châteaux" !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iza Shutsujin!! Shiro Guard!</title>
<summary>Mutsumi tells his brother Kazuma, "Serinuma-san is my girlfriend." However, Kazuma keeps on pursuing Kae, now with even more gusto. Igarashi, Nanashima, Shinomiya and Nishina all try to band together to get in Kazuma`s way, but Kazuma has a way of making sport of their efforts.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721131</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182441" update="2016-12-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄, 襲来☆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brother Invasion!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`attaque du grand frère !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ani, Shuurai</title>
<summary>Mutsumi finds a hidden treasure map in the History Club room and invites everyone to go treasure hunting. Igarashi, Nanashima, Shinomiya and Nishina are less than thrilled about the idea, but after finding out Kae would be going alone with Mutsumi, they decide to go too. The four of them are confused by Mutsumi, because he treats Kae now the same way he always had. And so, they decide to ask him how he really feels.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721129</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182442" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海だ水着だ本気出す!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beach! Bathing Suits! Time to Get Serious!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mer et maillots de bain !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi Da Mizugi Da Honki Dasu!</title>
<summary>The six go to Nishina`s holiday house by the ocean to swim. Everyone has fun bodyboarding, eating at a beach hut, and playing beach volleyball. But while doing so, Shinomiya realizes just how unreliable he is and loses confidence in himself. What exactly can he accomplish? After another failed attempt to be useful at the evening barbecue, Shinomiya runs off on his own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721127</identifier>
<identifier>kiss-him-not-me</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
