<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11977" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>22</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2016-09-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kidou Senshi Gundam UC RE:0096</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">機動戦士ガンダムユニコーン RE:0096</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Gundam UC Re:0096</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">機動戰士GUNDAM UC RE:0096</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">機動戰士高達UC RE:0096</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">机动战士高达UC RE:0096</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">機動戦士ガンダムUC RE:0096</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mobile Suit Gundam Unicorn Re:0096</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">机动战士高达独角兽 RE:0096</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6517" type="Summary">Kidou Senshi Gundam Unicorn</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.gundam-unicorn.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3331" type="Animation Character Design">Takahashi Kumiko</name>
<name id="3117" type="Story Composition">Fukui Harutoshi</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="1410" type="Direction">Furuhashi Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="6722" type="Music">Sawano Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="11716" type="Chief Animation Direction">Genma Nobuhiko</name>
<name id="3331" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takahashi Kumiko</name>
</creators>
<description>U.C. 0096. Three years after Char`s Rebellion, Banagher Links, a boy living at the manufacturing colony Industrial 7, meets a mysterious girl who calls herself Audrey Burne. Audrey claims that she is trying to stop the Vist Foundation from handing over Laplace`s Box to the Neo Zeon remnants known as the Sleeves, an act which could spark another war, and Banagher decides to help her. But the colony becomes a battlefield as fighting breaks out between the Sleeves and the Earth Federation Forces, who have also come to stop the handover...
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="244">6.46</permanent>
<temporary count="246">6.88</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>185213.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18087</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32792</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gundam-unicorn.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4130</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355841</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3216" parentid="2626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>Universal Century</name>
<description>Refers to the Universal Century timeline in Gundam anime. Gundam anime with this tag all belong in the same universe.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13498" type="main character in" update="2010-04-07">
<rating votes="29">3.25</rating>
<name>Banagher Links</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Banagher Links is a boy who is a student at Anaheim Industry Technical School in the colony Industrial 7. He is described as seeing war as something akin to fiction, as he was born after the One Year War ended and did not experience the more isolated wars that followed it. However, upon meeting http://anidb.net/ch13499 [Audrey], he is drawn into a new conflict. He does a part-time job clearing space debris with a miniature MS.</description>
<picture>39640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13499" type="main character in" update="2018-08-16">
<rating votes="19">6.83</rating>
<name>Audrey Burne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Audrey Burne is a girl from a noble family, whose life changes after she meets http://anidb.net/ch13498 [Banagher]. Her name appears to be derived from famed actress Audrey Hepburn. She is actually http://anidb.net/ch16540 [Mineva Lao Zabi] under a pseudonym.</description>
<picture>39641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="441" picture="171611.jpg">Fujimura Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13500" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="1">1.22</rating>
<name>Takuya Irei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another student of Anaheim Industry Technical School and also Banagher`s roommate. He wishes to become a test pilot for Anaheim Electronics and he knows a lot about mobile suits.</description>
<picture>39642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13501" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="4">4.17</rating>
<name>Micott Bartsch</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who commutes to a high school adjacent the Anaheim Industry Technical School. Her father is the plant manager of Industrial 7.</description>
<picture>39643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13502" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="10">1.14</rating>
<name>Riddhe Marcenas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>MS pilot of Earth Federation`s Londo Bell team. Son from a family of politicians. He entered the army opposing his family wishes for him to be a politician. He wants to make a name on his own and became a pilot. Originally pilots the mass-produced RGZ-95 ReZEL, a successor to the RGZ-91 ReGZ(Refined Gundam Zeta), eventually becomes the second pilot of the RX-0 Gundam Unicorn Unit-2 "Banshee"</description>
<picture>39644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13503" type="appears in" update="2010-05-10">
<rating votes="3">4.26</rating>
<name>Mihiro Oiwakken</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A newly appointed female officer onboard the Nahel Argama.</description>
<picture>39645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13504" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="29">7.97</rating>
<name>Marida Cruz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female pilot of the MS "Kshatriya" on board the Garancieres. A capable pilot and artificial Newtype. She refers to captain Zaberoa as "Master" and loyally carry out his orders. Originally known as "Puru Twelve", she is actually a clone of Elpeo Puru. She was awakened by Glemy Toto and fought with her sisters during the first Neo Zeon movement. After the fight with Chara Soon in U.C.0089.1.17, one of the clones survived and was retrieved by an MS pod. She was then sold into sex slavery, and from then on she worked as a prostitute. Before coming under the protection of Suberoa, she experienced countless pregnancies and abortions and her body is scarred by the abuse of her customers. During an examination on board Nahal Argama when she was captured, it was ascertained that she cannot bear children anymore.
Later assigned to the Unicorn Gundam Unit-2 "Banshee".</description>
<picture>39646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13505" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-28">
<rating votes="10">8.20</rating>
<name>Full Frontal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The mysterious leader of the Neo Zeon remnant forces who is described as the "2nd coming of Char". Like Char Aznable, he is a blonde man whose face is hidden behind a mask, and he wears a red uniform and pilots a red mobile suit. Similar to Char, he holds the Neo Zeon remnants together with his high charisma. Whether the name is an alias is unspecified. On the contrary, his name holds the meaning of "stark naked"(or fully exposed) although it could easily be reference to a full frontal assault. He plays around Banagher and the others with his puzzling speech and behaviour. He is fighting against the Earth Federation for "the secret" of the foundation of the Universal Century.
His face and tone closely resemble Char`s. Nahel Argama`s captain Otto, who watched Char`s archived recordings, remarked that the voice is just like it. He is later revealed to be a cyber NewType who was genetically altered to resemble the missing-in-action Char Aznable. His memories were then implanted from the psycho frame of one of the Mobile suits previously piloted by Char (possibly Sazabi).</description>
<picture>39647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13506" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="8">1.30</rating>
<name>Angelo Sauper</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A MS pilot of "The Sleeves". Team leader of the Frontal bodyguards. He adores Full Frontal. Pilots a purple Geara Zulu.</description>
<picture>39648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13507" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="3">7.15</rating>
<name>Suberoa Zinnerman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Captain of "Garancieres", the ship of "The Sleeves" which is disguised as a cargo ship.</description>
<picture>39649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11025" picture="43745.jpg">Tezuka Hideaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13510" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="1">5.05</rating>
<name>Cardeas Vist</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grandchild of Syam Vist, second generation head of the Vist family. Was a helicopter pilot in the Earth Federation when he was young. He is the real father of the protagonist, Banagher Links. With his dying breath, he entrusted the Unicorn Gundam to Banagher.</description>
<picture>39655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="24725.jpg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13512" type="appears in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="1">2.31</rating>
<name>Syam Vist</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy born in a small country located in Western South Asia. He became a terrorist because of the twisted society and tough life. During the terrorist activity at the official residence "Laplace" he came into possession of a strange object (U.C.001). Though underworld connections he married into the Vist family and became the head of the influential Vist Foundation. He is still alive in U.C.0096 as he used cryonics.</description>
<picture>39657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="201" picture="17016.jpg">Nagai Ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13513" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-03">
<rating votes="3">1.57</rating>
<name>Alberto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A staff of Anaheim Electronics who board the Nahal Argama to stop the opening of the "Laplace`s box". Shows attachment to the "Unicorn".</description>
<picture>39658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45187" type="appears in" update="2012-05-26">
<rating votes="1">5.05</rating>
<name>Otto Mitas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The captain of the assault landing ship Nahel Argama, which is assigned to the Londo Bell unit of the Earth Federation Forces. He holds the rank of Captain.</description>
<picture>88444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45188" type="appears in" update="2012-05-26">
<rating votes="1">5.05</rating>
<name>Liam Borrinea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female officer who serves as second in command of the assault landing ship Nahel Argama, which is assigned to the Londo Bell unit of the Earth Federation Forces. She holds the rank of Commander.</description>
<picture>88445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25" picture="16608.jpg">Watanabe Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45198" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-26">
<rating votes="6">7.47</rating>
<name>Bright Noa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The commander of the Earth Federation Forces` Londo Bell auxiliary unit. He holds the rank of Captain. Ever since the One Year War, he has been known throughout the world as a commander of Newtype corps, but the Federation Forces leadership regards his career history as dangerous, and he has been removed from the military mainstream. As the captain of the Londo Bell flagship Ra Cailum, he becomes involved in the events surrounding Laplace`s Box.</description>
<picture>88460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45210" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-05-26">
<rating votes="3">3.69</rating>
<name>Martha Vist Carbine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A grandchild of Syam Vist. In order to maintain the Vist Foundation`s control over the Earth Sphere, she has married into the family of Chairman Carbine of Anaheim Electronics, and with the death of her brother Cardeas she is now the acting head of the Vist Foundation as well.</description>
<picture>88472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17052" picture="234928.jpg">Shiota Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45212" type="appears in" update="2012-05-26">
<rating votes="2">1.21</rating>
<name>Ronan Marcenas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Riddhe`s father, and a member of the Earth Federation`s Central Assembly. He serves as chairman of the Council on Colony Relations, which is jokingly referred to as the shadow cabinet.</description>
<picture>88474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="544" picture="238510.jpg">Ogawa Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45213" type="appears in" update="2012-05-26">
<rating votes="5">3.53</rating>
<name>Loni Garvey</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mobile suit pilot in the Zeon remnant group led by Kirks. She is the daughter of the wealthy Mahdi Garvey, a former Zeon soldier who brought the remnants together. Filled with hatred for the Earth Federation Forces who killed her father, she seeks revenge as the pilot of the huge mobile armor Shamblo.</description>
<picture>88475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="176681" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">96年目の出発[たびだち]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departure 0096</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Départ 0096</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">96 Nenme no Tabidachi</title>
<summary>On the day of the ceremony marking the transition from the A.D. to the Universal Century calendar, the space station Laplace, official residence of the Earth Federation prime minister, is destroyed by a terrorist bombing. One of the terrorists, a young man named Syam Vist, is caught in the explosion but barely manages to survive. He obtains a forbidden box that will come to be known as Laplace`s Box.
Almost a century later, in Universal Century 0096...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702375</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176682" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦士, バナージ・リンクス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Banagher Links, Soldier</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Banagher Links, soldat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senshi, Banagher Links</title>
<summary>Attacked by the Banshee, Banagher and the Unicorn Gundam are captured and brought aboard the Ra Cailum. Riddhe is surprised to learn that Alberto is Banagher`s older half-brother. Riddhe`s father Ronan has handed Mineva over to Alberto`s aunt Martha, who transfers her aboard the giant airlifter Garuda as a pawn to get Banagher to talk. With no avenue of escape, Banagher still continues to hide the new coordinates to Laplace`s Box. Bright, the commander of Londo Bell, recognizes that Banagher has the same possibilities as previous generations of Gundam pilots and gives him encouragement. Via Kai Shiden, Bright contacts the Garencieres to plan a joint operation to rescue Mineva. As he makes plans to send the Nahel Argama to provide backup, he sends Banagher to the Garuda, where Mineva is being held.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715341</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176683" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">個人の戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Private War</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une guerre privée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kojin no Sensou</title>
<summary>Tri-Stars mobile suit team intercepts and destroys Kirks, who raised Loni like a father. Filled with rage and sorrow, Loni continues her massacre. The wishes of the dead Kirks bring her back to her senses, but the fury of the Zeon remnants makes the Shamblo run wild again, until Riddhe uses the Unicorn Gundam`s beam magnum to destroy it. Stunned by Loni`s death, Banagher is now confronted by the approach of a black Unicorn Gundam.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702399</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176684" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリントン攻防</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle at Torrington</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataille à Torrington</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Torrington Koubou</title>
<summary>As they cross the desert, Banagher learns of Zinnerman`s tragic past, and how his family were killed by the Federation Forces. He decides to head for the Torrington base, where new information will be disclosed, to look for a better way to use Laplace`s Box. Loni, the pilot of the Shamblo that attacked the Earth Federation capital of Dakar, urges Frontal to attack the Torrington base. Meanwhile, Riddhe`s Delta Plus joins the Ra Cailum, the warship commanded by Captain Bright. The Ra Cailum then learns that the Torrington base is under attack. Zeon remnants have gathered in response to Kirks`s call, and the Shamblo has appeared in the Sydney Bay,　indiscriminately attacking the nearby city. The fury of the Zeon remnants is driving Loni to commit a massacre.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702395</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176685" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">灼熱の大地から</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From the Scorching Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De la terre brûlante</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakunetsu no Daichi kara</title>
<summary>After saving Banagher and the Unicorn Gundam, which were falling toward Earth, the Garencieres crash-lands in the Western Sahara. Meanwhile, Zeon remnants who have been hiding on Earth launch a diversionary attack on the Earth Federation capital at Dakar. Ronan, a Federation government official, orders Bright Noa to hunt down the Garencieres. Having descended to Earth with Riddhe, Mineva flees the Marcenas household out of fear that she will be used for political purposes. But the words of an old Earth-born man, who speaks of the good intentions of those who carried out the settlement of space, help her realize what she should do, and she turns herself in to her pursuers. At the same time, Alberto`s aunt Martha is reconditioning the Cyber-Newtype Marida so that she can be controlled. And Zinnerman decides to cross the desert to make contact with the Zeon remnants, taking Banagher with him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702393</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176686" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">リトリビューション</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Retribution</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Châtiment</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Retribution</title>
<summary>The Unicorn Gundam reaches the wreckage of Laplace, and the La+ Program`s seal is broken. A speech given 96 years earlier by Ricardo Marcenas, the first prime minister of the Earth Federation government, begins playing back. Daguza realizes that the Gundam is more than just a killing machine to eradicate Zeon, and he tells Banagher that it incorporates something else that is controlled by a human heart. But then Frontal`s Sinanju launches an attack, escorted by Angelo and the rest of his guards, and Daguza is killed. Responding to Banagher`s anger, the Unicorn Gundam activates its NT-D system and changes into Destroy Mode, overpowering the Sinanju. However, Gilboa`s machine is shot down while acting as a shield. As the Unicorn Gundam falls toward Earth, Mineva witnesses it as a descending beam of light.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702391</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176687" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラプラス, 始まりの地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laplace, Where It All Began</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Laplace, où tout a commencé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Laplace, Hajimari no Chi</title>
<summary>Marida, now a prisoner of the Federation, tells Banagher to keep on saying, "Even so..." She says that he has the power to awaken another system that sleeps within the Unicorn Gundam. Marida herself is to be transferred to Earth on the instructions of Martha Carbine, Syam Vist`s granddaughter and currently the acting head of the Vist Foundation. It was Martha who ordered Alberto to prevent the opening of Laplace`s Box, the Foundation`s lifeline. Meanwhile, Banagher heads for the new set of coordinates revealed by the La+ Program. This is the wreckage of Laplace, the prime minister`s residence that was destroyed by a terrorist bombing at the dawn of the Universal Century. At first, Banagher resists Daguza`s orders, but after he learns from Otto that Daguza was the one who led the operation to rescue him, Banagher agrees to launch in the Unicorn Gundam.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702389</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176688" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">パラオ攻略戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of Palau</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bataille de Palaos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Palau Kouryakusen</title>
<summary>Together with the ECOAS special forces group, the Nahel Argama of the Earth Federation Forces` Londo Bell unit begins an operation to recapture Banagher and the Unicorn Gundam. The resource satellite Palau, stronghold of the Neo Zeon remnants known as the Sleeves, becomes the newest battlefield. Amid the chaos Banagher is reunited with Mineva, who tells him that she is going to Earth to seek the help of Riddhe`s father. Meanwhile, Frontal attempts to use the Cyber-Newtype Marida to trigger the Unicorn Gundam`s NT-D (Newtype Destroyer) system, which is the key to Laplace`s Box. As Banagher fights against Marida and her Kshatriya, he learns of her past history and the pain within her heart, thanks to the resonance between fellow Newtypes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702387</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176689" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">その仮面の下に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Mask</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sous le masque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Kamen no Shimo ni</title>
<summary>Removing his mask and revealing his face, Frontal requests the cooperation of Banagher, who can activate the Unicorn Gundam. When Banagher refuses, Angelo berates him for killing one of his subordinates. As Banagher struggles with the knowledge of his guilt, Marida takes him to shrine inside Palau. Meanwhile, the Nahel Argama prepares for an operation to recapture the Unicorn Gundam. Captain Otto is frustrated by his impossible orders from staff headquarters, but Daguza, the commander of the operation, asks him to also think of it as a mission to rescue Banagher. A Federation Forces spy notifies Banagher of the upcoming surprise attack, and he is appalled to learn that Palau will now become a battlefield. At the same time, Micott discovers that Riddhe, having gotten to know Mineva, plans to help her escape to Earth. Learning of Mineva`s resolve, Micott lets them go.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702385</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176690" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突・赤い彗星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash with the Red Comet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Affrontement avec la comète rouge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu: Akai Suisei</title>
<summary>Daguza has taken Mineva (or Audrey) hostage, but Frontal rejects his demand for a ceasefire and declares that he will sink the Nahel Argama. In order to save Audrey, Banagher sorties in the Unicorn Gundam, with the support of the Anaheim executive Alberto. However, Alberto`s true intention is to have Frontal destroy the Unicorn Gundam, and thus block his path to obtaining the Box. The Unicorn Gundam changes into Destroy Mode, and Banagher engages the Sinanju, but he is taken captive along with the Unicorn Gundam when Marida`s Kshatriya launches a surprise attack. Banagher is dragged away to the resource satellite Palau, the stronghold of the Neo Zeon remnants known as the Sleeves. The masked Full Frontal is waiting there to meet him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702383</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176691" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フル・フロンタル追撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Full Frontal`s Pursuit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Poursuivis par Full Frontal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Full Frontal Tsuigeki</title>
<summary>After repulsing the Kshatriya, Banagher loses consciousness, and along with the Unicorn Gundam, he is retrieved by the Earth Federation Forces warship Nahel Argama. The ship has also rescued Audrey, as well as Banagher`s friends Takuya and Micott. Zinnerman of the Sleeves detects the Nahel Argama`s position via a clever trap, and the ship comes under a fierce attack by Full Frontal, known as the second coming of the Red Comet, and his mobile suit Sinanju. Audrey begs Banagher to escape the ship with her in order to dispose of the Unicorn Gundam, the key to Laplace`s Box. But Daguza of the Federation`s ECOAS special forces group takes her prisoner, demanding that Frontal halt his attack. For Audrey is actually Mineva Zabi, the Zeon princess.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702381</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176692" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">それはガンダムと呼ばれた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">They Called It Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ils l`appelaient Gundam</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Gundam to Yobareta</title>
<summary>The negotiations between Cardeas and Zinnerman break down as a mobile suit battle begins inside the colony, claiming the lives of Banagher`s classmates. Banagher rushes back to Magallanica to help Audrey, but loses his way, and in an industrial block he discovers a white mobile suit with a single horn. Cardeas has been mortally wounded by Alberto, who infiltrated Magallanica, and he now reveals that he is Banagher`s long-estranged father. Entrusting Banagher with the hope that he can change the fate of the Vist family, who have been cursed by Laplace`s Box, Cardeas gives him the Unicorn Gundam, the key to the Box, and then disappears amid the flames. As Banagher`s suppressed childhood memories return, he activates the Unicorn Gundam and confronts the Sleeves mobile suit Kshatriya. He pushes it out of the colony, but finds himself in peril as it counterattacks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702379</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176693" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最初の血</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Premier sang</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saisho no Chi</title>
<summary>Evading Marida, who has come to take Audrey back to the Garencieres, Banagher finally manages to get Audrey to the mansion in Magallanica where she hopes to meet with Cardeas, the current head of the Vist Foundation. Here he sees the "Lady and the Unicorn" tapestry, and feels a strange sense of déjà vu. Cardeas appears, sending Banagher away and then refusing Audrey`s plea that he halt the handover of Laplace`s Box, which could start another war. At the same time, the Earth Federation Forces assault landing ship Nahel Argama, which is carrying an ECOAS special forces team on a secret mission to stop the Box from changing hands, is approaching Industrial 7. Zinnerman and his comrades, who are members of a Neo Zeon remnant group known as the Sleeves who have survived Char`s Rebellion, begin negotiations to transfer the Box. But what Cardeas is offering them is merely its key. Zinnerman is also suspicious of Cardeas`s claim that he is keeping Audrey under his protection. Then they learn that Federation Forces mobile suits have engaged the Sleeves in battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702377</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176822" update="2016-04-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176823" update="2016-04-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode C1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178154" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイド共栄圏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Side Co-Prosperity Sphere</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La sphère de coprospérité des Sides</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Side Kyoueiken</title>
<summary>Now on the run from the Federation Forces, the Nahel Argama has taken the desperate step of forming a joint front with the Sleeves. Though his crew resist the idea, Otto orders them to allow Frontal aboard the ship, in an attempt to learn his true intentions. Mineva likewise asks Frontal what he would do if he obtained the Box, and he reveals his idea of forming a Side Co-Prosperity Sphere that would strengthen the economic ties between the Moon and the Sides, excluding Earth and weakening the Federation. The disappointed Mineva predicts that this would result in further tragedies, but nonetheless she tells Frontal that the final coordinates for Laplace`s Box are at Industrial 7`s Magallanica. Meanwhile, Riddhe has received the Banshee Norn from Alberto, and he sets off in pursuit of the Unicorn Gundam.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715347</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178155" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙[そら]で待つもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Waiting in Space</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attente dans l’espace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora de Matsu Mono</title>
<summary>With Banagher, Mineva, and the others aboard, the Garencieres takes off for space. It suffers engine trouble en route, but Banagher refuses to give up. As he struggles, the Unicorn Gundam is surrounded by a mysterious light, and its power brings the Garencieres safely to its rendezvous with the Nahel Argama. However, the Earth Federation Forces` General Staff Headquarters has decided to eliminate the Nahel Argama and the Garencieres due to their connection to Laplace`s Box. As Banagher and the others return to space, they are confronted by the huge General Revil, the biggest warship of the Federation Space Force. They are saved from this desperate predicament by Full Frontal and his Neo Zeon fleet. Having escaped the General Revil`s pursuit thanks to the Sinanju`s attack, the Nahel Argama is forced to form a join front with the Sleeves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715345</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178156" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘, 二機のユニコーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash of the Two Unicorns</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`affrontement des deux Unicorn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitou, Niki no Unicorn</title>
<summary>The Garencieres launches an operation to rescue Mineva and Marida, and Alberto orders Marida to stop them. Herbage changes the Unicorn Gundam into Destroy Mode and confronts the Banshee. Meanwhile, Mineva has escaped Martha`s hands, and rejects Riddhe`s offer of help. Trusting that Banagher will catch her, she throws herself into the air. Just as Mineva hopes, Banagher saves her and takes her to the Garencieres, then heads back to the Garuda to rescue Marida and Zinnerman. Marida is controlled by her hatred of the Gundam, but Zinnerman`s appearance disrupts her determination. In his anger, Riddhe reminds Marida that the Banshee is also a Gundam. She is ejected from the Banshee, and rescued by Zinnerman.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715343</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179152" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラプラスの箱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Laplace`s Box</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Boîte de Laplace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Laplace no Hako</title>
<summary>Banagher`s great-grandfather Syam Vist has been waiting for him and Mineva at Magallanica. In the first year of the Universal Century, Syam carried out the terrorist bombing of the Earth Federation prime minister`s official residence, and he has used the Charter of the Universal Century that he obtained at that point, now known as "Laplace`s Box," to do business with the Federation. However, troubled by the stagnant state of the Federation, he worked with his grandson Cardeas in an attempt to find someone who could be entrusted with the world`s future. They used the Unicorn Gundam, which had the ability to discover true Newtypes, as the key to the Box. Having passed this test, along with Mineva, Banagher will now receive the Box from Syam and intends to use it for everyone`s benefit. But then Full Frontal appears in the cold sleep room, claiming that he is the Box`s legitimate inheritor. Banagher and Frontal begin a final battle over the Box.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715355</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179153" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再び光る宇宙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Cosmic Glow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une autre lueur cosmique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatabi Hikaru Uchuu</title>
<summary>Banagher struggles against the psycho-jammers of Angelo`s Rozen Zulu. Meanwhile, as Riddhe confronts Marida, he is overwhelmed by a thought resonance phenomenon and destroys the Kshatriya Repaired. Marida`s last thoughts reach Zinnerman, Mineva, and the others, warning them that the sector is dangerous. With the shock of her death, the Unicorn Gundam emits psycho-waves beyond measurement, and the bewildered Angelo destroys his own machine. With Zinnerman`s help, the Nahel Argama successfully holds off the Sleeves fleet and reaches Industrial 7 airspace. At the same time, Bright enters the Cheyenne base to confront Martha and Riddhe`s father Ronan. And at Magallanica, where Banagher and Mineva are headed, Syam Vist awaits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715353</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179154" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命の戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fateful Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bataille fatidique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei no Tatakai</title>
<summary>As the Nahel Argama rushes toward Industrial 7, its course is blocked by Sleeves mobile suits. Unless it can break through the enemy lines, Full Frontal will be allowed to obtain Laplace`s Box. Also standing in the way is Riddhe`s Banshee Norn, which confronts Banagher`s Full Armor Unicorn Gundam. Meanwhile, Bright learns from Kai Shiden that an operation is under way to activate the Gryps 2 colony laser and annihilate the Box, and he hurries in the Ra Cailum to the Cheyenne base where the control center is located. Riddhe, trapped by a blood curse, begins running wild. Despite her injuries, Marida comes to the rescue in the Kshatriya Repaired, and orders Banagher to go on ahead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715351</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179155" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪還! ネェル・アーガマ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nahel Argama Recaptured</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Nahel Argama recapturé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakkan! Nahel Argama</title>
<summary>Banagher is despondent now that Full Frontal has learned the final coordinates to Laplace`s Box. Marida encourages him, saying that his chance will come if he holds onto his dreams. Meanwhile, Takuya and a few others have secretly called in a Federation Forces patrol ship and are awaiting the opportunity for a counterattack, but they are discovered by Angelo. Taking them hostage, Angelo demands the destruction of the patrol ship, and Captain Otto decides to dissolve the joint front. As fierce fighting unfolds, Banagher confronts Frontal. Mineva also takes a stand against Frontal`s plan for a Side Co-Prosperity Sphere, and is joined by Marida. Zinnerman orders Marida to surrender, but her determination overcomes Zinnerman`s hatred. Driven back by Banagher and Marida, Frontal and his comrades escape from the Nahel Argama and head for the Box`s final coordinates.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715349</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179844" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Retur</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan</title>
<summary>An article of the Charter of the Universal Century entitled "Future" records the fact that humanity set out into space with the expectation of new possibilities. As a central figure in the Federation government, Riddhe`s father Ronan is terrified of Laplace`s Box, in which this article is recorded. Now he has approved the firing of the colony laser in order to destroy Magallanica, where the Box is located. Banagher`s and Riddhe`s Gundams successfully use a psycho-field to defend Magallanica, at the cost of Banagher being absorbed by the Unicorn Gundam. Mineva reveals the truth about the Box to people all over the world, while Otto and Zinnerman help her escape the pursuing Federation fleet. And meanwhile, urged on by the thoughts of his father Cardeas, Banagher returns to Mineva`s side.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715359</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179845" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">この世の果てへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the World`s End</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jusqu’au bout du monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Yo no Hate e</title>
<summary>As Full Frontal attempts to seize Laplace`s Box, Gael`s Silver Bullet stands in his way, only to be crushed by Frontal`s overwhelmingly superior firepower. Seeing Gael`s plight, Banagher summons the Unicorn Gundam. Riddhe also joins the fight with his Banshee Norn, and the two Gundams confront the huge mobile armor Neo Zeong. However, Frontal uses the Neo Zeong`s psycho-shards to destroy all of the Gundams` weapons. Luring Banagher to the end of space and time, he tries to plant the seeds of nihilism and despair. But Banagher refuses to give up, and he is aided by the thoughts of Lalah and others. In response, the Neo Zeong begins to self-destruct. Meanwhile, Ronan decides to use the colony laser to consign the Box to oblivion, and approves its activation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715357</identifier>
<identifier>mobile-suit-gundam-unicorn-re0096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
