<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12009" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Natsume Yuujinchou Go</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Natsume`s Book of Friends (5)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Natsume Yujin-cho 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">natsume5</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">夏目友人帳 伍</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Natsume Yujin-cho Go</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">นัตสึเมะกับบันทึกพิศวง ภาค 5</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">夏目友人帐 伍</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12675" type="Sequel">Natsume Yuujinchou Roku</anime>
<anime id="8667" type="Prequel">Natsume Yuujinchou Shi</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.natsume-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="40621" type="Animation Work">Shuka</name>
<name id="15726" type="Character Design">Takada Akira</name>
<name id="2315" type="Series Composition">Murai Sadayuki</name>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="3542" type="Original Work">Midorikawa Yuki</name>
<name id="17699" type="Direction">Deai Kotomi</name>
<name id="4359" type="Chief Direction">Oomori Takahiro</name>
<name id="6006" type="Music">Yoshimori Makoto</name>
<name id="7033" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takada Akira</name>
<name id="9263" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Hideki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on fantasy manga series by http://anidb.net/cr3542 [Midorikawa Yuki].
Note: The first episode received an early screening at a special event on 01.10.2016. The regular TV broadcast started on October 5, 2016.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="960">8.73</permanent>
<temporary count="966">8.12</temporary>
<review count="1">6.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>190395.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18168</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32983</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>18849</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>34534</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.natsume-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/natsume5/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Natsume's_Book_of_Friends#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>夏目友人帳</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4300</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19501</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>NatsumeYujincho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5781" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>exorcism</name>
<description>Eviction of demons or other spiritual entities from a person or place which they are believed to have possessed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6004" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>development hell</name>
<description>Due to unforeseen circumstances, the production or release of this anime has been pushed back, stalled, or cancelled one or more times from when it was first announced.
While some of them have eventually been completed, others might have only had a trailer released or have been changed into another format (e.g. a TV series turned into an OVA).
Common reasons for a work to become stuck in development hell include creative differences, legal issues, financial problems, scheduling conflicts or the death of an involved creator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1806" type="main character in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="448">7.98</rating>
<name>Natsume Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character of the story. Like his grandmother, http://anidb.net/ch1808 [Natsume Reiko], Takashi has the ability to see spirits. He has inherited the Book of Friends, a book of names that no one but Reiko, Takashi, and other spirits can read. Because of Takashi`s strong resemblance to Reiko, he is often mistaken for her, causing spirits who hate Reiko to chase him constantly. He decided to dissolve the Book by giving all the names back to their owners. He is accompanied by the spirit http://anidb.net/ch10380 [Madara], nicknamed "Cat" because of the spirit`s appearance, and has promised that to pass the book on to Cat when he dies.</description>
<picture>31015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1807" type="main character in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="640">8.91</rating>
<name>Nyanko-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious feline spirit. Madara was sealed in to a shrine, before accidentally getting released by Natsume. Because he was trapped for so long, Madara has shaped in to a "fortune cat" or manekineko, leading Natsume to nickname him Cat. In this form, other people could see him, leading for Natsume having to ask his guardians if he could keep him. He is a powerful spirit, who protects Natsume from others, and teaches him spells on occasion. They often fight each other, which leads to Natsume punching Madara on the face and knocking him out. Despite his protests of not being a cat, he likes to play with cat toys. Natsume is more respectful to Madara in the anime, calling him "nyanko-sensei" (master cat). Natsume has promised the Book of Friends to him when he dies.</description>
<picture>16394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1808" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="112">8.22</rating>
<name>Natsume Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Natsume`s grandmother, from whom he inherited the ability to see spirits. When Reiko was young, she was considered a freak by everyone else because of her ability. Since she believed no human could ever understand her, she turned to the spirits for companionship. Reiko`s power was extraordinarily powerful, and so she bullied spirits in to obeying her by playing games with them. If they lost, she would make them give her their names. Reiko gathered the names in to the Book of Friends, and commanded most spirits, except for Madara, who beat her in a game. Reiko died when she was young, so no one remembered her.</description>
<picture>31023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1809" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="105">7.48</rating>
<name>Tanuma Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Another student that had recently moved into the area. He is sickly and quite susceptible to illnesses. Like Natsume Takashi, he is able to detect spirits, but to a lesser degree limited to seeing merely shadows and sensing slight presence of spirits.</description>
<picture>31017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="403" picture="74821.jpg">Horie Kazuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1810" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="139">5.90</rating>
<name>Sasada Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The class president of Takashi`s class. Sasada believes that Takashi can see spirits, and constantly asks him questions about it, to which he replies that he doesn`t have such an ability. Much to Takashi`s chagrin, she wants to come along with him when he`s visiting spirits.</description>
<picture>31018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1811" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="93">5.98</rating>
<name>Natori Shuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A man who is also able to see spirits. He is a famous actor and exorcist and has a lizard tattoo that moves around on his body.</description>
<picture>31016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3700" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="115">7.80</rating>
<name>Taki Tooru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A new girl at school who doesn`t talk much because of a curse a Youkai has placed on her, which Natsume later helps her to break. She`s an omniyojist. She can`t actually see youkai but she is able to once she uses a stick to draw a magic circle. One of Natsume`s friends, Nishimura, has a crush on her, but thinks that she and Natsume are going out.</description>
<picture>68118.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3788" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="42">4.48</rating>
<name>Kitamoto Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kitamoto Atsushi is a classmate of Natsume, and best friend to Nishimura Satoru. He is a sensible and rational person. Although Natsume initially rejects Atsushi`s overtures of friendship because of his fears of his ability being found out, he eventually becomes friends with Atsushi and Satoru, although they still hang around more with each other than Natsume.</description>
<picture>31020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2226" picture="23215.jpg">Suganuma Hisayoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3789" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="50">4.67</rating>
<name>Nishimura Satoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nishimura Satoru is a classmate of Natsume, and best friend to Kitamoto Atsushi. He is funny and easy-going, with a slightly perverted side. Although Natsume initially rejects Satoru`s overtures of friendship because of his fears of his ability being found out, he eventually becomes friends with Satoru and Atsushi, although they still hang around more with each other than Natsume.</description>
<picture>31019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3790" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-24">
<rating votes="126">8.55</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Touko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>19666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="229" picture="152363.jpg">Itou Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3791" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-24">
<rating votes="79">8.01</rating>
<name>Fujiwara Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>19667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2224" picture="21768.jpg">Itou Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10360" type="appears in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="28">5.95</rating>
<name>Chobi-hige</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10365" type="appears in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="20">5.00</rating>
<name>Hitotsume no Chuukyuu Youkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10366" type="appears in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="20">5.24</rating>
<name>Ushikao no Chuukyuu Youkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4481" picture="26754.jpg">Shimozaki Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10367" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-23">
<rating votes="128">8.44</rating>
<name>Hinoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hinoe is a powerful youkai whose form is a human woman. She is madly in love with Natsume Reiko. Being knowledgeable, she often acts as Natsume Takashi`s mentor. Hinoe enjoys teasing Natsume and Madara.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>30995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10370" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="99">8.04</rating>
<name>Hiiragi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10377" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-05">
<rating votes="41">8.37</rating>
<name>Misuzu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>30986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10380" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-13">
<rating votes="198">8.91</rating>
<name>Madara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>31024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30370" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-22">
<rating votes="42">3.11</rating>
<name>Matoba Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matoba Seiji is the head of one of the major exorcism clans, the Matoba Clan. In order to hunt them, he shows ayakashi, and sometimes even humans, no mercy. He takes great interest in Natsume. Cold hearted and rational. He uses ayakashi as bait to exorcise other ones and wants stronger ones to protect humans (although he doesn`t mind hurting humans too when they`re in his way). Ayakashis are just replaceable tools for him. He mainly uses a bow and arrow against them and if he finds their sealing troublesome, he prefers eliminating them. In the past one of the Matoba clan offered his right eye to an ayakashi for assistance, but in the end he never gave it. Ever since than the heads of the clan has had their right eye targetted by that ayakashi. Matoba Seiji still has his eye, but (according to his words) has a horrible scar.</description>
<picture>6314.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85558" type="appears in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="2">9.52</rating>
<name>Shoujo Yousei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85559" type="appears in" update="2016-10-16">
<rating votes="3">3.57</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34545" picture="224469.jpg">Kiyoto Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88969" type="appears in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Hidaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201462.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="485" picture="223410.jpg">Shintani Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89056" type="appears in" update="2017-04-28">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Sougo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="366" picture="17212.jpg">Gouda Hozumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89057" type="appears in" update="2017-04-28">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Nanako no Tomodachi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44949" picture="215709.jpg">Ueda Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89058" type="appears in" update="2017-04-28">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Kasa o Kureta Joshikousei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44698" picture="181976.jpg">Okutani Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89061" type="appears in" update="2017-04-28">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Kayatsubo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89083" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Donguri Suki no Youkai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29002" picture="151326.jpg">Fujiwara Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89084" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Kuchihige no Shou Youkai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40279" picture="156880.jpg">Hanawa Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89085" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Tsuno no Aru Youkai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35974" picture="132130.jpg">Takano Shinpei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89086" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Shinseki no Onna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="383" picture="24124.jpg">Okohira Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89087" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Shinseki no Chijin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9360" picture="171916.jpg">Chikiri Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89088" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Shoujo no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="580" picture="17973.jpg">Yuya Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99195" type="appears in" update="2018-11-11">
<rating votes="1">4.12</rating>
<name>Mitsuzara</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3132" picture="223652.jpg">Kikuchi Kokoro</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="176303" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変わらぬ姿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unchanging Form</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaranu Sugata</title>
<summary>Natsume continues to spend his days giving back Youkai their names from the book of friends.  One day, as he`s heading home, he finds himself chased by a giant, rolling pot.  The youkai in the pot insists that his grandmother Reiko stole a doll from her.  When she threatens to hurt his family, however, he`s forced to go out and find it.  But would his kind, smiling grandmother Reiko really steal a doll from someone?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721057</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180285" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">連鎖の陰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shadow of Linked Chains</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rensa no Kage</title>
<summary>An inexperienced exorcist tries and fails to completely seal a youkai near Natsume`s school.  Natsume decides to take the pot the youkai is sealed in to Natori, in hopes that it can be disposed of properly. While he`s there, he learns that there is an ongoing feud between exorcists lately, and that one exorcist in particular is attacking his rivals.  When Natsume gets home, he finds that Matoba, another exorcist who`s tried to take advantage of him in the past, wants his help dealing with just that particular problem...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721063</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180286" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祓い屋からの手紙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Letter from the Exorcist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haraiya kara no Tegami</title>
<summary>Natsume receives a letter from Matoba, an exorcist whom he`s had unpleasant dealings with in the past. The world of exorcists is a dangerous place lately, and Matoba wants Natsume`s help. Natsume wants to refuse, but Matoba threatens to reveal Natsume`s powers to his adopted family, which would spell the end of his peaceful life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721061</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180287" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪戯な雨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mischievous Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itazura na Ame</title>
<summary>On a rainy day, Natsume meets a young girl youkai.  Her name isn`t in the book of friends, but she wants his help anyway: she wants him to find a man she met once.  The man couldn`t see Youkai normally, but a mischievous trick of the weather let him see her for just one day.  For the next fifty years she visited him, hoping he`d see her one more time, but he never did.  Now he`s vanished. Can Natsume find him for her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721059</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180788" update="2016-10-05">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180789" update="2016-10-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181022" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">音無しの谷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soundless Valley</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otonashi no Tani</title>
<summary>Natsume`s friend Taki lives in a house filled with traps and mazes for youkai. She can`t see the youkai herself without the aid of a special circle, but she can hear them when they`re trapped in her house. She saves one of them, but it refuses to leave her home. Natsume suspects that there may be danger involved, and visits her to make sure that everything is okay.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721067</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181023" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">結んではいけない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Must Not Be Bound</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Musunde wa Ikenai</title>
<summary>Natsume arrives at the exorcist meeting to help smoke out the youkai that Matoba wants to find. But he quickly discovers that the situation is more complicated than it first seemed. The youkai is capable of replicating itself to possess targets, and no one but Natsume is able to see who is possessed. Natsume and Nyanko-sensei search the halls, still unsure if they even want to be there.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721065</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181282" update="2016-12-07">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歪みなき世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A World Unbent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hizumi Naki Sekai</title>
<summary>Natori`s family has always been exorcists... until they lost the abililty to see youkai.  After generations of fearing the youkai`s revenge, Natori is suddenly born with the ability to see them.  His family doesnt want anything to do with his powers, though, and he`s left to figure out how to live on his own.  His life changes when he meets a young Matoba at an exorcist gathering, and the two of them end up hunting a powerful youkai together...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721073</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181283" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠い祭り火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distant Festival Lights</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooi Matsuri Hi</title>
<summary>Natsume and his friends go to a distant hot springs to help with the renovations.  When he arrives, he meets an old friend of Tanumas, but he quickly gets caught up in local youkai trouble.  Tanuma`s old friend is actually a youkai, and she threatens terrible things if Natsume reveals her secret.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721071</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182062" update="2016-12-28">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">儚き者へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Ephemeral Ones</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakanaki Mono e</title>
<summary>Natsume has come down with a cold after adventuring in the hills.  All of his friends, both human and youkai, do their best to make him feel better.  As he lies in bed, he begins to realize how much the people around him care for him, and how valuable the bonds he`s established are.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721079</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182063" update="2016-12-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">塔子と滋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Touko and Shigeru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touko to Shigeru</title>
<summary>Touko and Shigeru are the kind elderly couple who took in Natsume when no one else would. But what were they like before they let Natsume move in?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721077</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182064" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">険しきをゆく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Following a Narrow Path</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kewashiki o Yuku</title>
<summary>While on the run from a fearsome youkai, Natsume accidently sits on a tiny mushroom youkai.  The mushroom youkai is incensed, as it has a meeting with a `noble person` later in that day.  It insists on Natsume helping it prepare for its meeting with this `noble person`, and Natsume finds himself drawn into the strange story of its past...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721075</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182102" update="2018-12-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニャンコ先生とはじめてのおつかい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nyanko-sensei &amp; the First Errand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyanko-sensei to Hajimete no Otsukai</title>
<summary>Nyanko-sensei runs away from Natsume to chase a dragonfly.  He finds himself stuck with two young children on their first errand.  He keeps trying to leave, but the area of the forest they`re in is filled with dangerous youkai.  Can he help them complete their errand, while still retaining his sanity?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721069</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186553" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一夜盃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Night`s Cups</title>
<title xml:lang="x-other">One Night Sake Cup</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichiya Sakazuki</title>
<summary>Natsume encounters a pair of youkai who make cups that turn sake delicious. Their power is waning, and they`ve come to a spring that`s said to restore spiritual energy.  But the spring is occupied by a monster...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734721</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189812" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遊戯の宴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Banquet of Play</title>
<title xml:lang="x-other">Party of Fun &amp; Games</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuugi no Utage</title>
<summary>While searching for Nyanko-sensei, Natsume gets invovled in a dangerous game of hide and seek.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>744285</identifier>
<identifier>natsume-yujin-cho-5</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
