<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12021" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-09-27</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-13</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaijuu Girls: Ultra Kaijuu Gijinka Keikaku</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">怪獣娘[かいじゅうがーるず] ~ウルトラ怪獣擬人化計画~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kaiju Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Kaijû Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">怪兽娘～奥特怪兽拟人化计划～</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13401" type="Sequel">Kaijuu Girls: Ultra Kaijuu Gijinka Keikaku (2018)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://kaiju-gk.jp/anime/</url>
<creators>
<name id="23382" type="Animation Work">Studio Pu Yukai</name>
<name id="11038" type="Original Work">Tsuburaya Production</name>
<name id="39147" type="Original Plan">Kaihou Norimitsu</name>
<name id="21007" type="Direction">Ashina Minoru</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
</creators>
<description>Humanity`s battle of many years with the kaiju, giant monsters, has finally come to an end. Now that Earth has entered an age of peace, girls with the souls of kaiju have begun to appear, giving them the ability to transform into kaiju. They are known as the Kaiju Girls, and this is the powerful, transient, beautiful, and at times easygoing story of the strange fate these girls bear.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="164">2.66</permanent>
<temporary count="164">5.09</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>195057.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18762</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33011</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kaiju-gk.jp/anime/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kaiju_Girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ウルトラ怪獣擬人化計画#.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1.E3.83.BB.E5.B0.8F.E8.AA.AC</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4375</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356112</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19603</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2677" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Osaka</name>
<description>Osaka Prefecture is a prefecture located in the Kansai region on Honshu, the main island of Japan. The capital is the city of Osaka. It is the center of Osaka-Kobe-Kyoto area.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214384.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3037" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Skytree</name>
<description>Tokyo Skytree is a broadcasting, restaurant, and observation tower in Sumida, Tokyo, Japan. It became the tallest structure in Japan in 2010 and reached its full height of 634.0 metres in March 2011, making it the tallest tower in the world, displacing the Canton Tower, and the second tallest structure in the world after Burj Khalifa (829.8 m).
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much older http://anidb.net/t3667 [Tokyo Tower].</description>
<picurl>161122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4042" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-17">
<name>odd jobs</name>
<description>A character (or several of them) in the anime takes on various jobs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="83299" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Agira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22171" picture="173757.jpg">Iida Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83300" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Windom</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36511" picture="134700.jpg">Endou Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83301" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Eleking</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83302" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Gomora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34407" picture="202909.jpg">Suwa Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83303" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Zandrias</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40415" picture="158225.jpg">Yuasa Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83304" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Zetton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83305" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Pigmon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83306" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Miclas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41296" picture="177392.jpg">Suzuki Aina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83307" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Red King</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="180599" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">配れ! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hand Them Out! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les filles-monstres font de la pub</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kubare! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Now that they`re all able to assume their Kaiju forms, the girls start out by helping with menial jobs for the organization.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720783</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180600" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Transform! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Me transformer en fille-monstre ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henshin! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Agira has a conversation with Zetton in hopes of finding out the trick to her transformation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720781</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180601" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身? 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Transform? Kaiju Girls?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On se transforme, les filles-monstres ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henshin? Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Aki, Miku, and Reika like the thought of being members of GIRLS, but have a hard time figuring out how exactly to transform into their Kaiju Girl forms.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720779</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180602" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私たち! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re Kaiju Girls?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des filles-monstres, nous ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashitachi! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Welcome to the International Kaiju Rescue and Mentoring Organization, better known as GIRLS. Here, young women who find the souls of Ultra Kaiju inhabiting their bodies are trained to become the incredible Kaiju Girls!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720777</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181266" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボケろ! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Joke! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Blaguons, les filles-monstres !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokero! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>The Kaiju Girls meet Gomora in Osaka, and she imparts some wisdom on the nature of their Kaiju Souls.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720791</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181267" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦え! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fight! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Battez-vous, les filles-monstres !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakae! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>The berserk Kaiju Girl is finally found, and it`s the rookie GIRLS Agira, Miclas, and Windom who encounter her. Can the fledgling trio fight someone on a rampage?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720789</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181268" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悩め! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Worry! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille-monstre inquiète</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nayame! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Miku continues to worry about her future as Red King and Pigmon talk to the girl about their career paths.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720787</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181269" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Senpai! Kaiju Girl!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trop de respect pour l’aînée, les filles-monstres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Miclas meets her idol, the feisty Red King, and ponders her future as a Kaiju Girl.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720785</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181713" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私たちが! 怪獣娘!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Are Kaiju! Girls!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nous sommes les filles-monstres !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashitachi ga! Kaijuu Girls!!</title>
<summary>It`s time for Agira, Miclas, and Windom to rise to the challenge when the members of GIRLS square off against the Shadows.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720799</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181714" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">試験! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exam! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C’est l’heure de l’examen, les filles-monstres ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiken! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>The time has come for Agira, Miclas, and Windom to take the exam to become official members of GIRLS.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720797</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181715" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛べ! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jump! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On s’envole, les filles-monstres ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobe! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>The girls visit Kyoto, and run into Zandrias and Red King who are trying to test a theory.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720795</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181716" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2016-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走? 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Going Berserk? Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On s’enrage, les filles-monstres ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou? Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>A trip to Sapporo turns dangerous, as Windom tries to avoid spoilers for the ScoreYou movie.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720793</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186592" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186593" update="2017-04-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221755" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221756" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-10-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221757" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221758" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221759" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-11-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221760" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221761" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221762" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1i</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
