<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12059" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-01</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Www.Working!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">WWW.WORKING!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Www.Wagnaria!!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">WWW.迷糊餐厅</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6780" type="Same Setting">Working!!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://working-www.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="10051" type="Original Work">Takatsu Karino</name>
<name id="9326" type="Direction">Kamakura Yumi</name>
<name id="3326" type="Music">Yokoyama Masaru</name>
<name id="25681" type="Character Design">Nakano Mayuko</name>
<name id="3730" type="Series Composition">Yoshioka Takao</name>
<name id="25681" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakano Mayuko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Working!! 4-koma seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr10051 [Takatsu Karino], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr23601 [Young Gangan].
http://anidb.net/ch81532 [Higashida Daisuke], a first-year high school student at an elite school in Hokkaido, learns that his father`s company went bankrupt. Thus Daisuke effectively loses his allowance to pay for his phone bill and even worse the money for his train pass to school that is 15 km away. Even though he very much would prefer spending his time studying, he takes on a part-time job at the conveniently close Wagnaria family restaurant, to support his irresponsible parents and younger sister. Working under the stern, same-aged floor chief http://anidb.net/ch81530 [Miyakoshi Hana], it quickly becomes clear that the staff at this restaurant is all but normal:
Hana bullies the manager http://anidb.net/ch84267 [Sakaki Ken`ichirou] for feeding stray cats close to the restaurant, but will put on the kindest smile for customers entering the restaurant. The slightly older http://anidb.net/ch81531 [Muranushi Sayuri] greets a regular elderly customer and serves him coffee, but seems to be the only one able to see said customer. Strangely she does not believe in the supernatural.
The sluggish, yet manipulative http://anidb.net/ch81534 [Kondou Kisaki], a university student, easily convinces the gullible manager that she should start her shift later, for the good of the restaurant. Hana objects, so Kisaki asks her a history question, embarrassing Hana. Kisaki`s trick to continue smoking does not work or impress Daisuke, though. The friendly http://anidb.net/ch81533 [Adachi Masahiro] is in charge of the kitchen, alongside http://anidb.net/ch84269 [Kouno Takuya] who also works there.
http://anidb.net/ch81536 [Kamakura Shiho], serving on the floor, is the daughter of a company president, solving problems by throwing money at them, literally. http://anidb.net/ch81535 [Shindou Yuuta] is working several part-time jobs, because his father is in debt to Shiho`s father. Obviously Shiho does not need to work at the restaurant, but she was rejected by Yuuta when they were young, and is still holding a grudge.
And so Daisuke`s unusual working life at this family restaurant begins...
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="941">5.75</permanent>
<temporary count="943">6.89</temporary>
<review count="3">6.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>190513.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18412</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33094</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://working-www.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://wagnaria-www.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>WORKING!!_(WEB版)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4285</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356300</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19495</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3119" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>restaurant</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3718" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>love between enemies</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6184" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>autumn</name>
<description>Autumn, interchangeably known as fall in the US and Canada, is one of the four temperate seasons. Autumn marks the transition from summer into winter, in September (Northern Hemisphere) or March (Southern Hemisphere), when the arrival of night becomes noticeably earlier and the temperature cools considerably. One of its main features is the shedding of leaves from deciduous trees.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161967.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13559" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="118">6.26</rating>
<name>Takanashi Souta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takanashi Souta is a high school student who was pressed into service at Wagnaria by Taneshima Poplar. Poplar keeps mispronouncing his name as `Katanashi`, and can never seem to say it properly. He is a self-described `minicon`, a person with an obsession with small, cute things such as children, kittens, hamsters, and water fleas, and as such is immediately charmed by the diminutive Taneshima.
Since he is the only boy in a family of five, he wound up wearing many of his sisters` old clothes as a child, and as such harbors deep insecurities about his masculinity. He arguably allows Inami Mahiru to keep hitting him as this works as affirmation for his manhood.</description>
<picture>39732.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="81530" type="main character in" update="2016-10-02">
<rating votes="21">7.34</rating>
<name>Miyakoshi Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81531" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-02">
<rating votes="13">7.48</rating>
<name>Muranushi Sayuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81532" type="main character in" update="2016-10-02">
<rating votes="11">7.04</rating>
<name>Higashida Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81533" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-02">
<rating votes="5">3.50</rating>
<name>Adachi Masahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81534" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-02">
<rating votes="11">5.88</rating>
<name>Kondou Kisaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81535" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-02">
<rating votes="5">2.80</rating>
<name>Shindou Yuuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81536" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-02">
<rating votes="16">3.59</rating>
<name>Kamakura Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84265" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-12">
<rating votes="2">1.90</rating>
<name>Saiki Kouki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84266" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-05">
<rating votes="7">7.44</rating>
<name>Yanagiba Miri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37985" picture="175206.jpg">Asakura Momo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84267" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-12">
<rating votes="2">1.56</rating>
<name>Sakaki Ken`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84268" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-25">
<rating votes="9">6.11</rating>
<name>Nagata Rui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39007" picture="148258.jpg">Ozawa Ari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84269" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-12">
<rating votes="4">2.19</rating>
<name>Kouno Takuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86140" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Higashida no Tannin Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34588" picture="243219.jpg">Yaoya Kyou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86141" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Higashida Sakiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86142" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Higashida Sachiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86143" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Higashida Kousaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86144" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<rating votes="1">4.17</rating>
<name>Sei Valentinus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86145" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Miyakoshi Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="309" picture="17145.jpg">Sonozaki Mie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86146" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Osanai Shindou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34407" picture="202909.jpg">Suwa Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86147" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Kamakura no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86148" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Arai-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="476" picture="23579.jpg">Saitou Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86149" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Isha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20273" picture="175422.jpg">Kijima Ryuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86150" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Miyakoshi no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86151" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<rating votes="1">3.32</rating>
<name>Muranushi Saiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194437.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86152" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Tasaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86153" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Banchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10906" picture="200861.jpg">Yanagita Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86154" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Osanai Saitou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86155" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Saitou Daichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194439.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86156" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<rating votes="1">8.07</rating>
<name>Kondou Hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86157" type="appears in" update="2016-11-12">
<name>Osanai Kamakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86874" type="appears in" update="2016-12-28">
<name>Muranushi Satoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="25450.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86875" type="appears in" update="2016-12-28">
<name>Shindou Taeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196226.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86876" type="appears in" update="2016-12-28">
<name>Shindou no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196227.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86877" type="appears in" update="2016-12-28">
<name>Manga no Onnanoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196228.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33628" picture="92051.jpg">Hamasaki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86878" type="appears in" update="2016-12-28">
<name>Manga no Otokonoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196229.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29668" picture="239507.jpg">Muro Genki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="180296" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いけるきがする</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Have a Feeling It`ll Go Well</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je sens que ça va le faire !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikeru Ki ga Suru</title>
<summary>Higashida and Miyakoshi visit a shrine and make wishes. While taking a stroll on her day off, Nagata sees those two together and can’t help but feel a little curious!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722151</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180297" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君にしか頼めない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`re the Only One I Can Ask</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Il n`y a qu`à toi que je peux demander ça</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi ni Shika Tanomenai</title>
<summary>Daisuke hears from Sayuri about a recent regular customer, a “high school girl who wears a scarf, even though it’s summer.” Daisuke is somewhat skeptical, but then sees the girl himself. She’s wearing his school’s uniform, even though he has no memory of ever seeing her before there!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722149</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180298" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人生そんなに甘くない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life Isn`t That Easy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vie n`est pas toujours rose</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinsei Sonna ni Amakunai</title>
<summary>As an obligation to Miyakoshi for the chocolate, Daisuke is forced to help her study. Meanwhile, the diner gets a new staff member in the form of an English-speaking transfer student.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722147</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180299" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アルバイトは人生を変えてくれる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Part-Time Jobs Can Change Lives</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un job peut changer votre vie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arbeit wa Jinsei o Kaete Kureru</title>
<summary>Daisuke Higashida is a high school student looking for a part-time job
due to financial difficulties at home. He starts working at a family
restaurant called Wagnaria.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721191</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180680" update="2016-10-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180948" update="2019-07-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181164" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかしなはなし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Funny Story</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une drôle d`histoire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okashina Hanashi</title>
<summary>Higashida is considering Valentine’s advice. Will Miyakoshi’s cooking actually get better if they start going out?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722159</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181165" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">料理は愛情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cooking Is Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La cuisine, c`est de l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryouri wa Aijou</title>
<summary>As always, Kamakura is teasing Shindou for his debt. Defeated with frustration, Shindou heads to the break room and finds Kisaki and Hime. His hunger finally drives him to beg for food from Hime!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722157</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181166" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命サバイバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fate Survival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rescapé du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei Survival</title>
<summary>Miyakoshi has made chocolate for Higashida, but she claims that it’s somewhat different this time. Meanwhile, Adachi is shaken to the core when Muranushi gives him chocolate for some reason!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722155</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181167" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふくしゅうしてみる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Try Getting Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je me vengerai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu Shite Miru</title>
<summary>Miri talks to Kisaki and Kouno about the love affairs of the staff members. On the surface, they seem to be in balanced relationships, but is everything really coming up roses?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722153</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182006" update="2016-12-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あらしの前の何か</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Something Before the Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quelque chose avant la tempête</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi no Mae no Nanika</title>
<summary>Kamakura wants to make Shindou pay off his father’s debt, and Shindou himself is harboring his untrustworthy father at home. Muranushi, worried about Adachi’s behavior, invites him to her home.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722167</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182007" update="2016-12-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">右の頬を殴られたら左腕でカウンター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If Someone Hits You on the Right Cheek, Counter with Your Left Fist</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Si on te frappe la joue droite, contre avec le bras gauche</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Migi no Hoo o Naguraretara Hidariude de Counter</title>
<summary>Miyakoshi feels that something is missing regarding her dating Higashida, so she asks Muranushi and Kisaki for advice. However, in the end, she turns to her last resort, which results in a surprising development!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722165</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182008" update="2016-12-04">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日に向かって吼えろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Howl at Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hurlons à demain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita ni Mukatte Hoeru</title>
<summary>Shindou has been acting kind of strange ever since he saw Kamakura’s tears the other day. He mulls over how their relationship has become so twisted and tries Kisaki’s advice, acting the way he used to with Kamakura when they were kids, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722163</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182009" update="2016-11-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕らはみんな病んでいる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re All Illing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On est tous malades</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokura wa Minna Yande Iru</title>
<summary>The atmosphere in the restaurant turns cold without Muranushi around. Adachi feels responsible and decides to visit her house.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722161</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182731" update="2016-12-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全てのことには理由がある</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s a Reason for Everything</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rien n`arrive sans raison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subete no Koto ni wa Riyuu ga Aru</title>
<summary>Higashida has been going along with Miyakoshi’s “practice cooking” for a long time now, and it’s for his sake as much as her own that she’s determined to succeed somehow with it. She thinks as hard as she can about what is necessary when cooking. What answer does she arrive at?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>722169</identifier>
<identifier>wwwwagnaria</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213123" update="2019-07-24">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-11-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213124" update="2019-07-24">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-12-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
