<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12089" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-03-18</startdate>
<enddate>2017-03-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hirune-hime: Shiranai Watashi no Monogatari</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ancien and the Magic Tablet</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Принцесса-соня ~история о другой мне~</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Принцесса-соня: история о другой мне</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ひるね姫 ~知らないワタシの物語~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Napping Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Ancien und das magische Königreich</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Ancien y el mundo mágico</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Спящая принцесса</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12807" type="Other">Ancien to Mahou no Tablet: Mou Hitotsu no Hirune-hime</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://wwws.warnerbros.co.jp/hirunehime/</url>
<creators>
<name id="205" type="Direction">Kamiyama Kenji</name>
<name id="43312" type="Animation Work">Signal MD</name>
<name id="16092" type="Music">Shimomura Youko</name>
<name id="205" type="Original Work">Kamiyama Kenji</name>
<name id="7795" type="Character Design">Sasaki Atsuko</name>
<name id="1757" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kise Kazuchika</name>
<name id="7795" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sasaki Atsuko</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch82079 [Morikawa Kokone], who lives with her http://anidb.net/ch86053 [father] in Kurashiki City, Okayama Prefecture, keeps having the same dream when she dozes off. Meanwhile, the police suddenly arrest her father three days before the 2020 Tokyo Olympics. Kokone finds it hard to believe that her father is involved in any wrongdoing, and she realizes that her dreams hold the key for resolving the situation.
Source: Japanese Film Database</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="225">5.77</permanent>
<temporary count="225">6.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>194718.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18871</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33204</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://wwws.warnerbros.co.jp/hirunehime/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hirune_Hime:_Shiranai_Watashi_no_Monogatari</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ひるね姫_〜知らないワタシの物語〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356422</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20067</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B079C84Q5N</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2996" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-31">
<name>dreamworld trip</name>
<description>A dreamworld trip is a "visit" to a dreamworld, a place that only exists in the mind of an asleep and dreaming person, or, more generally, any place in someone`s mind or other world that isn`t part of reality; in anime, this means the characters` reality, not our own.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4716" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-25">
<name>experimental technology</name>
<description>In generic use, experimental technology has not yet been fully proven in operating. Often only a prototype exists that`s being tested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5883" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-05-10">
<name>dreams</name>
<description>Waking or sleeping, the mind can go to some strange places, usually beyond the control of the dreamer. New worlds, strange creatures, unfulfilled fantasies, they are all there.
Sometimes a person`s dreams can be taken over, with catastrophic consequences for the character and sometimes the real world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7330" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into manga</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a manga.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="82079" type="main character in" update="2016-05-17">
<rating votes="1">9.12</rating>
<name>Morikawa Kokone</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="42087" picture="167234.jpg">Takahata Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86051" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-08">
<rating votes="1">9.12</rating>
<name>Morio</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="44281" picture="180140.jpg">Mitsushima Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86052" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-08">
<rating votes="1">7.98</rating>
<name>Shijima Isshin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="48834" picture="197891.jpg">Takahashi Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86053" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-08">
<rating votes="1">9.12</rating>
<name>Morikawa Momotarou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="21327">Eguchi Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86054" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-08">
<rating votes="1">1.45</rating>
<name>Watanabe</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="36066" picture="220265.jpg">Furuta Arata</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86055" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-08">
<name>Kijita</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="48833" picture="197890.jpg">Maeno Tomoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87528" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-07">
<name>Sato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87559" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-09">
<rating votes="1">9.12</rating>
<name>Joy</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="181671" update="2017-11-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2017-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195175" update="2018-01-15">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195176" update="2018-01-15">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195177" update="2018-01-15">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195178" update="2018-01-15">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195179" update="2018-01-15">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195180" update="2018-01-15">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195181" update="2018-01-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195182" update="2018-01-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">NCED</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
