<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12095" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-07-05</startdate>
<enddate>2016-09-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fudanshi Koukou Seikatsu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">腐男子高校生活</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Highschool Life of a Fudanshi</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">腐男子高校生活</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.dreamcreation.co.jp/fudanshi/</url>
<creators>
<name id="43522" type="Animation Work">EMT Squared</name>
<name id="29278" type="Character Design">Ishida Chinatsu</name>
<name id="31384" type="Work">Dream Creation</name>
<name id="6209" type="Direction">Tokoro Toshikatsu</name>
<name id="45850" type="Original Work">Michinoku Atami</name>
<name id="46454" type="Series Composition">Fujimoto Saeka</name>
</creators>
<description>The comedy depicts the daily life of Sakaguchi, a high school boy and also a "fudanshi" who loves boys-love stories.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="333">3.76</permanent>
<temporary count="336">5.68</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>185960.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18234</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36629</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>33222</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.dreamcreation.co.jp/fudanshi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>腐男子高校生活</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4224</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356457</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19233</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07GL8RH3Z</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4207" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>doujin</name>
<description>Doujin is a general Japanese term for a group of people or friends who share an interest, activity, hobbies, or achievement. The word is sometimes translated into English as clique, coterie, society, or circle (e.g., a "sewing circle").
In Japan the term is used to refer to amateur self-published works, including but not limited to manga, novels, fan guides, art collections, music and video games. Some professional artists participate as a way to publish material outside the regular publishing industry.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>68439.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4761" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-11">
<name>love letter</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime receives a love letter, usually stashed away in their school shoe locker. Or in other cases a girl might directly give the love letter to the boy she loves.
Plot device to further the relationship between characters, may also be used as comedic element creating awkward situations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="81832" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-31">
<rating votes="1">7.68</rating>
<name>Ueda Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23805" picture="66166.jpg">Masuda Toshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81833" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-31">
<rating votes="1">7.68</rating>
<name>Nakamura Toshiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81834" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-31">
<rating votes="1">1.71</rating>
<name>Daigo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32912" picture="183255.jpg">Nishiyama Koutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81835" type="main character in" update="2016-08-25">
<rating votes="1">7.68</rating>
<name>Sakaguchi Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81836" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-31">
<rating votes="1">1.71</rating>
<name>Shiratori Yuujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81837" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-31">
<rating votes="3">7.38</rating>
<name>Nishihara Rumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34426" picture="128153.jpg">Suzaki Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83031" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-17">
<rating votes="2">6.37</rating>
<name>Kana-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="578" picture="193571.jpg">Tatsumi Yuiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83032" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-31">
<rating votes="1">1.71</rating>
<name>Miyazaki Keiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34508" picture="211755.jpg">Tokuishi Katsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83033" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-31">
<rating votes="1">7.68</rating>
<name>Tozaki Reiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45619" picture="185812.jpg">Hase Norihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88257" type="appears in" update="2017-03-17">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Tozaki Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39889" picture="241534.jpg">Naganawa Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88258" type="appears in" update="2017-03-17">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40219" picture="156679.jpg">Horino Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88259" type="appears in" update="2017-03-17">
<name>Yoshiyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40342" picture="192446.jpg">Toki Shun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="178295" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめてのオタク友達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My First Otaku Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La première amie otaku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Otaku Tomodachi</title>
<summary>Sakaguchi and Rumi have a serious discussion about official pairings.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715451</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178296" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そこかしこに腐女子はいる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Are Fujoshi Everywhere</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les fujoshi sont partout</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soko Kashiko ni Fujoshi wa Iru</title>
<summary>Sakaguchi finds out that a kindred spirit is closer than he thought...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715449</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178297" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺のクラスメイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Classmates</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon camarade de classe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Classmate</title>
<summary>Sakamoto runs into Shiratori and his obedient dog, Ueda.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715447</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178298" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-07-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">腐男子高校生の日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Daily Life of a Fudanshi High School Student</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le quotidien d`un lycéen fudanshi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fudanshi Koukousei no Nichijou</title>
<summary>Sakamoto Ryo just wants one thing in life: to be able to buy BL manga without being judged.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715445</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178598" update="2016-07-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-07-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179031" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きになる女子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl on My Mind</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille qui l’intéresse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ki ni Naru Joshi</title>
<summary>Sakaguchi falls for a girl, but she apparently has a secret...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715459</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179032" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの楽しみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyone`s Fun Times</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À chacun son truc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Tanoshimi</title>
<summary>Sakaguchi catches up with the rest of the guys to see what they have been up to.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715457</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179033" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オタクの夏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer for Otakus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`été des Otaku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otaku no Natsu</title>
<summary>Sakaguchi goes to his first Comima convention and is ecstatic, but finds out something rather surprising.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715455</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179034" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">難ありな後輩たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Troublesome Kouhai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les seconde avec un problème</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanari na Kouhai-tachi</title>
<summary>While visiting Shiratori in the cooking club, Sakaguchi meets two of his underclassmen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715453</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179553" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレをうごかすモノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Moves Me</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les trucs qui me motivent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore o Ugokasu Mono</title>
<summary>Sakaguchi helps Daigo out at an event.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715467</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179554" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">甘くないバレンタイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bittersweet Valentine</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une Saint-Valentin au goût amer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amakunai Valentine</title>
<summary>The kids have various thoughts about Valentine`s Day.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715465</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179555" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">801の煩悩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Worldly Desires of 801 (Yaoi)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les 801 faiBLesses terrestres</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">801 no Bonnou</title>
<summary>The kids go to the shrine for their New Year`s greetings and wishes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715463</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179556" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変身[させたい]願望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Transformation Desires</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le désir de changer (les autres)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasetai Ganbou</title>
<summary>Rumi asks the boys to dress up as girls for Halloween.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>715461</identifier>
<identifier>the-highschool-life-of-a-fudanshi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194409" update="2017-12-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スポーツの秋煩悩の秋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sports no Aki, Bonnou no Aki</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
