<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12125" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Magic-Kyun! Renaissance</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Очарование ренессанса</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">マジきゅんっ! ルネッサンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Magic-Kyun! Renaissance</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">超心动！艺术之星</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.magic-kyun.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4418" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Kumi</name>
<name id="4418" type="Character Design">Ishii Kumi</name>
<name id="726" type="Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="11055" type="Direction">Yamazaki Mitsue</name>
</creators>
<description>A world where art becomes magic. In this world, people who can inspire passion with their Magic Arts are called Artistas, and are employed in show business. In Hoshinomori Private Magical Arts High School, where Artistas are taught, a strange new student named http://anidb.net/ch84289 [Aigasaki Kohana] transfers into the school. Kohana is placed on the planning committee for the school`s yearly Hoshinomori Summer Festa cultural festival. She spends her romantic school life with six other boys who aim to become entertainers in the future and, alongside Kohana, to be the school`s Artista Prince and Princess, only chosen once a year.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="152">4.41</permanent>
<temporary count="152">5.79</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>188244.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18467</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33299</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.magic-kyun.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Magic-kyun_Renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>マジきゅんっ!ルネッサンス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4322</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356647</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19499</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18838</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="82080" type="main character in" update="2016-11-07">
<rating votes="2">9.64</rating>
<name>Ichijouji Teika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82081" type="main character in" update="2016-11-07">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Tsukushi Mone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29613" picture="78208.jpg">Aoi Shouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82082" type="main character in" update="2016-11-07">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Suminomiya Aoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82083" type="main character in" update="2016-11-07">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Tatewaki Rintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82084" type="main character in" update="2016-11-15">
<rating votes="1">3.92</rating>
<name>Anjou Louis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82085" type="main character in" update="2016-11-07">
<rating votes="1">3.92</rating>
<name>Hibiki Kanato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84286" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Ichijouji Shinra</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84287" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Ichijouji Masana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2802" picture="176252.jpg">Shingaki Tarusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84288" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-08">
<name>Aigasaki Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84289" type="main character in" update="2019-02-17">
<rating votes="2">8.67</rating>
<name>Aigasaki Kohana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67186.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84290" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Kouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84291" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Chikamatsu Juri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84292" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Toudou Chieri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86211" type="appears in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Shounen Jidai no Louis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86212" type="appears in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Louis no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194639.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86213" type="appears in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Aigasaki Kohana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194632.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86214" type="appears in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Shounen Jidai no Aoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194633.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86215" type="appears in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Shounen Jidai no Teika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194634.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86216" type="appears in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Shounen Jidai no Rintarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194635.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86217" type="appears in" update="2016-11-15">
<name>Shounen Jidai no Mone</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194636.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="180324" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月の光で踊らせて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dancing on the Moonlight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuki no Hikari de Odorasete</title>
<summary>When Haruka learns there will be a dance party during the Hoshi festival, she begins practicing her dancing. With lesson books in one hand, she tries learning the steps, but it isn`t going well. Dance major Anjo Louis teaches her the basics, but his expression turns sad at one of Haruka`s remarks.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721285</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180325" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憧れはアルバムの中に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inspiration in an Album</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akogare wa Album no Naka ni</title>
<summary>When Kohana is chosen to perform a demonstration of her artistic talents for her class, she turns to an album of flower arrangements by her mother for inspiration. Will the photos left behind by her mother help Kohana put on a successful demonstration?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721283</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180326" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君しか...... 見えない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Only You Can See</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi Shika...... Mienai</title>
<summary>Kohana has been chosen to sit on the Hoshi Festival executive committee with Teika, who has unfortunately declared her his nemesis due to years of bad blood between their families. When none of the other members of the committee show up to the first meeting, Teika demands that they find new members, but Kohana promises she`ll convince them to come. Will Kohana have any success with Suminomiya Aoi, her first target?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721281</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180327" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きらきら花咲くルネッサンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brilliantly Blooming Renaissance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kirakira Hanasaku Renaissance</title>
<summary>Kohana has finally arrived at the Hoshinomori School of Magical Arts, her mother`s old school. There she encounters Ichijoji Teika, a handsome student with an enchanting voice, who explains to her the school`s tradition of crowning the year`s most talented students as the Prince and Princess Artista. Will Koahan be able to hone her craft and climb the Scala Artista by the end of the year?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721279</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180941" update="2016-10-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180942" update="2016-10-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181084" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かぬ光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Light Out of Reach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanu Hikari</title>
<summary>Two more weeks until the Hoshi Festival.
Kohana and the rest of the committee are busy preparing for the festival and practicing for the Art Session to be performed on the day of the event.
While the others are getting along, Teika chooses to practice alone and puts great pressure on himself.
As a member of the Ichijoji family, he must produce results that he won`t be ashamed of.
Teika works desprately to meet the weighty expectations of his family.
But from Kohana`s perspective, he seems to be in pain--
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721293</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181085" update="2016-11-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">太陽みたいに輝いて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shining Like the Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiyou Mitai ni Kagayaite</title>
<summary>The Hoshi Festival executive committee has finally gathered all its members.
As the committee is making steady progress, third-year Tatewaki Rintaro must take an important exam that will determine his future.
Rintaro will return after he passes his exam.
With full faith in himm, Kohana and the others quietly watch his progress.
Meanwhile, Rintaro faces his work alone.
However, with hazy feelings in his heart, he finds himself unable to identify what he wants to make.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721291</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181086" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いたずらな風に吹かれて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blown by a Mischievous Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itazura na Kaze ni Fukarete</title>
<summary>Kohana and the rest of the committee begin practicing for the collaborative "Art Session."
Their advisor Chieri instructs them on the secret of the Art Session: to make their hearts one. With no clear understanding of what they`re meant to do, they search for a solution using a variety of methods. Tsukushi Monet watches them with amazement and disgust.
Because he plans to study abroad in England, Monet comes to announce he can`t participate in the executive committee, but--
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721289</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181087" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">放っとけないっすよ, 先輩!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Just Can`t Ignore You, Senpai!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hottokenaissu yo, Senpai!</title>
<summary>Kohana is made responsible for responding to the concerns and complaints in the opinion box set up at school. Though the surprising number of opinions initially makes her uneasy, Hibiki Kanato agrees to help her. Kanato resolves the various concerns one after another with overwhelming vitality. Meanwhile, Kohana spots Kanato staying up late to practice the cello. Trying to be considerate of his upcoming recital, Kohana tries to handle the concerns alone, but there was something unbelievable written on the last remaining concern!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721287</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182035" update="2016-12-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">凍れる森の眠り姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sleeping Princess of the Frozen Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kooreru Mori no Nemurihime</title>
<summary>When Kohana begins producing destructive Light of Arte, she is recommended to drop out of school. Teika and the others do everything they can to find a way to save Kohana, but they`re unable to find any clues. Overwhelmed by the reality of her situation, she sees a vision of her mother who aspired to climb the Scala Artista. Kohana desperately begins arranging flowers despite being told not to, and--
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721301</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182036" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あなたは運命の王子様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Are the Prince of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anata wa Unmei no Ouji-sama</title>
<summary>Kohana and friends decide to put on a play based on Sleeping Beauty at the Halloween Party. However, planning comes to a halt when all the boys insist on playing the Prince.
Amused by the situation, their stage director Chikamatsu Juri decides to hold an audition to determine who will play the Prince of Destiny.
Teika and the others take on a variety of entirely unreasonable demands.
Who will be chosen to play the Prince of Destiny and end up with the Princess?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721299</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182037" update="2016-12-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ときめきサマーホリデー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Heart-Pounding Summer Holiday</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokimeki Summer Holiday</title>
<summary>Kohana and the rest of the committee arrive at a villa on the beach to celebrate the end of the Hoshi Festival. With sidelong glances, their always languid advisor Chieri watches them excitedly frolic about. When Kohana finds a secret greenhouse, Chieri tells her stories of her mother Sakura from when they were students. Kohana and her friends feel a great sense of relief and sadness now that everything is over. Now that the festival is over, the executive committee is to disband this day--
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721297</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182038" update="2017-01-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2016-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇跡と魔法のフェスタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Festival of Miracles and Magic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiseki to Mahou no Festa</title>
<summary>It`s finally the day of the Hoshi Festival. Kohana and the rest of the committee are busy working at the lively festival grounds. While working, Kohana runs into Teika`s brothers Ichijoji Masana and Shinra, who see the Aigasaki family as their greatest enemy.
Trouble appears to be brewing on the day of the festival. Will Kohana and the committee`s art session be a success? And will she make it through the dance party?
Now is the moment Kohana and the rest of the Hoshi Festival executive committee`s hard work all comes together!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721295</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182756" update="2016-12-28">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キミにマジきゅんっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Magic-Kyun for You!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi ni Magic-Kyun!</title>
<summary>Trapped by the thorny magical arts of her own creation, Kohana has fallen into a deep sleep. In a world blanketed with snow, Kohana was about to give up on everything.
Teika and the others sit by Kohana and convey to her their gratitude and hopes for the future in their own words. However, not even their passionate words reach Kohana`s closed off heart. As the boys consider what to do next, Teika realizes there may be a way to help Kohana.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721303</identifier>
<identifier>magic-kyun-renaissance</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
