<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12140" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>22</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-07</startdate>
<enddate>2018-06-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Cardcaptor Sakura: Clear Card Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Cardcaptor Sakura Clear Card</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">CCS2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">カードキャプターさくら クリアカード編</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Cardcaptor Sakura: Clear Card</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">카드 캡터 사쿠라 클리어 카드 편</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">魔卡少女樱 CLEAR CARD篇</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13060" type="Prequel">Cardcaptor Sakura: Clear Card Hen - Prologue - Sakura to Futatsu no Kuma</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="726375">Cardcaptor Sakura`s sequel continues the daily life and times of Sakura Kinomoto. However, there is a lack of story with the mystery being resolved in its final hour giving a bittersweet ending that leaves more to be desired and has lackluster innovation in comparison to its predecessor. Nevertheless, Clear Card retains the sweet, slice-of-life moments and cute, endearing cast that fans of the original show will enjoy if they desire to see more from their favorite Cardcaptor.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://ccsakura-official.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1525" type="Direction">Asaka Morio</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="1745" type="Series Composition">Ookawa Nanase</name>
<name id="1050" type="Work">NHK</name>
<name id="748" type="Work">Kodansha</name>
<name id="1234" type="Work">NHK Enterprises</name>
<name id="747" type="Original Work">Clamp</name>
<name id="7999" type="Character Design">Hamada Kunihiko</name>
<name id="2500" type="Music">Negishi Takayuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on shoujo manga series written and illustrated by the manga group http://anidb.net/cr747 [Clamp].
http://anidb.net/ch1283 [Sakura] had managed to capture all of the Clow Cards which could bring disaster to the world and turned them into her own Sakura Cards. Now it`s spring. With cherry trees in full blossom, Sakura is just entering middle school. Her beloved http://anidb.net/ch7238 [Syaoran] has returned from Hong Kong, and Sakura was thrilled to be going to school with him again. But one night, something strange happens to her Cards... On top of that, strange things keep happening in Tomoeda. Guided by the Key she encountered in her dream, Sakura starts collecting Cards again. And then, a new girl transfer into her class...
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="368">6.68</permanent>
<temporary count="370">7.04</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221342.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19487</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33354</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>37595</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nhk.or.jp/anime/ccsakura/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://ccsakura-official.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Cardcaptor_Sakura:_Clear_Card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>カードキャプターさくら</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4790</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358938</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20924</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ccsakura_info</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1283" type="main character in" update="2019-01-08">
<rating votes="567">8.88</rating>
<name>Kinomoto Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura`s given name (桜) means "cherry blossom". Her surname, Kinomoto (木之本), literally means "the origin of wood".
At the start of the series, Sakura is 10 years old and living in a fictional town called Tomoeda in Japan, located not far from Tokyo. One day in early April, shortly after her birthday and only slightly into her fourth grade year at Tomoeda Elementary School, young Sakura stumbles across a mysterious old book called The Clow in her father`s study. Instantly upon touching the book, a confused Sakura mistakenly awakens one of the card`s guardians, Cerberus who was sleeping on the front cover where he was supposed to be guarding the Clow Cards: a deck of 52 magical cards with incredible powers. Upon emerging from the book, Cerberus admits to having let the cards slip away as he slumbered, and, realizing Sakura`s magical potential, cunningly tricks her into becoming the "Cardcaptor" and duty bound to collect all of the missing cards and return them to the book where they will then be under her control.</description>
<picture>179473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="483" picture="27541.jpg">Tange Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7238" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="135">7.86</rating>
<name>Li Syaoran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Syaoran is a distant relative of Clow Reed (on Clow`s mother`s side), the creator of the Clow Cards. As a member of the Li clan of sorcerers from Hong Kong, of which Clow`s mother was a member, Syaoran believes that he should be the one to inherit the Clow Cards, not Sakura Kinomoto. He first appears as an antagonist in the story, capturing a few cards for himself in the anime (though none in the manga). He acted cold and nonchalant to Sakura. He never even says her name until the third season. As the series progresses, and especially after Sakura is officially deemed the new master of the Cards, Syaoran drops his rivalistic attitude towards her and becomes her ally and friend, eventually falling in love with her. However, Sakura is completely oblivious to these feelings and thinks of him simply as a close friend.</description>
<picture>82459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3794" picture="38865.jpg">Kumai Motoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7239" type="main character in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="91">7.31</rating>
<name>Cerberus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cerberus is the guardian of the mystical yet dangerous book of Clow cards. He is the guardian of the sun, one of the two duty bound to protect the powerful cards, and opposite of the lunar guardian, Yue. For several decades he was locked away in the book of the Clow, which held the cards upon the death of their previous master, Clow Reed, until a new master appeared to take hold of the cards and their guardians. Cerberus` character first appears at the beginning of the series when this new master, Sakura Kinomoto, releases him from the book. Once Cerberus is awakened (he was napping on the front cover) and released from the book he discovers the Clow cards have vanished, and appoints Sakura the title of Cardcaptor, and sends her off to retrieve the cards.</description>
<picture>82458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9580" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="150">7.84</rating>
<name>Daidouji Tomoyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomoyo is Sakura`s best friend and her second cousin on her mother`s side. The daughter of the president of Daidouji Toy Company, Sonomi Daidouji, Tomoyo lives a life of wealth and is watched over by a team of female bodyguards.
When she learns of Sakura`s new role as a Cardcaptor, she insists that Sakura must wear "special clothes" and begins providing Sakura with the various costumes she wears during her captures as well as accompanying her on missions to record the events with her video camera. She has access to a variety of prototype technological gadgets from her mother`s company, and supplies Sakura and Cerberus with different communication devices throughout the series. She is depicted as being mature, kind-hearted, and intelligent, and regularly speaking using more formal verb conjugations and expressions than normally seen in elementary students. She is a talented singer, and is shown performing in various school events.</description>
<picture>42195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9581" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="34">8.32</rating>
<name>Yue</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yue is the one of two Guardians of the Clow Cards, along with Cerberus. While Cerberus acts as the elector, choosing a candidate to become the next Master of the Clow, Yue is the judge who will test the candidate. On the outside he acts very cold and aloof and is much more serious and intimidating than his counterpart, Cerberus. He shared a special bond with Clow that made it hard for him to accept Sakura Kinomoto as a "replacement" for his creator during the Final Judgment, although Sakura manages to work her way into his heart at least as a very good friend. Yue has jurisdiction over all things wind and water, the elements "under him" which in part draw on him for their existence. The known Clow Cards under his jurisdiction are Dark, Windy, Watery, Wood and Time.</description>
<picture>42198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9583" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-29">
<rating votes="47">5.23</rating>
<name>Tsukishiro Yukito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukito is the classmate and best friend of Sakura`s brother, Touya Kinomoto. Yukito`s nearly omnipresent smile is evidence of his kind and gentle nature. Yukito also loves food and has an enormous appetite.
Yukito is the false form of the Moon Guardian Yue. Although Yue knows everything about Yukito, Yukito is initially unaware of Yue`s presence. Once Yukito learns of his alter-ego`s existence, the two are able to communicate mentally. It is suggested that Yue is the reason for Yukito`s large appetite, as he is in a sense "eating for two."</description>
<picture>42197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9721" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="41">6.03</rating>
<name>Kinomoto Touya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Touya is the older brother of Kinomoto Sakura. His birthday is on February 29th, which makes him a leap year baby, a person that can only "properly" celebrate their birthday once every four years. His blood type is O. He holds the belief that as Sakura`s older brother, he is the only person entitled to make fun of her, a belief that his best friend Tsukishiro Yukito refers to as a "sister complex." However, he is also protective and caring of her, which leads him to dislike Li Shaoran when he finds Shaoran cornering Sakura in the schoolyard. Though Shaoran and Sakura eventually stop fighting, Touya continues to dislike Shaoran when he becomes friends with Sakura.
He is often working, and a running gag in the series involves Sakura and Yukito running into him while he`s at work, which can happen virtually anywhere.
He is a perceptive young man and has had a vague idea as to what Sakura has been up to as a Cardcaptor, despite Sakura`s attempts to keep it a secret. Touya was born with some magical ability, allowing him to see ghosts (including the one of his late mother). His magical ability is also what helps him sense when Sakura is in danger or when she is doing other "magical" things.</description>
<picture>42196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14566" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="7">5.77</rating>
<name>Kinomoto Fujitaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kinomoto Fujitaka is the father of titular character Kinomoto Sakura. A busy professor of archaeology at Towa University, Fujitaka is a kind and caring father. He met his late wife Nadeshiko while doing his first year as a teacher at her high school. Nadeshiko had climbed a tree to return a baby bird to its nest, but fell out of the tree, landing on Fujitaka. Upon seeing her, he stated that "an angel has fallen from the sky." They fell in love and married when she was sixteen. Though Nadeshiko died seven years before the start of the series, Fujitaka is shown to still be very much in love with her and devoted to her memory. He keeps a picture of her in the dining room, changing it each morning.</description>
<picture>42189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14576" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="17">7.31</rating>
<name>Mizuki Kaho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mizuki Kaho is a shrine maiden and the daughter of the priest at the Tsukimine Shrine. She first appears in the series as a new substitute teacher at Tomoeda Elementary School for the math class of Sakura and Syaoran. While Sakura instantly likes the teacher and feels a connection with her, Syaoran is distrustful and believes she is up to no good.
When Sakura, Syaoran, Meiling, and Tomoyo are trapped by the Maze card, Kaho uses a mysterious bell to break through Maze`s walls allowing Sakura to capture it. After this incident, the readers learn that Sakura`s older brother Touya dated Kaho when she was his junior high school teacher and that they broke up when Kaho left to study in England. Before she left, she told them that when they met again, they would be in love with different people which he acknowledges is now true.
After meeting her, Cerberus incorrectly believes that Kaho is the false form of his fellow guardian Yue. Kaho`s role is to use the bell left at her family`s shrine to give Sakura another chance when she is unable to defeat Yue out of fear of hurting him. The bell changes Sakura`s staff into a new staff containing her own power of the stars and gives her the power to use the cards to defeat Yue. After fulfilling this duty, she returns to England. During the third season of the series, she is primarily "seen" through providing a steady, but oftentimes enigmatic exchange of letters with Sakura over the mysterious attacks. After Eriol Hiiragizawa reveals the truth behind the attacks, they learn that Kaho had met Eriol three years before Sakura discovered the Book of the Clow. As they leave for England, Kaho and Eriol confirm their feelings for one another and vow to remain together. Kaho is last seen in the second film expressing concern for Sakura and her friends due to the incidents with the final card.</description>
<picture>42191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14577" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-12">
<rating votes="10">8.78</rating>
<name>Hiiragizawa Eriol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiiragizawa Eriol is the principal antagonist in the second half of the series, commonly called the Master of the Clow arc. The reincarnation of http://anidb.net/ch9882 [Clow Reed], Eriol has both Clow`s memories and all of his magic power. He has a magical staff similar to Clow Reed`s, can control Clow`s creations http://anidb.net/ch9581 [Yue] and http://anidb.net/ch7239 [Cerberus], and has created his own similar pair of guardians: http://anidb.net/ch14581 [Ruby Moon] and http://anidb.net/ch14579 [Spinel Sun]. He moves from England to transfer to Tomoeda Elementary school after http://anidb.net/ch1283 [Kinomoto Sakura] passed the Last Judgement and became the official master of the cards. He is depicted as a quiet, mature boy while at school, though he also shows a mischievous side when he regularly joins classmate http://anidb.net/ch14585 [Yamazaki Takashi] in weaving complex lies about the history of objects, places, and events. While seeming a normal student to Sakura, Syaoran is suspicious of him. It is soon shown that Yue and Cerberus are able to detect his magical signature as being Clow`s, and Eriol must erase Yue`s memories after he is accidentally seen by him.
Eriol came to Japan in order to aid Sakura and force her to use her own magical powers to convert the Clow Cards into Sakura cards. This is necessary as the cards take their magical energy from their master, but until Sakura converted them, they could not use her magic and were slowly dying. The guardian Yue also was suffering the same fate, forcing Sakura`s brother to "feed" him all of his magical power to prevent Yue, and his false form Yukito, from dying.
Sakura does not become aware that Eriol is causing all of the magical disasters that are causing her to convert the cards until near the end of the series when Eriol reveals himself to her. He puts the city to sleep and challenges Sakura to convert the last two cards, the Dark and the Light, which must be converted together. He then takes Sakura, Syaoran, http://anidb.net/ch9580 [Tomoyo], Yue, and Cerberus to his home where he explains why he had to give her a reason to convert the cards, as her doing so without a need could have sent the cards out of control or drained Sakura`s own life.
Eriol`s true age is unknown, as he used his magic to halt his aging process to remain the same physical age as Sakura. He is romantically involved with http://anidb.net/ch14576 [Mizuki Kaho], whom he originally sent from England to aid Sakura in the Final Judgment and who offers Sakura support through letters during the second arc. In the second anime movie, they are shown together when Sakura calls for advice.</description>
<picture>42192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14579" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="8">3.68</rating>
<name>Spinel Sun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Spinel Sun is the cat-like magical guardian created by Eriol as a counter part to Clow Reed`s original guardian Cerberus. Spinel Sun`s true form is a winged black panther, while his false form is similar to a small winged cat. Nicknamed Suppi by Ruby Moon, Spinel Sun spends most of his time reading and projects a calm demeanor. Ruby Moon often teases him that he needs to have more fun. During the series, he mostly remains out of sight of the main characters, except when he once runs into Cerberus in his false form. Fortunately for him, Cerberus doesn`t suspect anything and instead declares him a monster and feeds him sweets, not realizing that the sweets would turn Spinel Sun into a hyperactive eating machine. Cerberus does not learn his true identity until just before the final battle where the two cats face one another. Initially, Spinel Sun appears to have the upper hand, however Cerberus` greater determination to protect Sakura enable him to defeat him.</description>
<picture>42199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14580" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="9">4.95</rating>
<name>Akizuki Nakuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruby Moon is one of two magical guardians created by Eriol. The counterpart to the original guardian Yue, Ruby Moon is genderless but prefers to act as a female. When Eriol transfers to Tomoeda Elementary, Ruby Moon created a false form named Akizuki Nakuru and enrolls in Seijou High School, entering the same class as Touya, Sakura`s brother, and Yukito, the false form of Yue who is unaware of his true nature. As Akizuki, she acts as a general annoyance, deliberately interfering every time Touya tries to talk to Yukito about the latter`s dwindling energy. She claims she wants to consume Touya`s energy herself, though it is never stated that she actually has a need for it nor why she couldn`t simply steal it. When Touya is finally able to speak with Yue and give him all of his magical energy to sustain Yue`s life, Akizuki gives up her pursuit. In the final battle, Ruby Moon battles Yue and initially appears to be winning. However, Yue is able to get past her due to his greater determination and desire to protect Sakura.</description>
<picture>42201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14581" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-02">
<rating votes="3">5.17</rating>
<name>Ruby Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruby Moon is one of two magical guardians created by Eriol. The counterpart to the original guardian Yue, Ruby Moon is genderless but prefers to act as a female. When Eriol transfers to Tomoeda Elementary, Ruby Moon created a false form named Akizuki Nakuru and enrolls in Seijou High School, entering the same class as Touya, Sakura`s brother, and Yukito, the false form of Yue who is unaware of his true nature. As Akizuki, she acts as a general annoyance, deliberately interfering every time Touya tries to talk to Yukito about the latter`s dwindling energy. She claims she wants to consume Touya`s energy herself, though it is never stated that she actually has a need for it nor why she couldn`t simply steal it. When Touya is finally able to speak with Yue and give him all of his magical energy to sustain Yue`s life, Akizuki gives up her pursuit. In the final battle, Ruby Moon battles Yue and initially appears to be winning. However, Yue is able to get past her due to his greater determination and desire to protect Sakura.</description>
<picture>42202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14582" type="appears in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="15">7.68</rating>
<name>Sasaki Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sasaki Rika is a classmate and friend of titular character Sakura Kinomoto. She is considered to be very elegant and mature for her age, though she can also be shy. During the series, she is also shown to be a skilled cook and very good at crafts. During the series, Rika is affected by the Clow Cards several times. Early in the series, she buys a brooch that is actually The Sword card. The card takes her over and causes her to attack Sakura. Sakura is able to stop Rika by using The Illusion card to show her an image of her beloved, allowing Sakura to capture the card. During the second half of the series, she is nearly drowned during a magical trial Eriol created to cause Sakura to convert a Clow Card to Sakura Card.
During the series, Rika is shown to be in a romantic relationship with her teacher Terada Yoshiyuki. Rika gives Terada the hand-made teddy bear she made, and he names it after her. When Sakura uses the Illusion card to stop Rika`s attacks, she calls the image "Sensei" which means "teacher" in Japanese. During the final judgment when Yue shows Sakura a world where everyone has lost their feelings for the one they love the most, Rika is shown handing Terada a paper without her usual blush and shy look.</description>
<picture>42203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14583" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="8">6.72</rating>
<name>Yanagisawa Naoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yanagisawa Naoko is one of Sakura`s elementary school classmates and friends. She is also on the cheerleading squad with Sakura. Naoko loves to read, particularly fantasy stories and ghost stories. She finds mysterious situations fascinating and shows no fear of scary situations. In the 31st episode of the anime adaptation, Naoko accidentally acquires the The Create card, which had disguised itself as a book. In book form, The Create would create anything that Naoko wrote in the book, though she was unaware of it. This results in Sakura and company having to deal with a confusing area of odd mystical creatures and circumstances, including a fire-breathing dragon. When she goes to bed and closes the book, the card`s power is stopped and Sakura is able to capture it. When Naoko wakes in the morning to find the book gone, she thinks it disappeared from a supernatural experience and is happy.</description>
<picture>42204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3954" picture="173079.jpg">Motoi Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14584" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="9">5.09</rating>
<name>Mihara Chiharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mihara Chiharu is a friend and classmate of Sakura, as well as a fellow member of the cheerleading squad. Chiharu is often in charge of stopping Takashi when he starts spinning lies about the history of objects and events. Though she is regularly seen jokingly strangling him or dragging him away by his collar, they have been friends since kindergarten and are a couple.
When Sakura is shown a world where everyone connected to the cards has lost their feelings for the one they love the most, Chiharu and Takashi are shown reacting to one another as virtual strangers.</description>
<picture>42205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6928" picture="211675.jpg">Matsumoto Miwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14585" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-30">
<rating votes="4">2.57</rating>
<name>Yamazaki Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamazaki Takashi is a student in Sakura`s class, and the only male student in the class to be referred to by name before the introduction of Syaoran. Throughout the series, Yamazaki`s defining trait is his ability to fabricate highly detailed fake stories and histories about practically any subject. While most of his classmates see through these fabrications, Sakura and Syaoran often believe them. When the character Eriol is introduced in the second half of the series, he becomes Yamazaki`s storytelling ally. The two are able to respond to one another`s clues perfectly and spin complex stories on the fly.
Fellow classmate Chiharu often interrupts his stories so others know when he is lying, and proceeds to punish him for lying by pretending to strangle him or by dragging him away by his collar. While the two often seem to be arguing, they are actually a couple and have known one another since kindergarten. She is the only girl in the series that he addresses by her first name.
Yamazaki is the only character to be rarely shown with his eyes open. On the day of Judgement when Sakura is shown a world in which everyone losing their feelings for the person they love the most, Yamazaki and Chiharu lose their feelings for each other and are shown to be strangers.</description>
<picture>42206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2899" picture="79024.jpg">Miyazaki Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14586" type="appears in" update="2012-01-26">
<rating votes="31">3.19</rating>
<name>Li MeiLing</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Li Meiling is a character that appears only in the anime adaptation of Cardcaptor Sakura. Introduced in episode 19, she is Syaoran`s cousin and self-proclaimed fiancée. As children living in Hong Kong, they both trained in martial arts under the tutelage of Wang Wei. One night her pet bird escaped from his cage, and the normally quiet and withdrawn Syaoran told her not to cry, then left. After spending hours in the rain, he returned with the bird and Meiling was both grateful and touched. From that day, she devoted herself to him, eventually declaring that she liked him above all others and, reasoning that he liked her as well, she declared them to be engaged. At the same time, she promised that if he ever found someone he liked more than her, she would give him up.
In coming to Tokyo, Meiling intends to help Syaoran gather the Clow Cards, and actively dislikes Sakura. As the series progresses, Meiling develops a grudging respect for Sakura that turns into a good friendship by the time Meiling returns to Hong Kong in episode 43. During her initial visit, Meiling seemed to recognize that Syaoran was falling in love with Sakura, but it wasn`t until she briefly returned in episode 60 that she fully acknowledges and accepts Sakura as the person Syaoran loves. Wanting to keep his promise, Syaoran attempts to tell her that he loves Sakura, but Meiling interrupts and tells him that she knows because he is now calling Sakura by her first name, something he only does for his sisters and herself. She smiles at Syaoran with tears in her eyes and declares that the engagement is called off, then quickly leaves. Meiling spends the night at Tomoyo`s house to release all of her sadness through much screaming and tears without burdening Syaoran. At the end of the episode, Meiling returns home and is not seen again in the main series. She returns in the second movie, with Syaoran, and together with Tomoyo tries to help Sakura confess her own feelings to him.
Unlike Syaoran, Meiling has no magical abilities, relying solely on her physical fighting abilities and a healthy dose of pride. Her lack of powers, however, results in her hindering more than helping Syaoran in most battles against the cards. She challenges the The Fight card in episode 20, and was nearly badly wounded and had to be rescued by Syaoran. Recognizing that she was being a burden, Meiling grew upset and lashed out at Syaoran. However, she was then able to be an aid to him while fighting The Twin card, as their years of practicing martial arts together enables them to match the card`s synchronized fighting style.</description>
<picture>42208.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47603" type="appears in" update="2012-08-08">
<name>Li Feimei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="29456" picture="186176.jpg">Sugawara Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47604" type="appears in" update="2012-08-08">
<name>Li Futie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1900" picture="156922.jpg">Yamaguchi Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47605" type="appears in" update="2012-08-08">
<name>Li Shiefa</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3833" picture="25459.jpg">Shibahara Chiyako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47606" type="appears in" update="2012-08-08">
<name>Li Fanren</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2787" picture="87896.jpg">Wakusawa Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47608" type="appears in" update="2014-01-29">
<rating votes="13">5.69</rating>
<name>Daidouji Sonomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>132444.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="47610" type="appears in" update="2012-08-08">
<rating votes="13">3.89</rating>
<name>Cerberus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="183" picture="16992.jpg">Onosaka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66290" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Wei Wang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wei Wang is the attendant that comes with Syaoran Li when he first moves to Japan. A kind elderly man he has been teaching martial arts to Syaoran and Meilin since there childhood.</description>
<picture>153020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93202" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-25">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Yuna D Kaito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93203" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-25">
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<name>Shinomoto Akiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44135" picture="185214.jpg">Suzuki Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95627" type="appears in" update="2018-05-20">
<name>Momo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="193710" update="2017-12-10">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193711" update="2017-12-10">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193712" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと素敵な転校生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Lovely Transfer Student</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et la merveilleuse nouvelle élève</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Suteki na Tenkousei</title>
<summary>A new transfer student named Akiho Shinomoto joins Sakura`s class. She`s just arrived in Japan after living overseas, so her Japanese is still very stiff and formal. Sakura invites her to eat lunch with her group, excited to make a new friend
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758871</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193713" update="2018-01-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらの大雨注意報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Heavy Rain Alert</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et l`alerte inondation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Ooamechuuihou</title>
<summary>It`s been raining buckets all day. Sakura and Tomoyo take shelter in a park on the way home from school, and suddenly the Key of Dreams at Sakura`s chest begins to shine... Is it the work of a card?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758869</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193714" update="2018-01-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと出口のない部屋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Room with No Exit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et la salle sans porte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Deguchi no Nai Heya</title>
<summary>It`s the new term, and the hot topic at school is clubs! Sakura and Tomoyo decide to join the same clubs they did in elementary school, cheerleading and chorus.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758867</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193715" update="2018-01-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと透明なカード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Clear Cards</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et les cartes transparentes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Toumei na Card</title>
<summary>It`s April, the cherry trees are in full bloom, and Sakura has entered Tomoeda Middle School. She`s reunited with Syaoran, who has returned from Hong Kong, and her new student life has begun.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758865</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195310" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと時計とかくれんぼ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, the Clock, and a Hide-and-Seek Game</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura, l`horloge et la partie de cache-cache</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Tokei to Kakurenbo</title>
<summary>Sakura finds out that Akiho has moved into the mansion formerly inhabited by Clow Reed`s reincarnation, Eriol. She pays a visit with Tomoyo and meets Kaito, the butler who`s been taking care of Akiho since her childhood.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758879</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195311" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとお庭でおにごっこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and a Game of Tag in the Garden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura joue à chat dans le jardin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Oniwa de Onigokko</title>
<summary>Sakura and Kero-chan visit Tomoyo`s house to test the abilities of the Record card. Tomoyo`s mother appears and gives Sakura an enthusiastic welcome, then the girls head outside to test the card.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758877</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195312" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとうさぎと月の唄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, the Rabbit, and the Song of the Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura, la lapin et la chanson de la lune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Usagi to Tsuki no Uta</title>
<summary>Sakura continues to face the hooded figure in her dreams. At school, everyone says they want to hear Akiho sing again after being charmed by her voice at their flower-viewing party, so they meet in the music room after classes are over.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758875</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195313" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとお花見ひっぱりだこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura Feels a Pull at the Flower Viewing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et les fleurs très demandées</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Ohanami Hipparidako</title>
<summary>Sakura is having a flower-viewing party with her friends Tomoyo, Syaoran, Chiharu, Naoko, and Yamazaki, as well as the new transfer student Akiho.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758873</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195949" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195950" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196075" update="2018-03-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとねむりのラビリンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Sleep Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et le labyrinthe du sommeil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Nemuri no Labyrinth</title>
<summary>Akiho pays a visit to Sakura`s house one evening while her father and brother are both away. They look at Sakura`s elementary school pictures and have dinner together, but then Akiho suddenly falls asleep.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758883</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196076" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのドキドキ水族館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Thrilling Aquarium Visit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura nerveuse à l`aquarium</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Dokidoki Suizokukan</title>
<summary>Sakura invites Syaoran out for the day with tickets given to her by her father. She`s worked hard on the rolled omelets for their lunch, and now they make their way to the aquarium Sakura visited when she captured the Clow Card, Watery.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758881</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196304" update="2018-03-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと氷の球技大会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Icy Ball-Sports Tournament</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Koori no Kyuugi Taikai</title>
<summary>It`s the day of the ball-sports tournament everyone`s been looking forward to. The athletic Sakura makes a strong showing in the basketball event!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766217</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196305" update="2018-03-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとさかさまペンギン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Upside-down Penguin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sakura et le pingouin renversé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Sakasama Penguin</title>
<summary>Syaoran meets Kaito through a chance encounter on the way home from school. He informs Eriol, whom he`s beem secretly keeping in touch with, and they both begin to suspect Kaito is a very powerful magician.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766215</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196888" update="2018-04-09">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとただいま苺鈴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Welcome Back, Meiling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Tadaima Mei Ling</title>
<summary>Sakura is overjoyed to see Syaoran`s cousin, Meiling, make an unannounced visit from Hong Kong. Meiling asks to stay at Sakura`s house, so they head straight there. Meanwhile, the power Toya lost by giving it to Yukito is gradually starting to return.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766219</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197094" update="2018-04-29">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと苺鈴とおともだち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Meiling`s Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Mei Ling to Otomodachi</title>
<summary>Sakura manages to capture the card that showed up at Tomoyo`s house, but her relief is short-lived. As they`re returning home, Sakura and Meiling are suddenly attacked by a mysterious girl in the road!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766225</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197095" update="2018-04-22">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらのおもいで鑑賞会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Nostalgic Viewing Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Omoide Kanshoukai</title>
<summary>Sakura has been invited to Tomoyo`s house, along with Meiling and Akiho. Tomoyo says there`s something she wants to show them and leads everyone to her home theater, where she plays the video of a play they were all part of in elementary school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766223</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197096" update="2018-04-15">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと神社と動物園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, the Shrine, and the Zoo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Jinja to Doubutsuen</title>
<summary>Sakura is visiting the Tsukimine Shrine market with Meiling, Akiho, and the rest of their friends. She enjoys a day of browsing the many shops and stalls on the grounds along with Akiho, who`s never seen a Japanese shrine before.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766221</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197482" recap="true" update="2018-03-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">総集編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushuuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197899" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197900" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198439" update="2018-05-27">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと虹とおじいさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, Rainbows, and Grandpa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Niji to Ojii-san</title>
<summary>Sakura is spending her Sunday morning making rolled omelets for the homemade lunches she`s taking for her outing with Syaoran.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766233</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198440" update="2018-05-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと秋穂の子守唄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and Akiho`s Lullaby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Akiho no Komoriuta</title>
<summary>Sakura is finally about to go and read to children with Yukito, and she invites Akiho, Syaoran, and Tomoyo to come along. Sakura`s enthusiasm convinces Akiho to join her for the reading, while Syaoran agrees to contribute a piano accompaniment.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766231</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198441" update="2018-05-13">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと炎と水の鳥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Fire and Water Birds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Honoo to Mizu no Tori</title>
<summary>When Sakura senses a card late at night, she heads to Tsukimine Shrine with Kero-chan, Tomoyo, and Syaoran.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766229</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198442" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらとおかしなお菓子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura and the Crazy Sweets</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Okashi na Okashi</title>
<summary>Today is the cooking lesson in home ec class that everyone`s been looking forward to. Sakura`s morning is thrown into a panic when she forgets her apron, but she and her friends are excited to make roll cakes in class.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766227</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199840" update="2018-06-10">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらの透明なカード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura`s Clear Cards</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Toumei na Card</title>
<summary>Sakura has seen the mysterious robed person in her dreams many times. It turns out Akiho has been having the same dreams herself, and she`s grown worried over their unsettling contents.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766237</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199841" update="2018-06-09">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さくらと鏡と思い出の鍵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakura, the Mirror, and the Key of Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura to Kagami to Omoide no Kagi</title>
<summary>Cerberus and Yue meet with Eriol via magic to discuss Sakura`s new cards. Eriol has found out that Kaito took something from the magic association he once belonged to, but at that moment, Kaito`s magic severs the trio`s communication link.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>766235</identifier>
<identifier>cardcaptor-sakura-clear-card</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
