<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12158" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>2016-09-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mahou Shoujo? Naria Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">魔法少女? なりあ☆がーるず</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mahou Shoujo? Naria Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">마법소녀? 나리아☆걸즈</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">魔法少女？Naria☆Girls</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.nariagirls.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="39675" type="Series Composition">Ishidate Koutarou</name>
<name id="39675" type="Direction">Ishidate Koutarou</name>
<name id="46775" type="Animation Work">Bouncy</name>
<name id="46776" type="Character Design">Misoyama Okazu</name>
<name id="40969" type="Music">Hajime</name>
<name id="29707" type="Music">Inoue Jun`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>Urara, Hanabi, and Inaho aim to become famous throughout Japan by creating anime renditions of themselves. To be a hit with everyone from kids to adults, they choose the theme of "magical girls." Now they aim to broadcast their one-cour (quarter of a year) magical girl anime.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="121">1.36</permanent>
<temporary count="123">2.96</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>187363.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18463</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33394</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nariagirls.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Naria_Girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>魔法少女%3Fなりあ☆がーるず</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4233</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>357289</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19467</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3487" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-18">
<name>talks too fast</name>
<description>This character speaks with a pace so frenetic that it can get hard to follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3696" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-28">
<name>off-model animation</name>
<description>Anime shows tend to most often run on an already tight budget; some have even tighter ones. Thus, over the years it became a norm to invest more time and money into the first and last episode, leaving many episodes in the middle to stand severe budget restrictions. This sometimes results in episodes which particularly stand out due to the drop in artwork or animation quality; bar some basic framework, they often have little in common with the rest of the series.
One clue to upcoming off-model animation is the noticeable addition of many Korean names in the production credits, as farming out more animation to Korean artists is a nearly universal indicator of a production company trying to save money in all possible ways.
This effect is often called yashigani, after the infamous http://anidb.net/e4682 [fourth episode] of http://anidb.net/a403 [Lost Universe], Yashigani Hoburu. Another prominent term describing the same effect is "QUALITY animation", with capital letters meant to show contrast to actual quality. http://anidb.net/a4531 [Yoake Mae yori Ruriiro na: Crescent Love] is another legendarily terrible offender: the TV airing of its http://anidb.net/e63752 [third episode] had a perfectly spherical ball in place of what should be a cabbage; the "cabbage" was so egregious that it became closely associated with the anime itself, to a point the show would henceforth be nicknamed "Cabbage Love" among Western viewers.
One should not confuse the yashigani effect with art shifts that stem from guest staff, changes in main staff, intentional art shifts, and similar effects. Another effect one shouldn`t confuse this one with is the so-called DVD/BD enhancement, which is when a studio scrambles to meet the deadline for a TV airing and airs a half-finished episode but eventually fixes it for a disk release; for example, http://anidb.net/cr792 [Shaft] is particularly infamous for its disk enhancements, to a point it has become known as "Shafting", and they prominently feature intentionally weird character models, but they don`t often leave bad artwork on the disk release. Additionally, it should also not be confused with intentional lack of detail on background plane characters; this effect is instead when even the foreground has art quality shifting over time due to the aforementioned budget restrictions.</description>
<picurl>29532.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6717" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-07-26">
<name>improvised dialogue</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="82463" type="main character in" update="2017-03-05">
<name>Inaho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82464" type="main character in" update="2017-03-05">
<name>Urara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39748" picture="152660.jpg">Fukagawa Seria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82465" type="main character in" update="2017-03-04">
<name>Hanabi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43430" picture="243752.jpg">Koga Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82466" type="main character in" update="2017-03-04">
<name>Animal</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39675" picture="141205.jpg">Ishidate Koutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="178375" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">転校生は甘くて危険な恋の罠なり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Transfer Student Is a Sweet Trap of Love?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenkousei wa Amakute Kiken na Koi no Wana Nari?</title>
<summary>It`s the season of love as a new boy comes to the Naria girls school, and they`re all instantly attracted to him.  But their love falls apart when he turns into a monster and uses the magic mirror to cast a spell.  This time the girls are transformed them into a boyfriend who loves huge breasts, asking his girlfriend`s strange father for her hand i marriage!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716351</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178376" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハピネスエネルギーをチャージするなり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charge Happiness Energy?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Happiness Energy o Charge Suru Nari?</title>
<summary>The girls come up with a new plot twist: to charge their Naria powers, they`ll need to become idols!  But then their plans go awry when a monsters puts a spell on them with the magic mirror.  Urara becomes an evil CEO, and Inaho a sketchy fortune teller.  Will they be able to break the spell and win the hearts of the audience? And how are they going to explain all this plot in an 8 minute show?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716349</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178377" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私たちは伝説の戦士なり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re the Legendary Warriors?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashitachi wa Densetsu no Senshi Nari?</title>
<summary>The girls mission to become famous magical girl anime characters continues.  This time they`re under attack from an old friend: pkpk from Gdgd fairies!  Will they be able to come up with a clever scene and win big ratings?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716347</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178378" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは不思議な出会いなり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s a Strange Encounter?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Fushigi na Deai Nari?</title>
<summary>It`s a bold new experiment in technology as three girls are tasked with making their own anime!  This 3 minute short version of a longer, 40-minute program uses 3D computer technology to turn aspiring actress into anime magical girls!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716371</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="178993" update="2016-07-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="178994" update="2016-07-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179061" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4人目の魔法少女なり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fourth Magical Girl?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">4 Ninme no Mahou Shoujo Nari?</title>
<summary>The girls meet a new magical girl, Usagi!  But when the new girl turns out to be a monster, they`ll have to become "a magical girl who`s anxious to fight the enemy that`s right in front of them, and a magical girl who`s started to get worried about things at the worst possible time, and a perverted magical girl who`s getting excited to realize that he`s actually a boy!"  Can they break out of the spell and transform by giving a plausible explanation for what they`d do with 150 crabs?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716359</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179062" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏休みはいなほの別荘でバカンスなり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take a Summer Vacation at Inaho`s Villa?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuyasumi wa Inaho no Bessou de Vacance Nari?</title>
<summary>The girls take a vacation at Inaho`s villa, only to be attacked by a monster maid!   The monster puts them in a delicate situation, where one girls comes to their villa only to find a squatter living there already, and then somebody else comes to do an open house.  An epic villa-pun battle breaks out to determine who will win the villa.  Can they transform while sharing their bitter summer memories and defeat this villa villain?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716357</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179063" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならおばあちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Granny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Obaa-chan</title>
<summary>Urara wants to visit her grandma, so she uses her magic powers to fly to the countryside.  When she arrives, she finds out that grannie is really sick!  Then a monster appears, and tells her that she`s walked right into a trap! Can the Naria girls successfully play the roles of a boy on a first date, his weird girlfriend, and the ghost of his grandmother who appears and starts giving him nosy advice?  It may be the only way to save Urara`s own grandmother!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716355</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179064" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">めざせ! CMデビューなり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aim for Our Commercial Debut!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezase! CM Debut Nari?</title>
<summary>The next step for the Naria girls on their road to idol stardom is to do a TV commercial!  But a cunning monster traps them in a hallucination!  The monster makes them think that they`re a traveling conman trying to pass a married woman off as a high-tech maid robot, and a pure boy who`s suspicious, but still can`t refuse because he can`t stop thinking about the maid`s breasts. To get out, they`ll have to pretend to be a store employee trying to sell a cucumber, and cast magic spells to get the hair out of a drain!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716353</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179756" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法少女のいない世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A World Without Magical Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Shoujo no Inai Sekai</title>
<summary>It`s the last episode, and like that OTHER magical girl anime, that means it`s time for a downer ending!  But first, the gang needs to come up with clever ways to get past a horde of enemies!  Can they stop talking about Urara`s recent purchase of leopard-print bras long enough to think of a way to get past their foes?  And how, exactly, is Urara like a Christmas card?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716367</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179757" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! 冬将軍なり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash! Russian Winter?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Fuyushuugun Nari?</title>
<summary>Urara finds out the truth about her mom: that she wasn`t abandoned, her mother made a great wish to the Naria to save her life.  In a last-ditch attempt to stop her, the enemy Russian Winter turns her and her friends into a ditzy motorcycle gang readying for a battle against an enemy group.  Can they escape and defeat this final foe?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716365</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179758" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の舞台でエネルギーをフルチャージなり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fully Charge Your Energy on the Stage of Dreams?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Butai de Energy o Full Charge Nari?</title>
<summary>The Naria girls have a new friend: a producer who wants to help them make their performance at the Nippon dome a big success.  She wants them to come up with new ideas for a concert, and then they`ll all have to sing their hit holiday songs: "Don`t touch my azukisoba", "Roll Roll Rollypolly", and "Stop Illegal Parking!"
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716363</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="179759" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うららはひとりぼっちなり?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Urara Is Alone?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Urara wa Hitoribocchi Nari?</title>
<summary>Urara is in the doldrums.  What is a monster? Why is she fighting them?  She meets another reluctant monster who shares her concerns, but then when her friends show up they have to fight!  The monsters attack turns them into a manager who catches a girl shoplifting at the supermarket when her father comes to apologize, but he`s actually the manager`s ex-boyfriend and things get super-awkward.  Then they almost run out of air time! Can Urara transform without using a catchphrase to speed things up?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>716361</identifier>
<identifier>mahou-shoujo-naria-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
