<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12150" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2017-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Trickster: Edogawa Ranpo "Shounen Tanteidan" yori</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">TRICKSTER -江戸川乱歩「少年探偵団」より-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Trickster</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">TRICKSTER -来自江户川乱步「少年侦探团」-</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2874" type="Alternative Setting">Wanpaku Tanteidan</anime>
<anime id="12455" type="Other">Trickster: Edogawa Ranpo "Shounen Tanteidan" yori OVA</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11523" approval="3" total="8">Bungou Stray Dogs</anime>
<anime id="8370" approval="2" total="5">Kamisama no Memo-chou: It`s the Only NEET Thing to Do.</anime>
<anime id="10169" approval="1" total="1">Hamatora The Animation</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://trickster-project.com/anime/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1284" type="Animation Work">Shin-Ei Animation</name>
<name id="917" type="Animation Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="1312" type="Character Design">Peach Pit</name>
<name id="28427" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Erika</name>
<name id="28339" type="Direction">Mukai Masahiro</name>
<name id="27786" type="Music">Hayashi Yuuki</name>
<name id="45934" type="Animation Character Design">Yamada Shin`ya</name>
</creators>
<description>It is the 2030s. The Boy Detectives Club gathers under Akechi Kogorou, the mysterious detective. The group solves cases great and small using their unique skills. One day, a member of the club, Hanazaki Kensuke, meets the boy Kobayashi Yoshio. Kobayashi`s body cannot die due to the effects of the "Unidentifiable Mist," but he yearns for death, and shirks from contact with other people. Taking an interest in him, Hanazaki invites him to join the Boy Detectives Club. Their meeting is connected to the fate tying together Akechi Kogorou, and the era`s greatest villain, the Fiend With Twenty Faces.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="391">2.47</permanent>
<temporary count="395">5.13</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>189276.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18456</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33377</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://trickster-project.com/anime/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Trickster_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>TRICKSTER_-江戸川乱歩「少年探偵団」より-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4326</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>356883</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19502</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>@trickster_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B077QWFWNL</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3589" parentid="4251" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-04">
<name>multiple protagonists - TO BE MOVED TO PARENT OR DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be moved into its parent tag http://anidb.net/t4251 [ensemble cast], or removed entirely. If the tagged entry meets the updated definition of ensemble cast, tag ensemble cast and delete multiple protagonist. If it does not meet the ensemble cast definition, delete this tag and take no further action.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5902" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-27">
<name>organ trafficking</name>
<description>Illegal trafficking of human organs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6724" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-07">
<name>Anime no Me</name>
<description>Anime no Me was an anime brand and programming block by http://anidb.net/cr917 [TMS Entertainment], http://anidb.net/cr1284 [Shin-Ei Animation], East Japan Marketing &amp; Communications, Inc., Sumitomo Corporation, and http://anidb.net/cr36685 [Asmik-Ace]. It ran from July 2016 to March 2018. The "Me" in its name means "eye" and refers to the eye of a typhoon.</description>
<picurl>64114.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="82294" type="main character in" update="2016-06-01">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Kobayashi Yoshio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82295" type="main character in" update="2016-06-01">
<rating votes="3">2.54</rating>
<name>Hanasaki Kensuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>187315.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82561" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Inoue Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192700.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84113" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="3">3.90</rating>
<name>Nakamura Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33509" picture="204529.jpg">Tadokoro Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84114" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Katsuta Masaharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192702.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33595" picture="223803.jpg">Masumoto Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84115" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Ootomo Hisashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34070" picture="130103.jpg">Furukawa Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84116" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Yamane Tasuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36495" picture="176250.jpg">Yamaya Yoshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84117" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="2">1.18</rating>
<name>Kaijin Nijuu Mensou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8808" picture="33233.jpg">Gackt</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84118" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Akechi Kogorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84119" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-12">
<rating votes="2">3.81</rating>
<name>Noro Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>192701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86299" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Pippo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38921" picture="147228.jpg">Hon`izumi Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86300" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Miyanishi Takumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44231" picture="179635.jpg">Wakabayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86301" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Aragaki Naoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86302" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Senou Chuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11025" picture="43745.jpg">Tezuka Hideaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86303" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Akagi Meiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38232" picture="140073.jpg">Asai Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86304" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Kyoumoto Harumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86305" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Nemoto Junko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12608" picture="42590.jpg">Yoshizawa Kiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86306" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Nemoto Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86309" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Imaizumi Masayoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33784" picture="93013.jpg">Takeuchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86310" type="appears in" update="2016-11-21">
<name>Kanda Toshifumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>194956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30755" picture="189414.jpg">Seki Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="180402" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地底迷宮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Underground Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitei Meikyuu</title>
<summary>After school, Inoue watches Katsuda of the tennis club practicing before heading home, and Hanasaki tests out some tools of the Boy Detectives` Club trade with Scientific Experiments Club members Ohtomo and Yamane. Meanwhile, a police car is found overturned after a crash. A film reel labeled "For Akechi-kun" is found in the car, and one of the passengers, Senior Officer Kanda, is missing. The film reel depicts Twenty Faces telling Akechi that if he can`t find Kanda by 9:00 PM, the senior officer may lose his life...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180403" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">塔上の無業者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hopeless on the Tower</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toujou no Mugyousha</title>
<summary>Kobayashi somehow feels that maybe he can die if he stays with Hanasaki, so he joins the Boy Detectives` Club. His first mission is to help find a jobless young man who`s gone missing. The club starts by receiving files on missing persons from Detective Nakamura and her subordinate, Miyanishi, who are facing an investigation of their own now after a medical examiner went missing. They were all set to begin the search, but when the mysterious and socially awkward Kobayashi perpetually clashes with Inoue and Noro, he tries to make a run for it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180404" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金色の追跡者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Golden Tracker</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kin`iro no Tsuisekisha</title>
<summary>A young woman approaches the Boy Detectives` Club and asks them to find the intended recipient of a series of threat letters her boyfriend made. They accept the job and begin to tail her boyfriend. Meanwhile Kobayashi, after missing his chance to return Hanasaki`s dropped wallet, uses it to buy a desperately needed meal. Hanasaki finds out by checking his electronic money usage history, and he convinces Kobayashi to join him on the current investigation in a second attempt to get him to join the club...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180405" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">D坂蜃気楼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mirage on D. Hill</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">D Saka Shinkirou</title>
<summary>In the year 203X, a security robot goes on a rampage in Shibuya. Nakamura Nao, a police detective with the public safety department, commissions detective Akechi Kogorou to solve the case... but Akechi, along with Inoue Ryou of the Boy Detectives Club, is already heading toward Hinomoto Heavy Industries, the robot`s manufacturer. Meanwhile, Hanasaki Kensuke of the Boy Detectives club is pursuing a lost dog after receiving a report from the club`s technical whiz, Noro Makoto. As Hanasaki corners the dog in an abandoned building, he finds himself face-to-face with a mysterious boy...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180792" update="2016-10-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180947" update="2017-01-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181233" update="2016-11-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">箱庭の楽天地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Paradise in a Miniature Garden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakoniwa no Rakutenchi</title>
<summary>The residents of the Kokorogaoka Housing Complex refuse to vacate their homes for the sake of urban development, so they declare its independence from Japan as an autonomous borough. The one to make this announcement is none other than Hanasaki`s older brother, who ran away from home years ago. Hanasaki asks Akechi for help, but Akechi refuses to do any job he hasn`t been hired for and confines Hanasaki to the building. Then a mysterious package arrives, and its contents reveal that Twenty Faces was the one behind these current events. Unable to wait around, Hanasaki heads for the housing complex himself...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="181234" update="2016-11-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">穢れなき逢瀬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pure Tryst</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kegare Naki Ouse</title>
<summary>Akechi is relaxing at a spa to relieve the exhaustion of his recent cases. A story about the security robot incident, the organ-selling incident, and the underground waterway kidnapping incident come on the TV, discussing a "mysterious cooperant" who resolved them all... in other words, Akechi himself. Then Nakamura asks him about his history with Twenty Faces, and Akechi begins to recount the trauma of his youth. Meanwhile, Hanasaki also carries the weight of a checkered past, as he`s summoned home by his father.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="181235" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">余暇の散歩者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Holiday Stalker</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoka no Sanposha</title>
<summary>Hanasaki has been trying various things to help Kobayashi die, but nothing has worked. Then, while Akechi is away, Hanasaki takes the liberty of accepting six job requests. He`s noticed that all the times Kobayashi has been injured were after completing a job, so he thinks that if they complete lots of jobs, his wish will come true... but things don`t go exactly as he planned.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="181236" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蜘蛛の糸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spider`s Thread</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kumo no Ito</title>
<summary>Kobayashi and Inoue are trapped in the underground discharge channels as a result of Twenty Faces` maneuvering, and a massive amount of water is pouring into their chamber. Worried about the police officers searching elsewhere in the channels, Inoue tells Kobayashi to escape with the message that the map they were given is fake and they need to evacuate immediately. However, the officers still end up trapped. Hanasaki rushes to rescue them and talks the former Boy Detectives` Club member Katsuda into helping him get to the scene faster. But as they`re en route, more and more water surrounds Inoue...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182069" update="2016-12-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">煙霧陰る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shade by Haze</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Enmu Kageru</title>
<summary>Even with a gun pointed at him, Hanasaki is brought to tears by the conversation between Twenty Faces and Akechi. Then the Boy Detectives` Club arrives on the scene. Inoue and Katsuda try to rescue the employees being held hostage by the security robots, while Noro and Ohtomo struggle to stop the robots. Kobayashi is stricken by an impulse he`s never felt before and runs toward Hanasaki, but Twenty Faces had already seen all this coming and brainwashed the employees to turn on Inoue and Katsuda. He then declares that if Akechi kills Hanasaki, he`ll make the employees stop and the whole thing will end.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182070" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">残虐戯具</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cruel Tool</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zangyou Gigu</title>
<summary>Hanasaki`s act is successful in convincing Akechi and the Boy Detectives` Club that he was kidnapped by Twenty Faces. Akechi takes off to try to save him, saying he has an idea where Hanasaki might be. Kobayashi and the others are left behind, but Ohtomo gives them a hint as to where Akechi`s gone, so they set out to track him down. Hanasaki is at Le Waqua, following Twenty Faces` instructions to take over the complex by controlling its security robots. Then Akechi arrives, and an epic shoot-out with the security robots unfolds.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182071" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無垢なる天秤</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Innocent Scale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukunaru Tenbin</title>
<summary>Hanasaki runs out of the office after an argument with Akechi and the others, only to end up confined by Twenty Faces and shown several video clips: Haruhiko in the hospital after surviving the gunshot, a girl who died when she didn`t receive a needed organ transplant from the facility that the Boy Detectives` Club shut down, Hanasaki`s father at a press conference for the opening of his new commercial complex... and finally, the rest of the Boy Detectives` Club carrying on without him. These videos and Twenty Faces` words cut deeply into Hanasaki`s psyche.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182072" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">陥落の英雄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fallen Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanraku no Eiyuu</title>
<summary>Kensuke is bewildered when Haruhiko invites him to live together, but Isuzu is negotiating with the police for three billion yen in exchange for the removal of the residents of the housing complex. Meanwhile, Nakamura requests the aid of Akechi and the Boy Detectives` Club in the case.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182919" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">年末だよ『TRICKSTER』男だらけのピザパーティー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s the End of the Year: A Pizza Party Full of Male "Tricksters"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nenmatsu Da yo "Trickster" Otoko-tachi Darake no Pizza Party</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183303" update="2017-02-07">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蘇る陰獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Regenesis of the Beast in the Shadows</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Injuu</title>
<summary>To escape the enemies targeting Fukiya, the death row prisoner they`re guarding, the Boy Detectives` Club takes refuge in the abandoned building that Kobayashi had once been using as his base. They manage to hold their ground as they wait for a helicopter sent by Noro. In the meantime, Kobayashi has no choice but to play along with Fukiya`s word association game, which causes his mental state to grow increasingly unstable. Meanwhile Hanasaki, after being accepted into Hide-chan`s Red Beetle gang, learns of their involvement in the case and has to make a choice...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="183304" update="2017-01-24">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">断罪の甲虫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beetle of Conviction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Danzai no Kabutomushi</title>
<summary>After being out of touch for so long, Akechi calls the office. Kobayashi complains to him that Hanasaki is acting weird, and Akechi tells him, "do to him what he did to you." Then the Boy Detectives` Club receives an odd request: a death-row prisoner who`s received a death threat has asked specifically for them to guard him when he`s escorted to the district court. Inoue is reluctant, but Kobayashi, thinking that solving this case with Hanasaki will restore things to the way they were, accepts the job for them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="183305" update="2017-01-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">螺旋の梯子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spiral Ladder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rasen no Hashigo</title>
<summary>Yamane Tasuku, a younger member of the Scientific Experiments Club alongside Ohtomo, is troubled by three things. The first is that Ohtomo picks on him too much. The second is that he`s always left behind in conversations. The third and most troubling of all is that he doesn`t know how to become a member of the Boy Detectives` Club. One day Yumeko approaches him, mistaking him for a member of the club and asking him to investigate a case in which the school`s most attractive boys are becoming victims of theft. But Yamane is so pleased by the mistake that he accepts the job...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="183306" update="2017-01-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜光人, 乱舞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wild Dance of the Luminous Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakoujin, Ranbu</title>
<summary>With the Le Waqua incident resolved and Twenty Faces in custody, the world appeared to be at peace again. However, the trauma of the incident left Hanasaki psychologically unstable, and the Boy Detectives` Club is reluctant to let him return to the ranks. Meanwhile, Inoue and the others are approached by Police Detective Miyanishi with a request to catch whoever is responsible for uploading candid photos of celebrities to a website called "Lynch Shot" without permission. The investigation begins, but Kobayashi can`t help worrying about Hanasaki.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="183994" update="2017-03-01">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">堕ち行く道化師</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fallen Clown</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ochiyuku Doukeshi</title>
<summary>Kobayashi, along with Inoue, searches for the place that he saw in his dream. Hanasaki and Hide-chan then show up and offer to help. Shortly after, Kobayashi has a flashback after seeing gingko trees lining their path, then takes off running toward an abandoned building. Meanwhile, the police catch Akechi on the security cameras breaking the fake Twenty Faces out of prison. The police suspect Akechi is the real Twenty Faces, but Miyanishi disagrees and sets out to find the truth alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="183995" update="2017-02-26">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪意の応酬</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cycle of Malice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akui no Oushuu</title>
<summary>As he`s resting to recover from his gunshot wound, Kobayashi has an odd dream in which he sees a woman in a bed and a man approaching her. He doesn`t recognize them, but the dream gives him a strange headache. Meanwhile, Hide-chan makes contact with Hanasaki, inviting him to help them punish someone who`s been posting damaging information online under a pseudonym. But Hanasaki refuses, so Hide-chan leaves, saying there`s too much to do and not enough time. His words make Hanasaki think about what it is he wants to do, and he sets off to visit Kobayashi...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="183996" update="2017-02-22">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純悪錯誤</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mistaken Absolute Evil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junwaru Sakugo</title>
<summary>Inoue and the other detectives are disheartened after being told that the Boy Detectives` Club would be disbanded. The strange air around Kobayashi has returned and is working hard to heal his wound. Around the same time, Akechi is recalling his past with Twenty Faces. During a time of war, when Akechi was a mercenary, he and Twenty Faces came through many vicious battles together... but he was growing bored of the thrills that Twenty Faces arranged for him. Then he met Fumiyo, a Japanese reporter, and the two of them were increasingly drawn to each other...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="183997" update="2017-02-22">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">離散の反動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebound of Breakup</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Risan no Handou</title>
<summary>Kobayashi is in extreme pain after taking a gunshot.Has the mysterious power that protected him disappeared? Inoue is stunned by Akechi`s prediction. Perhaps Kobayashi actually wants to live? Hanasaki is shaken at the sight of Kobayashi at death`s door. Akechi gives advice on how to save him, but then reminds him that he was the one who made Kobayashi want to live, and tells him to do something about the situation himself before making another shocking declaration...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="184081" update="2017-01-26">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184082" update="2017-01-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="184894" update="2017-03-31">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年探偵団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy Detectives Club</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen Tanteidan</title>
<summary>Hanasaki left Kobayashi behind and took off for Twenty Faces` hideout alone, planning to put an end to everything. But Kobayashi can`t accept that, so he follows him... even though the aura surrounding him has already disappeared. Unaware of this, Hanasaki reaches the hideout and finds Akechi, but Twenty Faces also appears and warns him that the hideout will soon be destroyed. Hanasaki throws Akechi into an escape shuttle and turns toward Twenty Faces, with his finger on the trigger.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="184895" update="2017-03-22">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明星の蘇生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return of the Evening Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Myoujou no Sosei</title>
<summary>The Boy Detectives` Club arrives at the Space Expo. Hanasaki and Kobayashi board the shuttle for the craft in the sky that Twenty Faces uses as his base, where Akechi is being held captive, but the shuttle is blown up and the two of them are held in place by security robots. Inoue and the others face off against the special security force, but they`re at a disadvantage. Just when they thought all hope was lost, Ohtomo drills his way up from the ground in a vehicle being used as a Space Expo exhibit, but their relief is short-lived...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="184896" update="2017-03-14">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">火にいる小虫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Small Moth Flying into a Flame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hi ni Iru Komushi</title>
<summary>Akechi, stunned to learn that Nakamura was brainwashed by Twenty Faces, ends up captured by the special security force. Meanwhile, at the New Tokyo World Fair, the plane built to carry people to the stratosphere is involved in a catastrophic crash. The Boy Detectives` Club is at a loss, and their attempts to reach Akechi fail. Then, suddenly, Twenty Faces appears on their monitor...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="184897" update="2017-03-07">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">語りき生贄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Veracious Victim</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katariki Ikenie</title>
<summary>Miyanishi was shot to death by Nakamura. During her interrogation, Nakamura testifies that Twenty Faces is actually Akechi. Determining that she may have been under his control, the police conduct a search of the Akechi Investigation Firm office. Hanasaki insists that Akechi can`t be Twenty Faces, and Inoue demands proof, but the police ignore them, and the Boy Detectives` Club are reminded of their own powerlessness. Meanwhile Akechi, now on the run, suspects there`s something more behind this incident and starts looking for the truth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193465" update="2017-11-25">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193466" update="2017-11-25">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-03-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193467" update="2017-11-25">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193468" update="2017-11-25">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
