<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1217" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-08-30</startdate>
<enddate>2003-08-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tokyo Godfathers</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Los Padrinos de Tokio</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="synonym">Tokyo Godfathers - löytölapsen arvoitus</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Кръсниците от Токио</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Токійські хрещені батьки</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">TG</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">東京ゴッドファーザーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tokyo Godfathers</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Tokyo Godfathers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Tokyo Godfathers</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Tokyo Godfathers</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Tokyo Godfathers</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Однажды в Токио</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Rodzice Chrzestni z Tokio</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Tokyo Godfathers</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Padrinhos de Tóquio</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Tokyo Godfathers</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Tokijští kmotři</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Tokyo Godfathers</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Οι Νονοί του Τόκιο</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">סנדקי טוקיו</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Tokiói Keresztapák</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Tokijo krikštatėviai</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Tokyo Tanrıları</title>
<title xml:lang="sl" type="official">Tokijski botri</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Ükskord Tokyos</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">東京教父</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">东京教父</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Héroes al Rescate</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="570" approval="41" total="57">Sennen Joyuu</anime>
<anime id="51" approval="1" total="4">Love Hina Christmas Special: Silent Eve</anime>
<anime id="3389" approval="1" total="2">Itsudatte My Santa!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="12">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="92088">Tragic but very heartwarming story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="732962">weirdly i like it..i don`t know why but when i was younger i watched it dubbed for more than ten times i watched again last year and it`s not that good but i just like it.it`s weird..i definitely recommend it watch it..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="522223">About ten years ago, I bundled Tokyo Godfathers with John Ford`s Three Godfathers (featuring John Wayne) and Three Men and a Baby (directed by Leonard Nimoy) as a Christmas present for my sister and her husband. All three of these films (as well as two others) were based upon a 1913 novel about three bank robbers who become godfathers to a newborn child. Try watching all three films. I think you will enjoy seeing how the three directors each gave their own interpretation of the same story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="272102">Funny, intelligent and tragic...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;just watch it! you won`t regret!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="420391">Very thought provoking</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="230513">What a brilliant story this is! That is the best way I can discribe it for you cause words fail me... Go watch it please, you will love it!

Dp</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sonypictures.jp/archive/movie/worldcinema/tgf/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="54" type="Direction">Kon Satoshi</name>
<name id="54" type="Character Design">Kon Satoshi</name>
<name id="5748" type="Character Design">Konishi Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="54" type="Original Work">Kon Satoshi</name>
<name id="7267" type="Music">Suzuki Kei`ichi</name>
<name id="24612" type="Music">Moonriders</name>
</creators>
<description>Three homeless people — http://anidb.net/ch15686 [Gin], a former professional bicycle racer; http://anidb.net/ch15687 [Hana], a transvestite; and http://anidb.net/ch14271 [Miyuki], a run-away young girl — live together in Shinjuku, Tokyo. On Christmas Eve, the three discover a http://anidb.net/ch15688 [baby girl] at a garbage dump. They head for the brighter parts of the city, where people are enjoying the holiday festivities, to look for the baby`s parents. While the three search for the parents, uncanny luck results in their meeting other people while their adventures with the baby continue. Will the baby lead these three protagonists to their destiny? This small adventure lets each of the trio confront their own lives, which they almost threw away, while maintaining their dignity and happiness under unfortunate circumstances.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4349">8.16</permanent>
<temporary count="4369">8.08</temporary>
<review count="6">8.77</review>
</ratings>
<picture>18344.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2018</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1404</identifier>
<identifier>rcoqbk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sonypictures.jp/archive/movie/worldcinema/tgf/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tokyo_Godfathers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>東京ゴッドファーザーズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>566</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>241171</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6562</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4577" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-19">
<name>family values</name>
<description>Family values are traditional or cultural values, generally conservative in nature, that pertain to the family`s structure, function, roles, beliefs, attitudes, and ideals. They encompass a set of beliefs, the most common of which is the classical "traditional family" involving a middle-class family with a breadwinner father and a homemaker mother, raising their biological children.
According to Merriam-Webster, family values are "values especially of a traditional or conservative kind which are held to promote the sound functioning of the family and to strengthen the fabric of society."
Source: English Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="14271" type="main character in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="7">6.03</rating>
<name>Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A runaway senior high school student. During a family dispute concerning what seems to be her missing cat named `angel`, Miyuki stabbed her father (believing him to be responsible for the disappearance), and has stayed away from her home since, losing a substantial amount of weight. She found a personals ad in an old newspaper in the course of the film that hints that her father wasn`t responsible for the disappearance of her cat, and that the cat seems to have come back. That ad is the reason why she decided to call her father again.</description>
<picture>44418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15084" picture="44405.jpg">Okamoto Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15686" type="main character in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="8">7.62</rating>
<name>Gin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A homeless bicycle shop owner who claims to be a professional cyclist. He left behind his wife and daughter when his gambling debts became too large, and claimed they were dead to gain sympathy. His daughter, Kiyoko, shares the same name as the baby he and the others find.</description>
<picture>44419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15082" picture="44408.jpg">Emori Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15687" type="main character in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="9">7.91</rating>
<name>Hana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A homeless drag queen. He never knew his actual parents, and thus feels the most sympathy for "Kiyoko", the baby he finds and names. Because of his upbringing, he is the kindest out of the three main characters, but is also the sickliest, which he hides from the others.</description>
<picture>44420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15083" picture="44404.jpg">Umegaki Yoshiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15688" type="main character in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">1.65</rating>
<name>Kiyoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A newborn infant that was deserted in a dump. She is found by the three main characters on Christmas Eve, and is named after the Japanese title of the traditional Christmas song "Silent Night" by Hana.</description>
<picture>44421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15689" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">2.38</rating>
<name>Oota</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Yakuza boss who is found and saved by the three main characters when he becomes trapped under his car. As thanks, he invites them to his daughter`s wedding, which leads to Miyuki`s and Kiyoko`s kidnapping at the hands of a Hispanic hitman. His daughter, coincidently, is also named Kiyoko.</description>
<picture>44422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1986" picture="1919.gif">Iizuka Shouzou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15690" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">4.26</rating>
<name>Kaa-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The proprietor of a gay bar that Hana used to work at.</description>
<picture>44423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3298" picture="151659.jpg">Katou Seizou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15691" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">3.37</rating>
<name>Yasuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sachiko`s husband and the one who left behind Kiyoko.</description>
<picture>44424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2729" picture="186723.jpg">Ishimaru Hiroya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15692" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">8.95</rating>
<name>Roujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fellow homeless. He is discovered lying on the ground by Gin, and gives Gin a mysterious red bag before dying.</description>
<picture>44425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1814" picture="20690.jpg">Saikachi Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15693" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">2.63</rating>
<name>Miyuki no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A police officer. He unexpectedly finds Miyuki, his daughter, at the very end of the film.</description>
<picture>44426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15694" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="3">2.44</rating>
<name>Sachiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The self-proclaimed mother of Kiyoko. When Kiyoko is abandoned by her father, Sachiko falls into despair and prepares to commit suicide before Kiyoko is returned to her. In a strange turn of events, it is revealed that Kiyoko is not Sachiko`s biological daughter.</description>
<picture>44427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6871" picture="51988.jpg">Terase Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15695" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">2.63</rating>
<name>Gin no Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A nurse. She is on the verge of being married to the Doctor by the time she is rediscovered by Gin, her father. Her name is also Kiyoko.</description>
<picture>44428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15696" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">5.90</rating>
<name>Isha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A doctor who takes care of Hana when he collapses. He is the one Gin`s daughter plans on marrying.</description>
<picture>44429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15697" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">2.06</rating>
<name>Shinrou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The son-in-law of Oota.</description>
<picture>44430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15698" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-10">
<rating votes="2">3.53</rating>
<name>Taxi Untenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A Taxi driver who aids Miyuki and Hana during the climatic car chase.</description>
<picture>44431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="17840" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2003-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18876" update="2006-01-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2003-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18877" update="2006-01-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2003-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
