<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1218" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-11-20</startdate>
<enddate>2004-11-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Howl no Ugoku Shiro</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">El castillo errante de Howl</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">قلعة هاول المتحركة</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Keliaujanti Haulo Pilis</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Howl`un Yürüyen Şatosu</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Lâu đài di động của Howl</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Движещият се замък на Хоул</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hauru no Ugoku Shiro</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Замок-мандрівник</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Рухомий замок Хаула</title>
<title xml:lang="hr" type="synonym">Howlov putujući dvorac</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">HMC</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Howl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">HnUS</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ハウルの動く城</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">哈爾移動城堡</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Howl`s Moving Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Das wandelnde Schloss</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Le château ambulant</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Il castello errante di Howl</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">El Castillo Ambulante</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Ходячий замок</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Ruchomy zamek Hauru</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Det levande slottet</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">O Castelo Andante</title>
<title xml:lang="no" type="official">Det levende slottet</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">O Castelo Animado</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Zámek v oblacích</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="official">Det levende slot</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="official">Howl`s Moving Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Liikkuva linna</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Το Κινούμενο Κάστρο</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">הטירה הנעה</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">A vándorló palota</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="official">Haulo burtai: Keliaujanti pilis</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Yürüyen Şato</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="official">Castelul umblător al lui Howl</title>
<title xml:lang="sl" type="official">Čarovnik Howl in gibljivi grad</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Замъкът на Хаул</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Howli liikuv kindlus</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="official">Мандрівний замок</title>
<title xml:lang="hr" type="official">Pokretni dvorac</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">哈尔的移动城堡</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">El Increíble Castillo Vagabundo</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">قلعه متحرک هاول</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="112" approval="121" total="138">Sen to Chihiro no Kamikakushi</anime>
<anime id="331" approval="61" total="80">Tenkuu no Shiro Laputa</anime>
<anime id="286" approval="49" total="71">Majo no Takkyuubin</anime>
<anime id="7" approval="15" total="35">Mononoke-hime</anime>
<anime id="336" approval="3" total="25">Mimi o Sumaseba</anime>
<anime id="502" approval="3" total="10">Kumo no You ni Kaze no You ni</anime>
<anime id="303" approval="1" total="16">Tonari no Totoro</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="22">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="379739">Lots of great parts jumbled together equals mediocrity.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="370136">An excellent adaptation of the book. Contains all the ingredients needed to make a great fantasy movie</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="466222">A wonderful film that portrays perfectly that no mater how old or young you are you should always approach the world with a sense of wonder. For you never know what you will find.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="526796">This is also a very good one from Ghibli. A must-see for a fan of the studio!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="466624">A wonderfully fun fantasy film mixed with drama, comedy, action, fantasy, war, and lots of romance. Good for people who enjoy romance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="373896">Miyazaki`s movies are just a must see. Pure awesome.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="334763">Awesome!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="84121">Great animation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="428065">Beautifull art and amazing story, even if you don`t like anime its well worth your time!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.howl-movie.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="40" type="Direction">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="1947" type="Music">Hisaishi Joe</name>
<name id="729" type="Work">Studio Ghibli</name>
<name id="7184" type="Original Work">Diana Wynne Jones</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch10044 [Sophie Hatter], the eldest of three, is apprenticed to make hats for the people of Ingary, a place where spells, magic cloaks, and seven-league boots exist. She and all the young girls are warned to stay inside or be taken by http://anidb.net/ch5005 [Howl], the evil wizard whose black castle can be seen moving through the hills. After an encounter with a witch and with a spell cast on her to make her an http://anidb.net/ch10048 [old woman], Sophie goes to seek adventure. She heads towards Howl`s moving castle where she will encounter things she had never imagined.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9626">8.21</permanent>
<temporary count="9680">8.28</temporary>
<review count="5">6.89</review>
</ratings>
<picture>18364.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>889</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>431</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1495</identifier>
<identifier>dmgfsh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.howl-movie.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://disney.go.com/disneypictures/castle/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Howl's_Moving_Castle_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ハウルの動く城</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2863</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240799</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6882</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/770</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-08">
<name>teleportation</name>
<description>Teleportation is the transfer of matter from one point to another, possibly a distant one, without application of force, and generally instantly. This contradicts scientific law as we know it, and is therefore nowadays impossible. Sometimes it appears as a paranormal or supernatural ability, and sometimes it is shown in science fiction through technological devices backed up by scientific laws yet to be discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2616" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>mina</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word mina refers to a broad audience, which can be said to be "the entire family", from the grumpy grandpa to the newborn baby. In Japanese, the word means simply "everyone", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic. Mina works are deliberately targeted at a range of people as wide as possible, and are commonly associated with high-budget releases that require a very large audience to be financially viable. They usually bring mildly philosophical themes so that the adults can be interested, but do so without bringing objectionable content so that the children can be allowed to watch, and indeed also feature content specifically geared to spark their interest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3055" parentid="3876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>fairy tale</name>
<description>This anime is either based on or contains parts of fairy tales. Usually those parts are highly modified or twisted when compared with the original source.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5998" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-08">
<name>spider tank</name>
<description>A spider tank is a tank that uses four or more legs for movement instead of the tracks seen in most real-life tanks.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6900" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-23">
<name>gaslamp fantasy</name>
<description>Gaslamp fantasy is a subgenre of both fantasy and historical fiction, similar to but distinct from http://anidb.net/t2870 [steampunk], to which it is loosely related. While steampunk focuses on fantastic Industrial Revolution technology and as such is a genre of science fiction, gaslamp fantasy focuses more on supernatural elements and frequently includes magic and supernatural creatures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="5005" type="main character in" update="2018-12-30">
<rating votes="47">8.63</rating>
<name>Howl</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Howl is a wizard in the land of Ingary and he has several aliases in Ingary: he is known as Wizard Howl in Market Chipping, Wizard Pendragon in the capital Kingsbury, and Jenkin the Sorcerer in lower-class Porthaven. Howl`s original name is the similarly pronounced Howell (Welsh: Hywel). He lives in a moving castle, powered by a fire demon named Calcifer. He has an apprentice named Michael Fisher and was apprenticed to Mrs. Pentstemmon.</description>
<picture>1915.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1967" picture="21265.jpg">Kimura Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="5006" type="main character in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="28">8.05</rating>
<name>Calcifer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Calcifer is a fire demon from Diana Wynne Jones` 1986 novel Howl`s Moving Castle. He is described as "a thin blue face, very long and thin, with a thin blue nose" and curly green flames as hair. He has purple fire for his mouth, two green flames for eyebrows, and orange flame for his eyes. In the movie, he is a teardrop shaped orange flame, but in the scene where Howl moves the castle, Calcifer flares up and looks somewhat like his description in the book. In House of Many Ways, Calcifer is described as a blue teardrop. However, in the Japanese animated film adaption, Calcifer appears to be an adorable orange flame.</description>
<picture>21266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1968" picture="21267.jpg">Gashuuin Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10044" type="main character in" update="2012-04-25">
<rating votes="28">8.83</rating>
<name>Sophie Hatter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sophie is the oldest of three sisters and lives a boring life as a hat-maker. She has already determined that her life is everything but exciting, that nothing will ever happen to her and that she might as well give up any thoughts on adventure or excitement in her life. She hides away in the hat-shop and when she for once sneaks out to visit her younger sister, who works in a bakery, she is almost scared to death - even though she runs into a handsome young man who offers to buy her a drink (which she of course turns down).
But life takes an unexpected turn when the witch of the Waste decides that she really doesn`t care for this young girl and turns her into an old hag. Sophie realizes that it is impossible for her to stay on and she is forced on the road to seek her fortune (or at least a life). After a while she comes to a castle which moves around in the hills close to her home-town. She of course knows what it is, it belongs to a dreadful wizard, named Howl, that eats the heart of young women. But since she is now an old woman she is not afraid but enters - and enters a bargain with the wizard`s fire demon who promises to break her curse if she in turn can set him free.
The wizard Howl very soon turns out to not be quite the monster he was supposed to be, but he is a very sloppy and lazy young man so Sophie convinces him to let her stay on as the cleaning lady.</description>
<picture>30252.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5801" picture="30256.jpg">Baishou Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10048" type="main character in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="25">8.94</rating>
<name>Sophie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sophie is the oldest of three sisters and lives a boring life as a hat-maker. She has already determined that her life is everything but exciting, that nothing will ever happen to her and that she might as well give up any thoughts on adventure or excitement in her life. She hides away in the hat-shop and when she for once sneaks out to visit her younger sister, who works in a bakery, she is almost scared to death - even though she runs into a handsome young man who offers to buy her a drink (which she of course turns down).
But life takes an unexpected turn when the witch of the Waste decides that she really doesn`t care for this young girl and turns her into an old hag. Sophie realizes that it is impossible for her to stay on and she is forced on the road to seek her fortune (or at least a life). After a while she comes to a castle which moves around in the hills close to her home-town. She of course knows what it is, it belongs to a dreadful wizard, named Howl, that eats the heart of young women. But since she is now an old woman she is not afraid but enters - and enters a bargain with the wizard`s fire demon who promises to break her curse if she in turn can set him free.
The wizard Howl very soon turns out to not be quite the monster he was supposed to be, but he is a very sloppy and lazy young man so Sophie convinces him to let her stay on as the cleaning lady.</description>
<picture>30258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5801" picture="30256.jpg">Baishou Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19993" type="appears in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="8">3.11</rating>
<name>Lettie Hatter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lettie Hatter is Sophie`s younger sister.</description>
<picture>51912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16986" picture="46196.jpg">Kazuki Yayoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20005" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="11">3.65</rating>
<name>Arechi no Majo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4895" picture="28242.jpg">Miwa Akihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20006" type="main character in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="11">7.84</rating>
<name>Markl</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3785" picture="71854.jpg">Kamiki Ryuunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20011" type="appears in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="9">7.39</rating>
<name>Madame Suliman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30150" picture="79467.jpg">Katou Haruko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20012" type="appears in" update="2010-07-25">
<rating votes="10">7.65</rating>
<name>Heen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31967" picture="85812.jpg">Harada Daijirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102584" type="appears in" update="2019-05-07">
<name>Kakashi no Kabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15035" picture="170336.jpg">Ooizumi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102682" type="appears in" update="2019-05-07">
<name>Fanny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9864" picture="36832.jpg">Yasokawa Mayuno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102684" type="appears in" update="2019-05-07">
<name>Kokuou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102686" type="appears in" update="2019-05-07">
<name>Ouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15035" picture="170336.jpg">Ooizumi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102690" type="appears in" update="2019-05-07">
<name>Madge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57827" picture="233387.jpg">Kanno Rio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="13210" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">1.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">First Short Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21302" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">2.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview-Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27282" update="2016-01-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>120</length>
<airdate>2004-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42515" update="2015-02-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>2004-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42516" update="2015-02-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2004-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51103" update="2010-04-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2004-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51104" update="2010-04-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2004-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51105" update="2010-04-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>2004-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135849" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>120</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Storyboard (with movie soundtrack)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
