<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12199" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>50</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-09-18</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Heybot!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヘボット!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Heybot!</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="123101">Yeah, it`s commercial.
Yeah, it`s aimed at kids to sell toys.
Yeah, it`s fart jokes.

But in the middle of all this, lies a show filled of fun, gags, and 4th wall jokes.

I would never expect to see a show with a Bonfire joke before going to the commercials or with a complain about Super Mario`s pipes being familiar.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.heybot.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="42824" type="Animation Work">BN Pictures</name>
<name id="20123" type="Character Design">Sano Toshihiko</name>
<name id="3688" type="Series Composition">Tomioka Atsuhiro</name>
<name id="42824" type="Original Work">BN Pictures</name>
<name id="1051" type="Original Plan">Bandai</name>
<name id="5571" type="Direction">Ishihira Shinji</name>
<name id="23377" type="Music">Oosumi Tomotaka</name>
</creators>
<description>The anime takes place on the screw-shaped island country of Nejigajima and follows the two "Bokyabots" Hebot and the Yurui Prince Nejiru as they collect different "Bokya Neji" screws. When the Bokyabots wear the Bokya Neji screws on their heads, they`re able to compete in "Bokya Battles," battles for who can think up and tell the best jokes.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="37">3.28</permanent>
<temporary count="37">4.27</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221761.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18695</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33434</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.heybot.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヘボット!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4290</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>357079</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19534</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="84237" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-26">
<name>DJ Sarukky</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="39787" picture="191405.jpg">Nakatsukasa Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84238" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-26">
<name>Cutbi Tiger</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="39679" picture="152239.jpg">Yamaguchi Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84239" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-26">
<name>Sky Rabbit</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="9405" picture="228517.jpg">Yamaoka Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84240" type="main character in" update="2016-08-26">
<name>Nejiru Negil</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="35832" picture="191404.jpg">Tamura Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84241" type="main character in" update="2016-08-26">
<name>Heybot</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84859" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-18">
<name>MC Neji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84860" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-18">
<name>Kasrina</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="32675" picture="149044.jpg">Ozaki Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84861" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-18">
<name>Guchiriman</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2258" picture="21881.jpg">Uchida Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84862" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-18">
<name>Geroriman</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84863" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-18">
<name>Gororiman</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="36576" picture="134934.jpg">Yokojima Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84864" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-18">
<name>Suchat</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="31926" picture="85750.jpg">Uchida Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84865" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-18">
<name>Neji-ou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84866" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-18">
<name>Bokyami</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84867" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-18">
<name>Moel</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="46968" picture="223812.jpg">Shin Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="180105" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘボ流・ネジタネの育て方!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Art of the Bonehead! How to Raise a Screw Tree!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hebo Ryuu: Neji Tane no Sodatekata!</title>
<summary>Heybot buys a mysterious screw seed off a mysterious woman. But although he and Nejiru put a lot of love into raising it, it ends up growing into one flat tree! Enlisting the help of the ninja Naganagamaru and his Stretchy-Stretchy screw, they manage to get the screw to grow... and grow... and it won`t stop growing until it reaches the moon!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720403</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180106" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コワコワ~, はじめてのコワ話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scary-Scary! It`s My First Scary Story!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kowakowa, Hajimete no Kowabanashi</title>
<summary>Nejiru and Heybot have just established their new store, the Screw-Ya, and are abruptly visited by wannabe main characters Moeru, Kathleena, and Suchat. They decide to VocaBattle for the title, but Nejiru loses easily due to missing a key screw! Could the mysterious, ghostly Yuko be the key to getting the impact their gags are lacking?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720401</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180107" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネジ屋対ボキャリーマンズ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Screw-Ya Versus VocaReemans!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nejiya tai Bokyarymans!</title>
<summary>Driven out of the castle, Nejiru and Heybot head out into town to collect VocaScrews, where they are confronted by the three down-on-their-luck VocaReemans. The VocaReemans want Heybot`s Bungle-Bungle Screw to complete their comedy act and escape their hum-drum jobs. Who will win this latest VocaBattle?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720399</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180108" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘボッと生まれて屁ボーン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">HeyBot Is Born with a Hey-Boom!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heybot to Umarete Onara Born!</title>
<summary>The Screw Kingdom is a land where humans and VocaBots live in symbiosis, united by the screws they hold dear. Prince Nejiru is given a Screw Soul on his birthday, which leads him to his very own VocaBot, who awakens with a huge fart! Nejiru and his new bot, Heybot, then return to the kingdom to challenge his father to a VocaBattle for the throne!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720397</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180243" update="2016-09-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180244" update="2016-09-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-09-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180688" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! ノリノリヶ島!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle! Groovy-Groovy Island!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Norinorigajima!</title>
<summary>Heybot and Nejiru awaken to the sounds of samba music, and find the people of the town engaged in a mad dance. Everyone, from the maids to the king, is acting strangely! It turns out it all started when the king`s old rival Norio arrived to steal back the Groovy-Groovy Screw. To save his father and all the people of the town, Nejiru and Heybot must venture Groovy-Groovy Island to get it back!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720411</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180689" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘックションでフエフエのヘボ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heybot Makes More with a Sneeze!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heccushion de Fuefue no Hebo</title>
<summary>Fuerlu and his friend Gyakuran have come to the Screw-Ya for help. Fuerlu can`t stop hiccupping up VocaScrews! Nejiru and Heybot try to help him, but the problem just gets worse and worse. And soon Nejiru`s own motives begin to appear a bit suspect...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720409</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180690" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激走! ボキャバトルレース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rushing Out! The VocaBattle Race!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekisou! Bokya Battle Race</title>
<summary>Nejiru and Heybot decide to compete in a race for a rare VocaScrew and a lifetime`s supply of Imochin! Heybot works with the Zodiac VocaBot Cat Vitiger, while Nejiru works with Vocammy, who is clearly plotting something. Cat Vitiger`s overwhelming speed gets Heybot out to an early lead, but he`ll have to deal with the missions doled out by the Walls of Voca if he wants to finish the race!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720407</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180691" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘボット, いなくなったってよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hey, Heybot`s Missing, Y`Know!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heybot, Inakunattatte yo</title>
<summary>Heybot`s been kidnapped by the VocaReemans! Vocammy, who wants to take Heybot for herself, sends her devoted groupies out to steal him back! When Nejiru also comes after Heybot, they wind up in a three-way battle royal! Who will unlock a special move and earn Heybot`s eternal partnership?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720405</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181600" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘボットのアレがはれた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heybot`s You-Know-What Is Swollen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heybot no Are ga Hareta</title>
<summary>Moeru and Kathleena hold a secret meeting with some of the show`s more unloved VocaBots about how they can take the protagonist slot from Nejiru and Heybot. The Mojimoji, in a moment`s passion, sticks his plug into a picture of Heybot... which causes the real-life Heybot`s switch to start swelling!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720419</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181601" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇怪・呪螺子島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mystery! The Cursed Screw Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikai Kashiri Neji Shima</title>
<summary>Shortly after Nejiru loses a set of extraterrestrial screws in an online bidding war the VocaReemans, the island quickly becomes overrun by zombies! It turns out GeroReeman was possessed by the Sluggy-Sluggy Screw that they won at auction, and has been transmitting its curse of sluggishness to everyone around him. Can Nejiru and Heybot work together with GuchiReeman to combat this deadly (if slowly moving) threat?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720417</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181602" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">土星は地獄だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Saturn Is Hell!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dosei wa Jigoku Da!</title>
<summary>Heybot, whose only form of excrement is farting, has a dream that some day, he might poop. The extinguisher Zodiac VocaBot Togroll is tired of putting out the little fires around him, and longs for a big fire to put out. One day, after the two meet, they are called to save aliens from a vicious monster on Saturn. Will it spell a chance for both of their wishes to come true?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720415</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181603" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘボットは赤ちゃんバブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heybot`s a Baby, Burble!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heybot wa Akachan Bub</title>
<summary>Heybot has grown tired of taking care of the spoiled Nejiru, and, after seeing an ad for a deluxe baby doll on TV, decides to turn himself into a baby. The paternal Zodiac VocaBot Daddyboar shows up to take care of him back at his own home, which inspires jealousy among his youngest baby boar, Inoshiro...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720413</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182645" update="2016-12-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジョリポロリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scrape, Plop</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jolly Bokori</title>
<summary>The reptilian manager Mappiraja appears at the Screw-Ya with VocaBots Dekapurion, Ketsumakka, and Sexy Queen. They want to build a dance institute on Screw Island to show off Sexy Queen`s sexy moves, and ask Heybot and Nejiru`s help to secure funding. Despite assurances that they`ll receive ample compensation, it is quickly revealed that not everything is on the level...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>720421</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182986" update="2017-01-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">キケン! ボキャ美のターン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Danger! It`s Vocammy`s Turn!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiken! Bokyami no Turn</title>
<summary>Nejiru and Heybot have a fight! When Nejiru insists he could easily replace Heybot with another VocaBot just as good, Heybot storms out in tears. Will this be Vocammy`s chance to swoop in and break up the pair once and for all?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727147</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182987" update="2017-01-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネジが島クロニクルの巻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Screw Island Chronicle Scroll</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nejigashima Chronicle no Maki</title>
<summary>Screw Island is known for being the happiest island in the world. Private detective Muraki Harukaze is sent to find the Screw Island Chronicle and learn the island`s secret. But when he arrives, he finds the entire island in the grips of "Cool Japan"!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727145</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182988" update="2017-01-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘボヘボ漂流記!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Bonehead Castaway`s Tale?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hebohebo Hyouryuuki!?</title>
<summary>Heybot and Nejiru yearn to go on a journey, which the bad boy rooster Toricky and his boss, the swan Hakusencho, are happy to provide. Together, the trio ends up having their fill of adventure... by getting themselves stranded on a deserted island!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727143</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183557" update="2017-02-26">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘボ流・キッチンバトル!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heybot Style Kitchen Battle?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hebo Ryuu Kitchen Battle!?</title>
<summary>Heybot and Nejiru arrive at Gekidora Hanten, a lawless restaurant land where VocaBots compete to see who can make the most delicious food. The youngest of the four Gekidora Brothers, Gekiatsu Dragon, claims to be the heir to their father`s cooking arts. But can he prove it in a culinary battle for ownership of the restaurant?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727155</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183558" update="2017-02-23">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヨロシク, 湯煙ロクンロー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Rock to Steaming Rock `n` Roll!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoroshiku, Yukemuri Rock `n` Roll</title>
<summary>Nejiru and Heybot win a trip to a hot spring in a lottery. On the way, they meet a rock `n` roll horse named Charabred. Intrigue abounds between the Mini-Mini Inn`s proprietress and the tough guy owner of the Manly-Manly Hot Springs Hotel. The only way for the trio to get to the bottom of it is... time travel?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727153</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183559" update="2017-02-23">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネジル学校に行く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nejiru Goes to School</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nejiru Gakkou ni Iku</title>
<summary>Nejiru has enrolled in school. This might not seem unusual, except that Heybot is now the teacher for all the classes, as well. Despite suspicion from the students, classes continue, with Heybot constantly awarding Nejiru rare screws for good performance. It`s beginning to seem like there`s more to their presence than a simple desire for education...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727151</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183560" update="2017-01-25">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネジささる, ゆえにヘボあり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where There`s a Screw, There`s a Bonehead</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neji Sasaru, Yue ni Hebo Ari</title>
<summary>Heybot and Nejiru visit a toy store, which is selling everything from Deluxe Heybots to Heybot sofubi dolls to the cheap knockoff "Patchbot." One Heybot Sofubi decides to follow our Heybot home and become his apprentice... but it turns out to be a sinister scheme to replace him in Nejiru`s heart!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727149</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184342" update="2017-03-22">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">兄x弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Big Brother x Little Brother</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ani x Otouto</title>
<summary>Heybot and Nejiru go to see King Jiru, brimming with questions about Peyket and Chigiru. At the palace, they learn about Nejiru`s mother and the secret of Chigiru`s birth. Heybot also learns about what makes him Peyket`s "brother," and they hold a VocaBattle to test their respective skills!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727163</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184343" update="2017-03-10">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねらわれたネジ魂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">They`re After the Screw Soul!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nerawareta Neji Tamashii</title>
<summary>What starts as a severe stomachache on the part of Nejiru and Heybot quickly escalates, as the sky suddenly darkens and a man called Lord Nejikill descends. Using dastardly tactics, Nejikill steals all the Zodiac screws, as well as Heybot`s own screw soul and Bungle-Bungle Screw! When things get this bad, there`s only one thing that can save our heroes... a new character debut!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727161</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184344" update="2017-03-01">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライネジング・サン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Riscrewing Sun!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rainejing Sun</title>
<summary>A TV report on a "Mountain of Terror" leads Heybot and Nejiru to Mt. Pandai in search of treasure. But instead of a wealth of screws, they find the Happy Colorful Village, a refuge for rejected character designs. The village leader promises to assign their designs color if they work hard enough, but a sinister plot lurks behind this supposedly "noble" cause!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727159</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184345" update="2017-02-26">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">時をバグるピコピコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pixels That Bug Up Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki o Baguru Pikopiko</title>
<summary>Heybot has been shut away in his room, with the lights out, for a long time now. Worried, Nejiru peeks in... to find Heybot is obsessing over video games! Soon, a screwy mishap results in the video game and real worlds overlapping. Can our heroes set things right with the power of references?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727157</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="185112" update="2017-03-27">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プリンス・オブ・いもチン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prince of Imochin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Prince of Imochin</title>
<summary>The Imochin mascot, Imochin Prince, appears before Heybot. He`s going to be rewarded for being the world`s premier Imochin afficionado with a special pack of delicious and gorgeous Imochin! The only catch is... he has to grow it himself!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727167</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="185113" update="2017-03-22">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツルっとオチた流れ星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shooting Star That Slipped Up and Flopped</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsurutto Ochita Nagareboshi</title>
<summary>Screw Island is holding its yearly comedy contest, with the grand prize being a limited edition screw. Naturally, Nejiru and Heybot quickly enter. But they might just meet their match in the form of a legendary comedy duo from Cool Japan, Nagareboshi!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>727165</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186163" update="2017-04-23">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば, 愛しのモエカス!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, My Beloved Moe-Kath!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba, Itoshi no Moekas!</title>
<summary>After being replaced by a new rival pair, the Moe-Kath Trio are down in the dumps. Then, Kathleena decides that Suchat is the real reason behind their continued failures! Will rigorous training with Chigiru lead Suchat to a new gimmick that will make him a star?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733337</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186164" update="2017-04-23">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘボット, ペケット 地獄めぐり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heybot and Peyket`s Trip Through Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heybot, Peketto Jigoku Meguri</title>
<summary>For failing to learn from their continued losses, Peyket and Chigiru take Heybot and Nejiru on a training march to the God Screw. But what starts out as a routine pilgrimage to the extraterrestrial creator of all screws ends up as a trip through the factory where Heybots are made and tested... in other words, Hell!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733335</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186647" update="2017-05-08">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユカイYOUかい怪盗かい!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kidnapping, Youcapping, Catburglaring?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukai Youkai Kaitou kai!?</title>
<summary>Screw Island is all abuzz with news about the new phantom thief, Polidoroheybo! Heybot is about to be falsely arrested for the crimes by the police dog Polidoro, when a new advance notice from the culprit arrives. The thief`s next declared target? Heybot himself!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733345</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186648" update="2017-05-08">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">インネジクタス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Increwctus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">In Neji Kutasu</title>
<summary>Heybot and Nejiru decide to fire up their Heybotournament game for the first time in a while. But the game`s antagonist, the genius inventor Dr. Nejily, seems to have some kind of grudge against the two! He uses the power of the Shady-Shady Screw to project himself into the real world and encourages all comers to his laboratory to try to get it from him! Can our heroes surmount the dungeon`s dangers and find the powerful new screw?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733343</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186649" update="2017-04-23">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">忘れられないの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Forget</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wasurerarenai no</title>
<summary>The battle continues for the Awesome Fine Screw, the screw so awesome no `bot can get enough. While Nejiru and Heybot, the two time travelers, Chigiru, and the VocaReemans compete for its favor, Peyket wonders why the new screw won`t even look his way. Will he be able to prove himself with a VocaBattle?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733341</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186650" update="2017-04-23">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イインダヨ~, スゴスゴインダヨ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Just Fine! It`s Totally Awesome!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iinda yo, Sugo Sugoinda yo</title>
<summary>A red loincloth flutters through the air, sending a voice upon the wind: "It`s okay! It`s just fine!" Meanwhile, Mandriver and Lord Nejikill arrive at the Screw-Ya and reveal their own tragic backstories. But before things can get too heavy, the loincloth interrupts... and from it, an incredibly special new screw appears!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733339</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187470" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋のヘラがえしがえしがえし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flip, Flip, Flip of Love!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Hera Gaeshi Gaeshi Gaeshi</title>
<summary>Lovable ovine lug Dagasheep, proprietor of the best teppanyaki stall on Screw Island, falls in love with every girl he meets. His every attempt ends in heartbreak, but when Vocammy becomes the next girl to catch his eye, Heybot decides to try and help him. Will Heybot help Dagasheep win love... and get his stalker off his back?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733353</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187471" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">インスマ浜の呼び声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Call of Innsmouth Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Insuma Hama no Yobigoe</title>
<summary>Private detective Muraki Harukaze is back on Screw Island, investigating the disappearance of an eccentric billionaire who ran off with the world`s most dangerous book: the Screwcronomicon! With Nejiru and Heybot along, he travels to Innsmouth Beach, where a terrible and ancient secret awaits...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733351</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187472" update="2017-05-30">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">流さネジられて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Screwed Away</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagasanejirarete</title>
<summary>A Screw Island magazine publishes a damning expose on the Awesome Fine Screw: He`s been a normal screw this whole time! Ashamed, Awesome Fine Screw retreats to a lonely island far into the ocean. While lamenting his lot in life through song, he suddenly finds himself declared the chosen one of a terror-stricken populace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733349</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187473" update="2017-05-30">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハミガキしようぜ 牛肉, ミソッパ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Brush Your Teeth! Beef, Runaway Cavities!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hamigaki Shiyouze: Gyuuniku, Misoppa!</title>
<summary>Nejiru and Chigiru enjoy all-you-can-eat ice cream, and end up with terrible cavities. Miraculously, they just happen to receive a flyer from a dentist`s office the next day. But when they arrive at the "Dental Cattlinic" run by Dentaurus, they get drawn into an adventure involving shady scams, miniaturized drill tanks, and tooth-dwelling alien invaders!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733347</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188030" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">弁護士ボキャ美の法廷ファイル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Courtroom Files of Lawyer Vocammy!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bengoshi Bokyami no Houtei File!</title>
<summary>A terrible case is unfolding on Screw Island: Saturn Hag has been hella stabbed with Awesome Fine Screw, and the main suspects are Nejiru and Heybot! Can Vocammy`s lawyer skills save the duo from a long prison sentence?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733361</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188031" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">王妃ナグリ, 帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Queen Naguri Returns!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ouhi Naguri, Kikan</title>
<summary>It`s time for the return of Nejiru and Chigiru`s mother, Queen Naguri! She`s expecting to see Nejiru grown up and muscled up, but how will she react when she sees the scrawny, lazy boy he really is?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733359</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188032" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">12体そろったらエライ事になった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When All Twelve Are Together, Things Get Serious!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">12 Tai Sorottara Erai Koto ni Natta</title>
<summary>With the gathering of the twelve Zodiac VocaScrews, the world is going to be destroyed! Failed characters realize that this is their time to shine, and the main characters` nonchalance in the face of this uprising earns the wrath of God. Soon, failed characters and main characters are pitted together in a competition to see who will control the story, and who will get sent to Hell!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733357</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188033" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">電脳鼠はボキャボットのダメを見るか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do Cyber-Rats Dream of Loser Vocabots?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dennou Nezumi wa Bokyabot no Dame o Miruka</title>
<summary>Muka Muka Chori arrives at the Screw-Ya with a request: help her track down a hot guy she met on Fretter! She doesn`t know anything about his real life identity, though, so to track him down, they need the aid of Hacker Rat. Hacker Rat guides them into cyberspace to help them track down her man, but will they make it out alive?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733355</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188674" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">我々はネジである</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Are Screws</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wareware wa Neji de Aru</title>
<summary>The Screw Island castle has been taken over by cat maids! Their ransom consists of the twelve Zodiac VocaBots, whom they intend to offer to the God Screw in exchange for one wish. Can the VocaBots work together to save the castle... with the power of love?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742221</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188675" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘボ流・大脱走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bonehead Style Grand Getaway!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hebo Ryuu: Dai Dassou</title>
<summary>Vocammy`s lawyer skills were unable to save the duo from a long prison sentence. Now Nejiru, Heybot, Chigiru, and Peyket are all in jail after the events of last episode. Unable to bear the terrible weight of continuity, the group plots a way to bust out of prison and return to freedom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742219</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189006" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場版ヘボット! って, ナニそれ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heybot: The Movie! Wait, What`s That?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijouban Heybot! tte, Nani Sore?</title>
<summary>Heybot: The Movie is out, but reviews are decidedly mixed. To teach the bickering Nejiru and Heybot a lesson about the importance of quality cinema, the Movieities send them inside of a movie. To get out, Nejiru and Heybot must make amends with the help of the classiest of plot devices: the body swap!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742225</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189007" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネジ拳ボキャフェスinネジが島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Screw Fist VocaFest in Screw Island!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neji Ken Bokya Fes in Nejigashima</title>
<summary>Queen Naguri has made her move to turn Screw Island into a martial arts kingdom by holding a VocaScrew Martial Arts tournament. She`ll be inviting participants from all over the world! But not all of Naguri`s disciples have affection for their former teacher...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742223</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189862" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネジが島さいごの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Screw Island`s Last Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nejigashima Saigo no Hi</title>
<summary>Screw Island`s dark history is finally revealed. The universe is on the verge of collapse. Heybot, Nejiru, and their allies... don`t actually care very much, but there probably won`t be any cool action scenes if they just ignore it. Thus, the heroes head out to save the day!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742233</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189863" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すべてがNになる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everything Becomes N</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subete ga N ni Naru</title>
<summary>Danger awaits when Muraki Harukaze and his team comes to Antarctica to find a missing research expedition. Terrible secrets are thawed from the ice as the final chapter of Heybot begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742231</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189864" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">はたらくネジさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Working Screws</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hataraku Neji-san</title>
<summary>When Nejiru, Heybot, and Peyket stumble upon a newly built screw factory, they get to learn the complex process by which screws are made, from harvesting to shaping to voice recording. They even get to make their own! But will the power go to Nejiru`s head?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742229</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189865" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギザギザ・ザ・ネジ山</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jaggy Jaggy the Screw Mountain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gezageza the Neji Yama</title>
<summary>Panic sweeps Screw Island as all the screws begin losing their ridges. Nejiru in a panic, and Peyket and Heybot won`t stop fighting over whether they should still be called screws, or reclassified as nails! Will the plot be resolved in a logical fashion, or will it simply dropped for next week?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742227</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190624" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">にちようびのせかい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World of Sunday</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nichiyoubi no Sekai</title>
<summary>Beyond all the mysteries that surround Heybot and Screw Island, there lies one final truth buried deeper than all the others. To right a great wrong, Heybot and Nejiru must uncover this secret... but will doing so will bring an end to all their Sundays?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742237</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190625" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならヘボット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Heybot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Heybot</title>
<summary>The new VocaScrew Quartet heads deep into the God Screw to try to stop Fine from destroying the universe. Secrets are revealed, sacrifices made, character designs recycled. Can Nejiru and Heybot save the universe once and for all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742235</identifier>
<identifier>heybot</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
