<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1221" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>1995-04-21</startdate>
<enddate>1995-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shin Megami Tensei: Tokyo Mokushiroku</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">真・女転</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">shin megaten</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">真・女神転生 東京黙示録</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tokyo Revelation</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Tokyo Revelation</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3103" type="Alternative Setting">Digital Devil Story: Megami Tensei</anime>
<anime id="1967" type="Other">Shin Megami Tensei: Devil Children</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sakuhin/nenpyo/1995/02_megaten/megaten.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="1649" type="Character Design">Oonuki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="2197" type="Direction">Yamasaki Osamu</name>
<name id="4410" type="Music">Ike Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="4526" type="Music">Momose Keiichi</name>
<name id="720" type="Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="26337" type="Original Work">Suzuki Ichinari</name>
<name id="48021" type="Original Work">Ogishima Chiaki</name>
<name id="1039" type="Original Work">Atlus</name>
<name id="1169" type="Work">Sanctuary</name>
</creators>
<description>A satanic program is activated aboard a crowded commercial flight headed for Tokyo. It releases a swarm of invisible demons that send the aircraft plunging to a fiery doom. Everyone aboard is killed instantly, except Kobayashi Akito, owner of the devilish program and a sworn ally of hell itself.
Souma Kojirou, an old elementary school friend of Akito`s, is surprised to see him enroll back in school. Kojirou notices how this once lonely boy has grown into a suave and arrogant teenager. Later, when his classmates are attacked and legendary demons return to stalk to streets of Tokyo, Kojirou begins to truly understand what his old friend has become.
Akito has plans for the human race. The plans revolve around magnetite, the mysterious element that forms the living essence of every human soul. Combined with his demonic software, a strong enough source of magnetite would release a plague of devils upon the Earth. That source exists in Kojirou`s class, but when the evil plan expands beyond even Akito`s grasp, it is Kojiro who must find the ultimate power within himself, and go head-to-head with the greatest demon of all!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="233">3.03</permanent>
<temporary count="234">5.28</temporary>
<review count="1">6.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224722.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1338</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>401</identifier>
<identifier>bnbqvd</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sakuhin/nenpyo/1995/02_megaten/megaten.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Shin_Megami_Tensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>真・女神転生#.E7.9C.9F.E3.83.BB.E5.A5.B3.E7.A5.9E.E8.BB.A2.E7.94.9F_.E6.9D.B1.E4.BA.AC.E9.BB.99.E7.A4.BA.E9.8C.B2</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88259</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5423</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3167" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-16">
<name>Tokyo destroyed</name>
<description>Tokyo is depicted as being or having been destroyed, either partially or completely, by some sort of disaster, such as a nuclear blast, a very large-scale fire, or rising sea levels. Should the situation be dire enough, Tokyo may be destroyed again after a recovery, or a new Tokyo may be built and subsequently destroyed, by a new disaster.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3250" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-02">
<name>regeneration from death -- TO BE SPLIT AND REMOVED</name>
<description>This tag is meant for removal. The characters it would apply to should be tagged with http://anidb.net/t2209 [regeneration] and/or http://anidb.net/t1396 [immortality], as appropriate. Please tag the relevant characters with those two tags and remove this tag from their respective anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3323" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-07-03">
<name>computer</name>
<description>A device, usually electronic, that processes data according to a set of instructions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4184" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-05">
<name>demon dog</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4811" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-30">
<name>internet</name>
<description>It`s not a big truck. It`s a series of tubes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5781" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>exorcism</name>
<description>Eviction of demons or other spiritual entities from a person or place which they are believed to have possessed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="13250" update="2010-07-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1995-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23940" update="2004-09-09">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1995-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147821" update="2013-03-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
