<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12249" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1989</startdate>
<enddate>1989</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="main">Sun Wukong: Yusanjian Baobei</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">孙悟空: 与三件宝贝</title>
</titles>
<description>Adapted from the ancient Chinese novel "Journey to the West", this lively animated film depicts one of the most popular of the Monkey King stories. The Monkey King uses his three treasures to fight with an old monster. He saves the Buddhist Monk, Xuan Zang, as well as Bajie (a pig) and Sha Heshang (another Buddhist monk), so they can continue their journey to the West.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1">4.41</permanent>
<temporary count="1">1.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>188008.jpg</picture>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3752" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-10">
<name>Journey to the West</name>
<description>Journey to the West is a classic Chinese mythological novel. It was written during the Ming Dynasty based on traditional folk tales. Consisting of 100 chapters, this fantasy relates the adventures of a Tang Dynasty priest Sanzang and his three disciples, Monkey, Pig and Friar Sand, as they travel west in search of Buddhist Sutra. Several anime are loosely based on its story, most famously Dragon Ball.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
</anime>
