<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12265" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-03-12</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="main">Jebulchalssi Iyagi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">제불찰씨 이야기</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Story of Mr. Sorry</title>
</titles>
<description>An unprecedented media show is on air at a TV broadcasting studio. The show is asking people whether a spider that drove an assemblyman crazy should be publicly executed or not. The spider in question is Je Bul-chal(meaning `my mistake`), a hardworking young individual who became `an ear cleaner` because of a precious memory he holds concerning his sister. In order to take a poll about his execution, the story of how Mr. Sorry became a spider is gradually revealed.
Source: Official website</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="10">7.22</permanent>
<temporary count="10">6.30</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>188278.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8081</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6166" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-23">
<name>South Korean production</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/t6762 [North Korean production]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="179146" update="2016-07-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>65</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
