<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="123" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-12-22</startdate>
<enddate>2001-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Slayers Premium</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Slayers Movie 5</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Первосортные Рубаки</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スレイヤーズぷれみあむ</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Slayers Premium -The Movie-</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">秀逗魔导士 剧场版5</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="364" type="Sequel">Slayers Try</anime>
<anime id="95" type="Prequel">Slayers Next</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3"/>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20060505224906/http://www.hal-film.co.jp/sakuhin/slay/index.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="754" type="Animation Work">Hal Film Maker</name>
<name id="3611" type="Direction">Satou Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="1338" type="Original Work">Kanzaka Hajime</name>
<name id="680" type="Music">Hattori Takayuki</name>
<name id="4536" type="Character Design">Kumagai Tetsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch1000 [Lina] and http://anidb.net/ch7616 [Gourry] travel to a seaside town named Acassi, where octopus tentacle is a delicacy. However, the octopus meat carries a curse that dooms the eater to only speak Takogo — the octopus language. When http://anidb.net/ch7619 [Amelia], http://anidb.net/ch7618 [Zelgadis], and http://anidb.net/ch7489 [Xellos] all show up... Lina, Gourry, Amelia, and Zelgadis manage to get cursed.
The octopuses enlist the power of a mazoku to get rid of the humans once and for all. And so the white sorceress http://anidb.net/ch45563 [Ruma] must learn the cure to the curse from her long-lost master in order to save the town, and her friends.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1610">5.75</permanent>
<temporary count="1615">7.17</temporary>
<review count="1">8.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>228277.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>295</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>866</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>686</identifier>
<identifier>mkkmpy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20060505224906/http://www.hal-film.co.jp/sakuhin/slay/index.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Slayers_Premium</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スレイヤーズ_(アニメ)#.E3.82.B9.E3.83.AC.E3.82.A4.E3.83.A4.E3.83.BC.E3.82.BA.E3.81.B7.E3.82.8C.E3.81.BF.E3.81.82.E3.82.80</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1498</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236351</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5058</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7694</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1000" type="main character in" update="2014-09-22">
<rating votes="1994">9.10</rating>
<name>Lina Inverse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lina Inverse is the primary protagonist and the only character appearing in the whole Slayers-franchise. She is an adolescent but very powerful sorceress, with a great love for money, treasure and food. In the anime and manga (but not in the light novel) Lina uses overly destructive magic recklessly, often with little provocation. She is reputed to be an evil, powerful, destructive, diminutive sorceress (the evil part is arguably not true, though one may consider her greed and general lack of concern for others unless they are in danger of being killed can be considered "evil").
Lina has gained many different nicknames, including "Bandit Killer" and "Dragon Spooker", neither of which she`s very fond of, though to her, her most embarrassing nickname is "Lina the Pink" which is her official title amongst the sorcerer`s guild.</description>
<picture>161200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7489" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-23">
<rating votes="247">8.76</rating>
<name>Xellos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Xellos is a mazoku and the priest of Greater Beast Zelas Metallium.
Xellos was created by Zelas during the Kouma War. The mazoku put a barrier over the peninsula and managed keep the enemy`s reinforcements out of the battle. Because of this, however, four of the five lords were unable to participate in the war anymore, so priests and generals were created in order to represent them. Because he is her only immediate servant, and he was created from a great deal of her power, Xellos is more powerful than all the other priests and generals of Ruby Eye Shabranigdu`s subordinates.
In the Kouma War, Xellos single-handedly killed thousands of golden dragons; he is feared and hated by them ever since. They refer to him as the Dragon Slayer, although he does not like this name, probably because it does not fit the "image" he wants others to view him as. After the war, before serving Hellmaster, Xelloss`s duty for a thousand years was to find stray copies of the Claire Bible and destroy them so that humans could not find an easy way to defeat mazoku (with Zanaffar), or utilise the power of the Lord of Nightmares.
Xelloss` true astral form is that of a simple black cone. He is able to divide his power into dozens of tiny cones that can inflict damage over a long period of time.</description>
<picture>26124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7616" type="main character in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="257">7.18</rating>
<name>Gourry Gabriev</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Lina Inverse destroyed the Dragon no Kiba (Dragon`s Fang) gang, and was later encountered by a small array of vengeful bandits, Gourry Gabriev jumped in to save her. Though Lina appreciated the offer, she initially opted against accepting Gourry as a bodyguard, but Gourry`s big-brotherly nature prevented him from acting otherwise. Gourry, dense as a brick, saw Lina as a younger girl in need of protection, and thus, he offered it.
Gourry is the owner of the most powerful sword known to man, the mysterious Sword of Light. The Sword of Light channels its users intentions into energy, usually taking the form of a gleaming blade of light. Gourry has learned how to utilize the sword`s energy in different forms, though, most notably the power of swinging it quickly downwards to form energy beam projectiles.
Gourry is the swordsman of the group, and acts the role very well. He`s single-minded in his protection of Lina, and even after helping Lina defeat Ruby-Eye Shabranigdu, he has resolved to follow Lina around wherever she goes. Supposedly, he has nothing better to do, and perhaps still sees himself as her guardian.</description>
<picture>26399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7617" type="appears in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="149">8.82</rating>
<name>The Slayers</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>Major characters of the series, which form (mostly) stable group.</description>
<picture>26408.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="7618" type="main character in" update="2009-05-29">
<rating votes="293">7.70</rating>
<name>Zelgadis Greywords</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>When Lina Inverse overthrew the Dragon`s Fang bandit gang, one of Zelgadiss` men, Zolf, happened to be stuck inside. And, well, he got incinerated. Needless to say, Zelgadiss was mad. More importantly, though, Lina had gotten a very valuable Orihalcon statue, which was the reason Zolf was there to begin with. Zelgadiss wanted the statue in hopes that it could cure his chimaeric curse.
Only, it didn`t quite work out that way. Zelgadiss didn`t quite cure himself, even after the whole incident with Rezo, the Red Priest and Ruby-Eye Shabranigdu. So, he`s still searching for a cure, hoping to find one of the fabled Clair-Bibles in hopes to cure himself. The curse makes him 1/3 golem, 1/3 demon, and 1/3 human, which makes him impervious to most physical weapon such as swords and buckshot, but not to the physical impact of, say, a cannonball.
Zelgadiss is quite self-conscious about his appearance, almost ashamed of it. In fact, he`s a very quiet character all around, only speaking when necessary, and only interested in the shortest path to his cure. He also tends to get embarassed easily wherever the topic of romance is brought up.
Zelgadiss is a superb swordsman, having trained many long years. He often enhances his blade with the Astral Vine spell, one of many Shamanist spells at his disposal. He has more or less mastered the Spirit category of Shamanism, having learned its most powerful spell, the Ra-Tilt, among numerous other spells in other categories.</description>
<picture>26411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7619" type="main character in" update="2015-02-24">
<rating votes="293">6.53</rating>
<name>Amelia Wil Tesla Seyruun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amelia is the daughter of Philionel el de Seyruun, Crown Prince of the kingdom of Seyruun. Like her father, Amelia is a self-proclaimed Champion of Justice(tm) and is singleminded in her quest for truth, honor, and dignity. Also like her father, she`s a complete klutz and has no clue of what IS and ISN`T a true cause for justice.
Amelia has trained since birth for her cause; once convinced, she isn`t easily dissuaded from inflicting her particular flavor of justice on whoever she perceives to be an "enemy of the people". She thinks of Lina as a hero - a destructive hero, but nevertheless a hero - and wants to be just like her and every other good hero that comes along.
Amelia gets bored being royalty sometimes - she often follows her father Phil on journeys around the countryside. She often looks for trouble, simply so that she can right it. Whenever scouting out an area, she always includes a quick look for the highest place to stand.
...
Why does she always look for the highest place to stand, you ask? In case the enemy strikes, she wants to be able to strike back with a dynamic, triumphant pose of her own, terrifying the enemy with fear of justice. A lot of times, she ends up falling, too, she`s only a young girl after all. In fact, Amelia has the reputation of being one of the clumsiest characters in all of Slayers, topped only by Martina.
Amelia is also a budding sorcerer in her own right. Her specialty is white magic, however she also has reached the highest level of training in Shamanist Spirit magic, a testament to her quick learning time and eagerness to learn. She has even developed a spell or two of her own, most notably the Visfarank spell, which seems to be the glowing manifestation of justice as a pair of boxing gloves.</description>
<picture>169335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7725" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-09-18">
<rating votes="341">7.81</rating>
<name>Gracia Ul Naga Seyruun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naga the White Serpent is the self-proclaimed rival and companion of Lina Inverse.
Naga`s real full name is Gracia Ul Naga Seyruun, making her the first daughter of Crown Prince Philionel El Di Seyruun and the older sister of Amelia Wil Tesla Seyruun.
Naga is very skilled in white magic, no doubt because of where she grew up. Lina is often surprised when Naga uses these spells, because Naga does not seem like the kind of person to want to heal people. Naga also specializes in shamanistic magic, especially spells of the earth and water variety. She enjoys creating her own golems (even if they usually don`t turn out very well), and one of her favorite spells to use is Freeze Arrow.
Naga is also able to terrorize people with her obnoxious laughing. She`s extremely proud of her highly developed, self-confident laugh and the effect that it has on unsuspecting people. She also likes to use her body to tease or distract men who are trying to go against her.
Naga carries a large sword, but she is never seen using it, possibly because she is afraid of blood. This phobia was most likely caused by witnessing her mother`s brutal slaughter. The mere sight of blood, even from a small cut, is enough to cause her to faint.</description>
<picture>161192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45562" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-03">
<rating votes="1">1.93</rating>
<name>Chie Tako</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45563" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-03">
<rating votes="1">1.93</rating>
<name>Ruma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45564" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-03">
<rating votes="1">1.93</rating>
<name>Shishou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2942" picture="23713.jpg">Tanonaka Isamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="45565" type="appears in" update="2012-06-03">
<rating votes="1">1.93</rating>
<name>Shugoshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1818" picture="20692.jpg">Naya Gorou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="4212" update="2018-12-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2001-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175354" update="2016-02-18">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175355" update="2016-02-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175356" update="2016-02-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
