<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12301" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ani Tore! XX: Hitotsu Yane no Shita de</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あにトレ!!XX ~ひとつ屋根の下で~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Anime de Training! XX</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">动画锻炼!XX</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11540" type="Prequel">Ani Tore! EX</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://anime-training.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="5914" type="Animation Work">Rising Force</name>
<name id="15915" type="Character Design">Yamamoto Shuuhei</name>
<name id="15466" type="Series Composition">Ishibashi Daisuke</name>
<name id="19341" type="Direction">Nigorikawa Atsushi</name>
<name id="26108" type="Music">Yashikin</name>
</creators>
<description>Five girls who are aiming to become idols, lead the viewer through practicing various types of training, such as push-up, sit-up, back extension, dance, yoga, stretch, trunk training, and Tai Chi, while talking to viewers.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="237">2.87</permanent>
<temporary count="238">5.19</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>189343.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18673</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33746</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>38177</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anime-training.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4351</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>357846</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19641</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="77107" type="main character in" update="2015-12-20">
<rating votes="8">5.26</rating>
<name>Hiraoka Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a junior high school third grade, she is very shy and clumsy and can do nothing if she loses her glases.</description>
<picture>176920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43732" picture="177230.jpg">Takao Kanon</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77108" type="main character in" update="2015-12-20">
<rating votes="10">8.17</rating>
<name>Saotome Shizuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizuna is a very polite second year highschool student, she is has a pet ferret named Andalucia, and when she becomes scary when angry.</description>
<picture>176918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33692" picture="216159.jpg">Komaki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77109" type="main character in" update="2015-12-20">
<rating votes="11">7.72</rating>
<name>Hoshi Asami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a 16-year-old freshman high school, she is the leader of Ani Tore! Ex unit. She is very an inocent girl with an outgoing, cheerful, has "super positve thinking" personality. She has the ability to quickly make new friends.</description>
<picture>176921.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37283" picture="238137.jpg">Itou Miku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77110" type="main character in" update="2015-12-20">
<rating votes="10">7.67</rating>
<name>Higuchi Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest girl in the group, she hates losing and uses it as a motivation switch to try harder. She has a tiny chest complex.</description>
<picture>176919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42471" picture="242433.jpg">Waki Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77111" type="main character in" update="2015-12-20">
<rating votes="13">6.51</rating>
<name>Tachibana Shion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is a highschool first year and calls herself a Fallen that was descended from a jet-black darkness world. The tenebrea Angel. She sometimes falls out of her chuunbyoni act while talking.</description>
<picture>176917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39889" picture="241534.jpg">Naganawa Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78996" type="appears in" update="2016-10-05">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Andalucia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the Ferret owned by shizuno</description>
<picture>192357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44380" picture="181055.jpg">Sogabe Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83682" type="main character in" update="2016-10-05">
<rating votes="3">8.26</rating>
<name>Deumi Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is in her second year of the middle school</description>
<picture>64264.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="180772" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悦楽なる闇のXX! 終焉の始まりし時</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pleasurable XX of the Void! The Beginning of the End</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le *** des ténèbres exquises ! Le début de la fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Etsurakunaru Yami no XX! Shuuen no Hajimarishi Toki</title>
<summary>Join me, and give your back to the dark altar.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721705</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180773" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">回れ回れ, マット・エクササイズ! XXあるのみですわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spin, Spin, Mat Exercises! XX All the Way</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Roule, roule, avec les exercices sur tapis de sol ! Tu ne peux que ***</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maware Maware, Mat Exercise! XX Aru Nomi Desu wa</title>
<summary>Mat exercises are effective for improving your balance and motor control.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721703</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180774" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">走るXX電車!? いつでもどこでもトレーニング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Running XX Train!? Training Anytime, Anywhere</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des train*** sur le trajet ? N`importe quand et n`importe où</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashiru XX Densha!? Itsudemo Dokodemo Training</title>
<summary>Training you can do on a train!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721701</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180775" update="2016-10-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いざゆけ新XX! レッツお掃除&amp;サイドベンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go for It XX! Let`s Clean &amp; Side Bench</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C’est parti pour une nouvelle *** ! Let’s nettoyer et flexions latérales</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iza Yuke Shin XX! Let`s Osouji &amp; Side Bend</title>
<summary>Episode exercise is Lateral Side Bends performed by Asami.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721699</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180819" update="2016-10-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181338" update="2016-11-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マッサージでリラックス! 一緒にXXしましょう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Massage Relax! Let`s XX Together</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On se relaxe avec des massages ! Tentons de bien nous ***</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Massage de Relax! Issho ni XX Shimashou</title>
<summary>First, I shall banish the beasts within you back into the void.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721713</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181339" update="2016-11-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジョギングでさわやか有酸素! XXって気持ちいいね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jogging for Breezy Aerobics! XX Feels Great</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De l`exercice en plein air avec le jogging ! Ça fait du bien de ***</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jogging de Sawayaka Yuusanso! XXtte Kimochi Ii ne</title>
<summary>I`m going to teach you the tricks to jogging.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721711</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181340" update="2016-11-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バランスボールでシェイプアップ! 余のXXと認めよう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shape Up on the Balance Ball! I Dub Thee My XX</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retrouver la forme avec le ballon d`exercice ! Je t`accepte en tant que ***</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Balance Ball de Shape Up! Yo no XX to Mitomeyou</title>
<summary>I shall make you my noble steed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721709</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181341" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レッツ柔軟! XXほぐして, 目指せトップスイマー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Exercise! XX Stretch Out and Aim for Top Swimmer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Let`s s`assouplir ! *** d`abord afin de devenir un grand nageur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Let`s Juunan! XX Hogushite, Mezase Top Swimmer</title>
<summary>Hey, imagine making pudding in this pool.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721707</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182159" update="2016-12-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとつ屋根の下で! XXが始まる時間だよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Living Together! XX Is About to Begin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sous le même toit ! C`est l`heure de ***</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitotsu Yane no Shita de! XX ga Hajimaru Jikan Da yo</title>
<summary>Thanks for thinking of me all the time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721721</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182160" update="2016-12-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダンベルで二の腕スッキリ! 魅惑のXXが待ってるよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tighten Up Your Upper Arms with Dumbbells! XX Is Waiting for You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des haltères pour des bras bien fermes ! Un *** alléchant nous attend !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dumbbell de Ninoude Sukkiri! Miwaku no XX ga Matteru yo</title>
<summary>Goodbye arm flab.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721719</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182161" update="2016-12-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">腕立て&amp;背筋でお悩み解消! 優しくXXを入れて下さい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fix Your Worries with Push-ups and Back Muscle Exercises! Give It Your XX</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Résoudre ses soucis avec des pompes et en s`étirant ! Je vais essayer au mieux ***</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Udetate &amp; Sesuji de Onayami Kaishou! Yasashiku XX o Irete Kudasai</title>
<summary>They`re bigger than I thought.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721717</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182162" update="2016-12-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なわとびでポッカポカ! カラダだけでなく, XXも...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Skip Rope Warm Up! Not Just Your Body, but XX...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Se réchauffer avec la corde à sauter ! Et pas juste physiquement, ça me fait ***...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nawatobi de Pokkapoka! Karada dake de Naku, XX mo...</title>
<summary>I`m warmed up not just in body, but in mind, too.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721715</identifier>
<identifier>anime-de-training-ex</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198392" update="2018-04-21">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2017-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198393" update="2018-04-21">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2017-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198394" update="2018-04-21">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2017-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198395" update="2018-04-21">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198396" update="2018-04-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198397" update="2018-04-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
