<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12311" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-07-01</startdate>
<enddate>2016-07-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dragon Ball Z: The Real 4-D</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドラゴンボールZ・ザ・リアル 4-D</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1530" type="Parent Story">Dragon Ball Z</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.usj.co.jp/jump/dragonball/summer2016/</url>
<description>Having been revived by the Dragon Balls, http://anidb.net/ch9009 [Freezer] is back and stronger than ever. Overwhelmed by Freezer`s fierce attacks, http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] is driven into a corner. In order to prevail, he`ll need everybody`s support!
Note: This "4D" anime was shown at the Universal Studios Japan theme park as part of their 2016 "Universal Jump Summer" attraction lineup, premiering on 1 July with a scheduled run until 4 September 2016.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="61">2.72</permanent>
<temporary count="62">4.47</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>241856.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33947</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.usj.co.jp/jump/dragonball/summer2016/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3870" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>resurrection</name>
<description>At least one character in this anime is brought back from the dead or from a near-death experience. This is achieved by either very advanced technology or simply magic.</description>
<picurl>191152.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2085" type="appears in" update="2013-04-18">
<rating votes="689">8.50</rating>
<name>Kame Sennin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kame Sennin is an ancient and wise martial arts master and the first Earthling to wield the Kamehameha. Though he seems frail, he is a mighty warrior, having trained Grandpa Gohan, Gyuumaou, Son Gokuu, and others.</description>
<picture>135368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2279" picture="23207.jpg">Satou Masaharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2103" type="main character in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="2804">8.56</rating>
<name>Son Gokuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Son Gokuu is a Saiyajin warrior who was sent to Earth when he was a child.</description>
<picture>135352.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="386" picture="187997.jpg">Nozawa Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2105" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="1212">8.57</rating>
<name>Vegeta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Vegeta is the prince of the Saiyajin race and http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu]`s most fearsome rival. He is a very prideful person and, as a full-blooded saiyajin, loves the prospect of a good battle.</description>
<picture>230630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="132" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6867" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-08">
<rating votes="33">6.98</rating>
<name>Pilaf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24922.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7015" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="63">5.25</rating>
<name>Shenlong</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shenron is the dragon that appears when someone collects all seven of Earth`s Dragon Balls and calls him forth. He will grant one wish and then vanish, scattering the 7 Dragon Balls throughout the Earth once again.</description>
<picture>25280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2053" picture="23204.jpg">Ootomo Ryuuzaburou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11414" type="appears in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="230">7.05</rating>
<name>Kuririn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuririn is introduced in Dragon Ball as a rival of the main character, http://anidb.net/ch2116 [Son Gokuu]. Later in the series, he develops a close relationship with him as well as his son, http://anidb.net/ch11419 [Gohan].</description>
<picture>66653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11416" type="appears in" update="2014-06-16">
<rating votes="557">7.67</rating>
<name>Piccolo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Piccolo, whose full name is Piccolo Jr., was first introduced as the reincarnation of the evil http://anidb.net/ch22168 [Piccolo Daimaou] in http://anidb.net/a231 [Dragon Ball], making him a demon and arch-rival of the primary protagonist, http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Son Gokuu]. However, it is later revealed that he is from the race of alien beings called Namekians and he decides to team up with http://anidb.net/ch2103 [Gokuu] and his friends in order to beat newer, more dangerous threats.</description>
<picture>135357.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55085" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-22">
<rating votes="143">6.68</rating>
<name>Bulma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3058" picture="23960.jpg">Tsuru Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83562" type="main character in" update="2016-08-04">
<rating votes="25">6.93</rating>
<name>Freezer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Freezer`s true form.</description>
<picture>64037.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3149" picture="132209.jpg">Nakao Ryuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="179348" update="2016-08-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
