<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12324" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-04-15</startdate>
<enddate>2017-07-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sin: Nanatsu no Taizai</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">sin 七つの大罪</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Seven Mortal Sins</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">sin 일곱개의 대죄</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">sin 七大罪</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13599" type="Same Setting">Nanatsu no Bitoku</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6080" approval="18" total="19">Queen`s Blade: Rurou no Senshi</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.7-sins.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="29577" type="Character Design">Yasuda Shouko</name>
<name id="999" type="Work">Artland</name>
<name id="794" type="Work">TNK</name>
<name id="2415" type="Original Work">Hobby Japan</name>
<name id="708" type="Direction">Yoshimoto Kinji</name>
<name id="29577" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yasuda Shouko</name>
<name id="7259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ozeki Miyabi</name>
<name id="9771" type="Chief Animation Direction">Gotou Junji</name>
<name id="20876" type="Music">Tsutsumi Hiroaki</name>
<name id="3326" type="Music">Yokoyama Masaru</name>
<name id="48532" type="Series Composition">Yoshimoto Kinji</name>
</creators>
<description>The prideful archangel Lucifer disobeys God and is cast into the lowest level of hell as a fallen angel. On her way to hell, Lucifer happens to meet a high school girl on Earth named Maria, who helps her. In hell, Lucifer meets Leviathan, and Leviathan explains to Lucifer about The Seven Deadly Sins, the seven demon king rulers of hell. After The Seven Deadly Sins seal Lucifer`s powers, Lucifer goes on a journey with Maria and Leviathan to defeat them.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="554">2.01</permanent>
<temporary count="566">4.73</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>199384.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18689</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35559</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>33834</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>36569</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>35418</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>35417</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.7-sins.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>七つの大罪_(ホビージャパン)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4553</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>357960</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20113</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7sins_tv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07DGMCBP3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2659" parentid="2660" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Moon</name>
<description>The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth, being Earth`s only permanent natural satellite. It is the fifth-largest natural satellite in the Solar System, and the largest among planetary satellites relative to the size of the planet that it orbits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2763" parentid="2807" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Paris</name>
<description>Paris is the capital and most populous city in France. The city is a commune and department, and the heart of the Île-de-France region (colloquially known as the `Paris Region`). Since the 17th century, Paris has been one of Europe`s major centres of finance, commerce, fashion, science, and the arts.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214344.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2777" parentid="2809" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>London</name>
<description>London is the capital and most populous city of both England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south east of the island of Great Britain, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. It was founded by the Romans, who named it Londinium.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214379.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2807" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>France</name>
<description>France, officially the French Republic, is a country whose territory consists of metropolitan France in western Europe, as well as several overseas regions and territories. The metropolitan area of France extends from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean. The overseas territories include French Guiana in South America and several islands in the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian oceans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214343.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2905" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-14">
<name>erotic torture</name>
<description>Erotic torture involves deliberately using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure. Examples include, among others, hot wax on skin, nipple clamps, electricity, extreme verbal and derogatory abuse, forced public exhibition, etc.
This is distinct from the common, non-erotic http://anidb.net/t6730 [torture], which is generally for the purpose of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or to apply coercion to compel action from the victim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4413" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-16">
<name>heaven</name>
<description>Heaven, the Heavens or Seven Heavens, is a common religious, cosmological or transcendent place from which heavenly beings (such as a God, angels, the jinn, and sky deities like King or Queen of Heaven, Heavenly Father, Heavenly Mother, Son of Heaven, heavenly saints or venerated ancestors) originate, are enthroned or inhabit.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5638" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-25">
<name>military is useless</name>
<description>The regular military force per se or certain units thereof are way out of their league when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes (e.g. powerful aliens). Thus the regular military is completely useless. 
Often, only children (of all people) with special abilities and/or powered suits can defend Earth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5780" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-24">
<name>tsunami</name>
<description>The anime features a "huge wave" as part of the story, usually with devastating results: loss of live and destruction of property.
A tsunami (from Japanese: 津波, lit. "harbour wave") is a series of water waves caused by the displacement of a large volume of a body of water, typically an ocean or a large lake. Earthquakes, volcanic eruptions and other underwater explosions (including detonations of underwater nuclear devices), landslides, glacier calvings, meteorite impacts and other disturbances above or below water all have the potential to generate a tsunami.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="84440" type="main character in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="16">7.83</rating>
<name>Lucifer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84441" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="11">6.80</rating>
<name>Asmodeus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84442" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="12">7.51</rating>
<name>Satan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46412" picture="207957.jpg">Sakuraba Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84443" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="9">5.00</rating>
<name>Beelzebub</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84444" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="14">7.41</rating>
<name>Belphegor</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32939" picture="237666.jpg">Kakuma Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84445" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="13">6.58</rating>
<name>Mammon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84446" type="main character in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="12">5.66</rating>
<name>Leviathan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34976" picture="188448.jpg">Fujita Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86807" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="11">6.49</rating>
<name>Astaroth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33509" picture="204529.jpg">Tadokoro Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86808" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="12">6.53</rating>
<name>Belial</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88156" type="main character in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="8">5.41</rating>
<name>Totsuka Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33959" picture="203633.jpg">Toda Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92912" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-18">
<rating votes="14">8.28</rating>
<name>Michael</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105261" type="appears in" update="2019-09-02">
<name>Behemoth</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237951.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105262" type="appears in" update="2019-09-02">
<name>Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43492" picture="232251.jpg">Tomita Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105267" type="appears in" update="2019-09-04">
<name>Mammon no Kenzoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237992.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105270" type="appears in" update="2019-09-05">
<name>Ishi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105292" type="appears in" update="2019-09-07">
<name>Gnosis</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238060.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34406" picture="207995.jpg">Yamada Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="186636" update="2017-05-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強欲うごめく霧の街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Town of Fog Where Greed Brews</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La cité du brouillard où prospère l’avarice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouyoku Ugomeku Kiri no Machi</title>
<summary>The gang travels to London to face another Mortal Sin, the Demon Lord of Greed. Maria finds a strange shop that sells a potion that purports to grant anyone their wildest desires. Lucifer makes haste to the shop`s location, only for them to quickly fall into a trap, but will Maria and Levi be able to handle themselves once they`re separated from Lucifer?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734745</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186637" update="2017-05-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">色欲の渚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beach of Lust</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La plage de la luxure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikiyoku no Nagisa</title>
<summary>Lucifer, Maria, and Levi head towards Miami in search of a Mortal Sin that Maria has detected. Lucifer is now weaker after her fight with the Sins and has decided to take on each Sin, one by one. Lucifer is calculating the best way to fight against the Demon Lord of Lust, but Levi wants to do things her way, only for her to succumb.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734743</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186638" update="2017-05-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">2.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嫉妬ゆえの暴走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Driven Wild by Envy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Folle de jalousie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitto Yue no Bousou</title>
<summary>Maria is glad she gets to see Lucifer again, believing that she`s an angel, and then has her heart stolen by the Demon King. Lucifer forces Maria to follow her and lets her live a life of luxury. Meanwhile, Leviathan, who has strong feelings for Lucifer starts to get jealous over Maria because Lucifer won`t pay any attention to her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734741</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186639" update="2017-05-03">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傲慢たる堕天使</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Proud Fallen Angel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’orgueil de l’ange déchu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouman Taru Datenshi</title>
<summary>Totsuka Maria was praying in a chapel at Seiseki Girls` Academy when a black cross comes falling from the sky. On that cross, was a fallen angel, bearing the sin of pride, Lucifer. Maria attempt to tend to the angel, but the floor falls out and she disappears. Lucifer finds herself in the depths of hell, and runs into the Demon Lord of Envy, Leviathan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734739</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186640" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">放送直前!「sin 七つの大罪」焦[じ]らし特番 ~心理テストでキャストが丸裸!?~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Just Before the Broadcast! "Sin: Nanatsu no Taizai" Impatient Special Program: The Cast Bares Itself for a Mentality Test!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Housou Chokuzen! "Sin: Nanatsu no Taizai" Jirashi Tokuban: Shinri Test de Cast ga Maruhadaka!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186992" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187025" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #1 - 私, 乗せられやすいんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #1: Watashi, Noserare Yasuindesu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187220" update="2017-06-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187222" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #2 - 私, 趣味に素直なんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #2: Watashi, Shumi ni Sunao Nandesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187454" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">解き放たれた憤怒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unleashed Wrath</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Déchaînement de fureur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokihanatareta Funnu</title>
<summary>Satan, the Demon Lord of Wrath, plans on stopping Lucifer once and for all. She sets off for Earth to retrieve Beelzebub and defeat Lucifer. Lucifer is significantly weaker than Satan, but plans on accepting her challenge anyway. Maria watches from afar and tries to remain faithful to Lucifer, and Levi struggles against Satan. How will Lucifer overcome her final obstacle, and what will happen to the others?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734755</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187455" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">咎なき暴食</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Guiltless Gluttony</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une gourmandise sans limites</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toga Naki Boushoku</title>
<summary>Beelzebub, the Sixth Mortal Sin of Gluttony, is running underground eating parties when Lucifer decides to crash one of them. Beelzebub is challenged to an eating contest by Lucifer, but when they both eat as much as they can, Lucifer becomes ill and ends up in the hospital. Her magic should prevent her from getting sick, but she`s severely weakened. Will her time in the hospital bring her some humility?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734753</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187456" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怠惰オンライン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sloth Online</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La paresse 2.0</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taida Online</title>
<summary>Lucifer is now up against the Demon Lord of Sloth, Belphegor. Belphegor gathers her followers online, working with Mammon. Belial asks Belphegor to put an end to Lucifer once and for all. Lucifer ends up getting sucked into Belphegor`s game, along with Maria and Levi. With a battle for the virtual world ongoing, and tensions building between Maria and Lucifer, just what will happen?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734751</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187457" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憂鬱なる歌姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Languid Diva</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mélancolie de la diva</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuutsu Naru Utahime</title>
<summary>Astarotte, the Second Mortal Sin, is a net idol with a decent following, but Lucifer is ready to take her on with her own performances. Lucifer has a different style than Astarotte, starts to outshine Astarotte. As the crowds get bigger, and more is on the line for both Demon Lords, just who will come out on top?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734749</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187487" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #3 - 私, 親切なんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #3: Watshi, Shinsetsu Nandesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187562" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #4 - 私, クオリティには厳しいんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #4: Watashi, Quality ni wa Kibishiindesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187575" update="2017-05-23">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まさに悪魔の所業...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is Indeed the Work of Demons...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un monde démoniaque</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">그야말로 악마의 소행... (4.5화)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masa ni Akuma no Shogyou...</title>
<summary>Mortal Sins examines the motivations of the characters in this episode with a flashback analysis of episodes 1-4. Lucifer, Maria, and Levi all have different needs and desires, but they still came together as a team to help fight the Mortal Sins. There`s plenty more to come.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734747</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187585" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187586" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187587" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187588" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187589" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187590" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio Drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187595" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187596" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #9</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187597" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #8</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187598" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">音声ドラマ「罪の告白 電脳グリモワール」 #7</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Audio drama "Confession of Sin Dennou Grimoir" #7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsei Drama "Tsumi no Kokuhaku: Dennou Grimoire" #7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187764" update="2017-06-05">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187878" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #5 - 私, バイトが忙しいんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #5: Watashi, Baito ga Isogashiindesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187879" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188035" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #6 - 私, 慎ましいんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #6: Watashi, Tsutsumashiindesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188088" update="2017-07-07">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神は天にいまし, すべて世は事も無し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">God`s in His Heaven, All`s Right with the World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dieu est dans les cieux, et tout va bien sur Terre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kami wa Ten ni Imashi, Subete Yo wa Koto mo Nashi</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734763</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188089" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">求めよ, さらば与えられん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ask, and It Shall Be Given to You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Demande et il te sera accordé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Motomeru, Saraba Ataeraren</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734761</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188090" update="2019-03-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汝の敵を愛し汝らを責むる者のために祈れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Your Enemies and Pray for Those Who Persecute You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aime tes ennemis et prie pour ceux qui te condamnent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanji no Teki o Aishi Nanjira o Semuru Mono no Tame ni Inore</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734759</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188091" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">汝, 一切の希望を捨てよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ye Abandon All Hope</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Abandonne tout espoir, toi qui entres en ce lieu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanji, Issai no Kibou o Suteyo</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734757</identifier>
<identifier>seven-mortal-sins</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188118" update="2018-10-08">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #7 - 私, 可愛いものに目がないんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #7: Watashi, Kawaiimono ni Me ga Naindesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188145" update="2017-06-09">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188497" update="2018-10-08">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #8 - 私, アクティブなんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #8: Watashi, Active Nandesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188704" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #10 - 私, 幸せにしちゃうんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #10: Watashi, Shiawase ni Shichaundesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188705" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #9 - 私, バカなんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #9: Watashi, Baka Nandesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189008" recap="true" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">緊急特番! 門限破りの罪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Urgent Special Program! The Sin That Escaped</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinkyuu Tokuban! Mongen Yaburi no Tsumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189617" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #12 - 私, ○○なんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #12: Watashi, .. Nan Desu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189618" update="2017-08-07">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #11 - 私, 遊んじゃうんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #11: Watashi, Asonjaundesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194586" update="2017-12-31">
<epno type="2">S32</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #19 - 私, 悪魔なんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #19: Watashi, Akuma Nandesu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194587" update="2017-12-31">
<epno type="2">S31</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #18 - 私, 悩んでるんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #18: Watashi, Nayan Derundesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194588" update="2017-12-31">
<epno type="2">S30</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #17 - 私, 仕事熱心なんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #17: Watashi, Shigoto Nesshin Nandesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194589" update="2017-12-31">
<epno type="2">S29</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #16 - 私, 片付けられないんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #16: Watashi, Katazukerarenaindesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194590" update="2017-12-31">
<epno type="2">S28</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #15 - 私, 聖人なんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #15: Watashi, Seijin Nandesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194591" update="2017-12-31">
<epno type="2">S27</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #14 - 私, 下着がすごいんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #14: Watashi, Shitagi ga Sugoindesu.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194592" update="2017-12-31">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">懺悔録 #13 - 私, 負けず嫌いなんです.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records of Confessions #13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zange-roku #13: Watashi, Makezugirai Nandesu.</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
