<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12387" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-10</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hagane Orchestra</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">はがねオーケストラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hagane Orchestra</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">钢之管弦乐</title>
</titles>
<url>http://hagane-orchestra.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="23366" type="Animation Work">Fanworks</name>
<name id="9160" type="Character Design">Ookuma Takaharu</name>
<name id="6742" type="Series Composition">Aoshima Takashi</name>
<name id="7852" type="Direction">Oota Masahiko</name>
<name id="9160" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ookuma Takaharu</name>
<name id="7802" type="Music">Misawa Yasuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>The people of this world live happily, despite its inhospitable landscapes. http://anidb.net/ch85591 [Kureha] and the other members of the Defence Squad living in the Irodori Settlement spend their days here in meetings to figure out how to get more people to play Hagane Orchestra, the smartphone game they appear in. And they will do anything to promote their game! The inside story about the game? Its inner workings? Anything goes... be it friendship, determination, betrayal, or despair.
A young man tells his story, along with the girls, his friends, and the Haganes. All work together as one, just like an orchestra...
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="103">2.56</permanent>
<temporary count="103">4.74</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>195469.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18729</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34013</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hagane-orchestra.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>はがねオーケストラ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4365</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358111</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2927" parentid="2676" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Akihabara</name>
<description>Akihabara is a common name for the area around Akihabara Station in the Chiyoda ward of Tokyo, Japan. It gained the nickname Akihabara Electric Town shortly after World War II for being a major shopping center for household electronic goods and the post-war black market. Nowadays, Akihabara is considered by many to be an otaku cultural center and a shopping district for video games, anime, manga, and computer goods.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214314.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6623" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-04-02">
<name>tank warfare</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="85586" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-04">
<name>Den-tan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5576" picture="224283.jpg">Sasaki Hiroo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85587" type="main character in" update="2016-12-04">
<rating votes="1">1.47</rating>
<name>Kako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85588" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-04">
<name>Kajika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33512" picture="225800.jpg">Enoki Jun`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85589" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-16">
<name>Kyuubee</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="22317" picture="223929.jpg">Miya Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85590" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-04">
<name>Chris</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85591" type="main character in" update="2016-12-04">
<rating votes="1">6.67</rating>
<name>Kureha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39924" picture="223926.jpg">Tsutsui Erina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85592" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-04">
<name>Tsubaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39922" picture="203453.jpg">Nakae Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85593" type="main character in" update="2016-12-04">
<rating votes="1">2.44</rating>
<name>Nanaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85594" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-04">
<name>Hanzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34508" picture="211755.jpg">Tokuishi Katsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85595" type="main character in" update="2016-12-04">
<rating votes="1">8.83</rating>
<name>Marsha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34768" picture="129976.jpg">Satou Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85596" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-04">
<name>Yanagi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39165" picture="149507.jpg">Hatakeyama Gousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86587" type="appears in" update="2016-12-04">
<name>Yuzuki Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48039" picture="195595.jpg">Yuzuki Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86588" type="appears in" update="2016-12-04">
<rating votes="2">8.71</rating>
<name>Tsurumaki Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48040" picture="195597.jpg">Tsurumaki Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="180874" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">で, どうなったの?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">So, How`d That Turn Out?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">«Et donc, ça a donné quoi» Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">De, Dou Natta no?</title>
<summary>The girls answer a question about how long they can expect Hagane Orchestra to be in service.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724073</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180875" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どこのメーカーもやってますわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Every Developer Does It</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« Tous les éditeurs le font » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doko no Maker mo Yattemasu wa</title>
<summary>Masha tries some skeevy marketing tactics for Hagane Orchestra.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724071</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180876" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妄想による風評被害!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fantasy-Induced PR Disaster?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">«Tu veux salir mon image» Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mousou ni Yoru Fuuhyouhigai!?</title>
<summary>The gang talks about customizing Haganes in Hagane Orchestra.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724069</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180877" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やっちゃった♪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whoopsies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« On l’a fait » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yacchatta</title>
<summary>Kureha, Masha, Nanaka and Kako discuss ways to advertise Hagane Orchestra.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724067</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181501" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マキさんとは絶交です</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re Not Friends Anymore, Maki-san</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« C’est fini entre nous, Maki » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maki-chan wa Zekkou Desu</title>
<summary>Yukari and Maki visit Irodori. They discover a very easy way to advertise Hagane Orchestra.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723891</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181502" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">動いてなんぼだからね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Humbly Promote Myself</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« Je me proclame humblement » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ugoite Nanbo Dakara ne</title>
<summary>Chris and Nanaka are in the hangar, messing around...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723889</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181503" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さすがにこれはないっすわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is Out of the Question</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« Ça le fait clairement pas » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasuga ni Kore wa Naissu wa</title>
<summary>So, Brain, what do you want to do tonight? Same thing we do every night, Pinky: Try to take over the app store ranking!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724077</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181504" update="2016-11-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダウンロォォォォド!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Downloooooad!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« Télécharger ! » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Downloooooad!</title>
<summary>The Irodori crew hit the hot springs. No nudity involved -- unless you download the game!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>724075</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182492" update="2017-01-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">てなわけで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">So Anyway</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« Avec tout ça » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tena Wake de</title>
<summary>Hagane Orchestra: the story of a boy and a girl. And mechs. And friendship. And rivalry. At an app store near you.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723899</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182493" update="2017-01-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふふ, 可愛い子......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hehe, You`re So Adorable...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« Tu es mignonne » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fufu, Kawaii Ko......</title>
<summary>The gang start a doujinshi sale. But how does that even have anything to do with advertising Hagane Orchestra?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723897</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182494" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺を信じてくれるか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Will You Believe Me, My Comrade?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« Tu me fais confiance ? » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore o Shinjite Kureruka?</title>
<summary>The Hagane Academy Concert Band prepares to compete in the Nationals. Drama ensues.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723895</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182495" update="2016-12-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2016-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一理ある</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Have a Point</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">« Tu marques un point » Fin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichiri Aru</title>
<summary>The guys discuss how to reel in more fellow guy gamers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>723893</identifier>
<identifier>hagane-orchestra</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
