<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12395" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2017-06-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tsugumomo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">つぐもも</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tsugumomo</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">츠구모모</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">怪怪守护神</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14728" type="Sequel">Tsugu Tsugumomo</anime>
<anime id="14729" type="Other">Tsugumomo (2020)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6571" approval="2" total="2">Omamori Himari</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="469382">Classic harem, and a decent one at that. Definitely recommended if you need a change from all the isekai stuff. Also, the fanservice is fairly light. The "heavy" fanservice consists of about one bath cutesy bath scene per episode.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="610386">It`s unexpectedly a pretty fun watch. The fan service is pretty high tho, be careful when watching it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://tsugumomo.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="46859" type="Original Work">Hamada Yoshikazu</name>
<name id="44519" type="Animation Work">Zero-G</name>
<name id="4360" type="Character Design">Nakahara Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="47659" type="Series Composition">Kuraya Ryouichi</name>
<name id="47659" type="Direction">Kuraya Ryouichi</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="4360" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakahara Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch86824 [Kagami Kazuya]`s most treasured possession in the world is the http://anidb.net/t2024 [obi] left to him by his late http://anidb.net/ch88302 [mother]. The scent of cherry blossoms infused into it helps him through his day, but he never expected it to save his life, becoming a beautiful kimono-clad girl who calls herself an artifact spirit. Her name is http://anidb.net/ch86825 [Kiriha], http://anidb.net/t7145 [tsukumogami] of the sash, who naturally moves in with him, as he is her owner. Throw in his bespectacled childhood friend http://anidb.net/ch87312 [Chisato] who meddles in his affairs, an http://anidb.net/ch88301 [overprotective older sister] who wants to take baths with him, a busty priestess, a seductive sorceress named Kokuyoura, and Kazuya`s life has just gotten a lot more interesting.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="805">4.57</permanent>
<temporary count="810">6.39</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>227298.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18895</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34019</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://tsugumomo.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>つぐもも</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4509</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358156</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20051</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>tsugumomo_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07CVQ8L6Y</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2391" parentid="2608" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>bishoujo</name>
<description>In Japanese, a bishoujo is any pretty female from toddlerhood to late adolescence. In the West, the word specifically refers to attractive girls generally from late childhood or early adolescence, especially those that appeal to males, and particularly to fictional characters designed in a way traditionally associated to shoujo manga. Fictional bishoujo tend to be cute, pastel-coloured teenagers; they lack the sophistication of older women, instead having detailed eye and hair design, fluttery costumes often including ribbons, and all sorts of generally sparkly fluff.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3721" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-07">
<name>RPG elements</name>
<description>The anime shows elements of a `R`ole `P`laying `G`ame, either as part of a parody or because the anime is actually based on an RPG.
Typical elements: When collecting items, beating opponents, or levelling up a distinct (often childishly sounding) sound cue is played. A HUD (`H`eads `U`p `D`isplay) may also be presenting in combat, showing vital player and "enemy" statistics.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4148" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-11">
<name>late for school</name>
<description>A common device for a series opening or Establishing Character Moment. Things begin in a frantic rush which usually results in taking short cuts, such as eating breakfast on the run. The classic image is of someone running down the street with a slice of toast hanging out of their mouth, dragging their backpack with one hand while trying to put on their jacket or sweater one-handed with the other, bumping into important people in a manner that gets the plot started.
Basically, they`re never on time for school. While some are Heavy Sleepers, it would appear that they may have simply set their alarm clocks so as to give them insufficient time to get to class. 
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>161002.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6028" parentid="2876" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-10-12">
<name>Shintoism</name>
<description>Shintoism presents a blessed being or creature that governs over areas of terrain, general space of existence, or an individual object (be it alive or inanimate). Everything has its own "spiritual essence".
Defined as the earliest Japanese thoughts of an unified religion, the word Shinto comes from the Chinese hanzi "神道", combining two kanji: "shin" (神), meaning gods or spirits; and "tō" (道), meaning a philosophical path or study.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6191" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>card games</name>
<description>A card game is any game using playing cards as the primary device with which the game is played, be they traditional or game-specific. Countless card games exist, including families of related games (such as poker). A small number of card games played with traditional decks have formally standardized rules, but most are folk games whose rules vary by region, culture, and person.
Many games that are not generally placed in the family of card games do in fact use cards for some aspect of their gameplay. Similarly, some games that are placed in the card game genre involve a board. The distinction is that the gameplay of a card game primarily depends on the use of the cards by players (the board is simply a guide for scorekeeping or for card placement), while board games (the principal non-card game genre to use cards) generally focus on the players` positions on the board, and use the cards for some secondary purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6252" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>feud</name>
<description>A feud, referred to in more extreme cases as a blood feud, vendetta, faida, beef, clan war, gang war, or private war, is a long-running argument or fight, often between social groups of people, especially families or clans. Feuds begin because one party (correctly or incorrectly) perceives itself to have been attacked, insulted or wronged by another. Intense feelings of resentment trigger the initial retribution, which causes the other party to feel equally aggrieved and vengeful. The dispute is subsequently fuelled by a long-running cycle of retaliatory violence. This continual cycle of provocation and retaliation makes it extremely difficult to end the feud peacefully. Feuds frequently involve the original parties` family members and/or associates, can last for generations, and may result in extreme acts of violence. They can be interpreted as an extreme outgrowth of social relations based in family honour.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="86824" type="main character in" update="2017-05-16">
<rating votes="8">4.40</rating>
<name>Kagami Kazuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86825" type="main character in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="27">8.87</rating>
<name>Kiriha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37280" picture="136935.jpg">Oozora Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87311" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="14">5.85</rating>
<name>Kukuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198389.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87312" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="7">4.06</rating>
<name>Chikaishi Chisato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40520" picture="200561.jpg">Shibasaki Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87313" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="12">7.68</rating>
<name>Kokuyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88301" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-16">
<rating votes="8">5.24</rating>
<name>Kagami Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88302" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-10">
<rating votes="8">5.52</rating>
<name>Kagami Kanaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88303" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="3">6.09</rating>
<name>Osanai Osamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38842" picture="146423.jpg">Sasaki Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88304" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="4">3.88</rating>
<name>Shiramine Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9365" picture="34581.jpg">Kokuryuu Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88305" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="14">4.90</rating>
<name>Sumeragi Sunao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201472.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88306" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="4">5.10</rating>
<name>Kotetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88307" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="7">4.61</rating>
<name>Kanayama Taguri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88754" type="appears in" update="2017-06-19">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Iraha Isuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204038.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49728" picture="201172.jpg">Tachibana Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88890" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Kagami Kazuaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88891" type="appears in" update="2017-04-17">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Kukurihimei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89105" type="appears in" update="2017-04-30">
<rating votes="2">2.38</rating>
<name>Tadata Tadataka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201870.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89231" type="appears in" update="2017-05-08">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Ookado Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40436" picture="186230.jpg">Hamada Youhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89232" type="appears in" update="2019-10-08">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Tadata Tatami</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46819" picture="224887.jpg">Inoue Honoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89401" type="appears in" update="2017-05-21">
<rating votes="2">4.89</rating>
<name>Misago Misako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89573" type="appears in" update="2017-05-28">
<rating votes="3">4.27</rating>
<name>Nanakai Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89574" type="appears in" update="2017-05-28">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Nago Eiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37977" picture="226053.jpg">Oowada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89575" type="appears in" update="2017-05-28">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Muratsuki Sakumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37986" picture="139351.jpg">Yuuki Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89576" type="appears in" update="2017-05-28">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Kosakabe Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89893" type="appears in" update="2017-06-10">
<rating votes="3">5.80</rating>
<name>Honoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="588" picture="41015.jpg">Orikasa Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90055" type="appears in" update="2017-06-19">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Sumeragi Suzuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49728" picture="201172.jpg">Tachibana Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="186181" update="2017-04-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">土地神の試練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trials of the Local God</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`Épreuve de la divinité locale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tochigami no Shiren</title>
<summary>Kiriha is being battered by the water goddess Kukuri-hime`s attacks, when a mysterious vision gives Kazuya advice on how he and the tsugumomo might manage to survive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734383</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186182" update="2017-04-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">くくりひめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kukuri-hime</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kukurihime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kukuri-hime</title>
<summary>A towering priestess shows up looking for Kazuya, and the person who sent her has an offer he and Kiriha might not be able to refuse.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734381</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186183" update="2017-04-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">図書室と幼馴染</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Library and the Childhood Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bibliothèque et l`amie d`enfance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toshoshitsu to Osananajimi</title>
<summary>Kazuya and class rep Chisato find themselves trapped in the school library, and it`s up to Kiriha`s knowledge of spirits and the forms they take to get them out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734379</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186184" update="2017-04-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜の香り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scent of Cherry Blossoms</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le parfum des cerisiers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Kaori</title>
<summary>Kagami Kazuya is an ordinary school boy who has one slightly odd habit: he carries around the obi of a kimono that belonged to his late mother. This wouldn`t be a big deal, until the obi reveals itself to be a tsukumogami--an object that, after a great length of time, has attained consciousness! With a ghost in the silk now demanding his servitude, more supernatural trouble doesn`t seem far behind.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734377</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186434" update="2017-03-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『つぐもも』先行上映会直後の生放送特番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Tsugumomo" Zenkoujoueikai Chakugo no Namahousou Tokuban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186621" update="2017-04-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186622" update="2017-04-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187100" update="2017-05-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ある日の加賀見家 / モテモテフレグランス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Certain Day in the Kagami Household / The Super Popular Fragrance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une journée chez les Kagami / Un parfum attirant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aru Hi no Kagami-ke / Motemote Frangrance</title>
<summary>Kazuya takes Kiriha and Kokuri grocery shopping, and then Shirou finds his charisma boosted to uncontrollable levels by a cologne amasogi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734391</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187101" update="2017-05-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金山さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kanayama-san</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kanayama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanayama-san</title>
<summary>Kukuri and Kokuyou have nowhere to live, and almost no income. Kiriha forces Kukuri to visit a neighboring local god for a loan, but the collateral being demanded might cost the two of them much more than just money.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734389</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187102" update="2017-05-08">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出と幼馴染</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories and Childhood Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs et amis d`enfance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide to Osananajimi</title>
<summary>When the entire school starts acting like characters from a dating sim, Kazuya and Kiriha are forced to find the amasogi responsible before the affected people do something they`ll regret.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734387</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187103" update="2017-05-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特訓</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Training</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Entraînement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokkun</title>
<summary>Now that Kazuya has accepted the duty of exorcising any supernatural trouble that crops up, it`s up to Kiriha to whip him into shape.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734385</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187711" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パートナー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Partner</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Partenaires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Partner</title>
<summary>Kazuya`s duel with Sunao concludes, with Kiriha and Kazuya dead set on proving that a tsugumomo who works together with their master is stronger than one that`s just treated like a tool.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734399</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187712" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kettou</title>
<summary>The duel between Sunao and Kazuya begins. Can Kazuya and Kiriha manage to overcome Sunao`s thirst for vengeance?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734397</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187713" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はだかふとん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nude in the Futon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nus sous les draps</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hadaka Futon</title>
<summary>A malison cleanser who knew Kazuya`s mother is unimpressed with his skills, and wants to strip of him of his duties. But after seeing how malison atonement impacts the people struck by it, does Kazuya even want to put up a fight?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734395</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187714" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">手紙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Letter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lettre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tegami</title>
<summary>A mysterious phantom student is stalking Kazuya`s school, and Kiriha says that there`s no such thing as ghosts. That leaves only one explanation: another amasogi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734393</identifier>
<identifier>tsugumomo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
