<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12460" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-11-03</startdate>
<enddate>2017-11-03</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Escha Chron</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">エスカクロン</title>
</titles>
<url>http://escha-chron.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="27220" type="Animation Work">Lerche</name>
<name id="18168" type="Character Design">Watanabe Satomi</name>
<name id="45916" type="Direction">Yamaguchi Hikaru</name>
<name id="130" type="Chief Direction">Mizushima Seiji</name>
<name id="42623" type="Music">Hifumi</name>
</creators>
<description>The story follows the two titular women http://anidb.net/ch85405 [Escha] and http://anidb.net/ch85406 [Chron], whose contrasting personalities are like the sun and moon. The two women are from Terminal, a future post-apocalyptic world that`s empty and monochrome. The two women cross worlds and arrive in the present day, which they call Transit. As Escha and Chron experience the light (scenery) and sound (music) of the real world, the future world of Terminal gradually changes into a more vivid world.
Source: ANN
Note: Both episodes were screened on a special event on July 15, 2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="72">5.22</permanent>
<temporary count="72">6.07</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>200111.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19474</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34208</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://escha-chron.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>エスカクロンプロジェクト</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4754</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358453</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>escha_chron</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="85405" type="main character in" update="2017-07-27">
<rating votes="2">7.42</rating>
<name>Escha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10759" picture="38748.jpg">Anzai Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85406" type="main character in" update="2017-07-27">
<rating votes="2">5.78</rating>
<name>Chron</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27357" picture="75009.jpg">Yasuno Kiyono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90625" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-27">
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<name>Kasai Hayata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90626" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-27">
<rating votes="2">5.78</rating>
<name>Saitou Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="195206" update="2018-05-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195207" update="2018-05-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
