<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12478" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-04-15</startdate>
<enddate>2017-04-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Eiga Crayon Shin-chan Shuurai! Uchuujin Shiriri</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Crayon Shin-chan Movie 25</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">映画クレヨンしんちゃん 襲来!! 宇宙人シリリ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="708" type="Parent Story">Crayon Shin-chan</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.shinchan-movie.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4202" type="Original Work">Usui Yoshito</name>
<name id="13338" type="Direction">Hashimoto Masakazu</name>
<name id="5785" type="Character Design">Hariganeya Hideo</name>
<name id="53168" type="Character Design">Kuno Youko</name>
<name id="1403" type="Character Design">Sueyoshi Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="5655" type="Music">Arakawa Toshiyuki</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="8">6.37</permanent>
<temporary count="8">6.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>199059.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19582</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34244</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.shinchan-movie.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358499</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20189</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="8382" type="main character in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="202">6.65</rating>
<name>Nohara Shinnosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the main character, a kindergarten-aged boy whose antics are the basis for the series. His affectionate name is Shin-chan. He is 5 years old and loves chocolate biscuits and a TV superhero named "Action Kamen". He is attracted to older girls and women, despite his young age. He brazenly pursues any girl who catches his eye. He shares this trait with his father and paternal grandfather, but this often results in Mom`s cruel punishment. The only girl he seems to really like is a college student named Nanako. Some of his strange activities include dressing up and mooning. In general, he is brutally honest, highly curious, and has no shame whatsoever. Ironically, there have been several instances in which his antics actually solved the problems of those around him. He also displays a surprising amount of talent at various activities including kendo. On rare occasions, he displays bouts of selfless kindness (for example, in one anime episode he saved a frog from a truck on a rainy day, getting all wet and dirty in the process and risking Misae`s ire since it was his last set of clean clothes), but these are often immediately followed by antics that negate the goodwill others feel. There are also times when Shin-chan displays a level of maturity beyond his usual self in his concern for others, and in a few rare instances he shows that deep down he really does care for his family, despite his constant disrespect towards them. This shows up more often than not in the feature length movies as compared to the regular series episodes.</description>
<picture>2220.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8384" type="main character in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="43">5.02</rating>
<name>Nohara Misae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The mother of the Nohara family from Kumamoto on the island of Kyushu. She is 29 years old and a typical housewife of post-war Japan, she cleans, launders, cooks, sews, mothers, and lazes all to varying degrees of success. While at heart a caring and nurturing individual, her positive aspects are often offset by her many shortcomings. A paragon of hypocrisy, after handing out irrevocable edicts to her husband and children, she will not hesitate to immediately break them once they are out of sight. She administers brutal punishment to her husband, son, and on rare occasions her year-old daughter whenever they disobey her. While she spends as little as possible on the less-essential needs of her husband and son, she loves to splurge on Himawari and herself, though she is noted to have instances of great generosity. She is the source of boundless diet and savings plans, all of which fail within the first week. For example, she is prone to immediately partake in bargain sales when she sees them, thinking she is saving the family money. However, she buys in extreme quantities, which defeats the purpose. Additionally, she secretly hoardes money for her own personal use.</description>
<picture>2221.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4717" picture="186206.jpg">Narahashi Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8386" type="main character in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="20">1.63</rating>
<name>Nohara Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Father of the Nohara family from Akita in Northern Japan, and its sole source of income. He met Misae at the age of 29, and after dating for around a year the two wed. He is a loving father to his two children, and ultimately a devoted husband. While he is the family bread-winner, he hands the reins of finance over to his wife, who maintains a totalitarian level of control on family spending. At age 35, he is a stereotypical salaryman, working eight-hour days, enduring overstuffed trains, and enjoying the occasional nightlife. While his relationship with his family is positive on the whole, there is an abundance of recurring conflict. He and his wife bicker on many different things, from how little he gets for spending money every month, to whose turn it is to give the baby a bath. Misae is also notorious for inflicting violence on Hiroshi whenever she gets very angry. He enjoys a playful relationship with his children; but sometimes they`re the source of his daily woes. He will not hesitate to save his allowance for things he wants, but can be seen spending much of it to buy his family creature comforts. A running joke is made of the pungent odor of his feet.</description>
<picture>2222.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8390" type="main character in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="16">2.14</rating>
<name>Nohara Himawari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2223.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="556" picture="17848.jpg">Koorogi Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8393" type="main character in" update="2009-06-04">
<rating votes="18">1.63</rating>
<name>Shiro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A white, fluffy pup Shin-chan found in a cardboard box early in the series. While a beloved member of the family, he is the subject of neglect thanks to his owner`s forgetfulness and short attention-span. He is a very intelligent dog, often presenting logic and intellect that surpasses his human owners. As his meals from the Noharas are at best inconsistent, he has developed a talent for foraging. An oddly human like dog, he is very responsible and painstakingly careful.</description>
<picture>2224.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3221" picture="24202.jpg">Mashiba Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83105" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-24">
<name>Sakurada Nene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31035" picture="83149.jpg">Hayashi Tamao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83599" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-24">
<name>Satou Masao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9347" picture="34528.jpg">Ichiryuusai Teiyuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83600" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-24">
<name>Kazama Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3221" picture="24202.jpg">Mashiba Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83601" type="appears in" update="2016-08-06">
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<name>Kitamoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189764.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2040" picture="186173.jpg">Suzuki Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83603" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-24">
<name>Bou-chan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3838" picture="25826.jpg">Satou Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="181038" update="2017-04-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>105</length>
<airdate>2017-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195468" update="2018-01-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">クレヨンしんちゃん×パンパカパンツ イオンシネママナームービーコラボ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crayon Shin-chan x Panpaka Pants: Aeon Cinema Manner Movie Collab</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Crayon Shin-chan x Panpaka Pants Aeon Cinema Manner Movie Collab</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197976" update="2018-04-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197977" update="2018-04-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
