<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12474" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-03-21</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kemushi no Boro</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Boro the Caterpillar</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">毛虫のボロ</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="773955">There really is not much to say here. It`s a short and cute movie that is shown exclusively at the ghibli museum. Just go watch it if you happen to be there and enjoy the show.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="40" type="Direction">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
<name id="40" type="Original Work">Miyazaki Hayao</name>
</creators>
<description>A story of a tiny, hairy caterpillar, so tiny that it may be easily squished between your fingers.
Source: Wired
Note: A short CG film which screen exclusively at the http://anidb.net/cr729 [Studio Ghibli] Museum in Japan. A preview screening was held on 14.03.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5">4.78</permanent>
<temporary count="5">6.80</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>214818.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20506</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32133</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ghibli-museum.jp/cinema/works/#kemusshinoboro</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>毛虫のボロ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358710</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3968" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>animal protagonist</name>
<description>The anime revolves around an animal, usually only communicating with typical onomatopoeia. The animal mostly lives in a human family and has adventures on a regular base. This can be the discovery of a new room, or being lost by having taken a wrong turn in the outside world.
Typical example: http://anidb.net/a5801 [Chii`s Sweet Home].
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t4259 [animal world], where the whole world is composed of animals.</description>
<picurl>10255.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4259" parentid="2857" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>animal world</name>
<description>All characters of the show are walking-talking animals. Their behaviour and clothing can resemble that of humans. They also may try to mirror human society.
There are no humans present in this world.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3968 [animal protagonist].</description>
<picurl>10254.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4542" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>no dialogue</name>
<description>The anime either has no spoken dialogue or no dialogue at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="187419" update="2018-01-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
