<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="125" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>51</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-10-13</startdate>
<enddate>2002-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Groove Adventure Rave</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">レイヴ</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Рэйв Мастер</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Пътешествието на Рейв</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">RAVE</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">the groove adventure RAVE</title>
<title xml:lang="mn" type="synonym">RAVE мастер</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GAR</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">GROOVE ADVENTURE RAVE</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Rave Master</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Rave</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Rave Master</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8132" type="Other">Fairy Tail (2011)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6662" approval="223" total="239">Fairy Tail</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="221392">eng: anime adventure cool in the midst of an accelerated and ends asking for more (final kind of weak), but worth watching!
Pt: anime de aventura bem legal, no meio da uma acelerada e termina pedindo mais (final meio fraco), mas vale assistir!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20031207083741/http://www.tbs.co.jp/rave2001/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1946" type="Music">Kawai Kenji</name>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="1418" type="Character Design">Matsushima Akira</name>
<name id="4336" type="Series Composition">Kishima Nobuaki</name>
<name id="7578" type="Original Work">Mashima Hiro</name>
<name id="2120" type="Direction">Watanabe Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>RAVE takes place on another world that was at one point dominated by a light stone (Rave), and a dark stone (Darkbring). There was a fierce battle between the two which led to an explosion that destroyed 1/10 of the world. After 50 years, Darkbring was revived by a group called the Demon Card. Demon Card uses the power of Darkbring to bring chaos to the world. Only the power of the light stone can resist it... Rave. Could Haru who catched Plue from the ocean and inherited Rave from Rave Master Shiba save the world? Watch as his adventure begins!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1304">4.80</permanent>
<temporary count="1338">6.94</temporary>
<review count="4">8.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>11158.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1784</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>246</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>714</identifier>
<identifier>rpxluz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20031207083741/http://www.tbs.co.jp/rave2001/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Rave_Master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>RAVE_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236318</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4994</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9818" type="main character in" update="2009-06-24">
<rating votes="8">7.54</rating>
<name>Elie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Elie is very lively and optimistic girl with a hot temper. She also has no memories of who she is, which is why she sets out to look for someone who could tell here what is her real name and where are her parents. While travaling Elie meets Haru Glory who promises her that they will find her memories together.</description>
<picture>29814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13713" type="main character in" update="2010-01-07">
<rating votes="29">5.53</rating>
<name>Plue</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Plue`s body is a pure white creature with a yellow horn-like nose. It`s always trembling, and it can only say "puun". Its favorite food is candy. When it`s hungry or enters a bath, its body and nose become shrivelled. Hiro Mashima, the author of the manga, has said that Plue feels close to a stuffed animal. It`s age and gender are a mystery.
In Groove Adventure Rave, Plue is a strange creature that Haru discovered, Plue is the Rave Bearer, and is able to sense the presence of the other Rave Stones. Plue`s nose also has the ability to destroy Dark Bring. It has the ability to utilise the Rave of Combat, which powers itself and Haru up.
In Fairy Tail, Plue is a Silver Key Celestial Spirit officially called "Nicola the Canis Minor", but named Plue by its summoner Lucy. Its only unique ability is magic cancellation, and so serves more as a pet for Lucy.</description>
<picture>3894.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="23531" picture="222835.jpg">Yukiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31610" type="main character in" update="2011-04-27">
<rating votes="3">7.32</rating>
<name>Haru Glory</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haru Glory is the current Rave Master. He lives with his sister, Cattleya Glory on Garage Island. Haru was entrusted with the responsibility of finding all the Rave Stones and bringing peace to the world when he was chosen as the second generation Rave Master. He is in love with Elie.</description>
<picture>70603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31611" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-12">
<name>Hamrio Musica</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hamrio Musica is the leader of a band of thieves named Silver-Rhythm. He can manipulate silver into any form and weapon he wants it to be. He uses the silver skull around his neck to manipulate silver to a weapon of his choice. The silver skull is fused with Reina`s bracelet after she dies and there he gains the weapon "Silver Ray". He is Haru`s good and strongest friend. He later forges Haru the holy sword "Ravelt" which is derived from "Rave" and "Velt", the German word for world.</description>
<picture>83441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20316" picture="53453.jpg">Amano Erika</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31612" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-27">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Griffon Kato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Called Griff by his friends, he mostly praises Plue and calls him `Master Plue`. He looks like a strange blue eggplant, with eyes and arms. He is close to Plue in size but with the ability to speak. Griff has limited shape-shifting abilities; such as inflating portions of his body and elongating his limbs. He is also a voyeuristic character, and in a couple of episodes he is seen spying on Elie. He is the cartographer of the group.</description>
<picture>1595.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20322" picture="186181.jpg">Shiga Katsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31613" type="appears in" update="2011-04-27">
<rating votes="2">1.32</rating>
<name>Tanchimo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19929" picture="51183.jpg">Tanaka Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31614" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Let Javad Dahaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Let is a Dragonrace, a race of dragon people who reside in the Mystic Realm. When Let was first introduced, he was an evil warrior who worked for Demon Card as a guardian for King. He only wanted to fight until Haru defeated him and showed him the path of justice. His initial appearance in the story is of a human with a lizard like face. In the fight against Jegan he performs Dragon trial and takes the appearance of a human. Soon, he joined Haru in hope of bringing peace to the world. He uses Dragon roar of the gods to defeat Jegan which consumes ones life in return for the power. He manages to defeat Jegan and turn Julia back to normal using a potion given by Alice. He is saved by Julia using the same potion.</description>
<picture>78648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31615" type="appears in" update="2011-04-27">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Julia Line Dragoon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Julia is Let`s girlfriend, somewhat of a feisty one who`s loud, rowdy, and not above beating people up to get her way, which is a polar opposite to the cool and calm Let. Initially in the story Julia is shown to have become a dragon as she had failed to pass the dragon trial. Julia is saved by Let and turned back to normal using a potion given by Alice. She can usually be found at a bar. A sisterly figure to Haru`s party. She was first thought to be a kind and shy girl in Let`s flashbacks. In the anime her hair is green.</description>
<picture>70622.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39721" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-17">
<rating votes="1">1.32</rating>
<name>Shuuda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shuda is the first member of Demon Card`s Oracion Six to be introduced. He fought and lost to Haru Glory twice in the beginning of the series, and after his second defeat, he reforms and becomes an ally of Haru and his friends. He holds the utmost respect for Gale Glory. He uses the high six star Dark Bring Ballettänzer Zeffrea, which allows him to cause an explosion within a spherical targeting grid that manifests over a chosen point in space. He also wields two swords: the ghost sword Entenka (which spews forth flames by cutting the wind), and the divine sword Heavenly Blossom, which is claimed to be a weapon of the gods. He is skilled in dancing and taught Elie how to dance for the dance festival in volume 22 and 23. Shuda also is revealed to have a relationship with Haru`s sister.</description>
<picture>78644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39722" type="appears in" update="2011-12-17">
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<name>Cattleya Glory</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cattleya Glory is Haru`s older sister. She is reluctant to let Haru leave Garage Island. She is the self-proclaimed "Queen of "Karaoke". Since their parents were away, she had to take over in raising Haru and hence, at the start of the series, Haru is often quoting things he should not do because his sister said so. She is revealed to be in a relationship with Shuda when he tested the Stellar shard on himself.</description>
<picture>78645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19182" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39724" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Let Javad Dahaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39725" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<name>Ruby</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ruby is a pink penguin sentinoid who owns a massive floating casino. Ruby likes to use his wealth to buy rare treasures. When he learns Doryu is using his cash for evil ends, he is almost killed by Doryu, but Haru saves him, and he decides to join his side. He is the only person to know who would be the third Rave Master if Haru dies. Ruby also has a tendency to blab out plans that the Rave Warriors have decided on during battle, making them entirely useless. He recently learned how to use "Wind" magic from the bell given to him by his father. The bell was actually named "the Holy Bell" and it was a weapon used by Dalmatian of Knights of the Blue Sky. It can turn into a magic sword, and use "Magic Reflection", "Twister", and "Air Ball" (from the videogame). In Chapter 75 the characters of Fairy Tail go to casino owned by Ruby.</description>
<picture>78650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23531" picture="222835.jpg">Yukiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39726" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-19">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Sieg Hart</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sieg Hart is a Defender of Time from Mildea and an elemental master, he was originally out to kill Elie, but eventually helped Haru occasionally on his quest after realizing that Elie needed to be saved. He was originally working with Demon Card (he was plotting to kill King) but left after trying to kill Elie. He helps uncover Elie`s memories, at the cost of his life.</description>
<picture>84182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39727" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Malakia Symphonia Glory</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Malakia Symphonia Glory is the deceased King of the former Symphonian Kingdom and father to Gale Glory and Grandfather of Haru. He existed in Elie`s memories when he went under the alias of Kaim and entrusted Evermary to take care Gale after his death from the curse placed on him by Shakuma.</description>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39728" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Shiba Roses</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiba Roses is the first Rave Master. He acknowledged Haru as the second Rave Master when Rave chose Haru and tasked Haru with the responsibility of bringing peace to the world by gathering all the Raves. In his battle to against Haru in his final test to prove if he is a worthy Rave Master, Shiba was given an elixir so he could revert back to his younger self to when he was the Rave Master himself. Only being able to sustain his younger body for 15 minutes, Shiba fought knowing that if he drank the elixir, he would die. Shiba, however, died happy in Elie`s arms having recognized her as Resha, his "lost" and only love.</description>
<picture>78652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39729" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Shiba Roses</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39730" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Alpine Spaniel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alpine Spaniel is a heroic knight of the kingdom of Symphonia who becomes one of the guardians of Rave.</description>
<picture>82473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39731" type="appears in" update="2012-05-12">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Deerhound</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A huge brute of a warrior who seems to laugh at everything. He was one of the four Knights of the Blue Sky .</description>
<picture>87698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39732" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Deerhound</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1756" picture="53985.jpg">Nakajima Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39733" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">1.32</rating>
<name>Clea Maltese</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Clea Maltese is a dark-skinned beauty from Lyric Continent, or more</description>
<picture>78656.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39734" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<name>Clea Maltese</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78657.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="39735" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Dalmatian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dalmatian is a member of the Knights of the Blue Sky.</description>
<picture>78658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39736" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Galien Musica</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Galein Musica is Hamrio Musica`s grandfather and the blacksmith who created the TCM.</description>
<picture>78661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2244" picture="52187.jpg">Nagashima Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39737" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Gale Raregroove</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gale Raregroove primarily referred to as King is the initial ruler of Demon Card and a decendant to the former Raregroove kingdom. He founded Demon Card with Gale but after Gale left from their conflicting bloodlines, King became the sole leader of Demon Card, and soon fell under the influence of Dark Bring, whose power he used to strengthen the organization which later after 10 years, the organization became a force for evil that terrorized the world with the power of Dark Bring. Years later King is reported to the empire by Gale which causes his intentions misread and instead the empire commences a slaughter upon the forces of Demon Card, killing King`s wife Emilia and presumably his son Lucia. King himself was taken into custody by the Empire but later broke out with the power of Dark Bring. In the present, Haru and Gale Glory fight King at the Tower of Din where the battle ends with King dying and Gale Glory dying in the aftermath of the fight. King is extremely strong and is often used as a reference to show the relative strength of other villains. Although he uses 5 dark bring, which is considered an extraordinary feat, he does not use any Sinclaire like the other main villains of the series. The fact he can still match them in combat is a testament to his strength. King`s sword Decalogus is a dark bring which is the evil counterpart of the Ten Powers. His Dark Bring, Black Zenith fires a huge black sphere that disintegrates anything that it touches. The Dark Bring, Gate which can open doors between worlds. King used this to summon his warriors, the 5 Palace Guardians, from the Mystic realm. Monster Prison is one of the "reverse" Dark Brings feared for their unchecked power, which seals the bearer`s body and soul within it for all eternity, transforming them into a beast with just bestial instincts; in this form, he is immune to pain and can fire energy beams from the mouth. The last Dark Bring he possess is Warp Road which has the power of teleportation which King used to extract the Dark Bring End of Earth from within Gale and teleport it to the distant Demon Card HQ, which was annihilated in the subsequent Overdrive.</description>
<picture>82475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39738" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Lucia Raregroove</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lucia Raregroove is the son of King and was the heir to the throne of Demon Card and also the Raregroove Kingdom. During the Empire`s infamous raid of Demon Card headquarters 10 years prior to the series present, Lucia was presumably killed in the slaughter along with his mother, Emilia. When he was seen to still be alive, he was imprisoned within the 66th basement of the maximum security desert prison Mega Unit where he became an infamous legend known among the Empire as the Blonde Demon, a boy whose power was so great and terrifying, he was a threat to the entire world. Sometime after the death of his father during the battle at the Tower of Din, he became powerful enough to violently break out of his imprisonment within Mega Unit. Much like Gale Glory and King were destined to oppose each other, Lucia is every bit the antithesis to the second Rave Master Haru Glory, as the self-proclaimed Dark Bring Master. Initially, he possessed the first piece of Sinclaire (The mother of all Dark Brings) that was the main piece which has the power of creating a warped dimensional space that has enough pressure to annihilate anything. After having over 10 years of influence over him, Sinclair managed to bestow upon Lucia a high amount of superhuman strength, speed, stamina, endurance and durability as well as giving him knowledge. He also wields his fathers former sword, Decalogus which has the same abilities as Haru`s Ten Powers.</description>
<picture>78662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39739" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Haja</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haja is the de facto leader of the Oracion Six and one of its most powerful members (second only to Berial, according to the author). He is one of the top mages in the world, second only perhaps to his master Shakuma (the world`s greatest mage). His overwhelming might is primarily attributed to his ability to generate limitless quantities of mana, which gained him the title of "Haja the Infinite"; while this was seemingly a natural ability at first, it was later revealed to be derived from a Dark Bring implanted within him. Like the archmage Sieghart, he hails from the town of Mildea, the city of time. He was initially depicted as being one of Demon Card`s most loyal members, but later events would later reveal him to be a highly devious and ambitious individual, who plotted to have the most powerful forces for both good AND evil eliminated and coveted ultimate power to achieve control over the entire world and all of time. To that end, he returned to his hometown of Mildea to acquire the great power that dwelled beneath it, but was opposed and inevitably killed by Sieg, who was aided by the Mildeans. It was revealed afterwards that Haja carried within him the essence of the Demon Card scientist Igor Kilkila, who was released after Haja was killed (Igor was subsequently defeated and imprisoned by Sieg and the Mildeans).</description>
<seiyuu id="66" picture="216211.jpg">Bifu Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39740" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Reina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Reina is a Silver Claimer, like Musica. She became a member of Demon Card and the Oracion Six to avenge the injustice done to her deceased father, as well as to find the silver ship Silver Ray (her father`s greatest work), whose theft her father was unjustly accused of. She has an issue with Musica, as his mentor Rize is who Reina believes to be the true culprit behind the theft of the Silver Ray, and hence is privy to its location. She uses the Six Star Dark Bring White Kiss, which she uses to create silver out of thin air, which she then manipulates to create silver weapons. In the battle against ogre she teams up with Musica to defeat him. In this battle they use the Silver Bonds to defeat Ogre. She liked Musica and told him how she felt before destroying the Silver Ray. At the last moment, Reina pushed Musica off the Silver Ray and used Silver Bonds, causing an explosion in the sky. She died but her silver combined with Musica`s and her soul slipped inside Musica`s silver ray spear, which fell out of the heavens.</description>
<picture>78663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39741" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Jegan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jegan is a member of the Dragon Race in the Demon World, and the younger brother of Empire`s Western General Jade. He is involved in a bitter feud with his former friend Let, because of Jegan`s destruction of their home village and the massacre of their kind, in particular Julia, Let`s girlfriend. In reality, however, Jegan faked Julia`s death, and she became a full dragon who serves as his mindless companion and steed, after she purposely failed her dragon trial to spite him. He uses the "tree" Six Star Dark Bring Yggdrasil, which can absorb energy and manipulate plant life.</description>
<picture>78664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="211" picture="17028.jpg">Kanna Nobutoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39742" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Berial</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Berial is an archduke in the Demon World. A four-eyed demonic bat named Boi Boi often sits on his shoulder. He was the one who proposed to the Great Demon Lord Megido of the Lava and his peers for them to ally with Demon Card, as part of the organization`s ambitious Project: Dark Rendezvous. He uses the Six Star Dark Bring G-Earth, which allows him to manipulate the ground. He appears again after The Blue Guardians are defeated and sends an army of monsters to kill Haru and his friends after Haru had retrieved the final RAVE. Haru kills him with a single hit. This is surprising because the author`s notes define him as the strongest.</description>
<picture>78665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19929" picture="51183.jpg">Tanaka Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39743" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Deepsnow</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Deep Snow is the Northern General of the Empire, but is in reality a double-agent working for Demon Card. He returned to the organization when Lucia became its new ruler, and was chosen as Shuda`s replacement within the Oracion Six. He uses the "flow" Six Star Dark Bring Zero Stream, which allows him to control all that flows (water, wind, blood, etc.), and has also the Dark Bring Type 56 implanted within him when he was an infant, allowing him to tap into his latent power and enhance his physical abilities.</description>
<picture>78666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4587" picture="26895.jpg">Oda Yuusei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39744" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Ltiangle</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4565" picture="26895.jpg">Arima Katsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39745" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Racas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="66" picture="216211.jpg">Bifu Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39746" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Rionette</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39747" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Ron Glace</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19929" picture="51183.jpg">Tanaka Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39748" type="appears in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Zashippe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zashippe is a huge cyclops demonoid with a Shadow Stone, able to swim in ground like water; he is used by King to find Ray Barrier.</description>
<picture>145243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2207" picture="41549.jpg">Makishima Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39749" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Feber</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Feber is probably the weakest enemy ever mentioned by his name. He was the first Demon Card soldier Haru fought. He badly injured Shiba with a bazooka in Volume 1, but Haru punched him with the Rave and defeated him. Shuda later gave him the Dark Bring "Full Metal", which enabled him to turn his skin into metal. He went after Haru again, and was again defeated with the Explosion form of Ten Powers Sword. It is possible Gemma later hired him in Cafe Tsubomi.</description>
<picture>78669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2090" picture="151718.jpg">Toochika Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39750" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Poosya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="274" picture="17101.jpg">Ishikawa Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39752" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Range 70</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4425" picture="26689.jpg">Sugino Hiroomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39753" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Jouko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39754" type="appears in" update="2012-03-12">
<name>Lance</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lance is Commander of the 17th unit of Demon Card soldiers, he wields the Beast Sword, forged by Galein Musica. It allows him to create illusions at his will. His DB allows him to make his illusions real. Somewhat of a psychopath, he captured Elie and injured Hamrio Musica in volume 2, and was defeated by Haru in Volume 3. He was also responsible for killing off Musica`s family.</description>
<picture>83442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39755" type="appears in" update="2012-03-12">
<name>Bis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bis is a Demon Card minion under the command of Lance`s squadron. He is an obese man with a green mohawk, piercing on his head and the word "Death" written on his forehead. While fighting Musica, he uses a giant drill machine that he wears on his arm. Later on in the series after Lance`s defeat, he is seen on a chapter cover begging to Galein Musica. He appears in Mashima`s later series Fairy Tail in a minor role as a random member of the dark guild Grimoire Heart where he is easily defeated by Pantherlily and gets his sword taken from him.</description>
<picture>83439.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4425" picture="26689.jpg">Sugino Hiroomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39756" type="appears in" update="2012-04-01">
<rating votes="1">1.32</rating>
<name>Go Rockwell</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39757" type="appears in" update="2012-04-01">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Rosa Splash</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>84986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39758" type="appears in" update="2012-05-12">
<name>Schneider</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Schneider is a very swift hired assassin of Shuda that sent to kill the current Rave Master, he acted like a normal doctor to insert enough paralysis poison for Haru not to move.</description>
<picture>87697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39759" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Pumpkin Doryu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pumpkin Doryu is the founder of the Doryu Ghost Squad and holder of its top position. He holds one of the five True dark brings, a piece of Sinclaire itself with powers greater than the ordinary Dark Bring. His dark bring, Vampire gives him complete control over the forces of gravity and repulsion which lets him, at the most extreme, pull physical matter into darkness (which he did to Musica). He first fought Haru in Volume 15, and he nearly killed Haru with the Twilight sword. The second time they fought in Volume 17, Haru seemed to have gained some new strength (he might have gotten stronger as a result to losing the first match), and he destroyed the Twilight sword and the Jet Black sword. Haru also received some help from his friends, but it ended up being a one on one fight between Haru and Doryu. Haru was able to overcome the pain of his earlier injuries, destroyed Doryu`s most powerful spell (which would have killed Haru and all of his friends), broke through the Vampire`s power of repulsion, and he killed Doryu with the Million Suns. After this point, Haru was stronger than Doryu.</description>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39760" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<name>Franken Billy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39761" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<name>Lilith Nina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4923" picture="51991.jpg">Tateno Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39762" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Hito Ookami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="4749" picture="27700.jpg">Katsuragi Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39763" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Ogre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ogre was an opponent of the rave warriors and he is the Leader of the Onigami.</description>
<seiyuu id="637" picture="151727.jpg">Matsumoto Dai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39764" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Jade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jade is Jegan`s older brother and is mayor of a village.</description>
<seiyuu id="5650" picture="30095.jpg">Murozono Takehiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39765" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Slade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="5626" picture="29921.jpg">Fujimoto Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39766" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="1">1.32</rating>
<name>Solasido Sharpner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82479.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39767" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="2">2.80</rating>
<name>Remi Sharpner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78674.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2036" picture="23185.jpg">Arishima Moyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39768" type="appears in" update="2013-08-17">
<rating votes="1">1.32</rating>
<name>Fua</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fua is One of the warriors in Ray Barrier City who alongside Remi and Solasido assist the Rave Warriors during the battle at the Tower of Din.</description>
<picture>141582.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1942" picture="50629.jpg">Amada Masuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39769" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<name>Julius Rayfield</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2936" picture="75539.jpg">Sasanuma Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39770" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">7.39</rating>
<name>Gale Glory</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gale Glory is The father of Haru and Cattleya. He along with King formed Demon Card to protect the people from demons but left because of their conflicting ideals. After leaving Demon Card he met Sakura on Garage Island where they started a family. When Haru was still young, Gale left Garage Island to search for Rave and put an end to King`s corrupt ways. His wife Sakura Glory, who was a native to Garage Island was killed by King as payback for what the Imperial forces did to his wife and son when Gale reported him. Haru is reunited with Gale at the Tower of Din where they together fight King. After the battle both Gale and King die settling their dispute.</description>
<picture>78675.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39771" type="appears in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="2">3.92</rating>
<name>Sakura Glory</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haru`s and Cattleya`s mother and Gale`s wife, she was killed by King as part of his revenge against her husband for what he had done to his wife and son (even though he didn`t know his son was alive).</description>
<picture>82478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3914" picture="224310.jpg">Kikuchi Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39772" type="appears in" update="2012-03-12">
<rating votes="2">1.32</rating>
<name>Nakajima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakajima is a strange lifeform that lives stuck to the outside wall of Cattleya and Haru`s house. He looks like a flower, but claims that the petal-looking things ringing his round face are feathers. His favorite (and perhaps only) hobby is "golling".</description>
<picture>83445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39773" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">1.32</rating>
<name>Genma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Genma is the owner of Cafe Tsubomi on Garage Island. He is good friends with Gale and the rest of the Glory family and has a habit of constant laughing.</description>
<picture>78676.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39774" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Rize</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rize is the man who taught Hamrio Musica Sliver-claiming. He was originally going to steal the Silver Ray because it was too dangerous to fall in the wrong hands but failed as someone already stole it before him. On his way back, he found and took Musica in after the rest of family was slaughtered by Lance.</description>
<seiyuu id="3161" picture="69050.jpg">Yamanoi Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39775" type="appears in" update="2012-03-12">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Hebi Shirubetto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hebi is Musica`s right-hand man and second in command of the Silver-Rhythm gang which are a motley crew of thieves and brigands, but are nonetheless loyal to Musica. He and the rest of the Silver-Rhythm gang occasionally join and help out Haru`s group with their state-of-the-art air ship, the "Silver Knights" gained from ill-gotten wealth. He also knows a lot about animals. However, when questioned as to what Plue was, he was clueless and turned away. He has a tattoo on his head that says "snake". Hebi and the rest of the gang appear during the final fight to assist Haru and gang in reaching the Star Memory.</description>
<picture>83440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39776" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Lasagna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lasagna is Chino`s mother who runs the hotel in Ska Village.</description>
<picture>78677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16799" picture="186162.jpg">Tezuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39777" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Chino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chino is a boy from Ska Village who blamed the constant raining caused by Go &amp; Rosa on frogs and tried hurting them. His mother Lasagna runs the hotel in Ska Village.</description>
<picture>78678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4923" picture="51991.jpg">Tateno Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39778" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Melodia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Melodia is an old girlfriend of Hamrio Musica. He meets back up with her when the gang prepare to leave Song Continent.</description>
<picture>78679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4923" picture="51991.jpg">Tateno Kanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39779" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="5">1.56</rating>
<name>Wonderful Gotche</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wonderful Gocche is the leader of the Jiggle Butt Gang. He and his gang meet Haru while attempting to rob a train.</description>
<picture>87378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39780" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="5">1.49</rating>
<name>Karen Borg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39781" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="5">2.13</rating>
<name>Marco Berunju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39782" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Celia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celia is a beautiful mermaid who falls deeply in love with Haru Glory, much to Elie`s displeasure. The group meets her on their journey as she was returning to her hometown. She had been on a year long mission to find a light shell. Her magic is strong, but useless in the absence of water. She is the younger sister of the Queen of the Mermaids.</description>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39783" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Hole</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hole is a girl who detests Demon Card and helps out those who are targeted out of the Hip Hop Town through underground tunnels.</description>
<picture>78680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16799" picture="186162.jpg">Tezuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39784" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Pearl</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="39785" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Tsuyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20322" picture="186181.jpg">Shiga Katsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39786" type="appears in" update="2011-12-18">
<name>Soleil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78682.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="389" picture="56097.jpg">Okano Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42333" type="appears in" update="2012-03-12">
<name>Demon Card</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="42334" type="appears in" update="2012-03-12">
<name>Doryu Ghost Squad</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="42335" type="appears in" update="2012-03-12">
<name>Onigami</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="44418" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="1">1.34</rating>
<name>Ketsupuri-dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>87377.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="45765" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-06-11">
<rating votes="2">7.39</rating>
<name>Hamrio Musica</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>89325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="20316" picture="53453.jpg">Amano Erika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61061" type="appears in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Gnett</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2207" picture="41549.jpg">Makishima Naoki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="61062" type="appears in" update="2013-11-02">
<name>Shinegun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>145245.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="91813" type="appears in" update="2017-10-17">
<name>Yajirushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4565" picture="26895.jpg">Arima Katsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92621" type="appears in" update="2017-12-03">
<name>Ootokage</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93351" type="appears in" update="2018-01-23">
<name>Uranai no Rouba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="804" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">爆炎のシュダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exploding Shuda</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shuda, le seigneur infernal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bakuen no Shuda</title>
<summary>Haru, Elie, and Plue try to depart from the town, but end up underground meeting Hole, who resides underground. Meanwhile, Shuda tracks them down and battles Haru. After being defeated and having his Shadow Stone destroyed, Shuda leaves with knowledge about Haru`s father, Gale Glory. Haru offers to help Elie recover her memory, if she helps him destroy the Shadow Stones.
Source: wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="805" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レイヴを継ぐ者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Inheritor of Rave</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Rave Master</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rave o Tsugu Mono</title>
<summary>In Hip Hop Town, Haru Glory stumbles upon Elie, while trying to find Plue. Plue ends up finding Elie, but is soon taken to a dog race. Haru and Elie finds Plue, but encounters Georco, who is able to turn his body into smoke. Haru defeats Georco, using the power of the Rave.
Source: wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="806" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の鍛冶屋 ムジカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Legendary Blacksmith Musica</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Musica, le forgeron légendaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Kajiya Musica</title>
<summary>While walking in a desert, Haru and Elie encounter Hedara Musica of the Silver Rhythm Gang, due a misunderstanding. Later on, Haru and Elie arrive at Punk Street to fix Haru`s broken sword from his battle with Shuda. However, Haru is unaware that Musica was the person he had met in the desert. An old man, named Garein Musica, attempts to fix Haru`s sword. After Elie finds the other Musica, Bis arrive to confront them. The three of them defeat Bis, while Garein has possession of the Rave.
Source: wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="807" update="2012-03-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">雷鳴の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory of Thunder</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs d`orage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raimei no Kioku</title>
<summary>As they all continue to head toward Experiment City, a thunderstorm begins to downpour. The sight of thunder stirs up Elie`s memory. They stop at a hotel in Ska Village for Elie to get some rest. Later on, she takes a hot shower to relax. The hotel manager, Lasagna, explains that the thunderstorm has been occurring for five years nonstop. Her son, Chino, believed that the frogs in the town causes this thunderstorm. However, it was really caused by Go, one who control thunder. Haru leaves to fight Go, and Elie leaves to recover her memory, as they both head toward Thunder Mansion.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="808" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活! テン・コマンドメンツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Restoration! Ten Commandments</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ten Commandments réparée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu! Ten Commandments</title>
<summary>Garein repairs Haru`s sword, making it stronger than before. Meanwhile, Musica finds Lance holding Elie captive. He then is faced against Bis, who is furious from his previous defeat. Lance disables Bis for destroying his headquarters. Lance battles Musica, wielding a sword of beast illusions, being able to defeat Musica. Haru arrives just in time to save Elie from death. Lance uses his beast illusive sword on Haru, but was unsuccessful in his attack. However, he summons a beast from the Shadow Stone engraved in the sword.
Source: wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="809" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">獣剣の男 ランス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Man of Beast Sword, Lance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Lance, le maître de l`épée bestiale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juuken no Otoko Lance</title>
<summary>When Lance finds Elie and attempts to kidnap her, Musica arrives to intervene but fails to defeat him. Meanwhile, Haru finds out that Garein is working for the Shadow Guard. Haru remembers when he first met Shiba, and how he first had the responsibility to search for the Shadow Stones. Haru and Musica plan to rescue Elie.
Source: wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="810" update="2012-06-11">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の暗殺者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Assassin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le tueur mystère</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Ansatsusha</title>
<summary>Schneider gets Haru, Elie, Plue, and Griff lost in the caves and tunnels of Tremolo Mountain. While they decide to rest for a while, Schneider attempts to murder Haru. Much to his chagrin, he is stopped by Musica in the disguise of a Shadow Guard. Musica explains that he came to Tremolo Mountain to take the Rave Stone for himself. Haru then has a match against Musica, but Elie intervenes. Musica decides to help the others in finding the Rave Stone. Plue helps them find a secret passageway. An inception on a wall, written in an ancient language tells that the Rave Stone is inside. Once inside, they are confront by a Knight of the Blue Sky.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="811" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プルーのひみつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plue`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Plue est tout mou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Plue no Himitsu</title>
<summary>As Haru, Elie, and Plue prepare to head the north, they are to be escorted by Griffon Kato. Griff informs them that they will stop at Ska Village as a checkpoint, then continue on their way toward Experiment City. While at a nearby hot spring, Elie decides to twist Plue`s nose to discover anything unusual, which leads to Plue deflated. Haru and Elie make an effort to return Plue to normal. However, this results in an argument between the two. Griff tells Elie to go to a nearby strawberry valley to retrieve a special strawberry that will help cure Plue. After retrieving the strawberry, she is then confronted by an insect monster. Haru arrives to defeat the insect monster and to rescue Elie. When they went back, they saw that Plue was already back to normal. However, Elie realizes that the hot spring caused Plue`s deflation.
Source: wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="812" update="2012-05-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">星降りの地</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Meteor Crash site</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des météorites</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshifuri no Chi</title>
<summary>Haru, Elie, Plue, and Griff make their way toward Tremolo Mountain in search of the Rave Stone. However, they soon realize that Shuda is there as well. Plue runs off in a nearby forest, and Haru sets out to look for Plue. Haru then encounters Deerhound, a talking bear, who gives him advice upon entering Tremolo Mountain. Meanwhile, Elie took suits from a few of the Shadow Guard as a disguise for her and Haru to gain access inside Tremolo Mountain. Once inside the caves and tunnels, Haru and Elie get caught in their disguise. They quickly run for cover, but they end up in a dead end. Haru and Elie jumps off a cliff, using Griff`s ability to shape-shift to land safely. The flowers on the ground nearby emit pollen that causes them to sleep. Schneider, a doctor though really an assassin, inflames the flowers, seemingly saving them. Schneider offers to help them find the Rave Stone.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="813" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀の律動[シルバリズム]のムジカ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Silver Rhythm`s Musica</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Musica et le Silver Rythm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Silverhythm no Musica</title>
<summary>The Silver Rhythm Gang break into a city bank. Using Musica`s help, they manage to get inside the safe. They are unable to find a silver object, known as the Silver Ray, among the gold bars and dollars, much to their chagrin. Hebi, second-in-command of the Silver Rhythm Gang, finds Plue in his bag, which results in setting off the alarm. Hebi and Plue are in custody, and Musica turns himself in, having a plan to break out. They manage to escape, but the police are out to search for them. It is revealed that Garein is Musica`s grandfather. To prove that, Garein shows the Musica family tattoo on his right arm. But Musica doesn`t have the tattoo on the same arm, as it is revealed later on that he has it on his left arm. Garein informs Haru and Elie that there is a Rave Stone that was located in the north.
Source: wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="814" update="2012-04-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラストシーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Scene</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La scène finale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Last Scene</title>
<summary>Haru must destroy the Shadow Stone place in the middle of Go`s hammer. Elie memory is jogged once again, which causes her to throw Plue into the hammer, breaking the Shadow Stone and the hammer. Due to this, Go is asked to stop the rain. He brings out a machine that caused the rain, having six unlabeled buttons. Since Go doesn`t remember which button stops the rain, Plue pushes one of them, being successful. As Haru, Elie, Plue were about to leave, Go mentions to them about Sieg Hart, who is an elemental master, the person in Elie`s memory. Ska Village returns to normal, with a clear blue sky. Meanwhile, Shuda is searching for a Rave Stone in Tremolo Mountain.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="815" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着! 勝利の爆発の剣(エクスプロージョン)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conclusion! The Victory Explosion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La victoire d`explosion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku! Shouri no Explosion</title>
<summary>Haru hesitates as he is able to charge into Garein and Lance with his sword. Haru runs and jumps onto Garein and aims for the Shadow Stone engraved in Lance`s sword, thereby destroying it. Haru defeats Lance afterward by knocking the sword out of his hands. Lance surrenders, begging for his life to be spared. However, he attempts to kill Haru, but to no avail. Haru then decides to destroy Lance`s sword. The Shadow Guard attempts to attack, but they are stopped by Musica. Then the Imperial Guards infiltrate Lance`s headquarters, only to find the Shadow Guard defeated.
Source: wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="816" update="2012-04-01">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダンシング・ヒーロー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dancing Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dancing Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dancing Hero</title>
<summary>Elie arrives at Thunder Mansion. Go mistakes Elie as the Rave Master. Go shows off his super strength and his good looks, which doesn`t seem to impress Elie. Haru arrives at the Thunder Mansion, accidentally knocking Go unconscious. Rosa, able to make males dance uncontrollably, explains to Haru that Go is starring her in a movie in which is rains continuously. Elie and Rosa engage in a battle, tonfa blasters against chain sword. Rosa`s chain sword becomes out of control, and Elie prevent it from doing any further damage. Go obtains consciousness and accidentally punches Rosa, blaming it on Haru. He then prepares to battle Haru, who happens to be worn out from constant dancing.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="817" update="2012-03-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! ムジカのふたつの剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confrontation! The Showdown of Musica`s Swords</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les deux épées de Musica</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Musica no Futatsu no Ken</title>
<summary>A flashback reveals how Lance possessed the Shadow Stone that would be engraved in the sword. Haru uses the power of the Rave Sword to fight off the beast illusions from Lance`s sword. Plue gets in the middle of their fight to intervene, but then falls victim to the beast illusions. Haru tries to figure out Lance`s weakness, but to no avail. Garein shows up to restrain Lance, with the help of Plue. Garein tell Haru to stab them both in order to defeat Lance.
Source: wiki</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="828" update="2012-06-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第2のレイヴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The 2nd RAVE</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le second Rêve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 2 no Rave</title>
<summary>The Knight of the Blue Sky happens to be Deerhound, who is not convinced that Haru is the Rave Master. To prove that he is the Rave Master, he must fight against Deerhound, showing his skills of the Rave Stone. Deerhound explains that he was human in the past, fighting alongside Shiba to destroy all the Shadow Stones. Deerhound then shows Haru the graveyard of all the Symphonia warriors that risked their lives to destroy the Shadow Stones. Deerhound gives Haru the Rave of Knowledge, but Deerhound is then stabbed by Schneider. Haru uses the Rave of Knowledge to defeat Schneider. Deerhound tell that Haru should collect all the Rave Stones to unlock all the powers the sword contains. Haru swears to obtain peace by the power of the Rave Stones, and Deerhound returns to his grave.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="829" update="2012-08-16">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決闘! バニッシュフィールド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel! Vanish Field</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat : le ring invisible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kettou! Vanish Field</title>
<summary>Shuuda appears, demanding for the Rave of Knowledge. He then begins to destroy the graveyard of all the Symphonia warriors, resulting in the collapse of Tremolo Mountain. While Shuda faces off against Shuuda on an invisible floating platform, Elie and Musica are interfered by Poosya and Rugar on the ground. Shuda explains that Gale was a member of the Shadow Guard, which surprises Haru. Shuuda then starts attacking Elie and Musica, using the Explosive Flame Ballet, to aggravate Haru. Elie becomes unconscious from the attack.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="830" update="2012-08-26">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">3173の女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girl #3173</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille aux chiffres 3 1 7 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">3173 no Onna</title>
<summary>Haru, Elie, Musica, Plue, and Griff go to the beach to have some fun. They then all go to the Symphonia Museum, where there is rumors about the legend of the Rave Master. There are paintings that depict Shiba and Plue fifty years ago. Later on, Elie begins to experience dizziness, as she unwillingly leads herself in a room displaying a portrait that resembles her, seeing that her name is Resha Valentine. She then remembers that she visited Resha`s grave. Meanwhile, Sieg Hart says to Reina that he must kill Elie since she has the power of Etherion, even though he was assigned to kill Haru. Sieg Hart then senses Elie`s presence and begins to look for her from the sky. Haru, Musica, Plue, and Griff encounter a fortune teller than predicts a bad fate for Elie. Elie wanders off in the city, in tears of her memory.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="831" update="2012-08-16">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラプソディア爆発5秒前</title>
<title xml:lang="en">5 Seconds Until Rhapsodia Explodes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rhapsodia : cinq secondes avant l`explosion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rhapsodia Bakuhatsu Go-byou Mae</title>
<summary>In the underground base, Musica soon realizes that Rugar preventing the self-destruct sequence from being cancelled. Haru lands in the base, badly wounded. Haru, Elie, Musica, Plue, and Griff manage to find an old war plane, flying off seconds before self-destruction. The plane capacity, however, is overweighted, as it dives into the forest. Fortunately, Hebi comes to the rescue at the last second. Jegan and Reina are introduced. The two discuss with Sieg Hart about Shuuda`s failure to obtain the Rave of Knowledge, and the assignment for the annihilation of Haru. Meanwhile, Haru, Elie, Musica, Plue, and Griff go to a hotel to relax and then to a restaurant to eat.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="832" update="2012-08-16">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シュダ 天空に散る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shuda Falls through the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La défaite de Shuda dans le ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuda Tenkuu ni Chiru</title>
<summary>Haru and Shuuda continue their battle, while Musica fights against Poosya and Rugar alone. Rugar uses his Delta Cannon and Poosya uses his Glue Tear in combination, putting Musica on edge. Elie wakes up to distract Poosya and Rugar, enabling Musica to defeat them both. Haru figures out that Shuda cannot use the Explosive Flame Ballet at close range, since it explodes at the area around the target. However, Shuuda uses the Explosive Flame Ballet regardless, causing a massive explosion. Meanwhile, Elie, Musica, Plue, and Griff finds an underground base, where Poosya and Rugar were hiding. Rugar sets the underground base to self-destruct. Later on, as both Haru and Shuda are weakened, Haru defeats Shuuda, using all the strength he can muster. As Shuuda admits defeat, his launches himself from the floating platform, by using the Explosive Flame Ballet to explode his arm.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="833" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼天四戦士クレア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One of the 4 Azure Sky Warriors, Clea</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Claire, la guerrière du ciel bleu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souten Yon Senshi Clea</title>
</episode>
<episode id="834" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第5の剣 ブルークリムゾン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The 5th Sword, Blue Crimson</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La cinquième épée, Blue Crimson</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 5 no Ken Blue Crimson</title>
</episode>
<episode id="835" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファイナルカウントダウン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Countdown</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le compte à rebours final</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Final Countdown</title>
</episode>
<episode id="836" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦慄! 王宮守五神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fear! The 5 Guardians of the Royal Palace</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les cinq dieux protecteurs du palais royal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senritsu! Oukyuu Shugoshin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="837" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔人の頭ゲイル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Head of Demons, Gale!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gale, le chef des Majin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majin no Atama Gale!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="838" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bonds of Fate</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les liens du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Kizuna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="839" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">結界の都 ラーバリア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Barrier Capital Lavaria</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Larvaria, la ville barrière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kekkai no Miyako Lavaria</title>
</episode>
<episode id="840" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大強盗! ケツプリ団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Robbers! Ketsupuri Gang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Voleurs professionnels : le clan des fesses dodues</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daigoutou! Ketsupuri Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="841" update="2013-04-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらばソング大陸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Song Continent</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu continent Song</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Song Tairiku</title>
<summary>Haru, Elie, Musica, Plue, and Griff head to Blues City. They are to take a train to Lyric Continent, however the train scheduled was robbed by the Big Butt Bandits, who are planning to go to Lyric Continent as well. Musica explores the city, reminisces on his memories there. He reunites with Melodia, spending the day together. Musica is caught between going with Haru and Elie to Lyric Continent, or staying with Melodia at Blues City. Musica ultimately chooses to go to Lyric Continent.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="842" update="2013-01-14">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エリーとの約束</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Promise With Elie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma promesse à Elie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Elie to no Yakusoku</title>
<summary>Reina comes after Haru, using Spear Rain. She attacks Haru multiple times, but Haru stands his ground. Musica attempts to fight her, however Jegan arrives to interrupt the fight and summon her back to headquarters. Sieg Hart explains that Reina and Jegan, are part of the Oracion Six, a group of elite warriors and leaders of the Shadow Guard. He requests they Haru and the others should go to Lyric Continent and acquire the Rave of Combat. Meanwhile, the Oracion Six will be summoned for a meeting at headquarters.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="843" update="2012-12-11">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エーテリオン覚醒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Etherion`s Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le réveil d’Æthelion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Etherion Kakusei</title>
<summary>Haru is trapped in the Altealice. He encounters an illusion of Sakura Glory, his mother, as she changes into a pillar of fire. He then encounters an illusion of Cattleya Glory, his sister, as she changes into a pool of water. This traumatizes Haru. Reina stabs Sieg Hart with her sword, calling him a traitor. Musica, Plue, and Griff find Sieg Hart and Reina, asking for the whereabouts of Haru and Elie. Surprisingly, Elie entered the Altealice, spoiling Sieg Hart`s plan to keep them both separated. Elie tries her best to snap Haru out of his traumatic state. Altealice is destroyed after Elie comes in contact with Haru, awakening the power of Etherion. Haru uses his sword on Elie to seal the power of Etherion.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="844" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">RAVE誕生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Birth of Rave</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La naissance du Rave Master</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rave Tanjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="845" update="2012-11-04">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">封印の剣 ルーンセイブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sword of Sealing, Runesave</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`épée du sceau Lune Save</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuuin no Ken Runesave</title>
<summary>Haru absorbs the power of Etherion from Elie to his sword. This causes his attacks to be very effective against Sieg Hart. Reina remembers why she was ordered to watch over Sieg Hart. Sieg Hart explains to Haru that Elie is an experiment in the Etherion Project. He later explains about how Resha used the power of Etherion to cause a worldwide destruction that happened fifty years ago. Haru vows that he will save both Elie and the world from the power of Etherion, which doesn`t convince the pessimistic Sieg Hart. Sieg Hart then summons Altealice, the element of the universe, to alter time and space into nothingness. Musica, Plue, and Griff continue to search for Haru and Elie. Elie wakes up from her comatose state.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="846" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">星の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stellar Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mémoire des étoiles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi no Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="847" update="2012-10-11">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! ハル対ジークハルト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash! Haru vs. Sieghart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Combat : Haru contre Sieg Hart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Haru tai Sieghart</title>
<summary>As Sieg Hart prepares to deliver the final blow to Elie, Haru arrives to intervene. Meanwhile, the fortune teller finds Musica, Plue, and Griff to warn them that the future is unfortunate for Haru and Elie, beginning the search for them. Haru reminisces on his memories of Elie since they first met. Elie becomes comatose, due to her weakened state. Haru struggles as he engages in combat against Sieg Hart. Sieg Hart remembers why he was assigned to kill Haru.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="848" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば友よ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye My Friend!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu, mon ami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Tomo yo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="849" update="2012-09-16">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エリーの悲劇...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Elie`s Tragedy...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La tragédie d’Elie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Elie no Higeki</title>
<summary>Sieg Hart finds Elie, not knowing how he is connected to her past. Sieg Hart explains to Elie that she is an experiment in the Etherion Project. Haru, Musica, Plue, and Griff continue to search for Elie, Hebi informs them that she is with who seems to be Sieg Hart. Sieg Hart attempts to kill Elie using Sinclaire, but the power of Etherion manages to keep her alive until she collapses. Haru goes back to the fortune teller to receive help to locate Elie.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="850" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しき空の向こうに...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On the Other Side of the Sad Sky...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Par delà le ciel du chagrin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashiki Sora no Mukou ni...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="851" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦う理由</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reason to Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une raison pour lutter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakau Riyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="852" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲイルとキング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gale and King</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gale et King</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gale to King</title>
</episode>
<episode id="853" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">デスストーム突破!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charging Into Death Storm!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une percée à travers la tempête de la mort</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Death Storm Toppa!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="854" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケツプリ団の大逆襲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ketsupuri Gang`s Big Comeback</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le clan des fesses dodues contre-attaque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ketsupuri Dan no Daigyakushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="855" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">空中カジノエーデルレイク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Air Casino Edel Lake</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le casino en plein ciel, Edelack</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuuchuu Casino Edel Lake</title>
</episode>
<episode id="856" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決死の路上パフォーマンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desperate Street Performance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Spectacle de rue extrême</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kesshi no Rojou Perfomance</title>
</episode>
<episode id="857" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">0065プルー・レジェンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">0065: Plue Legend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">An 65, la légende de Plue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">0065 Plue Legend</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2202" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲しき銀術師(シルバークレイマー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sad Silver Claimer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La mauvaise fortune du Silver Clamer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashiki Silver Claimer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2203" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜人(ドラゴンレイス)の真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Truth About the Dragon Race</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret de la race des Dragons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dragon Race no Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2204" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">復活!!六祈将軍(オラシオンセイス)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revival of the Orashion Seis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La résurection des Orassionne Sehis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukkatsu! Oracion Seis</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2205" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">降臨ダークブリングマスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter, Dark Bring Master</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’héritage du Darbri Master</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kourin Dark Bring Master</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4433" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦いの果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of The Fight</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une lutte sans merci</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakai no Hate ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4434" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶の扉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Doors to The Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La porte de la mémoire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kioku no Tobira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4435" update="2011-10-17">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来への誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The vow to the future</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un pacte pour le futur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai e no Chikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87808" update="2013-06-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87809" update="2013-06-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121117" update="2013-06-17">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121118" update="2013-06-17">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121119" update="2013-06-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121120" update="2013-06-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-04-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
