<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12524" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-12</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ikemen Sengoku: Toki o Kakeru ga Koi wa Hajimaranai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ikemen Sengoku: Love Won`t Start by Crossing Through Time</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">イケメン戦国◆時をかけるが恋ははじまらない</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ikemen Sengoku: Bromances Across Time</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">美男战国 穿越时空的爱恋</title>
</titles>
<url>http://anime-ikemen-sengoku.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="22091" type="Animation Work">Jinni`s Animation Studio</name>
<name id="5795" type="Character Design">Yamanaka Junko</name>
<name id="41139" type="Series Composition">Kibe Masayuki</name>
<name id="41140" type="Direction">Watanabe Shigeyuki</name>
<name id="50417" type="Music">Itou Keisuke</name>
<name id="50419" type="Original Work">Cybird</name>
</creators>
<description>My name is Sasuke.
I was a college student, but one day I fell into a time slip back to the Sengoku Period.
What`s more is that this Sengoku Period is nothing like what I learned about in the history books...
The much anticipated anime version of the popular romance game "Ikémen Sengoku"!
A high-tension Sengoku comedy interlaced with adorable generals.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="80">2.19</permanent>
<temporary count="80">4.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>228419.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19725</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34337</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anime-ikemen-sengoku.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>イケメン戦国◆時をかける恋</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4631</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360658</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20368</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20909</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2752" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tennis</name>
<description>Tennis is yet another sport involving hitting a ball. Were it not for the copious amounts of grass involved in certain varieties, it seems hard to imagine that people would pay it any attention at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="90401" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Uesugi Kenshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="552" picture="23199.jpg">Miura Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90402" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Date Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35755" picture="131624.jpg">Katou Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90403" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Tokugawa Ieyasu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23805" picture="66166.jpg">Masuda Toshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90404" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Akechi Mitsuhide</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42164" picture="176249.jpg">Takeuchi Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90405" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Takeda Shingen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90406" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Mouri Motonari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90407" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Sarutobi Sasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2487" picture="23183.jpg">Akabane Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90408" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Sanada Yukimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90409" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-16">
<name>Ishida Mitsunari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36495" picture="176250.jpg">Yamaya Yoshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90410" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Oda Nobunaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90411" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Toyotomi Hideyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90412" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-13">
<name>Kennyo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2802" picture="176252.jpg">Shingaki Tarusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188510" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメン迷惑矢文</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen Junk Mail</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Meiwaku Yabumi</title>
<summary>As a spy for the Uesugi forces, Sasuke has been spying on the Oda Forces looking for a way to bring them down for his master. One of his suggestions is the idea of junk or spam mail, basically in an attempt to annoy Nobunaga and his men. The men write hundreds of letters and shoot them off, greatly underestimating the kind of men Nobunaga has in his service.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743091</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188511" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメンヘイメーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen Hey Man</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Hey Man</title>
<summary>At one of the regular meetings of the warlords, Date Masamune appears and wants Sasuke to teach him something new for an upcoming poetry competition. Sasuke teaches Masamune and being a quick study the warlord takes to it instantly. The other warlords are inspired and each try their hand at their own rapping style.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743089</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188512" update="2017-07-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-07-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメン秘密のスケッチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen: Secret Sketch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Himitsu no Sketch</title>
<summary>Hideyoshi wants to put a new piece of art on a lonely looking wall in the palace with Nobunaga as the obvious subject. He comes up with a plan to distract Nobunaga with the assistance of Sasuke, Ieyasu and Ishida Mitsunari. Ieyasu and Mitsunari are supposed to do the distracting while Hideyoshi does the drawing, but nothing quite goes as planned.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743087</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188513" update="2017-07-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメンスマッシュ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen Smash</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Smash</title>
<summary>Sasuke is a college student and a history nerd who has made a hobby out of studying time slips. One day, he slips through one of these time slips and finds himself in the Sengoku Period, although it`s nothing like what he`s read about in the history books. He takes the name Sarutobi Sasuke and becomes a retainer of the infamous Oda Nobunaga. His first mission is to win the confidence of Nobunaga`s other famous retainers, Toyotomi Hideyoshi and Tokugawa Ieyasu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742371</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189027" update="2017-07-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189493" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメンパーティーピーポー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen Party People</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Party People</title>
<summary>With both forces facing off in a series of three challenges on the beach, Oda and his men won the first challenge. The second challenge is a summer time tradition--watermelon splitting! But of course, nothing is traditional with these warlords.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743099</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189494" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメンビーチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Beach</title>
<summary>With things finally coming to a head, the Oda and Uesugi Forces come together at the beach for a final show down. Itching for a fight, Sasuke manages to convince the warlords to participate in a series of challenges to determine who will come out on top.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743097</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189495" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメンは激怒した</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen Are Furious</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen wa Gekido Shita</title>
<summary>Frustrated and fed up with their lack of progress, Uesugi wants to storm Azuchi Castle. Sasuke manages to quell his fury and asks for time in order to negotiate with Nobunaga, leaving Yukimura as a hostage for Uesugi if he doesn`t return. Will Sasuke make it back in time to save his friend?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743095</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189496" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-08-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメン天井裏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen Attic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Tenjouura</title>
<summary>Uesugi Kenshin is not the only one seeking Nobunaga`s down fall. The monk, Kennyo, also seeks revenge on Nobunaga and, thanks to some help from Akechi Mitsuhide, manages to sneak into Azuchi Castle. Things seem to be going smoothly until the attic he has snuck into turns out to be much more heavily fortified than he was led to believe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743093</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190339" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメン戦国◆時をかけるが物語は終わらない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Story Won`t End by Crossing Through Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Sengoku: Toki o Kakeru ga Monogatari wa Owaranai</title>
<summary>The Sengoku warlords seem to have settled in to the fast pace life of the modern age, much to Sasuke`s chagrin. Not all is quite as it seems though as even despite skyrocketing to idol fame, the warlords from a past have had ulterior motives all along. With another storm rolling in, will Sasuke make it to their final concert in time to say goodbye for real this time?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743107</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190340" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならイケメン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye Ikemen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Ikemen</title>
<summary>Sasuke has confessed to being from the future and explains how his whole adventure began. With time ticking away and the lightning flashing at his heels, Sasuke attempts to say goodbye to his companions. However, this may not really be goodbye...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743105</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190341" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-09-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメンサンダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen Thunder</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Thunder</title>
<summary>With Mouri Motonari showing his true colors, Nobunaga, Kenshin, and Shingen temporarily call a truce to work together to take the pirate on. However, the storm that has suddenly rolled in is not any normal storm. Items of Sasuke`s seem to disappear with the suspicious lightning and Sasuke is forced to make a bold confession to his historical companions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743103</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190342" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-09-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イケメン危機一髪!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ikemen Close Call!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikemen Kikiippatsu!</title>
<summary>The arrival of a mysterious, unexpected visitor has all the men on their toes when the stakes are raised. What was a simple series of friendly matches between rivals has now escalated into a life or death clash for the history books!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>743101</identifier>
<identifier>ikemen-sengoku-bromances-across-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
