<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12523" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-03-31</startdate>
<enddate>2018-06-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Lost Song</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">LOST SONG</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">로스트 송</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Kayıp Şarkı</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">失落的歌谣</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14409" type="Other">Lost Song (Shinsaku)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://lost-song.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1255" type="Work">Dwango</name>
<name id="35233" type="Work">Liden Films</name>
<name id="46619" type="Original Work">Morita to Jumpei</name>
<name id="5875" type="Main Character Design">Kaneko Shizue</name>
<name id="46619" type="Direction">Morita to Jumpei</name>
<name id="29401" type="Music">Shirato Yuusuke</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch86002 [Rin] is an energetic girl who loves to eat and lives in a verdant frontier village. Deep within the royal palace in the bustling capital city, the songstress http://anidb.net/ch86644 [Finis] spends her days in solitude. Both share a special power no other person has. A miraculous power that can heal wounds, create water and stir the wind - the power of song. Guided by destiny, the two young women each face an arduous journey with the power of song. The shadow of war looms over the kingdom, tainting even the miraculous songs with the blood of innocents. Loved ones meet their deaths as silent screams echo through a stone prison.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="114">3.79</permanent>
<temporary count="114">5.69</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221688.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19988</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34338</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://lost-song.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Lost_Song_(anime)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>LOST_SONG</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4866</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359355</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20595</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>lostsonganime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3145" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-14">
<name>impact event</name>
<description>An impact event is a collision between celestial objects causing measurable effects. Impact events have physical consequences and have been found to regularly occur in planetary systems, though the most frequent involve asteroids, comets or meteoroids and have minimal impact. When large objects impact terrestrial planets like the Earth, there can be significant physical and biospheric consequences, though atmospheres mitigate many surface impacts through atmospheric entry. Impact structures are dominant landforms on many celestial solid objects and present the strongest empirical evidence for their frequency and scale. In fiction, an impact event is a common way to end the world as we know it, either through the impact itself or through its aftermath, and it may happen either naturally or through human hands; this may include man-made objects, such as space debris and fictional space colonies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3589" parentid="4251" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-04">
<name>multiple protagonists - TO BE MOVED TO PARENT OR DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be moved into its parent tag http://anidb.net/t4251 [ensemble cast], or removed entirely. If the tagged entry meets the updated definition of ensemble cast, tag ensemble cast and delete multiple protagonist. If it does not meet the ensemble cast definition, delete this tag and take no further action.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="86002" type="main character in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="4">9.12</rating>
<name>Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212743.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31768" picture="153115.jpg">Suzuki Konomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86644" type="main character in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="6">8.07</rating>
<name>Finis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91498" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="2">2.00</rating>
<name>Aryu Lucks</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212744.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91499" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="1">5.89</rating>
<name>Al</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20806" picture="182700.jpg">Kuno Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91500" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-07">
<name>Corte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212746.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91501" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Tarjia Hawkley</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3239" picture="225574.jpg">Ito Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91502" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-11">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Doctor Weisen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216088.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91503" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-11">
<name>Bazura Bealmors</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216089.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91504" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Henry Leobort</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37882" picture="173035.jpg">Yamashita Seiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91505" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="2">4.93</rating>
<name>Pony Goodlight</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91506" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="1">3.86</rating>
<name>Mel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91507" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="2">2.00</rating>
<name>Monica Lucks</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36230" picture="242785.jpg">Serizawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91508" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-07">
<rating votes="2">1.00</rating>
<name>Rude Bernstein IV</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11275" picture="65394.jpg">Suzuki Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="197162" update="2018-04-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">堕ち行く歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Depravity</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kötülük Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ochiyuku Uta</title>
<summary>Henry deploys to the front lines, with Rudo forcing Finis to follow. Pony, Rin and Al meet two sisters, Allu and Monica.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197163" update="2018-04-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛慕の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Aşk Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aibo no Uta</title>
<summary>A squad of soldiers with orders to apprehend a young songstress accosts Pony, Rin and Al. Assassins target Finis, who is attracted to Henry.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197164" update="2018-04-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ちの歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ayrılış Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi no Uta</title>
<summary>Rin and Al reach a small town, where they meet another songstress, Pony Goodlight. Henry returns to the capital and finds his superiors eager for war.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197165" update="2018-04-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">癒しの歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Healing</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Şifa Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iyashi no Uta</title>
<summary>Village girl Rin longs to leave her home to perform in the capital, where the songstress Finis must use her powers for the war effort.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197818" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197819" update="2018-04-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197958" update="2018-05-31">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悠久の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Eternity</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sonsuzluk Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuukyuu no Uta</title>
<summary>In the dark future brought about by her song, Finis waits through many lifetimes to meet Henry again and to unleash the final armageddon.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197959" update="2018-05-31">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">終滅の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Mortality</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ölümlülük Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuumetsu no Uta</title>
<summary>Finis and Henry make plans to flee the camp, assisted by Corte poisoning Rudo`s wine. Rin and her friends are heading their way.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197960" update="2018-05-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">別れの歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Goodbye</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Veda Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakare no Uta</title>
<summary>Rin and her group seek out Dr. Weissen, who researches the power of song. Henry and Finis reunite, but Rudo`s noticed their feelings for one another.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197961" update="2018-05-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">邂逅の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Rastlaşma Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaigou no Uta</title>
<summary>On his way back to the capital, Henry is detained by an official who also imprisons Rin and her party. At the front, Finis and Corte are burning out.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="198888" update="2018-06-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">始まりの歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Başlangıç Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimari no Uta</title>
<summary>As Finis sings the Song of Mortality, destruction draws ever closer. While Henry and Bazra`s forces struggle, Pony tells Rin that all hope is not lost.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="198889" update="2018-06-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">無響の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Silence</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sessizlik Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukyou no Oto</title>
<summary>Finis and Bazra return to the capital for the Star Song Festival. Rin tells her friends what she`s learned of Finis`s ultimate plan.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="198890" update="2018-06-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚悟の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Determination</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Azim Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakugo no Uta</title>
<summary>Rin has a series of strange visions about her past. Henry confronts General Bazra while Rin`s friends try to flee.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="198891" update="2018-05-31">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">郷愁の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Nostalgia</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Nostalji Şarkısı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoushuu no Uta</title>
<summary>Rin and her friends finally reach Finis`s position, but they have to sneak into the army camp to meet her. There, Rin learns the truth.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208852" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209196" update="2018-10-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「歌えばそこに君がいるから」Animelo Summer Live 2018 "OK!" 演出用特別映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Utaeba Soko ni Kimi ga Iru kara" Animelo Summer Live 2018 "OK!" Special Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Utaeba Soko ni Kimi ga Iru kara" Animelo Summer Live 2018 "OK!" Enshutsuyou Tokubetsu Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217685" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217686" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217687" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217688" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217689" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special TV CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217690" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Episode Special CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217691" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Episode Special CM 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
