<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1252" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-10-24</startdate>
<enddate>2004-04-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kingdom of Chaos: Born to Kill</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kingdom of Chaos</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">キングダム・オブ・カオス ~ボーン・トゥー・キル~</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.ideaf.co.jp/anime/b2k/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1164" type="Animation Work">Idea Factory</name>
<name id="2160" type="Character Design">Kumazen Takashi</name>
<name id="6270" type="Original Plan">Kuwana Shingo</name>
<name id="7014" type="Direction">Katou Taisuke</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the online game Kingdom of Chaos (K.O.C.).
On Neverland`s Old Continent there is a country called Bjor, which under the command of its present ruler Fract is on a warpath across the land. The country has already taken over roughly 75% of the continent, and next on Fract`s list is Orthozes, a small country that was able to fend off Bjor when it was Fract`s first attempt at conquest. In Orthozes, there is an amnesiac wanderer named Aide who joins the mercenary front in order to protect the country. Alongside Mara, a member of the Crimson Knight guard, and Dino, a mazoku who is considered a killing machine, Aide will find out who he is, and why he looks exactly like Fract.
Source: The Land of Obscusion</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="36">4.52</permanent>
<temporary count="37">6.62</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>1062.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3513</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ideaf.co.jp/anime/b2k/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>753</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>318671</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="13515" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2003-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エイド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aide</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13516" update="2004-06-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2003-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マーラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13517" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2004-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dino</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dino</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13518" update="2006-08-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2004-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">フラクト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fract</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fract</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
