<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12547" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-02-24</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shikkoku no Shaga The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Jet Black Shaga The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Shaga of Jet Black the Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">칠흑의 샤가</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">漆黒のシャガ THE ANIMATION</title>
</titles>
<url>https://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=1105</url>
<creators>
<name id="17263" type="Original Work">Nishikawa Takashi</name>
<name id="27343" type="Animation Work">Seven</name>
<name id="17263" type="Direction">Nishikawa Takashi</name>
<name id="17263" type="Character Design">Nishikawa Takashi</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="103">5.62</permanent>
<temporary count="108">6.69</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>194650.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34388</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=1923&amp;cid=4</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=1105</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=2027</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19753</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2707" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-20">
<name>internal shots</name>
<description>Internal shots are pictures that display the interior of the body of a living being, either through the skin, kind of as an "x-ray" of sorts, or from the inside, as if the camera was also inside. This is generally used during sex scenes to display the inside of any area being penetrated. Those shots may happen either by making an area of the body transparent or by displaying the same area again, but from the inside; the latter method is shown in the picture.</description>
<picurl>213307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2899" parentid="2712" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-04-21">
<name>strapon</name>
<description>Employs the use of an artificial phallus so that the female can engage in the penetrating role during intercourse. Not to be confused with a http://anidb.net/t6455 [double-sided dildo].</description>
<picurl>185955.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3443" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-05">
<name>orgy</name>
<description>A wild gathering marked by promiscuous sexual activity.</description>
<picurl>190911.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4318" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-07-28">
<name>plot with porn</name>
<description>Any adult-rated work where porn is not the only point to it. As in, it has a plot that is not merely an excuse for having sex on screen. Even better if the sex is actually plausibly worked into said plot or used for characterization.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="86633" type="main character in" update="2017-01-06">
<rating votes="2">5.65</rating>
<name>Shaga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196501.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86634" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-31">
<rating votes="1">2.99</rating>
<name>Jorougumo no Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218350.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86635" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-06">
<rating votes="2">6.02</rating>
<name>Yori-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24052" picture="37361.jpg">Oohana Don</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86636" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-06">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196505.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="86637" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-26">
<name>Tokiwa Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6818" picture="177897.jpg">Takana Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86638" type="appears in" update="2017-01-06">
<name>Tairanokiyomori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48064">Tatsumaki Jingorou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86639" type="appears in" update="2017-01-06">
<name>Mura Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39321">Naniwa Tatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86640" type="main character in" update="2017-04-03">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Ushiwakamaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42786">Ichii Naruse</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86641" type="appears in" update="2017-05-26">
<name>Shoukan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="39491">Teruma Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86642" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-06">
<rating votes="2">6.02</rating>
<name>Toyo-hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27978">Matsuda Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86989" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-06">
<rating votes="3">4.90</rating>
<name>Yama ni Sumu Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196507.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="90515" type="appears in" update="2017-07-18">
<name>Okina</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="59404" picture="241807.jpg">Hoshino Kotetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90516" type="appears in" update="2017-07-18">
<name>Sumahi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="59405" picture="241808.jpg">Yano Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90517" type="appears in" update="2017-07-18">
<name>Tomoji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="90518" type="appears in" update="2017-07-18">
<name>Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="57695" picture="231804.jpg">Kagami Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90519" type="appears in" update="2017-07-18">
<name>Hiko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="90520" type="appears in" update="2017-07-18">
<name>Mashira</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="90521" type="appears in" update="2017-07-18">
<name>Kamuro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="90522" type="appears in" update="2017-07-18">
<name>Yatagarasu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205271.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95887" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-16">
<name>Kurenai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17321" picture="23754.jpg">Kaga Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95888" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-03">
<name>Inn Keeper</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218485.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="182085" update="2016-11-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2017-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女郎蜘蛛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jorougumo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196930" update="2018-03-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2018-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kudan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218335" update="2019-06-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2019-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜照物語</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
