<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12562" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-04-13</startdate>
<enddate>2018-09-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Isekai Izakaya: Koto Aitheria no Izakaya Nobu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Isekai Izakaya - Koto Aitheria no Izakaya Nobu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">異世界居酒屋~古都アイテーリアの居酒屋のぶ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Isekai Izakaya: Japanese Food from Another World</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">异世界居酒屋～古都阿伊特力亚的居酒屋「阿信」</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12385" approval="33" total="35">Isekai Shokudou</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>https://r.gnavi.co.jp/nobu/</url>
<creators>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="11283" type="Character Design">Itou Mariko</name>
<name id="4333" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Shin</name>
<name id="7668" type="Direction">Ono Katsumi</name>
<name id="47908" type="Original Work">Semikawa Natsuya</name>
<name id="34369" type="Music">Mito</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr47908 [Semikawa Natsuya] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr47909 [Kururi].
On a deserted street somewhere in Kyoto resides a Japanese style pub called "Izakaya Nobu." But this hole in the wall holds a secret: its entrance is mysteriously linked to another world! Chief http://anidb.net/ch93523 [Yazawa Nobuyuki] and his server, http://anidb.net/ch93522 [Senke Shinobu], have decided to open up business in this distant and strange land, an ancient city known as "Aitheria." Palace guards, craftsmen, merchants, noblemen... Nobu`s doors are open for business, welcoming one and all with a cold beer and a warm meal!
[i]Source: Official page[i]</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="231">5.25</permanent>
<temporary count="231">6.53</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221767.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20594</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34420</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://r.gnavi.co.jp/nobu/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Isekai_Izakaya_"Nobu"</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>異世界居酒屋「のぶ」</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4918</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359038</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21066</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>isekaiizakaya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3119" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>restaurant</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3504" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>sake</name>
<description>Sake, generally referred to as a Japanese rice wine, is an alcoholic beverage made by fermenting rice.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215208.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4610" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-22">
<name>commercial</name>
<description>This title is used to sell and/or promote a real-life product or service. Not to be confused with "product placement" or "subliminal advertising" — this features *direct* promotion for such element.
Depending on the setting, some could even be considered as "animated infomercials".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5779" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-18">
<name>anachronisms</name>
<description>Customs, events, or objects are shown in a period to which they do not belong, e.g. jet planes in medieval Japan.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6028" parentid="2876" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-10-12">
<name>Shintoism</name>
<description>Shintoism presents a blessed being or creature that governs over areas of terrain, general space of existence, or an individual object (be it alive or inanimate). Everything has its own "spiritual essence".
Defined as the earliest Japanese thoughts of an unified religion, the word Shinto comes from the Chinese hanzi "神道", combining two kanji: "shin" (神), meaning gods or spirits; and "tō" (道), meaning a philosophical path or study.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6090" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Norse mythology</name>
<description>Norse mythology, or Scandinavian mythology, is the body of mythology of the North Germanic people stemming from Norse paganism and continuing after the Christianization of Scandinavia and into the Scandinavian folklore of the modern period. The Norse mythology consists of tales of various deities, beings, and heroes derived from numerous sources from both before and after the pagan period, including medieval manuscripts, archaeological representations, and folk tradition. [...]
Most of the surviving mythology centres on the plights of the gods and their interaction with various other beings, such as humanity and the jötnar, beings who may be friends, lovers, foes and/or family members of the gods. The cosmos in Norse mythology consist of Nine Worlds that flank a central cosmological tree, Yggdrasil. Units of time and elements of the cosmology are personified as deities or beings. [...]
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6537" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-09">
<name>beer</name>
<description>A popular alcoholic drink with a relatively low alcohol content. It is traditionally made from malted cereal grains with hops.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="93522" type="main character in" update="2018-04-13">
<rating votes="8">8.71</rating>
<name>Senke Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214504.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93523" type="main character in" update="2018-04-13">
<rating votes="4">7.83</rating>
<name>Yazawa Nobuyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214503.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94363" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Nikolaus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94364" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Hans</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94365" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-08">
<name>Berthold</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214507.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94366" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Edwin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94367" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<rating votes="2">8.71</rating>
<name>Eleonora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94368" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<rating votes="2">6.86</rating>
<name>Eva</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20806" picture="182700.jpg">Kuno Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94369" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Gernot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94370" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Gotthard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94371" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Damian</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94372" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Backeshof</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94373" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Hildegard</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94374" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Brentano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94375" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-08">
<rating votes="2">8.71</rating>
<name>Hermina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94376" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Holger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94377" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Johann Gustav</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94378" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Reinhold</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="177" picture="170981.jpg">Hoshino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94379" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Leontine du Louv</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94380" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Lorenz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98004" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Rolf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98005" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Corona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98006" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Jean-Francois Mount de La Vigny</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98007" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Sentei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98008" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Byakko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1735" picture="31933.jpg">Shimoda Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98009" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Ignaz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98010" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Kamil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98011" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-17">
<name>Bjorn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101970" type="appears in" update="2019-04-08">
<name>Gregorius</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43359" picture="226056.jpg">Tadokoro Hinata</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102632" type="appears in" update="2019-05-03">
<name>Frank</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="436" picture="90853.jpg">Kobushi Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103068" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<name>Eva no Otouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103069" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<name>Eva no Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43794" picture="177499.jpg">Kingyo Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103131" type="appears in" update="2019-06-02">
<name>Wolfram</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40850" picture="188478.jpg">Shimizu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103804" type="appears in" update="2019-06-23">
<name>Raul</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39787" picture="191405.jpg">Nakatsukasa Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104041" type="appears in" update="2019-07-01">
<name>Lukas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="197950" update="2018-04-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめての海鮮丼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Kaisendon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mon premier bol de fruits de mer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Kaisendon</title>
<summary>Ignaz, a wheat broker in the city of Aitheria, is concerned about the timid personality of his sister’s fiancé, Kamil. He hopes the young man will become a person capable of protecting his sister. In order to test his resolve and bravery, Ignaz gives him an assignment: eat raw fish. Specifically, a dish called “sashimi” served at Nobu.
But despite Kamil’s assumption that eating raw fish is dangerous, he finds himself stunned by the beautiful, shining plate of sashimi presented to him…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769631</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197951" update="2018-04-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お嬢様の難題</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rich Girl and the Impossible Order</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`impossible commande de la petite princesse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ojou-sama no Nandai</title>
<summary>Two nobles, Johann Gustav and his niece Hildegard, arrive at Nobu one day. Hildegard makes an almost laughably complicated order. “Something tasty, but nothing smelly, spicy, sour, bitter or hard. And absolutely no potatoes, porridge, eggs, bread, or stew.” Not even the most famous of restaurants in Aitheria have been able to meet her request. 
Just how will Nobuyuki get himself out of this pickle?
He whips out a pot and a strange device that can make fire. What exactly is he up to…?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769629</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197952" update="2018-04-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">若鶏の唐揚げ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Juicy Kara-Age</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Juicy Kara-Age</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakadori no Karaage</title>
<summary>Guard Captain Berthold decides to swing by Nobu with his subordinate, Hans, in tow. There, he orders a chicken dish in order to see just how good Nobuyuki’s skills as a chef really are. In the ancient city of Aitheria, chicken dishes are typically dismissed as universally terrible.
Without a single moment of hesitation, Chief Nobu starts marinating the chicken using a dark colored sauce before dropping them into a pan filled with oil. Berthold can barely hold his appetite together at the sounds of the sizzling meat being cooked.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769627</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197953" update="2018-04-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おでんのじゃがいも</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Potatoes in Oden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La pomme de terre en oden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oden no Jagaimo</title>
<summary>Hans, a palace guard in Aitheria, is taken by his associate Nikolaus to a strange pub known only as Nobu. He steps inside only to find himself surrounded by an exotic ambience. It is here that he meets reticent Chief Nobuyuki and his cute server, Shinobu. Hans anxiously waits to be served, and is eventually confronted with a strange, gold drink referred to as “whatsontap,” and a warm dish called “oden,” neither of which he’s ever seen before.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769625</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198245" update="2018-05-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仕事帰りの豚汁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After Work Tonjiru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigotogaeri no Tonjiru</title>
<summary>It’s a freezing winter night… Only a handful of customers have swung by Nobu, and there’s an abundance of tonjiru left in the kitchen. As Nobuyuki and Shinobu are about to call it quits, they find Nikolaus passed out in front of the pub. They quickly bring him inside and tend to him as he starts telling them about the disaster he faced and the hardships that followed. Just what kinds of painful things has this man been through? What’s his secret to overcoming it all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769639</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198246" update="2018-05-25">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">盗人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Burglar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nusutto</title>
<summary>Upon hearing that Nobu’s been robbed, Deacon Edwin pays a visit to the pub with Nikolaus. Much to their shock, the place is open for business as usual. Nikolaus begins to ask Shinobu questions, and she tells the tale of a small thief that showed up during the day. Just who is this criminal…?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769637</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198247" update="2018-05-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キスの日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kiss Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiss no Hi</title>
<summary>Hans learns from Nikolaus that today is “Kiss Day” at Nobu. But what in the world does that even mean? Could it be that Shinobu…? He swings by, feeling a bit anxious and excited, to find the place swarming with male customers. Shinobu excitedly proclaims that she’s been looking forward to “Kiss Day.” What does she mean?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769635</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198248" update="2018-05-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しのぶちゃんの特製ナポリタン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shinobu-chan`s Special Napolitan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinobu-chan no Tokusei Napolitan</title>
<summary>Gernot is a tax collection agent capable of scaring a crying child into silence. He’ll do anything to milk people out of their tax money. This terrifying man sets his eyes on Nobu. While waiting for Chief Nobuyuki to return to the pub, he begins nitpicking and criticizing every part of the establishment that he can. 
It’s then that he sees a pasta dish that Shinobu whips up for the staff. This is the tale of Gernot’s fateful encounter with the joy and splendor known as napolitan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769633</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199650" update="2018-06-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美女と油揚げ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beauty and the Abura-age</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bijo to Aburaage</title>
<summary>It’s just another day at Nobu, when the crew spots a woman sitting at the counter before closing time. She’s wearing a suikan, a type of outfit that only Japanese nobles wear, and carries a bizarre aura about her. She orders cold sake with abura-age. Oddly enough, she’s never been to Nobu, and yet Nobuyuki and Shinobu both feel like they’ve seen her gloomy eyes somewhere before…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769647</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199651" update="2018-06-22">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">親方喧嘩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Clash of Masters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oyakata Kenka</title>
<summary>Holger, a blacksmith maestro, and Lorenz, a glass crafting master, have been friends since childhood. One day, they run into each other at Nobu and immediately begin to glare at each other. Competitive as always, the two begin to argue about whose order goes better with whatsontap, whose order tastes better, etc… An uneasy atmosphere begins to settle over Nobu…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769645</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199652" update="2018-06-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">招かれざる客</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uninvited Guests</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manekarezaru Kyaku</title>
<summary>Baron Brentano is known as something of a foodie throughout Aitheria. One day, he and his servants drop by Nobu. Damian, one of Brentano’s loyal men, uses a hired bodyguard to force Nobuyuki into closing up shop for everyone but his master. He then demands that he serve ankake yudofu immediately. Nobuyuki turns down the request, explaining that he only serves that dish during the winter. Damian goes on to then order schnitzel. Nobuyuki steps out to get a recipe for it, while Shinobu and Eva remain behind to make sandwiches for the staff, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769643</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199653" update="2018-06-08">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">中隊長の弱点</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Company Commander`s Weakness</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuutaichou no Jakuten</title>
<summary>Berthold is known far and wide as a devil of sorts. There are few in the ancient city who don’t fear him. But even a man as intimidating as he has something he cannot eat: squid. Unfortunately for him, he is soon to meet with a squid fisherman’s daughter for a potential arranged marriage. He comes to Nobuyuki hoping to squash his distaste for squid by trying a multitude of different dishes, but no matter how hard he tries, he can’t even bring himself to take a single bite. Roasted dry squid, squid sashimi, minced squid balls, fried calamari… Nevermind salted squid guts. Just what IS Berthold’s beef with squid...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769641</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201943" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メンチカツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Menchi-Katsu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minced Katsu</title>
<summary>Rolf and Corona run an inn called “The Flying Wheel” together. One day, the two of them swing by Nobu. Impressed by Shinobu’s work ethic, Corona asks her to marry her grandson. While she’s bewildered and flustered by this sudden proposal, Rolf challenges Nobuyuki to a duel to see which establishment serves better meat dishes. Nobuyuki goes into battle with menchi-katsu, determined to win.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774504</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201969" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">中隊長の凱旋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Company Commander`s Triumphant Return</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuutaichou no Gaisen</title>
<summary>Berthold returns to the ancient city having successfully married Hermina. However, things don’t go quite as planned and the couple are unable to move into their new home. Berthold takes his newly betrothed to Nobu and asks if they can watch over her for a bit. Meanwhile, things have gotten busy for Nobuyuki and Shinobu ever since their kabayaki became a huge hit in the city. They’re worried they might not be able to accommodate customers who come in for drinks. It’s then that Hermina says something that could very well lead them to the answer to their problems…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774507</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201970" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仁義なき蒲焼き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kabayaki Without Honor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jingi Naki Kabayaki</title>
<summary>Reinhold’s subordinate from the water transport guild, “Golden Willow Boat,” is found poking around on “Water Dragon’s Scale” turf. Its master, Gotthard, comes to Reinhold asking for compensation, but unfortunately, all they can afford to give up are fishing rights to the river. Supposedly, it’s filled with rich eels, but people say their muddy smell makes them unpopular as food…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774506</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201971" update="2018-07-25">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">密偵とサラダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Spy and the Salad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mittei to Salad</title>
<summary>Jean-François Mount de La Vigny is a spy in the neighboring country of Oilia. He’s on an undercover investigation in Aitheria, the empire’s most ancient of cities. While doing research on food distribution, he comes across a special salad served at Nobu and is stunned. Do people in the empire always get to eat fresh vegetables? His mind is awash with questions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774505</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203225" update="2018-08-03">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三酔人のカラアゲ問答</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Drunken Kara-Age Debate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">San Suijin no Karaage Mondou</title>
<summary>Berthold, Hans, and Nikolaus are all having drinks at Nobu as per the usual. Today, they’re discussing which flavor of kara-age they should order: salt or soy sauce. Berthold prefers salt, but Nikolaus is all in on soy sauce. They both preach about their preferred flavor, but the debate seems to be going nowhere. Finally, the two turn to Hans for his opinion, but where does he stand…?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774509</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203226" update="2018-08-03">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天ぷら盛り合わせ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Tempura Early Summer Mix</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenpura Moriawase</title>
<summary>“Bears of the Flower Garden”   has not once closed since its opening many moons ago. Unfortunately, the sun is setting on the restaurant, and its final days are approaching fast. The regulars sit around with its owner, Björn, celebrating the start of his brand-new life. Nobuyuki sends over some mixed tempura as a farewell gift. The owner enjoys one final time with his regulars, drinking good drinks and eating good food. Nobuyuki and Shinobu, struck by this sight, have an idea.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774508</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203697" update="2018-08-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリアエズナマの秘密 (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of Whatsontap: Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriaezu Nama no Himitsu (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>City council chief Backeshof, one of the best merchants in all of Aitheria, has set his eyes on purchasing Nobu. Shinobu stubbornly refuses his offer, but he responds by informing her that whatsontap is actually an illegal alcohol. If that is true, then that means that they’ve been violating the empire’s law this entire time. Not only could Nobu get shut down for good, but Nobuyuki and Shinobu could find themselves sentenced to death!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774511</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203698" update="2018-08-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女傭兵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Female Merc</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna Youhei</title>
<summary>Léontine, a female mercenary working for the eastern kingdom of Oilia, is on her way north to visit a group of nobles. She takes this opportunity to search for a man she once crossed blades with on the battlefield: the “Devil.” Where does this man find himself now? Léontine says she’s looking to pay him back, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774510</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204361" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">老人と魚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Old Man and Fish</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Roujin to Sakana</title>
<summary>One day, Johann=Gustav swings by Nobu with a dignified looking old man at his side. The older gentleman savors whatsontap with a smile, excitedly trying all sorts of different dishes one after the other. Pickled small horse mackerel, panko-fried Spanish mackerel… The older man is overwhelmed by the multitude of exotic dishes he’s never tasted before. Supposedly, this strange gentleman is Johann’s uncle, but who is he really…?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776891</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204362" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリアエズナマの秘密 (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of Whatsontap: Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toriaezu Nama no Himitsu (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>Judgement day has arrived for Nobuyuki and Shinobu. Gernot runs a thorough investigation into the charges against the pair and discovers that there are lager barrels that have been moved about illegally. Gernot reveals the details in front of those gathered at Nobu. A shocking truth, unveiled!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776890</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="205824" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北方三領邦会議之顛末</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tale of the Three Northern Territories Conference</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoppou San Ryouhou Kaigi no Tenmatsu</title>
<summary>At the behest of the last emperor, the distribution of lager has been approved and made legal. Nobuyuki and Shinobu are thrilled by this news. Gernot drops by for the first time in a while and orders loads of napolitan. While he waits for his order, he starts talking about a certain incident that took place at a recent conference between three northern territories. Something about it sounds awfully familiar…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776892</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="205825" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">古都のエール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ale from the Ancient City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koto no Ale</title>
<summary>Baron Brentano shows up at Nobu one day with barrels of the finest ale in tow. Drinks on the house for all! After going so long drinking poorly stored ales, the wonderful aroma of this new arrival fills the customers with absolute joy. It was these loyal customers that had saved Nobu from its crisis. Six long months have gone by since Nobuyuki and Shinobu opened up shop in Aitheria…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776893</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-izakaya-japanese-food-from-another-world</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
