<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12566" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-02-09</startdate>
<enddate>2019-02-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">극장판 코드 기아스: 부활의 를르슈</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">geass3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">コードギアス 復活のルルーシュ</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">Code Geass 復活的魯路修</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Code Geass: Lelouch of the Re;surrection</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Код Гиас: Лелуш Воскресший</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12567" type="Prequel">Gekijou Soushuuhen Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="652565">OK, for someone who waited for this to happen since the original series ended airing on TV, I was quite disappointed, there were so many things I hoped they would achieve and try to resurrect the legend for what he was back in the day, and that is of course " a legend ", but overall, this was a good movie and covered some story of the past, while adding new stuff, I definitely enjoyed it, but to me, Lelouch is more than that.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="744069">Well, literally, this is fan-oriented. The movies seems like compressing a season of 13 episoded into 2 hours, lacking fluency and consistency. Almost every character appeared in this movie and enrolled in the action, which is some good fan service.
The knightmare fighting scenes are good, but not amazing. And the whole quality is more like a summary movie cut from seasonal anime than a newly made movie, which is a little disappointing. The dialogues and actions of characters are a little unnatural. Apparently the staff intended to cater to fans with some classical words from Lelouch, but the dialogues just feel weird.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="428629">first of all what happened to the first trailer in 2017? there is no scene or story to reach out ...i was really hoping that they can build a epic movie for this franchise... i cannot believe what ive watch... well based in what i ve researched it feels like they change the whole story.. it feels like lelouch epicness is not in this movie but it feels like specials...but still recommended for those waited for 10 years after R2....</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.geass.jp/R-geass/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1" type="Direction">Taniguchi Gorou</name>
<name id="665" type="Character Design">Kimura Takahiro</name>
<name id="1573" type="Music">Nakagawa Koutarou</name>
</creators>
<description>The world was united under the reformed http://anidb.net/ch15673 [United Federation of Nations] and enjoyed peaceful days. However, that peace suddenly comes to an end.
As http://anidb.net/ch338 [Suzaku], disguised as the masked man Zero, was accompanying http://anidb.net/ch2000 [Nunnally] on her visit to a refugee camp, he defeated by a mysterious KMF, and the two were taken away.
http://anidb.net/ch337 [Kallen], http://anidb.net/ch15098 [Lloyd], and http://anidb.net/ch2261 [Sayoko] infiltrate Zilkstan Kingdom, the Land of Warriors, following a secret order from http://anidb.net/ch1999 [Schneizel]; however, they are attacked by a mysterious Geass user. They discovered http://anidb.net/ch45 [C.C.] there, whom the attacker referred to as the "Former Head (of the Geass Order)".
Does the Zilkstan Kingdom, the invincible kingdom that once defeated the army of Holy Britannian Empire, wish for hope or despair? It all comes down to the intention of C.C. and the people of Zilkstan royal palace... those who know about Geass.
Source: Mononoke-no-Ko Tumblr</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="282">7.14</permanent>
<temporary count="287">7.26</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>230004.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21251</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34437</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>40315</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.geass.jp/R-geass/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>コードギアス_反逆のルルーシュ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358894</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21721</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>GEASSPROJECT</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Euj8XSLin0c</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=U4-klNK2gCw</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=X8HqcoR0vd0</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=PU3ZgEwUnHs</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=QdBkUSOtUAQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=n7edCA6Snqo</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=NT9RwnZZXow</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=_4XGUWBng80</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="45" type="main character in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="1725">8.56</rating>
<name>C.C.</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>C.C. is an immortal girl who outwardly appears to be little more than 16 years old. She becomes Lelouch Lamperouge`s accomplice when he makes a Geass contract with her. She is willful almost to a fault, usually doing whatever she wants regardless of whether or not it inconveniences others, particularly with Lelouch. She also likes to withhold information, usually telling people just enough to leave them wondering. C.C. has a strong penchant for pizza, especially Pizza Hut`s; she constantly orders pizzas to Lelouch`s house using his credit card.</description>
<picture>15902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103" type="main character in" update="2012-07-17">
<rating votes="1939">8.57</rating>
<name>Lelouch Lamperouge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="337" type="main character in" update="2010-01-23">
<rating votes="930">7.89</rating>
<name>Kouzuki Kallen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kallen Stadtfeld is a Britannian-Japanese girl, who believes herself to be a Japanese person at heart and prefers to be known by her birth name, Kouzuki. Her father is Britannian and her mother is an Eleven; her father comes from a prestigious Britannian family, which Kallen benefits from. Her brother, Naoto Kouzuki, with whom she had a deep connection, was a former leader of her resistance cell before his death.
Kallen is a highly-skilled Knightmare Frame pilot, rivaling the abilities of even the Knights of the Round. She is acknowledged as the best pilot of the Black Knights by enemies and allies alike. Her codename, "Q-1," is the Queen`s starting spot in descriptive chess notation. In Lelouch`s assessment of the core members of the Black Knights, her "Combat Ability" score is 100 out of 100, matching that of Kyoshiro Tohdoh; she also has the highest possible "Loyalty" score of 100.
Even when piloting outdated Knightmare Frames such as the Glasgow, Kallen proves to be a dangerous opponent easily defeating numerous Sutherlands, despite the Sutherland being a more advanced Knightmare. With the radiation arm of her Guren Mk-II, Kallen can take down almost any Knightmare Frame in a single attack should they allow her to make physical contact, and later models also have numerous secondary attack modes for mid- and long-range combat. Her Knightmare Frame is also incredibly fast, allowing her to fight on the same level as some of the most advanced Knightmare Frames in the series.
Outside of a Knightmare, Kallen displays superior fighting abilities. She is nimble enough to swat a bee with a single swipe (and cut it in half), and on two occasions she defeats numerous armed men with little trouble. She is also apparently intelligent, since her grades in school are top of the class despite frequent absences.</description>
<picture>14626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="338" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="646">2.46</rating>
<name>Kururugi Suzaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>14627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1999" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-27">
<rating votes="88">5.58</rating>
<name>Schneizel el Britannia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Schneizel el Britannia is the Second Prince of the Holy Britannian Empire and the Prime Minister of Britannia. He is one of the primary antagonists of the series and a strategist on par with Lelouch, as he is the only person whom Lelouch was unable to beat in chess as a child. Schneizel is ruthless and cold as a strategist, willing to sacrifice lives without a second thought to achieve his ends, but he is also very charismatic and caring toward his subordinates. He seems to show disdain for force when it is unnecessary, as he negotiates a peace treaty with the Euro Universe despite dominating them in every military engagement.
When Lelouch becomes Britannia`s 99th Emperor, Schneizel, alongside the Black Knights and other soldiers opposing Lelouch, confront him. Upon Schneizel`s defeat, Lelouch uses his Geass on him to make him follow Zero`s orders, having anticipated that Suzaku would take on the persona after Lelouch dies.</description>
<picture>16775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="633" picture="33549.jpg">Inoue Norihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2000" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-07">
<rating votes="186">2.77</rating>
<name>Nunnally Lamperouge</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nunnally was born Nunnally vi Britannia, daughter of the Emperor of Britannia, Charles zi Britannia, and Marianne vi Britannia. She was 87th in line of succession to the Britannia Throne. When her mother was assassinated, Nunnally was paralysed by bullet wounds, and went blind due to psychological trauma of witnessing the brutal murder of her mother. Lelouch believes that she may be able to see again someday. After the confrontation between Lelouch and the Emperor of Britannia about the murder of their mother, both Lelouch and Nunnally were exiled to Japan as political prisoners.</description>
<picture>16784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2238" type="appears in" update="2017-05-26">
<rating votes="248">6.19</rating>
<name>Shirley Fenette</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the members of the student council at Ashford Academy. She is also on the swimming team. She shows concern for Lelouch.</description>
<picture>17408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2239" type="appears in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="190">5.76</rating>
<name>Milly Ashford</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lelouch`s senior and the president of the Ashford Academy student council. She likes to play tricks and cause the student council members trouble, but is really a reliable "older sister" to everyone. Her grandfather is the chairman of the Ashford Academy.</description>
<picture>17410.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2242" type="appears in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="89">5.94</rating>
<name>Rakshata Chawla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rakshata Chawla is an Indian scientist who secretly backed the Kyoto Group before becoming the head of the research and development team of the http://anidb.net/ch2353 [Order of the Black Knights], where she was tasked with developing Japanese Knightmare Frames. She has extensive experience in medical cybernetics. Though she is not fond of speaking of the past, Rakshata is known to have studied at the Imperial Colchester Institute. She is fairly laid back in most situations, usually seen laying on a couch when not actively working, and is never seen without her tobacco pipe. She is visibly enraged, a contrast to her normal demeanor, upon learning that http://anidb.net/ch15098 [Lloyd] and http://anidb.net/ch15096 [Cecile] modified the Guren without her consent. She used to be a colleague of Lloyd`s, but parted ways with him. Upon the formation of the http://anidb.net/ch15673 [United Federation of Nations] and the reorganization of the Order of the Black Knights as its military force, Rakshata is designated as the Chief of Science, a post similar to her previous position within the Order. She reacts to the Black Knights` betrayal of Zero with apathy, being more concerned with the aftermath of the affair. She is captured and imprisoned along with the rest of the Black Knights after the fall of http://anidb.net/ch1999 [Schneizel]. Rakshata is the creator of the http://anidb.net/ch8835 [Guren Mk-II] and of its upgrades, and its most powerful weapon, the so-called "radiation wave", is her original idea. She also developed the Gefjun Disturber, a force field generator that disables all sakuradite-powered technology within its area of effect. In http://anidb.net/a5373 [the second season], Rakshata also creates the http://anidb.net/ch15615 [Shinkirou] for http://anidb.net/ch1697 [Zero]`s personal use.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>17413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="634" picture="18161.jpg">Kurata Masayo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2243" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="54">5.90</rating>
<name>Anya Alstreim</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anya Alstreim is Knight of Six in the Knights of the Round and pilots the heavy assault Knightmare Frame, Mordred. She is a quiet and introverted person with a mysterious past and has a Britannian emblem tattooed on her left arm. She holds the distinction of being the youngest individual ever appointed to the Knights of the Round at the age of 15. She wants to be remembered, so she maintains a log/blog which she frequently updates with pictures she takes with her camera-phone. As one of the younger members of the Knights of the Round, she is close friends with Kururugi Suzaku and Gino Weinberg. Suzaku`s cat Arthur also takes a liking to her, though the cat seems to be more affectionate to everyone except Suzaku himself.
In the past, she went to stay in the palace as an apprentice for a proper etiquette and witness Marianne`s death at the hands of V.V.. It is also assumed that it was how Lelouch`s photo was in her camera-phone.
Anya maintains a detached attitude in most situations, usually declaring most things to be boring or dull. In battle, her fighting style reflects her heavily-armored Knightmare; she annihilates her enemies with overwhelming force and doesn`t hesitate to kill disabled enemies. However, this detached attitude also gives her a lack of common sense; she had piloted her personal Knightmare Frame just for the sake of capturing Lelouch`s hat to gain extra club budgets, disregarding the fact that she was piloting her Mordred in a non-combat area and had aroused the suspicion of the Knight Police, as well as forgetting the fact that she is to be a couple with Lelouch if she gets his hat.</description>
<picture>17414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2244" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-11">
<rating votes="152">5.73</rating>
<name>Cornelia li Britannia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cornelia li Britannia is the second princess of the Britannia Empire. After Clovis is assassinated, she is appointed as governor of Area 11. She has two loyal confidantes; Andreas Darlton and Gilbert G.P. Guilford. She has an obsession with her younger sister Euphemia.</description>
<picture>17415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2261" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="56">4.79</rating>
<name>Shinozaki Sayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Originally she was a maid working for the Ashford family, taking care of Lelouch and Nunnally.
She participated in the Black Knights behind the scenes as a spy for Diethard. She went missing after the Black Rebellion, but is currently on duty in secret. She is a person of mystery.</description>
<picture>17438.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2264" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-07">
<rating votes="200">1.40</rating>
<name>Nina Einstein</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Introduced as a bookish member of the student council at Ashford Academy. Nina demonstrates an acute xenophobic reaction to Elevens and is initially intimidated by Suzaku when he arrives in the school. She develops an obsessive crush on the Third Princess Euphemia.</description>
<picture>17442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2265" type="appears in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="84">3.43</rating>
<name>Rivalz Cardemonde</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lelouch`s friend. He takes Lelouch out on his favorite sidecar often.</description>
<picture>17444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="221" picture="17039.jpg">Sugiyama Noriaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2273" type="appears in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="190">7.38</rating>
<name>Villetta Nu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dark skinned elite Knightmare Frame pilot and subordinate of Jeremiah Gottwald, though she is more collected than Jeremiah in battle. She is not of noble blood, but supports Jeremiah and the Purist faction as she believes she can earn a title of nobility through them.</description>
<picture>17449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2279" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="166">6.58</rating>
<name>Jeremiah Gottwald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young officer and one of the "purists" who believe that the Britannian Forces should only consist of Britannians. He pilots the Knightmare Frame, Glasgow.</description>
<picture>17460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11341" type="appears in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="68">6.08</rating>
<name>Toudou Kyoushirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toudou Kyoushirou is the head of the Black Knights` military operations, and an extremely talented fighter in his own right. He earned the nickname Toudou of Miracles for his singular defeat of the otherwise unstoppable Holy Britannian Empire during the invasion of Japan, remarkably managing this feat without the use of Knightmare Frames. This event would later be known as the Miracle of Itsukushima. He was a childhood instructor to Kururugi Suzaku, and is one of the few Japanese people who understands his ideals. Toudou is often seen bearing a katana at his side.
Toudou is initially a member of the Japan Liberation Front, and resigns himself to death when the organization is wiped out. Zero convinces him to join the Black Knights in order to fulfil the promise of victory created by the Miracle of Itsukushima. Like Kaname, he remains faithful to Zero following his capture during the Black Rebellion, reasoning that Zero must have had a good reason not to inform his troops about his plans. He later leads Black Knight forces in liberation operations throughout the Chinese Federation and the Middle East before being named Chief of Staff of the newly reorganized Black Knights which serve as the national army of the UFN. Asahina`s last transmission about Zero`s massacre helps fuel his doubts about trusting Zero, which influences him when Schneizel reveals Zero`s identity to them. After losing a battle with Suzaku and being gravely wounded, he attempts to go back to the battlefield despite Nagisa Chiba`s pleads, but collapses because of his injuries.
Toudou and the remaining Black Knights are made prisoner and later taken away for public execution along with Schneizel and the U.F.N representatives. When Suzaku assassinates Lelouch as the last part of the Zero Requiem, a shocked Toudou appears to realize what has happened, voicing aloud his confusion. Before he can finish the thought, Kallen asserts that the Zero before them is the real Zero. He is last seen together with Chiba in traditional Japanese attire in a photo of Kaname Oogi`s wedding with Villetta Nu.</description>
<picture>33779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4689" picture="170829.jpg">Takada Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15094" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="83">2.81</rating>
<name>Ougi Kaname</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ougi Kaname is the leader of the original resistance cell. He took over leadership following the death of Kallen`s older brother, Kouzuki Naoto (紅月ナオト), leaving his teaching job to do so. He is a somewhat reserved individual who lacks self-confidence, often questioning his ability to lead. However, he is also fairly perceptive, recognizing Zero`s intentions to a degree and even deducing some of the things he keeps secret from the organization. Kaname turns over leadership of his resistance cell to Zero after Zero proves himself the more competent and effective commander. When Zero reorganizes the Black Knights, he appoints Ohgi as deputy commander.
Following a battle in which the Japan Liberation Front is all but wiped out, Ohgi finds Villetta Nu left for dead at a ship dock. He nurses her back to health, and lets her live with him when she cannot remember who she is. Though he knows she has seen Zero`s face (Villetta having said so when he recovered her), he cannot bring himself to kill her or use Refrain to recover her memories. Over time, he falls in love with her. During the Black Rebellion, Ohgi is shot by Villetta, who has regained her memories.
Despite being captured in the Black Rebellion, Ohgi maintains his faith in Zero, knowing that Zero alone can liberate Japan. During the opening ceremony for the second Special Administration Region in Japan, he prevents Villetta from being shot. She suspects it is him, but he doesn`t confirm her suspicions and bids her farewell. Later, Villetta arranges a meeting with Ohgi, intending to kill him to erase her links to the Elevens. Ohgi comes knowing full well what she intends to do, and confesses his love for her. Villetta is captured during an altercation with Sayoko and held hostage by Diethard to ensure Ohgi`s loyalty, but is set free shortly after the second battle of Tokyo is cut short. She and Ohgi help convince the leaders of the Black Knights that Schneizel`s claims are valid. However, Ohgi adamantly insists that Japan be freed if they betray Zero, feeling that he couldn`t forgive himself if any less came of it. Diethard notes that it is in Ohgi`s nature to protect, not lead, and considers his new leadership role a "miscast." During the battle against Lelouch, he has Villetta stay on Horai Island, telling her that he was the first to acknowledge Lelouch and that he doesn`t want to get new lives involved, as she is pregnant. He marries Villetta at the end of the series, and is elected Prime Minister of Japan.</description>
<picture>48321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="231" picture="23486.jpg">Madono Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15095" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="74">1.98</rating>
<name>Tamaki Shin`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamaki Shin`ichirou is the leader of the second special squadron of the Black Knights. He is hot-headed, carefree and the self-proclaimed best friend of Zero, quick to cheer others on when not doing the fighting but rash and impulsive when he`s on the front lines. His rashness is shown to border on recklessness, as he orders the execution of the Ashford Academy student council against Zero`s wishes, though extenuating circumstances prevent his orders from being carried out. He pilots a standard Knightmare during battles, but is rather inept at that; his frame is the first to be destroyed by Suzaku`s Lancelot in the first season and in all encounters after that, Tamaki is rather comically dispatched very early in battle, which ends up hurting his pride in the end of the second season (the only time Suzaku needs more than one strike to defeat him).
Tamaki dreams of being a bureaucrat, and states that if he didn`t have his dream to aim for, he would probably have become a Refrain user. He is initially skeptical about Zero, but comes to be one of his most vehement supporters, particularly after the Specially Administrated Zone of Japan fails. Even after being captured and imprisoned for a year following the failed Black Rebellion, he never gives up hope that Zero will rescue them, despite the fact that Zero was reported as dead.
Tamaki seems to be the most critical of C.C.`s involvement in the organization during the first season, due to her lack of an official position, and accuses her of being Zero`s lover. In the second season, this appears to have been lightened into simple back and forth banter. Tamaki also complains about his own lack of an official position in the second season (what happened to his old position is not revealed), wanting to be in charge of finances in some way (Lelouch relieved him of this responsibility early in the first season when he spent much of their money on frivolous dinners for recruiting). With the formation of the United Federation of Nations and the Black Knights` appointment as its unified army, Tamaki is made the Internal Cleaning Supporter. When Lelouch is exposed as Zero, Tamaki takes it the hardest, being the last to accept that Zero could have manipulated them all this time. At the end of the series, Tamaki opens his own bistro alongside Sugiyama, Minami, and Villetta and is last seen standing right next to Ohgi in Ohgi and Villetta`s wedding picture.</description>
<picture>48329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15096" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="152">5.38</rating>
<name>Cecile Croomy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cécile Croomy is Lloyd`s subordinate in Camelot and one of the Lancelot`s developers. She is a capable scientist in her own right, having designed the energy wing system used on the Guren Seiten and the Lancelot Albion. Cécile is a kind-hearted woman and a good friend to Suzaku, often helping him with homework. She also acts as Lloyd`s conscience, not hesitating to scold him or physically punish him for his unintentionally rude remarks or treating Suzaku as a "part". Cécile is a capable Knightmare Frame pilot, managing to single-handedly hold the entire contingent of Black Knights sent to occupy Ashford Academy during the Black Rebellion at bay using a Sutherland modified with equipment from the Lancelot. Prior to joining Lloyd in the military, she studied at the Imperial Colchester Institute.[4] Following Lelouch`s ascension to the throne, she follows Lloyd and Suzaku and willingly accepts Lelouch as the new emperor. A recurring joke is that Cécile is a bad cook, though no one has the heart to tell her; her recipes include onigiri mixed with blueberry jam and sandwiches made with ginger, sugar and wasabi.</description>
<picture>45009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15098" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-26">
<rating votes="145">6.05</rating>
<name>Lloyd Asplund</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lloyd Asplund is an earl of the Britannian nobility and the head of the scientific research team Camelot, which is responsible for the development of the elite Knightmare Frame Lancelot. To keep from being reminded of the fragility of human lives and friendship, Lloyd immerses himself in science and comes to view people as nothing more than tools — he regards Suzaku, for example, as a mere component of the machine that he pilots. He has a tendency to mock others and is often rebuked for this behavior by Cécile Croomy, his assistant. Prior to joining the military, he attended the Imperial Colchester Institute.[4] Lloyd`s research organization, Camelot (キャメロット?), is an irregular division of the Britannian Military that has permission from Prince Schneizel to operate outside the command structure and regulations of the regular Britannian armed forces.
Rakshata refers to Lloyd as the Earl of Pudding (プリン伯爵?), as pudding is his favorite food. He is engaged to Milly Ashford in the first season, having agreed to the union mostly in the hope that he might obtain the designs of the Knightmare Frame Ganymede. As such, he is forced into doing nice things for her by Suzaku, though Milly breaks off the engagement after she graduates in order to become more true to herself.
After the second battle of Tokyo, he is confronted by a distraught Nina after she realizes the fatalities caused by her F.L.E.I.J.A. Lloyd tells her that she has to make a choice between saving her heart and morals or discard them for science. When asked by Nina if he had already made that choice, he replies that he never had such a problem due to himself being a sociopath. He willingly joins Lelouch`s new regime, remarking that he and Cécile have become "parts" without ever realizing it. He and Cecile are among the few who know the details of the "Zero Requiem", Lelouch`s plan to unite the world. He expresses an interest in studying Lelouch`s Geass, but he is warned off by Jeremiah. He works with Nina and Cécile to create a countermeasure to F.L.E.I.J.A. and assists Sayoko during the rescue of the hostages on board the Avalon (as ordered by Lelouch). He and Cécile are last seen in Ohgi and Villetta`s wedding picture.</description>
<picture>4166.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2605" picture="22592.jpg">Shiratori Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98390" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="1">8.26</rating>
<name>Chestar Fogner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230640.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98391" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Chario</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98392" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="1">8.26</rating>
<name>Berk Batum Bitul</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100331" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-25">
<rating votes="1">8.26</rating>
<name>Swayle Kujapat</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100332" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Shamuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230638.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1734" picture="38029.jpg">Toda Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100333" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Borbona Fogner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230639.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101097" type="appears in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Lancelot Sin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>230643.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101098" type="appears in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Guren Tokushiki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>230644.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101099" type="appears in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Gekkou Kage</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>230645.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101100" type="appears in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Mahoroba Ichi Shiki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>230646.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101101" type="appears in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Mahoroba Rei Shiki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>230647.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101102" type="appears in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Nagido Shu Main</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>230648.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101103" type="appears in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Batarara Do</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>230649.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="101104" type="appears in" update="2019-02-25">
<name>Ged Bakka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>230650.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="183126" update="2017-02-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (2:54)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203767" update="2018-08-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2019年2月公開 特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">February 2019 Public Information Bulletin (0:28)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2019-nen 2-gatsu Koukai Tokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208935" update="2019-02-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2019-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212587" update="2019-02-14">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">2019年2月9日公開『コードギアス 復活のルルーシュ』劇場予告編 第1弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Theater Trailer for "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" Premiering on 2019-02-09 No. 1 (0:30)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2019-nen 2-gatsu 9-nichi Koukai "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" Gekijou Yokokuhen Dai 1 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212588" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">2019年2月9日公開『コードギアス 復活のルルーシュ』劇場予告編 第2弾 (90秒)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Theater Trailer for "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" Premiering on 2019-02-09 No. 2 (1:30)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2019-nen 2-gatsu 9-nichi Koukai "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" Gekijou Yokokuhen Dai 2 Dan (90 Byou)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212589" update="2019-02-14">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-02-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『コードギアス 復活のルルーシュ』TVCM第1弾 ルルーシュ編 (15秒)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" TVCM No. 1 Lelouch Version (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" TVCM Dai 1 Dan Lelouch Hen (15 Byou)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212590" update="2019-12-09">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『コードギアス 復活のルルーシュ』大ヒット上映中PV (90秒)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" Big Hit Currently Screening PV (1:30)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" Dai Hit Jouei-chuu PV (90 Byou)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225225" update="2019-12-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">1分くらいでだいたいわかる「コードギアス 反逆のルルーシュ」その①興道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Learn "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" in About 1 Minute Part 1: Initiation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1-pun Kurai de Daitai Wakaru "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" Sono 1 Koudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225226" update="2019-12-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">1分くらいでだいたいわかる「コードギアス 反逆のルルーシュ」その②叛道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Learn "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" in About 1 Minute Part 2: Transgression</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1-pun Kurai de Daitai Wakaru "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" Sono 2 Handou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225227" update="2019-12-13">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">1分くらいでだいたいわかる「コードギアス 反逆のルルーシュ」その③皇道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Learn "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" in About 1 Minute Part 3: Glorification</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1-pun Kurai de Daitai Wakaru "Code Geass: Fukkatsu no Lelouch" Sono 3 Oudou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225273" update="2020-01-18">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2019-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama [ Ref 1.03 ]</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225274" update="2020-01-18">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2019-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama [ Ref 1.05 ]</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
