<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12574" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-04-04</startdate>
<enddate>2017-10-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ao no Exorcist: Kyoto Fujouou Hen OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Blue Exorcist: Kyoto Saga OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">青の祓魔師 京都不浄王篇 OVA</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">青之驱魔师（OAD）</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12240" type="Parent Story">Ao no Exorcist: Kyoto Fujouou Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="23050" type="Original Work">Katou Kazue</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="8758" type="Direction">Hatsumi Kouichi</name>
<name id="23623" type="Series Composition">Oono Toshiya</name>
<name id="10834" type="Character Design">Sasaki Keigo</name>
<name id="15726" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takada Akira</name>
<name id="10834" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sasaki Keigo</name>
<name id="6722" type="Music">Sawano Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="48260" type="Music">Kohta Yamamoto</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the second chapter of the novel Ao no Exorcist: Home Sweet Home.
The story centers around http://anidb.net/ch85283 [Houjou Mamushi] and http://anidb.net/ch68236 [Shima Juuzou] when they were students studying at the True Cross Academy.
Note: Bundled with the 19th and 20th http://anidb.net/cr23050 [Katou Kazue]`s Ao no Exorcist manga volume.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="286">4.92</permanent>
<temporary count="290">6.57</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>201520.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34465</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21539</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3955" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>DESCRIPTION MISSING</name>
<description>The description for this entry is missing. e.g plot, biography...
Please help by adding it, and remove this tag afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="25808" type="appears in" update="2019-11-09">
<rating votes="107">6.84</rating>
<name>Okumura Rin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The fifteen year-old protagonist of the story, Rin is the son of Satan born from a human woman and is the inheritor of Satan`s powers. His powers were sealed at birth into the demon-slaying blade Kurikara, or Koumaken, by Mephisto Pheles, allowing him to live a normal human life for about 15 years. Rin became aware of his true identity after Kurikara could no longer seal the blue flames he inherited from Satan, setting a chain of events that led to the death of his guardian, Father and Exorcist Fujimoto Shiro, at the hands of Satan who attempted to drag Rin back to the demon realm. Exorcist Mephisto Pheles confronted Rin after Shiro`s funeral with several exorcists, giving Rin the option to kill them all or die. Rin instead demanded to become an exorcist, an idea that amused Mephisto. Rin was then enrolled personally by Mephisto into the True Cross Academy Exorcist School, and since been pursuing his goal to become a Paladin and to defeat Satan. He is currently an Exwire and attempting to gain the title of Meister as a "Knight" (an exorcist who fights with a sword).
Rin can tap into the power he has inherited from Satan through the use of a demon-slaying katana, called Kurikara or Koumaken. The sheath acts as a portal to Gehenna (the demon world) which when drawn returns Rin to his demon form. While in his human form, Rin exhibits a number of physical traits that are signs of his demonic nature, such as sharper-looking teeth, slightly pointed ears, and a black, fur tufted tail (which he keeps hidden in his shirt). As a demon, Rin gains two blue flames that float above his head, long, elf-like ears, and his eyes turn bright blue. In both forms Rin can control incredibly destructive bright blue flames, the trademark sign of anything related to Satan. However, when he draws Kurikara, the magnitude of the flames dramatically increases and often leads to Rin being "consumed" by his own flames and losing his mind. Rin also has a demon Familiar Cat Sith, Kuro, who was initially Father Fujimoto`s.</description>
<picture>91393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25809" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-09">
<rating votes="70">5.03</rating>
<name>Okumura Yukio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin`s younger twin brother. Though Satan`s powers were expected to be split between them, due to the weakness of Yukio`s body at birth, Yukio did not inherit any of Satan`s powers. Yukio received a Mashou at birth from his brother, allowing him to become aware of demons since he can remember. Yukio secretly trained to become an Exorcist since age seven in order to protect Rin (through the help of Fujimoto). While both Yukio and Rin are in their first year at True Cross Academy, Yukio is already an instructor at the Exorcist cram school who teaches Anti-Demon Pharmacology to Rin`s class. It is often stated that Yukio is a genius, having already acquired the title "Meister" in both the Dragoon and Doctor class, while ordinarily most people would aim for Meister in one class (both are still fully qualified exorcists). He is currently ranked a Middle First class exorcist.</description>
<picture>91394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25813" type="appears in" update="2011-05-15">
<rating votes="22">4.94</rating>
<name>Amaimon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25815" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="55">7.38</rating>
<name>Mephisto Pheles</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25816" type="appears in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="38">2.58</rating>
<name>Miwa Konekomaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91399.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25817" type="appears in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="47">4.68</rating>
<name>Suguro Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suguro Ryuji (nicknamed "Bon") is Rin`s rival and the prodigy in the class. He was the child of the Cursed Temple which was destroyed by Satan 16 years ago. Bon takes everything seriously and is trying his hardest in order to become an Exorcist powerful enough so he could one day defeat Satan ( a goal he claims Rin stole from him) and rebuild his Temple. Currently Bon is trying to acquire the title of Meister in both Aria (a person who recites holy texts to kill certain demons) and Dragoon (a person who fights with guns and other heavy artillery).</description>
<picture>91402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25818" type="main character in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="40">2.39</rating>
<name>Shima Renzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25819" type="appears in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="75">4.49</rating>
<name>Moriyama Shiemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiemi is Rin`s class mate and friend. Before she met Rin, Shiemi tended her grandmother`s garden while her mother ran an Exorcist only shop inside True Cross Academy. During her encounter with Rin and Yukio, they were able to discover that Shiemi was having her life force leached out by a Demon. After Yukio exorcised the demon, Shiemi finally decided to become an Exorcist and started to attend class. It was later revealed that Shiemi had talent in becoming a Tamer, as she was able to summon a Greenman Spirit during class. It is apparently a rare talent to possess amongst the Exorcists, where there are only a few who can control demons and fight.</description>
<picture>91400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25820" type="appears in" update="2012-07-23">
<rating votes="63">5.61</rating>
<name>Kamiki Izumo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91396.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33750" type="appears in" update="2012-09-10">
<rating votes="39">6.43</rating>
<name>Kuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93867.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36381" type="appears in" update="2011-10-24">
<rating votes="13">3.66</rating>
<name>Takara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takara is a quiet and mysterious exwire. He doesn`t talk much, but when he does, it`s usually through rude ventriloquism.</description>
<picture>73179.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37582" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-08">
<rating votes="11">4.04</rating>
<name>Suguro Tatsuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19172" picture="189066.jpg">Inagaki Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68236" type="main character in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="8">7.43</rating>
<name>Shima Juuzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shima Juuzou is the second son of the Shima family. As the second son, he has more responsibilities than his younger brothers. He is also an Upper Second Class Exorcist.
Juuzou is first introduced while fighting http://anidb.net/ch85283 [Houjou Mamushi] over their families, and although at first he is advising his younger brother http://anidb.net/ch68237 [Kinzou] not to get into a fight with her, he subsequently gets quite worked up about it, resulting in a physical confrontation. However, he seems to be more level headed and responsible than Kinzou, and less laid back than http://anidb.net/ch25818 [Renzou].
He is serious when it comes to his duties, and has showed concern about his childhood friend Mamushi, as well as taking care of his father. He has a lighthearted side and gets on well with his two youngest brothers.
Source: Ao no Exorcist Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>201478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68237" type="appears in" update="2017-04-05">
<rating votes="5">3.82</rating>
<name>Shima Kinzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85282" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-25">
<rating votes="3">2.67</rating>
<name>Toudou Saburouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toudou Saburouta was one of the Exorcists sent out to retrieve back the Left Eye of the Impure King.
While he and the rest of the team chased after the culprit, the culprit managed to take a little boy as a hostage, confining himself in a building afterwards. http://anidb.net/ch25809 [Yukio] arrived at the scene, accompanied with http://anidb.net/ch25822 [Shura] and http://anidb.net/ch25808 [Rin], and was briefed by Toudou about what happened. They put on a protective suits and entered the building.
After that, it was revealed that the Left Eye of the Impure King was actually the fake and that Toudou already had it and was possessed by a demon.
Sometime later, he was assisted by http://anidb.net/ch85283 [Houjou Mamushi] in stealing the Right Eye of the Impure King and, with that achieved, breaking the seal put on the Impure King and releasing him afterwards.</description>
<picture>201593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="245665.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85283" type="main character in" update="2017-04-05">
<rating votes="14">5.23</rating>
<name>Houjou Mamushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196959.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88972" type="appears in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="3">5.76</rating>
<name>Shima Yaozou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shima Yaozou is an Upper First Class Exorcist, and the Chief of the True Cross Order`s Kyoto Branch Office. He is the head of the Shima family.
Source: Ao no Exorcist Wiki</description>
<picture>201479.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88975" type="appears in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="3">7.08</rating>
<name>Houjou Uwabami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Houjou Uwabami is an Upper First-Class Exorcist at the Kyoto Branch Office.</description>
<picture>201483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88976" type="appears in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="3">4.01</rating>
<name>Houjou Ao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32840" picture="89165.jpg">Nishimura Maya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88977" type="appears in" update="2017-04-23">
<rating votes="3">4.01</rating>
<name>Houjou Nishiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1677" picture="223670.jpg">Matsumoto Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="182675" update="2017-04-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蛇と毒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snake and Poison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hebi to Doku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187485" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スパイ・ゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spy Game</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Spy Game</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
