<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12602" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sakura Quest</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">サクラクエスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sakura Quest</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">사쿠라 퀘스트</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">樱花任务</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10779" approval="5" total="7">Shirobako</anime>
<anime id="7874" approval="4" total="7">Hanasaku Iroha</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="279344">Just a simple reviving of a town in the sticks. The town is however becoming a ghost town, young people prefer to leave for Tokyo and old-timers don`t want changes. Still simple? It even sounds awfully realistic. But then there`s few heroines, each of them with their own problems. There`s a lot happening and I feel truly happy whenever I bring the events back to my mind that I watched the revilitalization of one decaying town in the sticks.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="736643">After a long time, I have seen such a nice and heart warming anime. The name aptly captures the underlying theme of the anime---a joint quest for reviving the lost culture of Manoyama village and finding one`s individual goal in life.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://sakura-quest.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1385" type="Animation Work">P.A. Works</name>
<name id="2243" type="Character Design">Sekiguchi Kanami</name>
<name id="3527" type="Series Composition">Yokotani Masahiro</name>
<name id="6192" type="Direction">Masui Souichi</name>
<name id="44449" type="Music">Know Name</name>
<name id="2243" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sekiguchi Kanami</name>
</creators>
<description>Five girls work in the tourism bureau of their small provincial town. The town revives its "micro-nation" tourism program, which originated from a nationwide movement during Japan`s bubble economy period, and hires the five girls as "monarchs" (tourism ambassadors).
Note: The first episode was streamed on Amazon Japan one day ahead of TV broadcast.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="812">6.54</permanent>
<temporary count="813">7.09</temporary>
<review count="1">7.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>228418.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18916</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34494</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sakura-quest.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sakura_Quest</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>サクラクエスト</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4512</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358995</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20106</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>manoyama_PR</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20979</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07DM898R7</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2964" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>OP variety</name>
<description>Several OP sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique OP for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3149" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-15">
<name>journalism</name>
<description>Journalism is the work and distribution of reports on the interaction of events, facts, ideas, and people that are the "news of the day" and that informs society to at least some degree. The word applies to the occupation (professional or not), the methods of gathering information, and the organizing literary styles. Journalistic media include: print, television, radio, Internet and, in the past, newsreels.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3481" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-04-19">
<name>recruiting teammates</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3921" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>occult</name>
<description>Having to do with paranormal or metaphysical activity and/or phenomena. Beyond the range of ordinary knowledge or understanding.
The unseen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4052" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-23">
<name>treasure hunting</name>
<description>A significant part of the anime centres on the protagonists` search for some obscure artefact or other treasure, an epic adventure and wild goose chase for something unusual and quite valuable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4642" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-08">
<name>economics</name>
<description>Economics is the social science that studies economic activity to gain an understanding of the processes that govern the production, distribution and consumption of goods and services in an economy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4712" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>childhood ties</name>
<description>At least two of the characters share a childhood experience together that plays a part in the plot of the anime. The experience can be anything that ties them together, be it a memory, friendship, promise, tragedy, etc. Something happened to them in their childhood which binds them in a way that is unique.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4811" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-30">
<name>internet</name>
<description>It`s not a big truck. It`s a series of tubes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4874" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>overcoming adversity</name>
<description>Hang in there!
Overcoming problems of different variety.
Sometimes the journey is as important as the goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5705" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-08-18">
<name>butchered foreign languages</name>
<description>In this anime, some characters "speak" foreign languages, successfully making the audience`s ears bleed. That is especially true if the viewer is a native speaker of or otherwise proficient in the languages in question.
The foreigners in the show do not seem to take much notice of the fact that their supposed native languages are being massacred. In fact, oftentimes they also actively participate in the butchering of said languages. That happens, of course, because they, too, are voiced by Japanese people without knowledge of the language they`re supposed to speak, or to pretend to speak at any rate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5962" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>rural town</name>
<description>The rural town is one that is either isolated from what is considered "normal" society or it is so far away from the city centre that there are not a lot of buildings. Some rural towns do not have the technology of the city (and some want it that way), while others just seem to be behind the times. Most of these towns have some sort of farming culture or inn culture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6840" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-07">
<name>social media</name>
<description>Social media are computer-mediated technologies that allow the creating and sharing of information, ideas, career interests and other forms of expression via virtual communities and networks.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="86613" type="main character in" update="2017-03-29">
<rating votes="14">7.75</rating>
<name>Shinomiya Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34984" picture="222849.jpg">Ueda Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86614" type="main character in" update="2017-10-20">
<rating votes="20">6.50</rating>
<name>Koharu Yoshino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43471" picture="200335.jpg">Nanase Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86615" type="main character in" update="2017-03-29">
<rating votes="10">6.52</rating>
<name>Midorikawa Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10759" picture="38748.jpg">Anzai Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86616" type="main character in" update="2017-03-29">
<rating votes="12">7.18</rating>
<name>Oribe Ririko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45090" picture="185899.jpg">Tanaka Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86617" type="main character in" update="2017-03-29">
<rating votes="7">5.96</rating>
<name>Kouzuki Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87621" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="4">6.07</rating>
<name>Angelica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38753" picture="145652.jpg">Mori Nanako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87622" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="6">3.65</rating>
<name>Sandal-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48868" picture="198002.jpg">Vinay Murthy</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87623" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<name>Yamada Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198137.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87624" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="2">2.93</rating>
<name>Oribe Chitose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41981" picture="170979.jpg">Izawa Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87625" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<name>Mino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39583" picture="186257.jpg">Hamano Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87626" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="5">6.29</rating>
<name>Suzuki Erika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87627" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<rating votes="2">2.90</rating>
<name>Kadota Ushimatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198135.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87628" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-13">
<name>Takamizawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88831" type="appears in" update="2017-04-15">
<name>Kadota Kinu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40709" picture="159960.jpg">Makihara Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89281" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Midorikawa Kousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89282" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<rating votes="1">2.58</rating>
<name>Kindaichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32890" picture="89265.jpg">Nogawa Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89283" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Doc</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="204956.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89284" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Shinomiya Takayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2361" picture="228618.jpg">Kusumi Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89285" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Shinomiya Chikako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50178" picture="202375.jpg">Imai Utako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89286" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Suzuki Anji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="578" picture="193571.jpg">Tatsumi Yuiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89287" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Noge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89288" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<rating votes="1">2.58</rating>
<name>Kazushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89289" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Tatsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36770" picture="151722.jpg">Nose Ikuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89290" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Kume Tomoharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89291" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Sawano Moe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89292" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Hayama Taiga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89293" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Sonoda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9288" picture="34149.jpg">Urayama Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89294" type="appears in" update="2017-05-12">
<name>Fujiwara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34070" picture="130103.jpg">Furukawa Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89800" type="appears in" update="2017-06-06">
<name>Midorikawa Iwao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203597.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89801" type="appears in" update="2017-06-06">
<rating votes="2">9.43</rating>
<name>Shinomiya Sayuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89802" type="appears in" update="2017-06-06">
<name>Kumano Katsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89803" type="appears in" update="2017-06-06">
<name>Shinomiya Ganjuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43013" picture="172173.jpg">Furukawa Tomomutsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89804" type="appears in" update="2017-06-06">
<name>Shinomiya Chiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48530" picture="197303.jpg">Arikawa Chie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91029" type="appears in" update="2017-08-19">
<name>Midorikawa Sumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>65325.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="186329" update="2017-04-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤高のアルケミスト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lone Alchemist</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">고고한 알케미스트</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokou no Alchemist</title>
<summary>The Queen and her Ministers come up with some exciting ideas to promote Manoyama wood-carving! Unfortunately, not all of the locals are thrilled.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="186330" update="2018-04-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マンドレイクの叫び</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cry of the Mandrake</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">맨드레이크의 비명</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mandrake no Sakebi</title>
<summary>Yoshino investigates the town`s passion for kabura (turnips), which leads to a strange showdown between their two kabura-based mascots!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="186331" update="2017-04-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">集いし五人の勇者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gathering of the Five Champions</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">집결한 5명의 용사들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsudoishi Gonin no Yuusha-tachi</title>
<summary>Yoshino faces her first trial as queen: sell one thousand boxes of the tourist board`s mistakenly-ordered snacks before their expiration date is up!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="186332" update="2017-04-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔の山へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Off to Magical Manoyama</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">마노야마로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manoyama e</title>
<summary>After being rejected in over 30 job applications, Yoshino Koharu finally gets an offer.  She probably should have read the contract more carefully...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="186711" update="2017-04-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186973" update="2017-07-19">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187197" update="2017-05-25">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精のレシピ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairy`s Recipe</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">요정의 레시피</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei no Recipe</title>
<summary>Yoshino and the Ministers struggle to find the right dish for their new C-Rank Gourmet plan. Meanwhile, Shiori finds that her sister has a mysterious relationship with an old classmate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187198" update="2017-05-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">煉獄の館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mansion in Purgatory</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">연옥의 저택</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rengoku no Yakata</title>
<summary>The movie shoot and all the activity in town forces Maki to further reflect on her acting aspirations, as well as her relationship with her father.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187199" update="2017-04-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">田園のマスカレード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rural Masquerade</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">전원의 매스커레이드</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Den`en no Masquerade</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187200" update="2017-05-04">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ユグドラシルの芽生え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Budding Yggdrasil</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">싹트는 위그드라실</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yggdrasil no Mebae</title>
<summary>Yoshino recruits a local artist to help the team design a big project for Manoyama Sculpture. Meanwhile, Sanae reflects on her work and its meaning.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187823" update="2017-06-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜明けのギルド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dawn Guild</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">여명의 길드</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoake no Guild</title>
<summary>Yoshino and the Ministers prepare for the Kingdom of Chupakabura`s Founding Festival, and are repeatedly surprised at who signs on to help out!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187824" update="2017-06-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">忘却のレクイエム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Forgotten Requiem</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">망각의 레퀴엠</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boukyaku no Requiem</title>
<summary>The matchmaking tour continues! Meanwhile, Ririko investigates the tale of the town`s dragon, and discovers some new things about herself in the process.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187825" update="2017-06-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラゴンの逆鱗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dragon`s Soft Spot</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">드래곤의 역린</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dragon no Gekirin</title>
<summary>The singles in the local Community Club organize a matchmaking tour with women from the city, with Yoshino and the Ministers as tour guides.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="187826" update="2017-08-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">淑女の天秤</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Lady`s Scales</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">숙녀의 저울</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukujo no Tenbin</title>
<summary>Shiori reveals her plan to bring together the Board of Merchants and the Tourism Board, along with the rest of the town.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188275" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">湖上のアルルカン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Harlequin on the Pond</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">호수위의 광대</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kojou no Arlucan</title>
<summary>Ushimatsu`s desperate attempts to pull something from the pond reveal a dark past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188276" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">国王の帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Queen`s Return</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">국왕의 귀환</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuou no Kikan</title>
<summary>A group of Spanish cryptid enthusiasts visit Manoyama in search of the Chupakabura. Meanwhile, Yoshino and the others work to find b and b`s for Manoyama.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188277" update="2017-09-30">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">国王の断罪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Queen, Convicted</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">국왕의 단죄</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuou no Danzai</title>
<summary>It`s summer break! Yoshino reunites with old friends and family when she visits her hometown. Maki and Sanae go back to Tokyo, while Shiori and Ririko work on a B and B proposal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188278" update="2017-06-29">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリオネットの饗宴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Marionette`s Banquet</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">마리오네트의 향연</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marionette no Kyouen</title>
<summary>The day of the Founding Festival finally arrives. Will the help of the TV network pay off? How will it change Manoyama?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189034" update="2017-08-16">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖夜のフェニックス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Phoenix in the Holy Night</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">성야의 피닉스</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiya no Phoenix</title>
<summary>The Ministers open up an old school to serve hot lunch, and come up with a new plan to promote the old building when that doesn’t go so well.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189035" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧のフォークロア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Foggy Folklore</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">안개의 포크로어</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiri no Folklore</title>
<summary>Maki receives a reply about her application for a role in a movie, and must once again reflect on her dreams. Meanwhile, Yoshino tries to figure out how the town can use one of their old, shut-down schools.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189036" update="2017-08-03">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミネルヴァの杯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Minerva`s Sake Saucer</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">미네르바의 잔</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minerva no Sakazuki</title>
<summary>The seniors of Warabiya stage a revolt against the Kingdom of Chupakabura, and the Queen herself is taken hostage!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189037" update="2017-07-26">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スフィンクスの戯れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sphinx`s Antics</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">스핑크스의 유희</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sphinx no Tawamure</title>
<summary>The Ministers begin their search for the festival treasures, and introduce some of the more remote seniors to the Internet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189210" update="2017-07-19">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189211" update="2017-07-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189914" update="2017-09-13">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悠久のオベリスク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eternal Obelisk</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">유구의 오벨리스크</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuukyuu no Obelisk</title>
<summary>Dark rumors of civic plotting abound as the revival of the Mizuchi Festival draws near.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189915" update="2017-08-10">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪解けのクリスタル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Crystal of Melting Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">융설의 크리스탈</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukidoke no Crystal</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189916" update="2017-08-31">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新月のルミナリエ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Moon Luminarie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">신월의 루미나리에</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shingetsu no Luminarie</title>
<summary>Erika continues her stay with the Ministers, and Shiori tries to convince her that Manoyama isn`t such a bad place. Also, the hunt for the Golden Dragon comes to an exciting conclusion!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189917" update="2017-08-23">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷の町のピクシー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Pixie in the Town of Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">얼음 마을의 픽시</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koori no Machi no Pixie</title>
<summary>Erika attempts to escape from Manoyama, but ends up staying with the Ministers. Meanwhile, Yoshino and Sanae try to gather support from shop owners for the Mizuchi Festival revival.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190081" update="2017-09-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜の王国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Kingdom of Cherry Blossoms</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">사쿠라의 왕국</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Oukoku</title>
<summary>Will the festival be a success? Will Mr. Kadota make it back in time for the play? What will Yoshino do when her contract expires?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
