<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12648" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-12-10</startdate>
<enddate>2019-02-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Saint Seiya: Saintia Shou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">聖闘士星矢 セインティア翔</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Aziz Seiya: Azize Shou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">聖闘士星矢 Saintia翔</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Saint Seiya: Saintia Sho</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">聖鬥士星矢 聖鬥少女翔</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">圣斗士星矢 圣斗少女翔</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="826" type="Other">Saint Seiya</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://www.saintia-sho.com/pc/</url>
<creators>
<name id="18096" type="Character Design">Ichikawa Keiichi</name>
<name id="36601" type="Character Design">Nishino Ayana</name>
<name id="3174" type="Music">Sahashi Toshihiko</name>
<name id="735" type="Animation Work">Gonzo</name>
<name id="14136" type="Direction">Tamagawa Masato</name>
<name id="9944" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Ikuko</name>
<name id="867" type="Original Work">Kurumada Masami</name>
<name id="18096" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ichikawa Keiichi</name>
<name id="36601" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishino Ayana</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a spinoff manga by http://anidb.net/cr48094 [Kuori Chimaki].
The whole Sanctuary was misled into danger due to the civil war instigated by the Gemini Gold Saint, Saga. The story begins right after the end of those events... This is a story of the girls protecting Athena. These are the records of love and fierce fights they meet while opposing destiny on their way to maturity...
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="77">2.55</permanent>
<temporary count="77">4.69</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>196067.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21285</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34539</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.saintia-sho.com/pc/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Saint_Seiya:_Saintia_Shō</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>聖闘士星矢_セインティア翔</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5128</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359195</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21565</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="10544" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-16">
<rating votes="29">7.93</rating>
<name>Aries no Muu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Under the tutelage of Shion, the Pope of the Sanctuary, Muu was able to become the Gold Saint of Aries at a young age. While all gold saints have a base of psychic powers to some degree, Muu has been stated to possess the strongest raw psychic talent among all living gold saints. This allows him to manipulate his gift to various degrees: psychokinesis, telepathy, teleportation, and various other powers are at his command.
Muu is very soft spoken, with a scholarly-like personality; his demeanor is very tranquil and logical, almost as if he is a professor of the Sanctuary. He is good friends with Taurus Aldebaran, and is very respectful to the 243 year old master Libra Douko.</description>
<picture>31552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10553" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-20">
<rating votes="12">6.22</rating>
<name>Taurus no Aldebaran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aldebaran is one of the 12 Guardians of Sanctuary, with the Taurus as his destined constellation. He was the physically strongest of the Gold Saints of modern era. He is Brazilian in origin.
Unlike most of the characters, Aldebaran is often depicted as a friendly guy, laughing and being less serious in times of peace. He was a good friend of Aries Mu, and with Pegasus Seiya (as this last is said in the anime adaptation of the Hades Saga, when Aldebaran sacrificed himself with the other eleven Gold Saints to destroy the Wailing Wall).</description>
<picture>31560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17680" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="4">9.17</rating>
<name>Pisces no Aphrodite</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Pisces Aphrodite is the last of the Gold Saints introduced by Kurumada in his manga, formally presented in vol.11. Aphrodite was a Saint famous not only because of his incredible, mesmerizing beauty, but also for his reputation as one of the strongest among the 88 Saints. However, this reputation is not explored very well in the series itself, as he is killed by Andromeda Shun rather easily by Gold Saint standards, and is beaten rather easily by Aries Mu during the Hades Saga.
Gold Saint Gemini Saga once stated that Aphrodite`s beauty was the greatest among Athena`s Saints. Kurumada named him after the Greek Goddess of love and beauty as a reference to the Greek myth associated to the Pisces constellation. However, Aphrodite never claimed to be the most beautiful creature, unlike the Silver Saint, Lizard Misty who claimed that even the stars` splendor dimmed next to his glory.
It is notable that despite his incomparable beauty, Aphrodite is not narcissistic. He is often described as cruel as his fellow Gold Saint, Cancer Deathmask, but not as sadistic. He is also ironic and sarcastic. According to Saga, despite his beauty, Aphrodite is the most feared of all the 88 Saints of Athena, however, as explained above, this may be due to his cruel nature as opposed to his fighting prowess. His reputation is supported more in the still non-canonical Saint Seiya Episode G, when Aphrodite appeared in front of the Titan`s soldiers who were awe-struck due to his beauty but also paralyzed by fear in his presence.
A recurring motif in the Pisces Saint is that he considers victory as the greatest beauty of all and, therefore, he believes what makes him really beautiful would not be his physique, but absolute power. Aphrodite is depicted as a man who believes the power is the only way to keep the order and assure the justice. Subscribing to this theory, he believes the stronger is allowed to rule over the weak.
Some casual fans believe Aphrodite is a female because of his name. In the French, European Spanish -first dubbing- and Chinese dubbing of the anime adaptation, he is voiced by a female actress.</description>
<picture>48024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3282" picture="24710.jpg">Nanba Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17681" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-18">
<rating votes="3">6.73</rating>
<name>Gemini no Saga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Along with Leo Aiolia, Saga disguised as the Pope was the first Gold Saint that Masami Kurumada introduced in his manga, although their rank wasn`t revealed until later volumes. In his first appearance, Saga presided the event in which Pegasus Seiya acquired the status of Saint. In the anime adaptation, he was introduced in identical manner, in episode 1.
Saga managed to put himself in control of the sanctuary treacherously for many years after killing Pope Shion, the original Grand Pope of Sanctuary by stealing his identity.
Saga is often described by other characters as someone with the kindness of an angel but with the darkness of a demon. This ambivalence ended up creating a split personality: a good Saga that was extremely loyal to Athena and an evil one that keeps control of the body most of the time and killed the previous Pope to steal his place. When it takes control of Saga`s body, his hair turns from blond to jet-black (the color schemes were altered for the anime, in which Saga`s normally blue hair turned light grey). Saga`s two "sides", can also communicate between them : in a dialogue the good Saga reproaches his evil "side" to have forced him to hurt Athena.</description>
<picture>1427.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17683" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="7">9.28</rating>
<name>Leo no Aiolia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As Masami Kurumada uses the revered Osamu Tezuka`s Star System, (A stable cast of characters which play a different or similar role in the author`s various works, sometimes with the same personality and sometimes with an entirely new one), he designed Aiolia`s appearance very similar to Zaji, the main character in Raimei no Zaji, a manga that Kurumada wrote and drew years before Saint Seiya.
In his manga, Kurumada gave Aiolia blonde hair. In the anime adaptation, due to a relative excess of yellow tones in Kurumada`s design, Aiolia`s hair color was modified to light brown to achieve a better color balance and contrast.</description>
<picture>1428.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17688" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="5">7.60</rating>
<name>Sagittarius no Aiolos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurumada introduced Aiolos in chapter 24 of his manga, contained in vol. 6.
He is one of the 12 Guardians of Sanctuary, with the Sagittarius as his destined constellation. Aiolos is the famous gold saint who died protecting Athena when she was an infant.
Aiolos always was a paradigm of righteousness, seen as the perfect Saint and one of the two Gold Saints who could succeed Aries Shion as the next Pope of Sanctuary and the chosen one.
Not much is known about Aiolos, since he died before the main story began. More of him is seen in Saint Seiya Episode G, like his relationship with Garan, a servant of his young brother, Leo Aiolia, who once trained with Aiolos for the Sagittarius cloth.
Despite his condition, Aiolos managed to help the main characters many times sending his cloth to aid them.
Aiolos is probably named after the Greek god of Wind, Aeolus.</description>
<picture>48028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17689" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-17">
<rating votes="4">8.66</rating>
<name>Scorpio no Milo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurumada introduced Milo in vol.7 of his manga. Though in the manga the first Gold Saints introduced are Aiolia and Saga, Kurumada didn`t revealed their rank until further volumes. The first Gold Saint he introduced revealing his rank was Virgo Shaka, in vol.5. In the anime adaptation, these introductions occur in the same manner, although Shaka`s is delayed and the first Gold Saint that appeared fully wearing a Gold Cloth was Scorpio Milo.
Milo is the Scorpio Gold Saint. Since his main technique inflicts immense pain to its victims, Milo always gives his opponents the option to either surrender, or become insane due to the unbearable pain. He also sees great importance in the pride of the Gold Saints and seems to be always ready to clean the name of his companions. Even so, he is a noble warrior who can admit defeat even against a weaker or inferior enemy. Since Milo fought Hyoga, he spoke to Aquarius Camus in a way that led the fans to believe they were close friends. Apparently, this was made official since the anime adaptation of the Hades arc of the manga included more interaction between them and they are depicted as friends in Saint Seiya Episode G.</description>
<picture>48029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="30885" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="73">6.82</rating>
<name>Pegasus no Seiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73090.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33220" type="appears in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="93">7.05</rating>
<name>Andromeda Seiza no Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12421" picture="78914.jpg">Kasuya Yuuta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33224" type="main character in" update="2011-06-09">
<rating votes="93">7.58</rating>
<name>Kido Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>73096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33483" type="appears in" update="2011-06-17">
<rating votes="4">8.05</rating>
<name>Unicorn no Jabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second Bronze Saint to appear in the story was Jabu the Unicorn Saint. As a fellow orphan he had been sent out with 99 more of his brothers by their father Mitsumasa Kido. He achieved the Unicorn Cloth in Algeria and returned to Japan to participate in the Galaxian Wars tournament to receive the Gold Cloth of Sagittarius. He easily defeated Lionet Ban in his first match but was outmatched against Andromeda Shun whose chains proved impenetrable. He returned to his master in Algeria to further his training, and during this time his Cloth came to upgrade itself as well. When Saori Kido had been shot by a golden arrow, he came to her rescue and protected her from the then antagonistic forces of the Sanctuary. After that he came to reside in the Sanctuary and protected it against the Saints Hades had revived, and protected Pegasus Seiya`s sister Seika from the attacks of the god of death.</description>
<picture>73627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="258" picture="17080.jpg">Ishikawa Hideo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48979" type="appears in" update="2012-09-18">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Musca no Dio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43359" picture="226056.jpg">Tadokoro Hinata</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48980" type="appears in" update="2012-09-18">
<rating votes="2">3.33</rating>
<name>Heracles no Algethi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40730" picture="228932.jpg">Kimura Hayato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99323" type="main character in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Delphinus no Mii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="423" picture="37799.jpg">Nakajima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99324" type="main character in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Equuleus no Shou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41296" picture="177392.jpg">Suzuki Aina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99325" type="main character in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Equuleus no Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229987.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100717" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Ursa Minor no Xiaoling</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100718" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Corona Borealis no Katja</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229990.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38300" picture="236362.jpg">Morishita Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100719" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Cassiopeia no Elda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229991.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100720" type="appears in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Zen Kyoukou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229993.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100721" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<name>Pavo no Mayura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100722" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Aquila no Marine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100723" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Scutum no Yuan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100724" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-08">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Southern Cross no Georg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100730" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Ruin no Ate</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42286" picture="167754.jpg">Tachibana Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100731" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Malice no Emony</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39199" picture="242466.jpg">Kouno Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100732" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Murder no Phonos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100733" type="appears in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Toki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42164" picture="176249.jpg">Takeuchi Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100734" type="appears in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Orion no Rigel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230017.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2674" picture="41437.jpg">Kase Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100735" type="appears in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Rumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100736" type="appears in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Shouko no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100737" type="appears in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Mirai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2980" picture="147242.jpg">Kanada Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100738" type="appears in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Shinato</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100739" type="appears in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Tatsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100740" type="appears in" update="2019-02-09">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Mito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10340" picture="222848.jpg">Uetake Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="210637" update="2019-01-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命の姉妹! 翔子と響子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fated Sisters! Shoko and Kyoko</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les sœurs élues ! Shoko et Kyoko</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kaderi Kaçınılmaz Kardeşler‚ Shoko ve Kyoko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei no Shimai! Shouko to Kyouko</title>
<summary>Shoko is a student at Ryuusei Private Academy Middle School. Her dear sister, Kyoko, had went to study abroad five years ago and hasn’t heard from her since. One day, an unknown entity suddenly attacks Shoko. The ones who attacked her had been the Dryads, underlings of the evil goddess, Eris, who was once sealed by Goddess Athena. When Shoko and Saori Kido awaiting the Galaxian Wars meet, the gears of destiny begin to turn!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780357</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210638" update="2019-01-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの決意! 女神と聖闘少女[セインティア]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Individual Decisions! The Goddess and Saintias</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La volonté de la déesse et d`une Saintia</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bireysel Kararlar‚ Tanrıça ve Azize</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Ketsui! Megami to Saintia</title>
<summary>Shoko cannot hide the shock knowing Kyoko was taken away instead of her as the evil god’s host. As Shoko finds out the special position of Athena’s handmaidens as well as bodyguards that only women can fill, she decides to become a Saintia herself from her desire to become stronger in order to rescue her sister. Saori requests the Silver Saint, Pavo Mayura, for Shoko’s training, however…
On the other hand, Milo and Aiolia at the Sanctuary were sensing the evil Goddess Eris’ suspicious moves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780471</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210639" update="2019-01-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇に咲く! エリスの邪精霊[ドリアード]たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blooming in Darkness! The Dryads of Eris</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les dryades d`Éris, fleurs des Ténèbres</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Karanlıkta Açan Çiçek‚ Orman Perisi Eris</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami ni Saku! Eris no Dryad-tachi</title>
<summary>The underlings of the evil goddess, Malice Emony and Murder Phonos, plot to take Athena’s head to offer it to Eris and raids Saori. Mii stands up against Emony who continues to call Saori an “incomplete god”. Shoko’s Cosmo flare up during the training with Mayura. Sensing Athena’s danger from the Cloth’s box, can Shoko ultimately save Saori?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780712</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210640" update="2019-01-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">哀しみの再会! 隔たれた姉妹の絆</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Reunion of Sorrow! The Bond of the Separated Sisters</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tristes retrouvailles ! Les liens des sœurs séparées</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kederin Birleşmesi‚ Ayrı Düşmüş Kardeşlerin Bağı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanashimi no Saikai! Hedatareta Shimai no Kizuna</title>
<summary>Shoko succeeded in entering Eris’ temple by chasing Phonos who fled battle. As she searches the temple to save her sister, Kyoko, she is informed of a shocking fact by Ate. When Ate’s vines catch Shoko off guard and begin to attack, a golden light enwraps her body! To bring back Shoko, Mii heads to Eris’ temple and reunites with her where they find Kyoko’s ragged body before their eyes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780934</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210896" update="2018-12-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210897" update="2018-12-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211391" update="2019-01-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">翔べ! ペガサスのように</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly! Like Pegasus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tel Pégase, prends ton envol</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kanatlı At Gibi Uç</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobe! Pegasus no You ni</title>
<summary>Kyoko’s Cosmo disappeared in the battle at Eris’ temple. Saori’s heart wavers as she questions her existence from not being able to save Kyoko in defeating the evil god. However, with Saori inheriting Mitsumasa Kido’s will, the Galaxian Wars start without mercy. On the other hand, Shoko who was in the hospital had been depressed from Saori telling her goodbye, and she drops the pendant of Pegasus given to her by her sister. The boy who caught it for her was Pegasus Seiya who was entering the Galaxian Wars.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780935</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211392" update="2019-07-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">せめぎ合う魂! 沙織vs.教皇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Colliding Souls! Saori vs. Grand Master</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux âmes s`affrontent ! Saori contre le Grand Pope</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Çarpışan Ruhlar‚ Saori Büyük Üstat’a Karşı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Semegiau Tamashii! Saori vs. Kyoukou</title>
<summary>Aphrodite of Pisces takes Athena to the Sanctuary by order of the Grand Master, where both will meet face to face. What secret does the Grand Master hide behind his tears? Meanwhile, Mayura has detected that the remains of Eris are producing an effect that could be catastrophic.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780936</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211393" update="2019-01-28">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">十二宮の死闘! 恐るべき邪霊の幻惑</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of the Twelve Temples! The Allurement of the Terrifying Ghosts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le combat à mort des douze maisons ! L`envoûtement des esprits maléfiques</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">On İki Tapınağın Savaşı‚ Korkunç Hayaletlerin Albenisi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juunikyuu no Shitou! Osorubeki Jarei no Genwaku</title>
<summary>The moment the golden arrow strikes Saori, the Ghosts begin to stir. Shoko who was the evil god’s shell had lost conscious, having her soul pulled by the Ghosts. Mayura and the Saintias work hard to calm the evil spirits while Seiya and the Bronze Saints hurry through the Sanctuary to save Athena. Now, the deadly battle of the twelve temples begin...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780937</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211394" update="2019-02-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪夢の激突! 燃えあがる獅子の拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Clash of Nightmares! The Fists of Leo Flare Up</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le choc des cauchemars ! Le poing enflammé du lion</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kabusların Çarpışması‚ Aslan Öfkesinin Yumruğu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumu no Gekitotsu! Moeagaru Shishi no Ken</title>
<summary>After the deadly battle, the Saints of the Sanctuary all swear their loyalty to Saori—Athena. Meanwhile, Eris, who was thought to have been sealed, had fused with her host, Kyoko, and multiplied her powers. Saori rises against Eris to protect Shoko, but receives the curse of the apple. The Gold Saints head to the Temple of Eris along with the Saintias to save Athena and to stop the evil god from scattering the Evil Seeds of war that fill people’s hearts with hate. That’s where Aiolia witnesses his own brother turning his fists against him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780938</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212290" update="2019-02-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">争いの渦! 黄金の林檎とオリオンの献身</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Spiral of Conflict! The Golden Apple and Orion`s Devotion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le maelström du conflit ! La pomme d`or et la dévotion d`Orion</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bir Anlaşmazlığın Sarmalı‚ Altın Elma İle Avcı’nın Fedakârlığı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arasoi no Uzu! Oudon no Ringo to Orion no Kenshin</title>
<summary>Can you defeat your sister who has fused with the evil god? With Mu’s question, Shoko agonizes over the fate she bears. That’s when Orion Rigel, the Ghost of an ex-Silver Saint, stands before Shoko. From Rigel’s sad eyes that once shared a past with Kyoko during Saint years, Shoko senses his true feelings and... 
Mii vs. Emony, Aiolia vs. Saga, the individual battles within the Temple of Eris begins…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780939</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212291" update="2019-02-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">輝け少女たちよ! 気高き祈りの果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shine Saintias! At the End of a Noble Prayer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Brillez, jeunes filles ! Aux confins de la noble prière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kagayake Shoujo-tachi yo! Kedakaki Inori no Hate ni</title>
<summary>Finally, Shoko faces the evil god Eris. As Saori’s Cosmo grows weaker, all of the Saintias—Shoko, Mii, Xiaoling, Katya, and Erda—put their hearts together to challenge Eris. The Gold Saints continue to protect the Sanctuary as they find out Eris’ plan of crashing the temple into it. Aiolia and Milo, who face Saga in a deadly battle, plans to destroy the temple, however…  A raging destiny encircles the Saintias, Gold Saints, evil god Eris, and Saori Kido. The final battle begins
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780940</identifier>
<identifier>saint-seiya-saintia-sho</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212294" update="2019-01-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
