<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12651" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shoukoku no Altair</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">PROJECT ALTAIR</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Altair: Racconti di Battaglia</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">将国のアルタイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Altair: A Record of Battles</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">장국의 알타이르</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">将国之天鹰星</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10910" approval="6" total="6">Arslan Senki (2015)</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://project-altair.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="14200" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kuwahara Mikine</name>
<name id="31375" type="Animation Work">MAPPA</name>
<name id="1410" type="Direction">Furuhashi Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="9390" type="Character Design">Kanno Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="7428" type="Series Composition">Takagi Noboru</name>
<name id="48132" type="Original Work">Katou Kotono</name>
<name id="44574" type="Music">Kawasaki Ryou</name>
<name id="9390" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kanno Toshiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr48132 [Katou Kotono]`s shounen manga series.
http://anidb.net/ch86834 [Mahmut] is a young Pasha serving on the council of the Türkiye Stratocracy. The clouds of war are gathering over his country as the threat of the aggressive Empire looms large. With Türkiye`s council split between the warmongers and the pacifists, Mahmut begins his quest to keep the peace at any cost. As he finds himself drawn deeper and deeper in the politics of the ancient world, new enemies and allies surface. Who will prevail? What will Mahmut do if war proves to be inevitable?
Source: M-U
Note: The first two episodes received an early screening at a special event held at United Cinemas Toyosu Screen 10 in Tokyo on 02.07.2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="386">5.65</permanent>
<temporary count="388">6.58</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>203556.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18966</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34547</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://project-altair.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Altair:_A_Record_of_Battles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>将国のアルタイル</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4598</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359232</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20293</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>pj_altair</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B073R6HDDW</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2833" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Middle East</name>
<description>The Middle East is a transcontinental region centered on Western Asia, Turkey (both Asian and European), and Egypt (which is mostly in North Africa). The corresponding adjective is Middle Eastern and the derived noun is Middle Easterner. The term has come into wider usage as a replacement of the term Near East (as opposed to the Far East) beginning in the early 20th century.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192047.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6614" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-12">
<name>Animeism</name>
<description>Animeism is a late-night Japanese programming block established in April 2012. It is devoted to anime and broadcast each Thursday night on MBS, in a fashion similar to Fuji TV`s http://anidb.net/t3865 [noitaminA] that also airs on Thursdays. Just like noitaminA, the block airs two series back to back. From April 2015 onwards, the block was moved to Friday nights.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>63625.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="86830" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-25">
<name>Sehir Khalil Pasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86831" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-25">
<rating votes="1">4.26</rating>
<name>Cyrus Ios Apolodros</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="367" picture="17213.jpg">Kenn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86832" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-25">
<rating votes="2">3.34</rating>
<name>Zehir Zaganos Pasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34070" picture="130103.jpg">Furukawa Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86833" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-25">
<rating votes="1">4.26</rating>
<name>Kara Kanat Suleyman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86834" type="main character in" update="2017-03-25">
<rating votes="3">7.40</rating>
<name>Tughril Mahmut Pasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200137.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86835" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-25">
<rating votes="2">5.17</rating>
<name>Virgilio Louis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88505" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-25">
<rating votes="1">1.69</rating>
<name>Abiriga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88506" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-25">
<rating votes="5">8.82</rating>
<name>Lelederik</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88507" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-25">
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<name>Garrat Berlich</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>200146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89666" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="4">7.70</rating>
<name>Shara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203243.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89667" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<name>Ibrahim</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203244.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2328" picture="171565.jpg">Satou Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89775" type="appears in" update="2017-07-09">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Aishe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89776" type="appears in" update="2017-07-09">
<name>Ismail</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89777" type="appears in" update="2017-07-09">
<name>Orhan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89778" type="appears in" update="2017-07-09">
<name>Bayezid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89779" type="appears in" update="2017-07-09">
<rating votes="1">1.69</rating>
<name>Balaban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="259" picture="17082.jpg">Nakai Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90360" type="appears in" update="2017-07-09">
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<name>Antonio Lucio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90361" type="appears in" update="2017-07-09">
<name>Silvestro Brega</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="245665.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188544" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬鷲の共闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eagle`s Joint Struggle</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">검둥수리의 공투</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inuwashi no Kyoutou</title>
<summary>Mahmut is demoted from Pasha after the incident in Hisar. Realizing his own shortcomings, he vows to become a man worthy of being Pasha. Mahmut visits his hometown and meets Suleyman, chief of the Göz Kulak spy network created by Zaganos.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188545" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">将軍会議</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Council of Generals</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">장군 회의</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougun Kaigi</title>
<summary>Mahmut infiltrates Hisar with Shara. The citizens of Hisar have been captured by the Araba Tribe and Louis` private army, the Röd Orm. In an attempt to rescue the citizens and stop the rebellion, Mahmut lures out the Röd`s commanding officer. However, the officer uses a hostage as a shield to protect himself, and Mahmut is put on the back foot. Only Shara will be able to turn things around.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188546" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">砦の町</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Citadel City</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">요새 마을</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toride no Machi</title>
<summary>Rebellion breaks out in the Citadel City of Hisar located in the Türkiye Stratocracy`s first province, and collusion between Ibrahim Vali and the Araba Tribe is suspected. Mahmut denies that his best friend Ibrahim would ever lead an uprising, while Zaganos immediately orders the revolt be quashed. Disagreeing with the plan, Mahmut heads to Hisar alone to discover the truth behind the uprising.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188547" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬鷲の将軍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Golden Eagle General</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">검둥수리의 장군</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inuwashi no Shougun</title>
<summary>Türkiye and Balt-Rhein are in a critical balance when the Empire`s minister is assassinated near the two nations` border. Balt-Rhein accuses Türkiye, and demands a representative be sent to take responsibility, or they will interpret it as an act of war.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188891" update="2017-12-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188892" update="2017-07-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189244" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">至誠の仮面劇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masquerade of Sincerity</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">지성의 가면극</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shisei no Kamengeki</title>
<summary>Having been brought to the Republic of Venedik by Capitan Brega, Mahmut is granted an audience with the Doge Lucio. Mahmut asks the Doge`s reasons for betraying his alliance with Phoinike. However, Lucio answers that Venedik had not violated the terms of their alliance. After their meeting, Mahmut seeks out a kulak to learn more about Venedik, but Abiriga informs him that there is no kulak here.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189245" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">古都陥落</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sinking City</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">고도함락</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koto Kanraku</title>
<summary>Mahmut and company intercepted the Imperial warship that had infiltrated the port. However, the warship was a decoy to hide the advancing troops coming from the crystal cliffs. After allowing Lelederik and her unit`s invasion, Phoinike decides to surrender to the Balt-Rhein Empire. Having managed to escape Phoinike, Mahmut and Kiros encounter the Venedik Armada off the coast of the city.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189246" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒鉄の鎖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Iron Chains</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">흑철의 쇠사슬</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurogane no Kusari</title>
<summary>It is day fifteen of the war between Phoinike and Balt-Rhein, and the stalemate continues. Phoinike cannot win without the support of their ally, the Republic of Venedik. With that thought, Mahmut sought the help of Kiros and decided to head to Venedik himself. Meanwhile, unable to penetrate Phoinike`s Great Wall, a single vessel appears waving the flag of surrender.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189247" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">燈台の都</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The City of the Lighthouse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">등대의 도시</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toudai no Miyako</title>
<summary>After taking Suleyman`s advice, Mahmut had decided to experience the outside world. His first stop is the City of the Lighthouse, Phoinike. Right after meeting the kulak Kiros at the water shrine, an officer finds Mahmut and brings him to the city Magistros Konstantinos where he learns that Balt-Rhein has requested Phoinike cede a section of their port. An assembly is held to make a decision.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190502" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇岩会戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle at the Unusual Rock Formations</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">기암회전</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kigan Kaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190503" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">剣の将太子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prince of Swords</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">검의 장태자</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ken no Shoutaishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190504" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月下佳人の舞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dance of the Moonlit Beauty</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">월하가인의 춤</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekka Kajin no Mai</title>
<summary>Mahmut and the others found themselves under house arrest in Balaban`s Crimson Palace. While there were some attempts to stop them, they manage to escape the palace. However, the Rod Orm are waiting for them outside. Mahmut is able to drive back the Rod Orm`s attack, but Muzrak`s cavalry are closing in. They desperately try to escape, but soon accept their fate when...
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190505" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紅虎の将王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Tiger Sultan</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">적호의 장왕</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Benitora no Shouou</title>
<summary>The Torqye Pashalu proposes a unified Birlik Torqye to prepare against an invasion from the Balt-Rhein Empire, but the other four nations vote it down. Meanwhile, Mahmut is in Muzrak`s port town of Liman and visits their water shrine in order to gather information. However, the shrine was completely closed off. Abiriga informs Mahmut that armed men are inside the shrine.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191153" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大戦の始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beginning of the Great War</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">대전의 시작</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taisen no Hajimari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191154" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">北の王国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Northern Kingdom</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">북쪽 왕국</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kita no Oukoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191155" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">隊商の娘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Caravan Daughter</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">대상의 딸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taishou no Musume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191156" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">内乱終結</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conclusion of the Civil War</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">내란 종결</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nairan Shuuketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192100" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">弔鐘遥かなり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distant Funeral Bells</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">조종은 멀어져가고</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choushou Haruka Nari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192101" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽園の檻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cage of Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">낙원의 함</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakuen no Ori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192102" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">冀う星々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wishing on Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">갈망하는 별들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koinegau Hoshiboshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192103" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">花の一計</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flower`s Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">꽃의 일계</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana no Ikkei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193146" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">胎動</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Instigation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">태동</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taidou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193147" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽園の終焉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">낙원의 종언</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakuen no Shuuen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193148" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬鷲の追撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Golden Eagle`s Pursuit</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">검둥수리의 추격</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inuwashi no Tsuigeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193149" update="2018-01-17">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">反帝の同盟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alliance Against the Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">반제의 동맹</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hantei no Doumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194182" update="2017-12-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194183" update="2017-12-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
