<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12653" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-10-13</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Inuyashiki</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Инуясики</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Инуяшики: Последният супергерой</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">いぬやしき</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Inuyashiki Last Hero</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">이누야시키</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">犬屋敷</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10272" approval="33" total="41">Kiseijuu: Sei no Kakuritsu</anime>
<anime id="2400" approval="24" total="32">Gantz</anime>
<anime id="4563" approval="7" total="16">Death Note</anime>
<anime id="61" approval="5" total="17">Ghost in the Shell</anime>
<anime id="807" approval="2" total="11">Tetsuwan Atom (2003)</anime>
<anime id="10537" approval="1" total="10">Zankyou no Terror</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="434710">|| W~A~T~C~H ||

!! M~A~S~T~E~R~P~I~E~C~E !!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.inuyashiki-project.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="17926" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kamata Shinpei</name>
<name id="805" type="Work">Dentsu</name>
<name id="51816" type="Work">DMM Pictures</name>
<name id="748" type="Work">Kodansha</name>
<name id="762" type="Work">Aniplex</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="1282" type="Original Work">Oku Hiroya</name>
<name id="21424" type="Direction">Yabuta Shuuhei</name>
<name id="3728" type="Chief Direction">Satou Keiichi</name>
<name id="2163" type="Character Design">Onda Naoyuki</name>
<name id="31375" type="Animation Work">MAPPA</name>
<name id="37817" type="Series Composition">Seko Hiroshi</name>
<name id="4410" type="Music">Ike Yoshihiro</name>
<name id="6065" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hayama Kenji</name>
<name id="11871" type="Chief Animation Direction">Haneda Kouji</name>
<name id="2163" type="Chief Animation Direction">Onda Naoyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a science fiction manga series written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr1282 [Oku Hiroya].
http://anidb.net/ch89791 [Inuyashiki Ichirou] is down on his luck. While only 58 years old, his geriatric looks often have him written off as a pathetic old man by the world around him and he`s constantly ignored and disrespected by his family despite all that he`s done to support them. On top of everything else, his doctor has revealed that he has cancer and it appears that he has little time left in this world. But just when it seems things couldn`t get any worse, a blinding light in the night sky strikes the earth where Ichirou stands. He later wakes up to find himself unscathed, but he soon starts to notice that there`s something... different about himself. However, it turns out that these strange, new changes are just what Ichirou needs to take a new lease on life and now it seems like there`s nothing to stop him from being a hero worthy of the respect that he never had before... unless, that is, there was someone else out there with these same changes...
Source: Kodansha Comics</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1641">6.51</permanent>
<temporary count="1651">7.24</temporary>
<review count="2">4.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221766.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19670</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34542</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.inuyashiki-project.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Inuyashiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>いぬやしき</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4721</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359187</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20613</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>inu_noitamina</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B076DKXRWS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2884" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>psychoactive drugs</name>
<description>Psychoactive drugs are chemical substances that affect the function of the central nervous system, altering perception, mood or consciousness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3086" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>parricide</name>
<description>Parricide, or the murder of family members, is the act of taking the life of of one or more of one`s own close family members, or even one`s entire family; that may include spouses, parents, grandparents, children, grandchildren, siblings, cousins, uncles, aunts, nephews, and nieces, among others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3145" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-14">
<name>impact event</name>
<description>An impact event is a collision between celestial objects causing measurable effects. Impact events have physical consequences and have been found to regularly occur in planetary systems, though the most frequent involve asteroids, comets or meteoroids and have minimal impact. When large objects impact terrestrial planets like the Earth, there can be significant physical and biospheric consequences, though atmospheres mitigate many surface impacts through atmospheric entry. Impact structures are dominant landforms on many celestial solid objects and present the strongest empirical evidence for their frequency and scale. In fiction, an impact event is a common way to end the world as we know it, either through the impact itself or through its aftermath, and it may happen either naturally or through human hands; this may include man-made objects, such as space debris and fictional space colonies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3167" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-16">
<name>Tokyo destroyed</name>
<description>Tokyo is depicted as being or having been destroyed, either partially or completely, by some sort of disaster, such as a nuclear blast, a very large-scale fire, or rising sea levels. Should the situation be dire enough, Tokyo may be destroyed again after a recovery, or a new Tokyo may be built and subsequently destroyed, by a new disaster.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3315" parentid="2623" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-28">
<name>superhero</name>
<description>In modern popular fiction, a superhero is a type of costumed heroic character who possesses supernatural or superhuman powers and who is dedicated to fighting crime, protecting the public, and usually battling supervillains. A female superhero is sometimes called a superheroine. Fiction centered on such characters, especially in American comic books since the 1930s, is known as superhero fiction.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3589" parentid="4251" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-04">
<name>multiple protagonists - TO BE MOVED TO PARENT OR DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is to be moved into its parent tag http://anidb.net/t4251 [ensemble cast], or removed entirely. If the tagged entry meets the updated definition of ensemble cast, tag ensemble cast and delete multiple protagonist. If it does not meet the ensemble cast definition, delete this tag and take no further action.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4387" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>good vs evil</name>
<description>A theme often used to relay lessons of morality. The fight between two entities, with one side representing all that is good and right and the other one all that is evil and wrong.
It’s one of the most conventional themes in literature, and sometimes considered to be a universal part of the human condition.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4398" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-23">
<name>antihero</name>
<description>An antihero is a main character in a story who lacks conventional heroic qualities and attributes such as idealism, courage and morality. Although antiheroes may sometimes perform actions that are morally correct, it is not always for the right reasons, often acting primarily out of self-interest or in ways that defy conventional ethical codes.
A villain protagonist is where the leading character of the story (the protagonist) is also a villain; this is a fairly rare occurrence.</description>
<picurl>70856.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11787" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-07-06">
<rating votes="55">7.43</rating>
<name>Kurono Kei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurono Kei is one of the two main protagonists of the series. He is a 10th grader who is summoned by Gantz, along with his childhood friend http://anidb.net/ch11788 [Katou Masaru], after being hit by a subway train in an effort to help a hobo who passes out on the tracks.
In the beginning, he is a rather selfish character, with a penchant for sexual perversity, who often ends up being the reluctant hero. However, after Katou dies in the third mission, Kei starts taking care of other people as well, and he starts to avoid casualties amongst Gantz team members. His innate skills and physical prowess eventually make him a hero to most of the other members.
During missions, Kei often uses unconventional tactics to great effect. He lives alone in an apartment complex, as he was not on good terms with his family. After reviving some of his former friends, Kei leaves the game due to a request from his comrades. The vampires group searches and eventually finds Kei, killing him.
After the first mission of Phase 2, he is revived by Kato Masaru but remembers nothing beyond his choice to leave after the Oni Mission. After the failed Italian mission, Gantz revives an additional copy of Kurono at Reika`s request, unknown to the others. After meeting the original Kurono, he decides to live with Reika.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>235879.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11788" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-07-06">
<rating votes="35">5.12</rating>
<name>Katou Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Katou Masaru is one of the two main protagonists of the series. He is summoned, along with http://anidb.net/ch11787 [Kurono], by Gantz after they were hit by a subway train while helping an unconscious hobo who fell on the tracks. He is a childhood friend of Kurono and serves as a secondary protagonist. At school, he acts as a guardian to the weaker students who often find themselves bullied, getting himself a bit of a reputation for fighting. He initially lives with an aunt who reluctantly adopted him and his brother after they were orphaned. They leave after Katou could no longer stand their aunt hitting his little brother.
He is killed during the Thousand Arms mission. He is later revived near the end of Phase 1 by Suzuki Yoshikazu who asked Kurono who he wanted to revive. After that, he manages to kill Nurarihyon and gains 100 points, choosing to revive Kurono.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>235869.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89791" type="main character in" update="2017-06-05">
<rating votes="34">7.29</rating>
<name>Inuyashiki Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49621" picture="200949.jpg">Kohinata Fumiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89794" type="main character in" update="2017-06-05">
<rating votes="31">4.64</rating>
<name>Shishigami Hiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51409" picture="206578.jpg">Murakami Nijirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91216" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-12">
<rating votes="14">6.54</rating>
<name>Andou Naoyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33645" picture="92134.jpg">Hongou Kanata</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91495" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-12">
<rating votes="11">3.55</rating>
<name>Watanabe Shion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208231.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91496" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-12">
<rating votes="30">6.64</rating>
<name>Inuyashiki Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93372" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="6">2.53</rating>
<name>Inuyashiki Marie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16176" picture="223836.jpg">Nishi Hiroko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93373" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="6">2.29</rating>
<name>Inuyashiki Koushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38232" picture="140073.jpg">Asai Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93374" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="4">4.31</rating>
<name>Hanako</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212284.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93375" type="appears in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="3">4.21</rating>
<name>Shishigami Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212285.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44878" picture="182634.jpg">Katou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93377" type="appears in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hamada Satoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212287.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93378" type="appears in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Inoue Fumino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93380" type="appears in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="3">1.13</rating>
<name>Samejima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93382" type="appears in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Daitouryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43109" picture="172742.jpg">Bill Fleming</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="190900" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鮫島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Samejima</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">사메지마</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samejima</title>
<summary>When the fully tattooed yakuza criminal Samejima finds a girl he likes, he kidnaps them, drugs them up, and then roughs them up. Fumino was happy. She had a job and a fiance. But one night, Samejima sets his sights on her, and has his men kidnap her. Fumino manages to escape, and runs to her fiance Satoru`s house, but Samejima is in hot pursuit. Inuyashiki comes to save them, but gets shot.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190901" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">安堂直行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naoyuki Ando</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">안도 나오유키</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Andou Naoyuki</title>
<summary>Shishigami is rattled to see Inuyashiki stand up from a blow that should have killed him before flying away. Seeing that, Inuyashiki knows that Shishigami has a robot body just like himself. After this meeting, Inuyashiki studies his abilities, and uses them to save others. Meanwhile, Shishigami confronts a group of delinquents who have been tormenting his best friend Naoyuki Ando.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190902" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">獅子神皓</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hiro Shishigami</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">시시가미 히로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shishigami Hiro</title>
<summary>Reborn a robot, Inuyashiki finds meaning by saving others. Meanwhile, high school student Hiro Shishigami has also been reborn a robot. Shishigami has no regard for anybody aside from his best friend and his family, and uses his robot powers to kill indiscriminately. Contrary to Inuyashiki, he feels alive when he is taking the lives of others. What happens when these two meet?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190903" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬屋敷壱郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ichiro Inuyashiki</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">이누야시키 이치로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inuyashiki Ichirou</title>
<summary>Ichiro Inuyashiki is a boring office worker who looks like an old man. Even after building them a new home, his family is nothing but ungrateful. One day, Inuyashiki is diagnosed with terminal cancer. Out on a walk to clear his head, a UFO crashes into him, and his body is rebuilt into a deadly robot. He steps in to stop a group of kids from torturing a homeless man when he is knocked unconscious.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191635" update="2017-10-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191636" update="2017-10-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192257" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬屋敷麻理</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mari Inuyashiki</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">이누야시키 마리</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inuyashiki Mari</title>
<summary>A special forces team bursts in to apprehend Shishigami. Shion and her grandmother are shot in the crossfire, and Shishigami manages to grab them before escaping. After taking them to safety, he wishes Shion a happy life. One day, Mari sees her father and Ando together. She follows after and sees Inuyashiki fly off into the sky. That night, Shishigami attacks a police station in vengeance.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="192258" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">渡辺しおん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shion Watanabe</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">와타나베 시온</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watanabe Shion</title>
<summary>As Shion believed he was innocent, Shishigami confesses to her that his body is a robot and has taken many lives in order to feel alive again. He coldly informs her that he will kill everyone in the country. However, Shion begs Shishigami not to leave her behind. Shion cries as she tells Shishigami that the people he`s killed had futures and loved ones, and Shishigami makes a proposition.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="192259" update="2017-11-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2chの人たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">People of 2chan</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">2ch 사람들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2ch no Hito-tachi</title>
<summary>Shishigami escaped from a dozen officers, but he has become a wanted man in connection to the home invasion spree. With nowhere to go, Shishigami stays with Shion Watanabe, a classmate who has feelings for him. Meanwhile, Inuyashiki learns to use his robot abilities with Ando`s help. After seeing Shishigami`s mother publicly apologizing on TV, they worry what Shishigami might do next.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="192260" update="2017-11-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">獅子神優子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yuko Shishigami</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">시시가미 유코</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shishigami Yuuko</title>
<summary>Ando is struggling with the fact that his friend Shishigami is responsible for the spree of home invasions. After reading that hospital patients were being cured, Ando theorizes that there is someone else out there with the same powers as Shishigami. Ando lures Inuyashiki by pretending to need help and asks him to stop Shishigami. Meanwhile, Shishigami learns his mother has terminal cancer.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193430" update="2017-11-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="24">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地球の人たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">People of Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">지구인들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikyuu no Hito-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193431" update="2017-11-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東京の人たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">People of Tokyo</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">도쿄 사람들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokyo no Hito-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193432" update="2017-11-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新宿の人たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">People of Shinjuku</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">신주쿠 사람들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjuku no Hito-tachi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
