<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12685" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-12-23</startdate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Drifters (2017)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドリフターズ (2017)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">漂流武士</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">漂流武士 第二季</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11164" type="Prequel">Drifters</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.nbcuni.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/drifters/</url>
<creators>
<name id="12197" type="Character Design">Nakamori Ryouji</name>
<name id="1557" type="Series Composition">Kurata Hideyuki</name>
<name id="3564" type="Original Work">Hirano Kouta</name>
<name id="12357" type="Direction">Suzuki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="12197" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakamori Ryouji</name>
<name id="2529" type="Music">Matsuo Hayato</name>
<name id="4588" type="Music">Ishii Yasushi</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: The thirteenth and fourteenth episodes were released on December 23 on Blu-ray discs in regular and limited-edition versions. The fifteenth episode was bundled with the sixth limited-edition manga volume.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="200">6.69</permanent>
<temporary count="202">7.15</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>235563.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36480</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>37046</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nbcuni.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/drifters/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Drifters_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドリフターズ_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4284</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>362271</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>366125</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>DriftersAnime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="79268" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="32">8.45</rating>
<name>Shimazu Toyohisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shimazu Toyohisa is the main protagonist and leader of the http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters]. Historically, he died in 1600 during the Battle of Sekigahara. When he first arrived in the new world, he was critically injured, only to be brought to http://anidb.net/ch79269 [Nobunaga] and http://anidb.net/ch79270 [Yoichi]`s hideout by the young elves, http://anidb.net/ch81509 [Marsha] and http://anidb.net/ch81508 [Mark].
Although impulsive and reckless, Toyohisa possesses a fearless, determined, and chivalrous spirit, assisting the elves and dwarves by liberating them from the Orte Empire. Born and raised in a war-torn era, Toyohisa has a keen sense for battle and tactics, though he remains unaware of these talents himself. Toyohisa primarily uses a nodachi in battle, though he is seen carrying a wakizashi. He also carries a Tangeashima on the back of his waist, which he only uses when his swords are infeasible to use against his enemies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>183705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79269" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="36">8.54</rating>
<name>Oda Nobunaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oda Nobunaga is a famous warlord who conquered most of Japan during Sengoku period. He is known for being the daimyo who took the first step of unification of the Japan, and the first Japanese military commander to utilize arquebuses in battles, using one as his main weapon in battle as a http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter]. Historically, he died during the Honnou-ji incident, the mutiny conducted by http://anidb.net/ch11507 [Akechi Mitsuhide].
As a Drifter, he has only aged six months since arriving in the new world. Nobunaga is highly ambitious and cunning, desiring to establish a multiracial federation in the new world with http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa] as their leader. Nobunaga acts as the group`s military strategist.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>183704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79270" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="19">7.10</rating>
<name>Nasu no Yoichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoichi is very effeminate man of nineteen. Although he lived hundreds of years before http://anidb.net/ch79269 [Nobunaga] and http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa], Yoichi is the youngest in the group. Born as the youngest of eleven siblings, Yoichi is a powerful warrior and military commander who served http://anidb.net/ch83938 [Minamoto no Yoshitsune] during the Genpei War. Yoichi`s exploits were recorded throughout Japanese history, including in The Tale of the Heike, though Nobunaga notes that Yoichi acts very differently from these historical accounts. During the Genpei War, he was forced to commit several dishonorable acts by Yoshitsune, despite having a strong belief of Bushido.
Now as a http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter], Yoichi resolves to maintain his honorable nature, and is the most level-headed of the trio. Yoichi acts as the group`s archer, killing fleeing enemies.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>183706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80624" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="23">7.11</rating>
<name>Olminu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Olminu is a young magician of the http://anidb.net/ch86428 [Octobrists]. She is charged with watching http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa]`s group of http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters]. She seems to be quite incompetent at reconnaissance, and is terrified of the Drifters she must follow.
After she is discovered and kidnapped by Toyohisa`s group, she tells them the story of the Drifters and http://anidb.net/ch86430 [Ends]. She is often used as comic relief, shown in a generally incompetent, powerless, and cowardly way, and is a frequent target of sexual harassment by http://anidb.net/ch79269 [Nobunaga], but can be helpful due to her skills in sorcery. Olminu can also serve as an spectator to the story, with the narrative enlightening plot elements through her perception. Her codename is Sem.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>184612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38593" picture="223625.jpg">Kokido Shiho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80626" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="7">6.59</rating>
<name>Abe no Haruakira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Abe no Haruakira, also known as Abe no Seimei, is a legendary Japanese magician who devoted his life to the extermination of the Ends soon after he first appeared in the new world as a http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter]. He now serves as the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch86428 [Octobrist Organization].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>184613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81504" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="5">5.91</rating>
<name>EASY</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>EASY is a young woman with long, black hair, and violet eyes. Apparently at odds with http://anidb.net/ch83939 [Murasaki], she is responsible for the http://anidb.net/ch86430 [Ends], an opposing force similar in origin to the http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters]. She primarily uses her laptop to keep tabs on the battles taking place in the other world. In the corridor, she is associated with and accompanied by darkness.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>195262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81505" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-17">
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<name>Shara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81506" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Scipio Africanus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81507" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="3">6.63</rating>
<name>Hannibal Barca</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hannibal Barca is a famous Carthaginian military commander. Now a http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter] and elderly, he is first seen arguing with http://anidb.net/ch81506 [Scipio Africanus] over the latter`s "plagiarism" of Cannae at the Battle of Zama. Despite nearly being killed by the http://anidb.net/ch81510 [Black King]`s army, Hannibal still insists that victory is still possible. After being separated from Scipio, Hannibal becomes depressed and senile, but he is still able to articulate battle tactics to his fellow Drifters via indirect means. He acts as http://anidb.net/ch79269 [Nobunaga]`s military advisor since being left in http://anidb.net/ch79268 [Toyohisa]`s group`s care.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>193129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="369" picture="223406.jpg">Aoyama Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81510" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Kokuou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Black King is the leader of the http://anidb.net/ch86430 [Ends]. He claims that he once tried to "save" humans, but he has since shifted his agenda towards non-humans after humans "denied" his efforts. His identity has yet to be established, but he is shown to possess healing powers and the ability to multiply any life form he wishes, infinitely producing food or wood. He also has puncture scars in both of his palms.
His ultimate goal is to eradicate all humans and create a new civilization of non-humans in a perpetual Dark Age, ensuring that they never advance far enough to become as destructive as humans, creating what the Black King believes will be a utopia. In order to achieve this, the Black King has instructed http://anidb.net/ch81071 [Rasputin] to create a simple alphabet and a syncretic religion to allow the different non-human races to find a common ground.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>188041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2231" picture="235895.jpg">Kusunoki Taiten</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83936" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="2">3.83</rating>
<name>The Sundance Kid</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83937" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2">4.74</rating>
<name>Butch Cassidy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Butch Cassidy is the leader of the Wild Bunch gang. He, along with http://anidb.net/ch83936 [Sundance Kid], was transported from Bolivia, and is now fighting against the http://anidb.net/ch81510 [Black King] and his armies. Unlike his partner, Butch has a more wild personality. He favors the use of firearms, particularly a pair of pistols, in battle.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>193131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83938" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="2">1.48</rating>
<name>Minamoto no Kurou Hougan Yoshitsune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83940" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-12-31">
<rating votes="3">5.57</rating>
<name>Kanno Naoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanno Naoshi is a World War II fighter pilot. During the battle with the http://anidb.net/ch81510 [Black King], with the http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifters]` side under attack by dragons, he was transported into the world in his plane. He decided to attack the dragons when their attacks reminded him of the U.S. bombing of Tokyo.
His plane later crashed and he soon found himself worshiped as a god by natives, only to be found by http://anidb.net/ch81506 [Scipio], who decides to use his status to unite the various anthropomorphic animal tribes under him to bolster the Drifters` army. He does not initially trust http://anidb.net/ch83937 [Butch] or http://anidb.net/ch83936 [Sundance Kid], as they are American, but Butch manages to convince him that they are Bolivian instead.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>193128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85378" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="3">2.16</rating>
<name>Alesta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alesta is an aide to Count http://anidb.net/ch85379 [Saint-Germi].</description>
<picture>195268.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37719" picture="138626.jpg">Fukuda Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85379" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="4">6.00</rating>
<name>Saint-Germi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saint-Germi is a nobleman and http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter] who owns a quarter of the http://anidb.net/ch86431 [Orte Empire] and was Hitler`s closest ally in its formation. It is said that the Empire could not have existed without his "betrayal", and as such, he is free to live as he pleases without criticism from any of his peers. Despite this position, however, he is not loyal to the Empire and later betrays the Empire when he realizes its impending demise.
He forms an alliance with the Drifters and their allies to take over the Empire. In spite of the fact he is well over fifty years old, Saint-Germi appears as a youthful drag queen with an effeminate personality. He has knowledge of the modern era (due to the fact that he is aware of the existence of firearms and gunpowder), as well as some knowledge of Japanese history.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>195274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85380" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="3">2.16</rating>
<name>Flame</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Flame is an aide to Count http://anidb.net/ch85379 [Saint-Germi].</description>
<picture>195269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85381" type="appears in" update="2016-11-28">
<rating votes="2">5.89</rating>
<name>Yamaguchi Tamon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yamaguchi Tamon is a former Japanese Rear Admiral (posthumously Vice Admiral) and the commander of the Second Carrier Division of the First Air Fleet during World War II.
Tamon appeared as http://anidb.net/ch86429 [Drifter] along with his badly-damaged aircraft carrier Hiryuu which is now beached on a small rocky island. He helped the http://anidb.net/ch86432 [Merchant Guild of Gubinnen] defeat the http://anidb.net/ch86431 [Orte Empire] and take control of the sea trading routes.
Source: Drifters Wiki, edited.</description>
<picture>195272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="415" picture="241624.jpg">Nakano Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93740" type="appears in" update="2018-02-14">
<name>Jigmente-shougun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93741" type="appears in" update="2018-02-14">
<name>Neiselle Brigante</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212972.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3162" picture="151662.jpg">Kiyama Shigeo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93742" type="appears in" update="2018-02-14">
<name>Banzelmassin Shylock VIII</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93743" type="appears in" update="2018-02-14">
<name>Remeku-shougun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2004" picture="67664.jpg">Shinomiya Gou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="183376" update="2018-01-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2017-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リライト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rewrite</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rewrite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191992" update="2018-01-02">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2017-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">BRING ON A WAR</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bring on a War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bring on a War</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194501" update="2019-04-12">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2018-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The outlandish Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Outlandish Knight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Outlandish Knight</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194555" update="2017-12-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒王様御乱心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black King Rogue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro-oosama Omidaregokoro</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
