<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12684" restricted="false">
<type>Music Video</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2013-10-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">6 Heart Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">6HP (Six Hearts Princess) Pink or Black</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">6♥Princess</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12682" type="Other">6HP</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.shuuemura.com/xmas/</url>
<description>Pink or Black?
Every woman has duality in her.
Nice vs Naughty
Innocent vs Sexy
Transform into your other self!
In collaboration with Takashi Murakami`s animation work, shu uemura introduces the holiday collection themed on the "dual beauty" of the pink and black princess. Every woman has pink side and black side in her, nice and naughty, innocent and sexy. Play with fascinating multi-faceted beauty and freely transform yourself from pink to black, black to pink.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="85">3.69</permanent>
<temporary count="86">5.08</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>209110.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20913</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.shuuemura.com/xmas/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=aoTP5Aig-wU</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="192818" update="2017-11-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
