<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12704" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-02</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fate/Apocrypha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">F/A</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">Fate/Apocrypha</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">페이트/아포크리파</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="3348" type="Same Setting">Fate/Stay Night</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="485070">Animation quality noticeably degrades in the second half (in some points it is just painful), the ending is sub par, the pacing is not quite accurate, and the romance comes out of left field and is less than believable (and annoying). 

However, if you are a fan of the Fate/ universe, this is a pretty good addition. The servants and masters are quite interesting and the story is reasonably intriguing.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://fate-apocrypha.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="18144" type="Character Design">Yamada Ariyoshi</name>
<name id="43783" type="Series Composition">Higashide Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="43783" type="Original Work">Higashide Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="927" type="Original Work">Type-Moon</name>
<name id="10241" type="Direction">Asai Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="3326" type="Music">Yokoyama Masaru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel from http://anidb.net/cr927 [Type-Moon]`s popular Fate/stay night franchise, written by http://anidb.net/cr43783 [Higashide Yuuichirou] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr48225 [Konoe Ototsugu].
There was once a Holy Grail War waged by seven Mages and Heroic Spirits in a town called Fuyuki. However, a http://anidb.net/ch89993 [certain Mage] took advantage of the chaos of World War II to steal the Holy Grail. Several decades have passed, and the Yggdmillennia family, who took upon the Holy Grail as its symbol, defected from the Mages` Association and declared their independence. Furious, the Association sent a force to deal with the Yggdmillennia, but they were defeated by the summoned Servants. With the Holy Grail War system changed, war with seven versus seven, breaks out. And so, the curtain rises on the epoch-making Great Holy Grail War.
Source: ANN
Note: The first two episodes received an advance airing on June 30, 2017. Regular TV airing started on July 2, 2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1199">4.62</permanent>
<temporary count="1205">6.39</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>223745.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18983</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36729</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>34662</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>36327</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://fate-apocrypha.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fate/Apocrypha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fate/Apocrypha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4614</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359304</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fate/Apocrypha</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=XRl0fQORwnE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20857</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2620" parentid="2841" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-21">
<name>battle royale</name>
<description>Many characters are removed from their normal lives or lifestyles and thrown into a game where they are forced to battle each other until one survivor remains. Much like the famous film `Battle Royale`.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2777" parentid="2809" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>London</name>
<description>London is the capital and most populous city of both England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south east of the island of Great Britain, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. It was founded by the Romans, who named it Londinium.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214379.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2809" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>United Kingdom</name>
<description>The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain, is a sovereign country in western Europe. Lying off the north-western coast of the European mainland, the UK includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland and many smaller islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64254.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3696" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-28">
<name>off-model animation</name>
<description>Anime shows tend to most often run on an already tight budget; some have even tighter ones. Thus, over the years it became a norm to invest more time and money into the first and last episode, leaving many episodes in the middle to stand severe budget restrictions. This sometimes results in episodes which particularly stand out due to the drop in artwork or animation quality; bar some basic framework, they often have little in common with the rest of the series.
One clue to upcoming off-model animation is the noticeable addition of many Korean names in the production credits, as farming out more animation to Korean artists is a nearly universal indicator of a production company trying to save money in all possible ways.
This effect is often called yashigani, after the infamous http://anidb.net/e4682 [fourth episode] of http://anidb.net/a403 [Lost Universe], Yashigani Hoburu. Another prominent term describing the same effect is "QUALITY animation", with capital letters meant to show contrast to actual quality. http://anidb.net/a4531 [Yoake Mae yori Ruriiro na: Crescent Love] is another legendarily terrible offender: the TV airing of its http://anidb.net/e63752 [third episode] had a perfectly spherical ball in place of what should be a cabbage; the "cabbage" was so egregious that it became closely associated with the anime itself, to a point the show would henceforth be nicknamed "Cabbage Love" among Western viewers.
One should not confuse the yashigani effect with art shifts that stem from guest staff, changes in main staff, intentional art shifts, and similar effects. Another effect one shouldn`t confuse this one with is the so-called DVD/BD enhancement, which is when a studio scrambles to meet the deadline for a TV airing and airs a half-finished episode but eventually fixes it for a disk release; for example, http://anidb.net/cr792 [Shaft] is particularly infamous for its disk enhancements, to a point it has become known as "Shafting", and they prominently feature intentionally weird character models, but they don`t often leave bad artwork on the disk release. Additionally, it should also not be confused with intentional lack of detail on background plane characters; this effect is instead when even the foreground has art quality shifting over time due to the aforementioned budget restrictions.</description>
<picurl>29532.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7083" parentid="2831" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-07">
<name>Romania</name>
<description>Romania is a sovereign state located in Southeastern Europe. It borders the Black Sea, Bulgaria, Ukraine, Hungary, Serbia, and Moldova. The country is the seventh most populous member state of the European Union. Its capital and largest city, Bucharest, is the sixth-largest city in the EU, other major urban areas include Cluj-Napoca, Timișoara, Iași and Constanța.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214407.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7478" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-22">
<name>Matter of Britain</name>
<description>The Matter of Britain is the body of medieval literature and legendary material associated with Great Britain and Brittany, and the legendary kings and heroes associated with it, particularly King Arthur. It was one of the three great story cycles recalled repeatedly in medieval literature, together with the Matter of France, which concerned the legends of Charlemagne, and the Matter of Rome, which included material derived from or inspired by classical mythology.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>241408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="38" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2581">8.43</rating>
<name>Saber</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saber, an agile and powerful warrior. Known as the King of Knights, she maintains a high code of honour. Saber is loyal, independent, and reserved; she appears cold, but is actually suppressing her emotions to focus on her goals. Her class is considered the "Most Outstanding", with excellent ratings in all categories.
In Fate/Zero, though she and Emiya Kiritsugu are Servant and Master seeking the same ultimate goal of peace, their differing ideological perspectives result in a strained relationship where Kiritsugu does not directly acknowledge Saber. After Kiritsugu summoned Saber, he made Irisviel hide Avalon - which had served as a catalyst to the summoning - inside her body so to serve as insurance while she performed her act of fake Master. Irisviel`s and Saber`s role at the time was to openly take action and serve as a decoy in order to lure out enemies, while Kiritsugu worked in the shadows with his assistant, Hisau Maiya. Because Saber could not dematerialise her spiritual body, she disguised herself as a man while staying at Irisviel`s side.
In the Fate route, because her master Emiya Shirou cannot effectively provide her with Mana, she minimises her activity to preserve what she has. Saber is bewildered by Shirou`s "protective" tendencies, and believes his erratic and reckless behaviour jeopardise her chances of winning the Holy Grail War.</description>
<picture>209482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37277" type="appears in" update="2012-05-27">
<rating votes="71">2.39</rating>
<name>Matou Zouken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Matou Zouken is the head of the Matou family and a specialist in worm and insect magecraft. He was originally known as Makiri Zolgen, but he first changed his name to Zouken, and eventually also his family name to Matou. He is quite ancient, being actually some centuries old, having much prolonged his lifespan by means similar to those of vampirism. His goal is to obtain eternal life, and, under his direction, the Matou family fights for the Holy Grail with that objective in mind.</description>
<picture>62482.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57870" type="appears in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="39">7.45</rating>
<name>Lord El-Melloi II</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58806" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="92">5.86</rating>
<name>Jeanne d`Arc</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jeanne d`Arc is the Ruler-class Servant, tasked with ensuring that the Holy Grail War proceeds as intended. She`s a Catholic saint born in Domrémy, France, and the heroine of France who liberated Orléans in the Hundred Years` War.
In anime, she possessed the body of a French girl named Laeticia, whose physique, personality and magical energy were compatible with hers. She has two types of Command Spells - regular ones under her gauntlet, and the ones granting her ability to command other Servants during the Great Holy Grail War on her back.
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>207612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88726" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="19">1.43</rating>
<name>Sieg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sieg is a http://anidb.net/t2027 [homunculus] who is initially nameless. http://anidb.net/ch88738 [Rider of Black] became his Servant after http://anidb.net/ch89997 [his former Master] got killed by http://anidb.net/ch88728 [Saber of Red].
He was created by Yggdmillennia as one of their many homunculi suited for various purposes, initially as a magical energy energy supply for Servants, later as a part of http://anidb.net/ch88739 [Caster of Black]`s golems` cores. Due to his unexpectedly high quality magic circuits, he was considered a good choice for Caster`s Golem Keter Malkuth.
Eventually, he managed to escape from his tank and, after he fell due to exhaustion, Astolfo carried him to his room. http://anidb.net/ch88736 [Chiron] treated him and mentioned that he has only 3 years to live and that he should use them well. With Astolfo`s help, he managed to escape the castle where he was held. Shortly after that, he was gravely wounded by http://anidb.net/ch89996 [Gordes], but saved by http://anidb.net/ch88735 [Siegfried] who sacrificed himself and gave him his heart. Out of gratitude and respect, homunculus gave himself a name after his savior.
Eventually, after he got gravely wounded once again—this time by Mordred—he gained the ability to transform into a Servant in Siegfried`s form for a short amount of time.</description>
<picture>207614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88727" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="12">6.11</rating>
<name>Shirou Kotomine</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shirou Kotomine is http://anidb.net/ch88734 [Assassin of Red]`s Master and initially the stand-in master for all the other servants with the exception of the http://anidb.net/ch88728 [Saber of Red].
Shirou`s true name is Amakusa Shirou Tokisada, the teenage leader of the Shimabara Rebellion. Born in the Edo period, he was a boy of miracles who could nearly be called a saint. However, how exactly he was discovered; a good half of his lifetime is wrapped in mystery. He, who concentrated on his studies since childhood, began to perform many miracles at the frontier for a time. Having healed wounds and walked on water, he eventually began to be enthusiastically worshiped as son of God by the peasants that believed in a prohibited religion.
In reality, he was merely a spellcaster. He wasn`t taught magecraft but it was something that came to him naturally but very rarely. His use of magecraft was mostly subconscious, so he had not even realized it himself. It just so happened that he was born with the power to exercise the miracles called magecraft, and no one around him ever pointed it out, and so he was revered as a boy of miracles.
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>207613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88728" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="34">6.50</rating>
<name>Aka no Saber</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saber of Red is http://anidb.net/ch89992 [Shishigou Kairi]`s Servant.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]Her true name is Mordred, the Knight of Treachery. She is the homunculus daughter of http://anidb.net/ch38 [Arturia Pendragon] and her sister http://anidb.net/ch91576 [Morgan le Fay]. She has a good relationship with her Master and wishes to use the grail to challenge her right to be King of Camelot and have her "father`s" recognition as her heir.
Her Noble Phantasm is Clarent Blood Arthur, a magic sword that can release a massive energy blast.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88729" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-10">
<rating votes="18">3.69</rating>
<name>Aka no Archer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Archer of Red was originally http://anidb.net/ch92255 [Rottweil Berzinsky]`s Servant. Her current Master is http://anidb.net/ch88727 [Shirou Kotomine]. She wishes to use the Grail to protect the children of the world.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]Her true name is Atalanta, a famous huntress known as the Chaste Huntress that appears in Greek Mythology. She is famous for her swift feet in Ancient Greek legend and included as a member of the Argonauts, which assembled brave heroes from all over Greece.
Her Noble Phantasm is Phoebus Catastrophe, which unleashes a devastating rain of arrows down on the enemy.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88730" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-28">
<rating votes="12">7.69</rating>
<name>Aka no Lancer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lancer of Red was originally http://anidb.net/ch92256 [Feend vor Sembren]`s Servant. His current Master is http://anidb.net/ch88727 [Shirou Kotomine].
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]His true name is Karna, the Son of the Sun God, the invulnerable hero of the Indian epic Mahabharata, as a hero on the vanquished side. The central conflict of The Mahabharata is the war over influence between the Pandava and Kaurava royal family. Karna became famous as the rival of Arjuna, the great hero of Hindu mythology.
He possesses multiple Noble Phantasms - Kavacha and Kundala, Brahmastra, Brahmastra Kundala, and Vasavi Shakti - that make him invulnerable and grant him powerful fire attacks.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>212419.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88731" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="9">5.69</rating>
<name>Aka no Rider</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rider of Red was originally Cabik Pentel`s Servant. His current Master is http://anidb.net/ch88727 [Shirou Kotomine].
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]His true name is Achilles, one of the famous heroes in the Trojan Wars. His mother was the immortal nereid Thetis, and his father, the mortal Peleus, was the king of the Myrmidons.
According to the Achilleid, when Achilles was born Thetis tried to make him immortal, by dipping him in the river Styx. However, he was left vulnerable at the part of the body by which she held him, his left heel. In another version of this story, Thetis anointed the boy in ambrosia and put him on top of a fire, to burn away the mortal parts of his body. She was interrupted by Peleus and abandoned both father and son in a rage.
His Noble Phantasm is Troias Tragōidia (Troy`s Tragedy), his war chariot that he can summon.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34070" picture="130103.jpg">Furukawa Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88732" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="10">4.53</rating>
<name>Aka no Caster</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caster of Red was originally http://anidb.net/ch92254 [Jean Rum]`s servant. His current Master is http://anidb.net/ch88727 [Shirou Kotomine].
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]His true name is William Shakespeare, a poet and playwright from the Elizabethan England.
His Noble Phantasm is First Folio, which allows him to trap his enemies in powerful illusions that force them to relive their most traumatic experiences.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88733" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-28">
<rating votes="7">2.07</rating>
<name>Aka no Berserker</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Berserker of Red was originally Diemlet Pentel`s Servant. His current Master is http://anidb.net/ch88739 [Caster of Black].
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]His true name is Spartacus, the strongest gladiator from Thrace and the leader of a large-scale rebellion of slaves in Ancient Rome. He was affiliated with a gladiator training camp in the Campania region, but escaped with 78 of his comrades in 73 B.C. He managed to repulse an assault force of nearly three thousand dispatched by the Romans, leading to him being known as a hero who inspired armed uprisings by slaves in many places. His army grew to seven thousand men, and they kept defeating the Roman army without losing a single battle. They were unable to cross the Alps and instead decided to head to the island of Sicily. They hired pirates to make the voyage, but were betrayed and attacked by the Roman Legions. He always fought at the head of the front lines, and even when the revolt was subjugated by the army, he fought until his death. His name was carved in history as a hope of the oppressed humans.
His Noble Phantasm is Crying Warmonger, which increases his power the more damage he receives.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>212418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88734" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="18">5.69</rating>
<name>Aka no Assassin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Assassin of Red is http://anidb.net/ch88727 [Shirou Kotomine]`s Servant.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]Her true name is Semiramis, the Wise Queen of Assyria. Born from the Syrian mermaid goddess Derketo and a human man, she was left on the waterfront by her loveless mother. She was wrapped in the warm wings of a dove, and fed with the dove`s milk. Semiramis was then found and educated by the shepherd Simmas until she married Onnes, an old general; but she was then taken away by the Syrian king Ninus who fell in love with her thanks to her beautiful face. This forced Onnes to commit suicide, and after Semiramis earned the favors of the king with original battle plans, she married him and formally became queen. A few days after the marriage, she killed the king with poison, and reigned as a regent over Assyria for the next few decades. This is the oldest case of murder by poisoning in legends.
She uses poison as her weapon but also has the ability to summon two Primeval Serpents. Her Noble Phantasm is the Hanging Gardens of Babylon, where she can construct a massive flying fortress.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209554.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="453" picture="45925.jpg">Shindou Kei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88735" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="12">2.90</rating>
<name>Kuro no Saber</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saber of Black is http://anidb.net/ch89996 [Gordes Musik Yggdmillennia]`s Servant. Upon http://anidb.net/ch88726 [Sieg]`s imminent death, he took his heart out and placed it inside him as he always wanted to save someone out of his own volition.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]His true name is Siegfried, the Dragon-Blooded Knight and the Dragon Slayer who defeated the evil dragon Fafnir with the holy sword Balmung in hand. He is a great national hero of Germany that has many different depictions in the various legends attributed to him.
His Noble Phantasm is his sword Balmung, which is capable of releasing a massive energy attack.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88736" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="9">6.22</rating>
<name>Kuro no Archer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Archer of Black is http://anidb.net/ch89994 [Fiore Forvedge Yggdmillennia]`s Servant. His wish is for the gods to return his immortality. He was the teacher of the http://anidb.net/ch88731 [Rider of Red] in previous life.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]His true name is Chiron, a centaur, who was known as a great sage among his kind in Greek mythology. He is the son of the titan Cronus, patron of the harvest and the earth, and the deity Philyra, making him a divine spirit that would not normally qualify for the status of heroic spirit. He received various teachings from the gods. Therefore, young and immature heroes gathered around him as a mentor. However, due to some unfortunate events, he lost his complete divinity along with immortality, allowing him to become an existence that could be summoned by the Grail.
His Noble Phantasm is Antares Snipe, which allows him to shoot a magical arrow that will automatically track its target.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42164" picture="176249.jpg">Takeuchi Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88737" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="5">5.37</rating>
<name>Kuro no Lancer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lancer of Black is http://anidb.net/ch89993 [Darnic Prestone Yggdmillennia]`s servant and leader of the Servants of Black.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]His true name is Vlad III, the Lord Impaler, the greatest hero of Wallachia, whose feats in war caused him to be known fearsomely as the Impaling Prince to the Turks. Due to the legends associated with him, another name has been spread across the world, The Little Dragon, better known as the vampire Count Dracula. While the nation was small, he was a hero who ascended to the throne and managed to turn back the numerous invasions of the Ottoman Empire that had trampled over every other country. Though the model for Dracula, he was not a vampire, but a man of devotion and great hero.
In anime, he despises the Dracula myth as he sees it as a corruption of his efforts in life to save his country and people. His Noble Phantasm is Lord of Execution, allowing him to summon thousands of stakes on which he can impale his enemies.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88738" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="36">5.30</rating>
<name>Kuro no Rider</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rider of Black was http://anidb.net/ch89997 [Celenike Icecolle Yggdmillennia]`s Servant, but became http://anidb.net/ch88726 [Sieg]`s Servant after Celenike`s death.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]His true name is Astolfo, one of the Twelve Paladins of Charlemagne. Among his fellow paladins, he is said to be the most handsome, eternally optimistic and completely lacking in sense. As the legends go, Astolfo was quite the ladies` man.
Astolfo has created many legends as he was an adventurer who flew to all over the world and even reached the Moon in the end. Through his journeys, he had won numerous Mystic Codes such as his flute, his grimoire, and his shining golden lance. Astolfo brought rise to various legends on the back of mounts like a griffin and the famous Rabicano, but particularly famous among them is something inconceivable for this world—the Hippogriff.
Although many are the glorious tales of Astolfo, it is said that he has made just as many mistakes. He was continually defeated in riding tournaments, fell victim to many thaumaturgical traps and even lost—in a matter of hours—the reason that he had picked up at the moon. However, Astolfo never faltered; he did not seem to consider failure or defeat as blunders in the first place.
His Noble Phantasm is Trap of Argalia, which can disable any living thing with a touch. [/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88739" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="3">1.98</rating>
<name>Kuro no Caster</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caster of Black is http://anidb.net/ch88739 [Roche Frain Yggdmillennia]`s Servant.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]His true name is Avicebron, also known as Solomon ibn Gabirol, a twelfth-century poet and philosopher. He was born in Malaga, Spain, and although he did not have the glory of a knight or king or the recognition of having produced works of art that would prosper for thousands of years, he was the father of an entire thaumaturgical system, Kabbalah, and one of the starting points of the process leading up to the European Renaissance through bringing Greco-Arabic and Jewish lore and enlightenment to the cultural circles of Europe. He is recognized as a "hero" who heavily influenced both the history of the world and thaumaturgy.
In anime, he is able to manufacture golems and thus given enough time is an army unto himself. His only wish is to see his Noble Phantasm (an actual living Golem) succeed. His Noble Phantasm is Golem Keter Malkuth, which allows him to construct the ultimate golem.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88740" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="19">6.22</rating>
<name>Kuro no Berserker</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Berserker of Black is http://anidb.net/ch89995 [Caules Forvedge Yggdmillennia]`s Servant. Her wish is to have the Grail give her a mate.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]Her true name is Frankenstein, the Frankenstein`s monster. Based upon the artificial life created by Victor Frankenstein in Mary Shelley`s novel "Frankenstein: or the Modern Prometheus". Victor sought to recreate the original couple described in the bible -- Adam and Eve. Due to the limitations of man, he first built Eve, intending for her to give birth to the counterpart. What started as a patchwork of lifeless flesh was given life by the energy harnessed from lightning. Unfortunately, what awoke was not the ideal woman that Victor envisioned, but an abomination with the mind of an infant. Having no developed capacity for expression, her sense of morality was completely absent. After presenting the entrails of a slain dog as a gift for the master, she was branded a failure and disassembled, before being abandoned completely.
Though still in pieces, she still lived, and over a period of time, was able to reconnect and repair herself. In her former master`s absence, she came into contact with the outside world, and developed the emotions and feelings that could never be created in the first place. Thus she realized a great anger towards the one who abandoned her, but also admiration for the one who was effectively her father. She doggedly pursued the man until finding him in Geneva, Switzerland, where she asked of him to make her a mate. However, he flatly refused. Believing himself to have birthed of a hideous creature, it seemed unthinkable to even consider creating another. Though she pleaded, he denied her again and again, causing her to realize the truth and fall into deep despair. She decided that she must have him create another no matter what, so she killed those acquainted with him, those with no relation at all, and even his fiancee. He continued to flee from her despite that, denying her request to the end.
Getting tired of her persistent chase, Victor fled to the South Pole, choosing to die over granting her one wish. Dying in madness, he regretted her creation until his last breath. With the man she had looked up to gone and without anyone to hate, she parted from Walton, the man who watched over Frankenstein`s final moment, and traveled to the uttermost north. She built herself a pyre, allowing herself to be consumed by the flames.
Her Noble Phantasm is Blasted Tree, which allows her to release massive amounts of electrical energy. This, however, will causes her to self-destruct, and she`s destroyed by the usage of her Noble Phantasm as a result of attacking http://anidb.net/ch88728 [Mordred] with it. It is also capable of reviving http://anidb.net/ch88726 [Sieg]`s heart.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88741" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="23">3.75</rating>
<name>Kuro no Assassin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Assassin of Black is http://anidb.net/ch89999 [Rikudou Reika]`s Servant. She was originally summoned by Sagara Hyouma but kills him when he tries to sacrifice Reika during the summoning and transfers master status to Reika.
[spoiler="True Name and Noble Phantasm"]Her true name is Jack the Ripper, the Legendary Serial Killer. Although there are numerous theories about who Jack the Ripper could have been, she is one interpretation of the series of gory murders in 19th Century England. Her true nature is that of a collection of wraiths born from the aborted children of prostitutes in Whitechapel, London. Because she is a collection of wraiths and not a single entity, piercing her heart will not lead to her immediate death, but the spillage of said wraiths.
Once the number of aborted children who were disposed of in rivers reached the ten-thousands, the collection of resentment that the children shared eventually formed the shape of a human. Because she was created from children who had yet to even be born, she lacked common sense and morality, and simply killed prostitutes so she could return to the womb. To put it another way, this is the heretical Jack who was born from the "side of the victims".
After killing several women, she was given the name "Jack the Ripper," and rejoiced at having been given a name that she had been denied for so long. However, even they themselves do not know for certain whether or not they were "Jack the Ripper". After all, they are an amalgamation of evil spirits, so their memories are always vague and, even if they remember having killed prostitutes, it`s uncertain who exactly they killed. What they kill as Assassin is not a specific individual, but rather the society that killed them, and the strong emotions they carry cannot be understood by any other hero, making them beyond salvation. Eventually, a magus discovered that the culprit of the bizarre killings was of a magical nature and extinguished her.
She will likely perpetually reign as an eternal mystery and eternal darkness carved into the history of England. While her identity was never discovered, her knives were left behind after her death and later obtained by Sagara Hyouma.
Her Noble Phantasm is Maria the Ripper, which allows her to instantly kill any female target as long as certain conditions are met.[/spoiler]
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="483" picture="27541.jpg">Tange Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89992" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="14">6.33</rating>
<name>Shishigou Kairi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shishigou Kairi is a freelance necromancer. He summoned http://anidb.net/ch88728 [Saber of Red] with a splinter of the Round Table.
Kairi is the seventh generation head of the Shishigou family, surprising for a family whose origins lie in the Far East where magecraft had a lesser standing. It was thought that he would follow in the footsteps of his father, Touki Shishigou, whose treatise had been highly praised at the Clock Tower of the Mage`s Association. The curse of the previous Shishigou generation has activated on Kairi, resulting him unable to produce children. His parents decided that Kairi should adopt a distant relative as his daughter, who they hoped will receive his Magic Crest. Unfortunately, she died as they tried transferring Kairi`s Crest onto her. He was devastated when she died and accepted that the Shishigou would end with his generation. Rather than following the similar path of a researcher, he left his family and education behind him before the end of his third year there, taking on the path of a bounty hunter and freelancer. He didn`t cut all ties with the Association and latest job he took was from http://anidb.net/ch91565 [Rocco Belfeban].
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209569.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89993" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="5">2.05</rating>
<name>Darnic Prestone Yggdmillennia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Darnic Prestone Yggdmillennia is http://anidb.net/ch88737 [Lancer of Black]`s Master and the leader of the Yggdmillennia group. He is almost a century old despite looking in his 20s as a result of researching eternal youth. He plundered the Holy Grail from the Third Holy Grail War of Fuyuki.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89994" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="11">4.56</rating>
<name>Fiore Forvedge Yggdmillennia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fiore Forvedge Yggdmillennia is http://anidb.net/ch88736 [Archer of Black]`s Master and a magus with great talent who is well versed in spiritual evocation and human engineering. She has been confined to a wheelchair since birth and wishes to have the Grail to heal her legs while keeping her magus abilities (something that would not be possible otherwise).
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89995" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="7">3.48</rating>
<name>Caules Forvedge Yggdmillennia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caules Forvedge Yggdmillennia is http://anidb.net/ch88740 [Berserker of Black]`s Master and an magus who can summon low-class spirits, insects and animals.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89996" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="9">1.58</rating>
<name>Gordes Musik Yggdmillennia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gordes Musik Yggdmillennia is http://anidb.net/ch88735 [Saber of Black]`s Master and an first-class alchemist.
Gordes comes from the Musik house, which once boasted a skill with alchemy which rivaled the Einzberns. Their thaumaturgical blood had eventually decayed enough that they were forced to fold themselves into the ranks of Yggdmillennia. It was shameful for such a once-famed house to have been absorbed by another, so Gordes` mother and father constantly told him of their legacy as alchemists from his youth. At the age of thirty-six, he is unable to separate dream from reality, having been raised to be proud of his family`s former legacy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89997" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="13">2.21</rating>
<name>Celenike Icecolle Yggdmillennia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celenike Icecolle Yggdmillennia is http://anidb.net/ch88738 [Rider of Black]`s Master and an Dark Arts practitioner who has sadistic and deviant sexual tastes. She was beheaded by http://anidb.net/ch88728 [Saber of Red].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89998" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="3">1.90</rating>
<name>Roche Frain Yggdmillennia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Roche Frain Yggdmillennia is http://anidb.net/ch88739 [Caster of Black]`s Master and a prodigy magus who creates golems with his Servant.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209568.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89999" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="9">5.57</rating>
<name>Rikudou Reika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rikudou Reika is http://anidb.net/ch88741 [Assassin of Black]`s Master and a prostitute with no talent as a magus so she has Assassin devour violent criminals to supply her with energy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91565" type="appears in" update="2017-09-26">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Rocco Belfeban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91566" type="appears in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="8">4.79</rating>
<name>Flat Escardos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91574" type="appears in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Serge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91575" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="5">5.94</rating>
<name>Tool</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tool is a female homunculus of Yggdmillennia, created by Gordes. Though her Magic Circuits are meager, she excels in fighting ability and inspiration, so she was selected as a commander. Just as told in the novels, battle-type homunculi have extremely short lifespans, with a limit of two to three months of life.
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>207609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91576" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="2">4.89</rating>
<name>Morgan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morgan le Fay is the sister of http://anidb.net/ch38 [King Arthur] and mother of http://anidb.net/ch88728 [Mordred].
Morgan was born as the proper, recognized daughter of King Uther. Although the older sister and of the same status, Arturia received the love and hopes of their father in Morgan`s eyes, driving her to eventually become a witch queen who craved for vengeance for the rest of her days. During Arturia`s training, Morgan executed a trap, and due to Merlin`s womanizing, Arturia was caught up in it and lost Caliburn. Once Camelot was built, she went into seclusion. She sent Agravain as an assassin. She was a fairy of the lake and the evil polar opposite of Vivian, the Lady of the Lake.
She eventually enchanted Arturia, a pseudo-male at the time due to Merlin`s intervention to produce an heir, and extracted sperm from Arturia to develop as a homunculus clone within her ovary. Mordred was soon born and aged rapidly, and Morgan raised her in secret while telling her of her right to the throne. She told Mordred to never remove her helmet and recommended her to the Round Table. She directed Mordred to hide her status and obey the King until she could defeat Arturia and take her place. While Mordred was initially idealistic and served as a proper knight, Morgan shattered her innocence with the truth of her birth to guide her towards the path of rebellion.
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>207611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91975" type="appears in" update="2017-10-24">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Dicale</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43111" picture="183457.jpg">Kobayashi Tatsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92190" type="appears in" update="2017-11-06">
<rating votes="4">6.70</rating>
<name>Medea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92246" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2">2.27</rating>
<name>Gilles de Rais</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92254" type="appears in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="2">3.83</rating>
<name>Jean Rum</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jean Rum is the original Master of http://anidb.net/ch88732 [Caster of Red] and is highly skilled in wind element magic.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209581.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92255" type="appears in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Rottweil Berzinsky</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rottweil Berzinsky is the original Master of http://anidb.net/ch88729 [Archer of Red] and is a freelance magus.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209579.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92256" type="appears in" update="2017-11-11">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Feend vor Sembren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Feend vor Sembren is the original Master of http://anidb.net/ch88730 [Lancer of Red] and a first-class instructor at the Clock Tower.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209580.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92266" type="appears in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Sagara Hyouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sagara Hyouma was originally http://anidb.net/ch88741 [Assassin of Black]`s Master, but was killed by her right after the summoning ritual and before he transferred his Command Spells to her new master, http://anidb.net/ch89999 [Rikudou Reika], who was supposed to be a sacrifice used in the ritual.</description>
<picture>209619.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92278" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="4">5.15</rating>
<name>Sieg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sieg, after he gained the ability to transform into a Servant in http://anidb.net/ch88735 [Siegfried]`s form for a short amount of time.</description>
<picture>209623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92280" type="appears in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Golem Keter Malkuth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Golem Keter Malkuth is http://anidb.net/ch88739 [Caster of Black]`s Noble Phantasm, a golem that he could not complete during his lifetime. Unlike regular Noble Phantasms that can be called "complete existences", it was recorded in history despite being incomplete.
Caster of Black`s wish in participating in the Holy Grail War was its completion, but simply constructing it wasn`t enough. He wished to reproduce God`s miracle in the creation of life, bringing forth a copy of the Primordial Human, Adam, so simply creating a golem of unparalleled power would not allow it to become a perfect existence.
For his golem to work, he needed a functional core to supply the magical energy needed to sustain it. He initially wanted to use http://anidb.net/ch88726 [Sieg] as a core, due to his exceptional Magic Circuits, but in the end he used http://anidb.net/ch89998 [his Master] instead.
After the Caster of Black was gravely wounded by the http://anidb.net/ch88736 [Archer of Black], he fused himself with his golem and assumed control.
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>209641.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92906" type="appears in" update="2017-12-18">
<rating votes="4">6.57</rating>
<name>Saber</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210945.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93187" type="appears in" update="2018-01-05">
<rating votes="7">5.17</rating>
<name>Laeticia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Laeticia is an ordinary French girl who got dragged in the Great Holy Grail War, after http://anidb.net/ch58806 [Ruler] chose her as her possession vessel. She`s a decent and honest person who has no Magic Circuits, but her religious piety alone surpasses that of others. Though she has lived an extremely normal life, she loaned her body upon Jeanne d`Arc`s request. Her facial features and style is only partly similar to Ruler`s. Due the effects of the possession, her body was somewhat changed to match Ruler`s.
Despite being dragged into the Great Holy Grail War, emotionally it was like watching a movie inside a dream for her. She served as the witness to Ruler and http://anidb.net/ch88726 [Sieg]`s relationship, and she was, in a certain sense, the final stronghold for Jeanne, a sheep that allowed Jeanne not to notice her own feelings of love.
After Ruler left her body, her appearance returned to normal and her memories of the Great Holy Grail War vanished. Despite this, she found a direction for her prayers in the form of wishing that "those two may find happiness together", and she prays believing in such small miracles every day.
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>211646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93235" type="appears in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="40">7.52</rating>
<name>Reines El-Melloi Archisorte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228556.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="94434" type="appears in" update="2018-03-10">
<name>Einzbern Master</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The unnamed Einzbern Master is the Master of http://anidb.net/ch40363 [Avenger] in the Third Holy Grail War mentioned in Fate/hollow ataraxia and the Master of http://anidb.net/ch88727 [Ruler] in the Third Holy Grail War of the Fate/Apocrypha universe.
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>214611.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="94436" type="appears in" update="2020-03-07">
<rating votes="1">4.77</rating>
<name>Merlin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Merlin, the Magus of Flowers, is a prophet and advisor who made his entry into Arthurian Legends as the court magus.
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>244835.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94437" type="appears in" update="2018-03-10">
<rating votes="2">5.80</rating>
<name>Justeaze Lizrich von Einzbern</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Justeaze Lizrich von Einzbern is the head of the Einzbern family at the founding of the Holy Grail War.
Source: TYPE-MOON Wiki</description>
<picture>214615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="333" picture="18379.jpg">Kobayashi Sanae</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="183374" update="2016-12-31">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-12-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV (1:01)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186459" update="2017-04-16">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (1:08)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188446" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生の代償, 死の償い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Price of Life, Redemption of Death</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">삶의 대가, 죽음의 속죄</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sei no Daishou, Shi no Tsugunai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188447" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歩き出す運命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fate Begins to Move</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">운명의 첫걸음</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arukidasu Unmei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188448" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖女の出立</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saint`s Departure</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">성녀의 출발</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seijo no Shuttatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188449" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">外典: 聖杯大戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Apocrypha: Grail Contest</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">외전: 성배대전</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gaiten: Seihai Taisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189111" update="2017-07-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">開戦の狼煙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Onset of Warfare</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">개전의 낭연</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaisen no Noroshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189112" update="2017-07-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自由の在処</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where Freedom Lies</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">자유의 소재</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jiyuu no Arika</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189113" update="2017-07-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">叛逆の騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Knight of Rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">반역의 기사</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hangyaku no Kishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189114" update="2017-07-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天の声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Voice of Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">하늘의 소리</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ten no Koe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189971" update="2017-08-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖人の凱旋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saint`s Return</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">성인의 개선</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seijin no Gaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189972" update="2017-08-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の輝き</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternal Radiance</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">영원한 빛</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Kagayaki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189973" update="2017-08-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花と散る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scatter with the Flowers</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">꽃처럼 흩날리다</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hana to Chiru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189974" update="2017-08-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">百の焔と百の華</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Hundred Flames and One Hundred Flowers</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">백의 불꽃과 백의 꽃</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyaku no Honoo to Hyaku no Hana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190708" update="2017-09-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャック・ザ・リッパー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jack the Ripper</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">잭 더 리퍼</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jack the Ripper</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190709" update="2017-09-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">道は違えど</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Differing Paths</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">길은 달라도</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michi wa Chigaedo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190710" update="2017-09-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">救世の祈り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prayer of Salvation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">구세의 기도</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyousei no Inori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190711" update="2017-09-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後のマスター</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Master</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">최후의 마스터</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Master</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190785" recap="true" update="2017-09-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖杯大戦開幕編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">성배대전 개막편</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seihai Taisen Kaimaku Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191726" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">空を駆ける</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soar Through the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">하늘을 달리다</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora o Kakeru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191727" update="2017-10-15">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">終わりの朝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dawn of the End</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">마지막 아침</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Owari no Asa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191728" update="2017-10-15">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フロム・ヘル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">프롬 헬</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">From Hell</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191729" update="2017-10-15">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トロイメライ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Traumerei</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">트로이메라이</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Traumerei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192619" recap="true" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖杯大戦動乱編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">성배대전 동란편</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seihai Taisen Douran Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193204" update="2017-11-19">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖杯戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Holy Grail War</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">성배전쟁</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seihai Sensou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193205" update="2017-11-19">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼方へと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Going Beyond</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">저편으로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanata e to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193206" update="2017-11-19">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会と別離</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion and Farewell</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">재회와 이별</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai to Betsuri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193207" update="2017-11-19">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天蠍一射[アンタレス・スナイプ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Antares Snipe</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">천갈일사</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Antares Snipe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193889" update="2017-12-17">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193890" update="2017-12-17">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193891" update="2017-12-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193892" update="2017-12-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194184" update="2017-12-23">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-31</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Apocrypha</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Apocrypha</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">Apocrypha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Apocrypha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198735" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T26</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第25話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 25 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198736" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T25</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-12-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第24話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 24 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198737" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T24</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-12-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第23話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 23 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198738" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-12-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第22話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 22 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198739" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-11-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第21話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 21 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198740" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-11-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第20話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 20</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 20 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198741" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-11-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第19話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 19 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198742" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-11-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第18話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 18 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198743" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第17話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 17 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198744" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-10-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第16話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 16 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198745" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第15話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 15 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198746" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第14話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 14</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 14 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198747" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第13話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 13 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198748" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-09-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第12話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 12 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198749" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第11話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 11 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198750" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第10話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 10 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198751" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第9話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 9 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198752" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第8話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 8 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198753" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第7話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 7 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198754" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第6話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 6 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198755" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第5話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 5 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198756" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第4話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 4 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198757" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第3話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 3 Wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198758" update="2019-08-26">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「Fate/Apocrypha」黒のライダーの次回予告 第2話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Fate/Apocrypha" Kuro no Rider no Jikai Yokoku Dai 2 Wa</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
