<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1271" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>39</episodecount>
<startdate>1975-05-15</startdate>
<enddate>1976-03-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Getter Robo G</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Formators</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Formators</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Force Five: Starvengers</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Jet Robot</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゲッターロボG</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Starvengers</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Getta Robot G</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1910" type="Sequel">Getter Robo Gou</anime>
<anime id="955" type="Prequel">Getter Robo</anime>
<anime id="1652" type="Character">Grendizer, Getter Robo G, Great Mazinger: Kessen! Daikaijuu!</anime>
<anime id="2223" type="Other">Great Mazinger tai Getter Robo G: Kuuchuu Dai-Gekitotsu</anime>
<anime id="10999" type="Other">Robot Girls Z Plus</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/getter_g/</url>
<creators>
<name id="868" type="Original Work">Nagai Gou</name>
<name id="737" type="Work">Toei</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="4419" type="Original Work">Ishikawa Ken</name>
<name id="3354" type="Original Work">Dynamic Production</name>
<name id="3962" type="Music">Kikuchi Shunsuke</name>
<name id="3184" type="Character Design">Komatsubara Kazuo</name>
</creators>
<description>The story take place just after the end of Getter Robo when the empire of the Oni, some sort of demons in the japanese mythology, wipes out the enemies of the first series: the dinosaurs. The primary goals of the oni`s empire, whose leader is the emperor Brai, it`s to take over the world and the getter rays technology. Dr. Saotome builds a new Getter Robo, the Getter Robo G, that is much stronger than the first one and still composed by three getter-machines: Dragon, the red one, Ryger, the blue one (instead of the white one of the first series) and Poseidon, the yellow one. The Getter`s pilots are the same except for the third getter-machine where Benkei has replaced Musashi.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="79">4.68</permanent>
<temporary count="82">6.12</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>143796.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1993</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4486</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1896</identifier>
<identifier>uxrbte</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toei-anim.co.jp/lineup/tv/getter_g/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Getter_Robo_G</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゲッターロボG</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89513</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="16">
<externalentity>
<identifier>178</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2847" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-22">
<name>Western</name>
<description>The setting and/or world are pretty much like in Western films depicting the American Old West, with cowboys, Indians, deserts, small towns, bounty hunters, and lots of revolvers.
Just think John Wayne, Clint Eastwood, and Sergio Leonne`s The Good, The Bad and The Ugly, or A Fistful of Dollars.</description>
<picurl>220675.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="32203" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Saotome Genki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The younger daughter of Dr. Saotome, she becomes traumatized after witnessing what truly happened to her older sister. When the nuclear bomb exploded, the trauma of everything caused her to go amnesic, where she began life fresh as "Kei Kuruma", Benkei`s tomboyish daughter.</description>
<seiyuu id="25701" picture="71454.jpg">Kikuchi Kouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32210" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-24">
<rating votes="24">4.28</rating>
<name>Saotome Hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82087.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3301" picture="24327.jpg">Tomita Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32211" type="main character in" update="2011-05-13">
<rating votes="74">8.24</rating>
<name>Nagare Ryouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nagare Ryouma is a fictional character created by Go Nagai and Ken Ishikawa. He is the protagonist and main pilot in the Getter Robo franchise. He is a hot-blooded youth in high school. He pilots the Getter-1, Getter Dragon, and Shin Getter-1 in the manga and anime.
Ryouma goes to high school with Musashi, Hayato, and Michiru. He travels to the Satome Research Institute on the day the Prototype Getter Robo is being tested. He witnesses the death of the Prototype Getter Robo team including the son of Professor Tomoe at the hands of the Evil Dinosaur Empire. He enlists the aid of Musashi Tomoe and Hayato Jin in order to pilot the real Getter Robo. Ryoma piloting the Getter-1 is key to battling the Dinosaur Empire. Ryouma and his friends fight the Dinosaur Empire until the final battle in which Musahi gives his life to defeat them.
Even after the defeat of the Dinosaur Empire, a new threat arises in the form of the Clan of the 100 Demons. The remaining members of the Getter Robo team get Benkei Kurama to pilot the last jet of the Getter Robo G. Ryouma pilots the Getter Dragon in the second series.
In the 1998 OVA series Getter Robo Armageddon, Ryouma was framed for the murder of Dr. Saotome. After a resurrected Dr. Saotome threatens to destroy the world, he is released from jail to commit the very murder he was accused of. Ryouma holds a grudge with Hayato; who not only committed the murder of Saotome, he also testified against him. After failing to stop a nuclear attack on Shin Dragon, he vanishes from Earth. He reappears 13 years later in an abandoned base located on the Moon. He rejoins the fight against The Invaders piloting a customized Getter, the Black Getter.
Ryouma appears as a supporting characters in Shin Getter Robo vs Neo Getter Robo. Mentally scarred after being tortured by the Dinosaur Empire and the death of Musashi, he quits the Getter Team and wanders Japan as a martial artist. He returns and helps the New Getter Team when the Dinosaurs Empire attempts to destroy Shin Getter Robo.</description>
<picture>71452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32214" type="main character in" update="2012-02-24">
<rating votes="8">5.91</rating>
<name>Kuruma Benkei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A baseball player, pilot of the third robot in the second series.</description>
<picture>82086.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32215" type="main character in" update="2012-02-24">
<rating votes="31">8.39</rating>
<name>Jin Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jin Hayato is a fictional character from the mecha series, Getter Robo. The aloof and seemingly anti-social Hayato Jin, displays considerable skill at various sports, but generally likes to be left alone. Despite this he eventually gets all the girls, including the Kyoryu Empire android spies. Hayato pilots the Jaguar Machine into battle with Ryoma Nagare and Musashi Tomoe. When combined with the others he pilots Getter 2. The machine reflects Hayato`s physical strength and speed.</description>
<picture>82084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21114" picture="39572.jpg">Yamada Shunji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32221" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-28">
<rating votes="6">3.33</rating>
<name>Saotome Michiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>82422.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5058" picture="43359.jpg">Yoshida Rihoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32222" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Saotome Kazuko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="25701" picture="71454.jpg">Kikuchi Kouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32224" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Oogarashi Monji</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3360" picture="24707.jpg">Yada Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32225" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Asatarou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32231" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Guraa Hakase</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3360" picture="24707.jpg">Yada Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32232" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Hidoraa Gensui</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32233" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-13">
<name>Burai Taitei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="36005" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">甦れゲッターロボ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revive, Getter Robo!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaere Getter Robo!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36006" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大攻撃! メカ要塞鬼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fear Of Imagination</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daikougeki! Mecha Yousai Oni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="36007" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐怖の水爆大作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Frightening Hydrogen Bomb Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoufu no Suibaku Daisakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39781" update="2005-09-01">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>105</length>
<title xml:lang="en">US Compilation Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41618" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">百鬼老兵は死なず</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 35</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakki Rouhei wa Shinazu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41619" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツバメよ元気に飛べ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 27</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubame yo Genki ni Tobe!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41620" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪の罠! 空飛ぶ船団</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Insidious Trap! The Flying Fleet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aku no Wana! Soratobu Sendan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41621" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夜空に輝く二つ星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Stars Shining in the Night Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yozora ni Kagayaku Futatsu Boshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41622" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベンケイ暗殺計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 36</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Benkei Ansatsu Keikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41623" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月光に踊るピエロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekkou ni Odoru Pierot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41624" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こうもり爆弾! 危機一髪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bat Bomb! In the Nick of Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koumori Bakudan! Kikiippatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41625" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大決戦! シャインスパーク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daikessen! Shine Spark</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41626" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大決戦! 日本上空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 39</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daikessen! Nippon Joukuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41627" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SOS! ゲッターロボ応答せよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SOS! Getter Robo, Please Respond</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SOS! Getter Robo Ootou Seyo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41628" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海に叫ぶ少年!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi ni Sakebu Shounen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41629" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">元気あの子ってなんなのさ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 32</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genki Ano Kotte Nanna no Sa!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41630" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死闘! 嵐吹く男の道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitou! Arashi Fuku Otoko no Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41631" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブライ決死の大反撃!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 38</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Burai Kesshi no Daihangeki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41632" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恐るべき百鬼帝国の謎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of the Fearsome 100 Demon Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osorubeki Hyakki Teikoku no Nazo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41633" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海底に消えたジャンボ機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitei ni Kieta Jumbo Ki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41634" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ベンケイ! 涙の勝利</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Benkei! Victory of Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Benkei! Namida no Shouri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41635" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドライスノー奇襲作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 30</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dry Snow Kishuu Sakusen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41636" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">湖に消えたミチル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizuumi ni Kieta Michiru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41637" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼になったあいつ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oni ni Natta Aitsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41638" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-08-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友達は風になった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Friend Became Like the Wind</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi wa Kaze ni Natta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41639" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃えろ! リョウの剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 31</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moero! Ryou no Ken</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41640" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤い蝶のバラード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akaichou no Ballad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41641" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遥かなる荒野の決闘!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of the Far Wilderness!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haruka Naru Arano no Kettou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41642" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涙のあとに口笛を</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 29</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Namida no Ato ni Kuchibue o</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41643" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">百鬼帝国! 将軍への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hyakki Empire! The Road to the General</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyakki Teikoku! Shougun e no Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41644" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔の島を攻撃せよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack the Demon Island!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma no Shima o Kougeki Seyo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41645" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">緑の地球が死ぬ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 28</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Midori no Chikyuu ga Shinu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41646" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夕焼け空が知っている</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 33</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuyake Sora ga Shitte Iru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41647" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢を引き裂く百鬼一族</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dream Shredding Hyakki Empire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume o Hikisaku Hyakki Ichizoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41648" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危機迫る日本近海!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 37</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiki Semaru Nippon Kinkai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41649" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1976-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! 百鬼三兄弟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 34</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Hyaku Oni San Kyoudai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41650" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追跡! 黒いジェット機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After That Black Jet!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuiseki! Kuroi Jet Ki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41651" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危うし伊豆半島沖!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayaushi Izuhantou Oki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41652" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">早乙女博士を救出せよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saotome Hakase o Kyuushutsu Seyo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="41653" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1975-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コロよ明日に吠えろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koroyo Ashita ni Hoero!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102035" update="2009-05-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102036" update="2009-05-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
