<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1272" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-02-18</startdate>
<enddate>2000-05-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kinbaku no Yakata: Ryakudatsu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">淫辱調教~メイド&amp;義母~ (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">긴박의 관</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Injoku Choukyou: Maid &amp; Gibo (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">緊縛の館 ~略奪~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Bondage Mansion</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.vanilla-jp.com/catalog/kinbaku/re_vol1.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="756" type="Animation Work">Y.O.U.C.</name>
<name id="757" type="Work">Digital Works</name>
<name id="23256" type="Original Work">Grand Blue</name>
<name id="6182" type="Direction">Nagahama Norihiko</name>
<name id="1710" type="Music">Yoshi.Hoka</name>
</creators>
<description>Mimura Yukio came from a wealthy family and never wanted for anything. Kind and gentle, he obediently fulfills his dying father`s final request: find a previously unknown cousin and allow him to live in the family mansion. But his cousin Hayato has other ideas for the family`s mansion, its fortune, and especially Yukio`s girlfriend Reika...
Woefully unaware of his family`s sadomasochistic history, Yukio is forced to agree to a sexual competition to avoid the exposure of the family`s dark secrets. A competition where Reika has become the playing field: the first to break her (as one would break a horse) is the one who gets both the mansion and the money.
Note: On 25.07.2008, Strawberry Jam re-released Kinbaku no Yakata: Ryakudatsu bundled with http://anidb.net/a658 [Haitoku no Shoujo] under the name Injoku Choukyou: Maid &amp; Gibo (淫辱調教～メイド&amp;義母～).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="264">3.13</permanent>
<temporary count="274">5.36</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>210327.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>489</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2894</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2625</identifier>
<identifier>ueavbr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.vanilla-jp.com/catalog/kinbaku/re_vol1.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>160068</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2225" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>whipping</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2708" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>uncensored version available</name>
<description>There`s an uncensored version available of the porn anime this tag is added to, which in most cases means, that there was a region 1 DVD (R1 DVD = North America) release.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2711" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>urination</name>
<description>Urination, also known as micturition, voiding, peeing, weeing, pissing, and more rarely, emiction, is the ejection of urine from the urinary bladder through the urethra to the outside of the body. In healthy humans the process of urination is under voluntary control. In infants, some elderly individuals, and those with neurological injury or extreme psychological problems, urination may occur as an involuntary reflex. In other animals, in addition to expelling waste material, urination can mark territory or express submissiveness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2715" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>rape</name>
<description>Rape means to force someone to engage in sexual interaction without their consent. If the rape is not successfully executed (both fellatio and penetration did not occur), tag with http://anidb.net/t7238 [attempted rape] instead.</description>
<picurl>212186.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2719" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-19">
<name>gang bang</name>
<description>A situation in which one person has sexual intercourse and performs other sex acts with a number of people, either in turn or at the same time.</description>
<picurl>181529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2735" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>enema</name>
<description>An enema is the procedure of introducing liquids into the rectum and colon via the anus for the purpose of cleaning the insides or for BDSM play.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3253" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-17">
<name>Vanilla Series</name>
<description>The Vanilla Series is a collection of unrelated hentai produced by http://anidb.net/cr757 [Digital Works].</description>
<picurl>2697.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="13586" update="2005-04-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2000-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13587" update="2005-04-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2000-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
