<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12732" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-08-18</startdate>
<enddate>2016-08-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="main">Seoulyeok</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Seoul Station</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">서울역</title>
</titles>
<creators>
<name id="58299" type="Direction">Yeon Sang-ho</name>
</creators>
<description>A homeless person at Seoul Station goes insane and the insanity spreads rapidly around the area. Soon, the whole city is in complete pandemonium.
Source: Asian Media Wiki
The film serves as the prequel to the live-action film Train to Busan by the same director.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="66">3.78</permanent>
<temporary count="66">5.59</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>10411.jpeg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34048</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Seoul_Station_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359610</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>서울역_(영화)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2796" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>movie</name>
<description>Based on a live action film, Japanese or otherwise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3815" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>human cannibalism</name>
<description>Cannibalism is the practice of an individual of a species eating parts or the whole of another individual of the same species; as such, human cannibalism is when a human eats the flesh, organs, or other parts of another human being.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6166" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-23">
<name>South Korean production</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/t6762 [North Korean production]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6850" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-13">
<name>STAFF MISSING</name>
<description>This anime is missing staff credits. If you can, please assign staff credits to the anime accordingly and then remove the tag.
If the tag is set on an anime level, please assign preferably all credits and then remove it from the anime. If that is not feasible, please assign, at a minimum, credits for all the major/key staff and then transfer it to all relevant episodes (broadly speaking, regular episodes and S-type episodes containing animation). If the tag is already set on an episode level, please assign all credits, including minor staff, to the episode and then remove the tag from it.
Likewise, this tag should either be applied on an anime level, when it is missing key staff (in full or in part), or to all relevant episodes, when key staff is present but at least some episodes don`t have full staff.
For further information on assigning staff credits, please see http://wiki.anidb.net/Content:Staff_Credits [the AniDB Wiki article on them].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="183943" update="2017-01-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2016-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
