<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1275" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>1990-09-25</startdate>
<enddate>1991-02-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bouken! Iczer 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Adventures With Iczer 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Adventure! Iczer-3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Iczer 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">冒険!イクサー3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Iczer Reborn</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Iczer-3 - A Última Guerreira Iczer</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1246" type="Sequel">Iczer-Girl Iczelion</anime>
<anime id="436" type="Prequel">Tatakae!! Iczer 1</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="995" type="Unknown Relation">Polydor Records</name>
<name id="8205" type="Music">Kudou Takashi</name>
<name id="1936" type="Character Design">Hirano Toshihiro</name>
<name id="1936" type="Original Work">Hirano Toshihiro</name>
<name id="1936" type="Chief Direction">Hirano Toshihiro</name>
<name id="1936" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirano Toshihiro</name>
<name id="1936" type="Series Composition">Hirano Toshihiro</name>
</creators>
<description>In deep space a battle wages between the forces of good and evil and the fate of the Earth hangs in the balance.
The evil Neos Gold dispatches her invading forces towards Earth with only one aim: the total destruction of all mankind. Now it`s up to Iczer 3 - the younger sister of Iczer 1 - to defend the Earth from the deadly armada of Neos Gold, with only the Earth`s single remaining battle cruiser on her side. But don`t count her out - what Iczer 3 lacks in experience she makes up for in all-out enthusiasm.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="165">3.62</permanent>
<temporary count="165">5.56</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>6950.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>682</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2292</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>483</identifier>
<identifier>raeznq</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Adventure!_Iczer_3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>冒険!イクサー3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88605</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2015</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2233</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>visiting alien superhero</name>
<description>Sometimes, the Earth does not have enough of its own Defenders of Justice. In such cases, a "Gastarbeiter" hero from a foreign planet or world has to appear to save the day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3516" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>insects of doom</name>
<description>Concerns insects, be them biological, magical or robotic in nature, that are either the bane, or a major stepping stone in the way of the main character(s) of the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5871" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-19">
<name>breathing in space</name>
<description>Find yourself in space without an oxygen tank? Not a problem! Breathing in the vacuum of space is just as easy as breathing on Earth, especially if you are a superhero or somehow able to leave the atmosphere under your own power.</description>
<picurl>166122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="21971" type="main character in" update="2010-09-29">
<name>Atros</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21972" type="main character in" update="2011-02-20">
<rating votes="7">8.37</rating>
<name>Iczer 1</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3607.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3274" picture="24702.jpg">Yamamoto Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21973" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="7">9.02</rating>
<name>Iczer 2</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>3608.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1734" picture="38029.jpg">Toda Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21974" type="main character in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="2">8.49</rating>
<name>Iczer 3</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21544" picture="55610.jpg">Cuty Suzuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21975" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-12">
<name>Insect</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21976" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-12">
<name>Candy Barts</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21977" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-12">
<name>Golem</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5058" picture="43359.jpg">Yoshida Rihoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21978" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-14">
<name>Sister Grey</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>78492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21979" type="main character in" update="2012-02-12">
<name>Neos Gold</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5154" picture="236895.jpg">Takahata Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21980" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-03-01">
<name>Fibre</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="542" picture="60897.jpg">Doi Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21981" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-12">
<name>Rob Onwa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="467" picture="38026.jpg">Ebara Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21982" type="main character in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kasumi Nagisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21983" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-12">
<name>Ro Yajin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8058" picture="17124.jpg">Nishimura Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21984" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-12">
<name>Shizuka Kawai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2054" picture="186267.jpg">Amano Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21985" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-12">
<name>Bigro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21545" picture="55611.jpg">Yanaga Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="16362" update="2010-05-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イクサー3 登場! 地球は私にまっかせなさい!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Enter, Iczer 3! Just Leave Earth`s Defense To Me!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iczer 3 Toujou! Chikyuu wa Watashi ni Makkasenasai!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16363" update="2010-05-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">野性のおばちゃん! 愛のダブルアタック!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beast Lady! The Double Attack of Love!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasei no Oba-chan! Ai no Double Attack!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16364" update="2010-05-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大ピンチ!! 恐怖のお姉様イクサー2が来た!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Major Crisis! The Arrival of My Scary Older Sister, Iczer 2!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Pinchi! Kyoufu no Onee-sama Iczer 2 ga Kita!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16365" update="2010-01-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ムシ, 虫, 巨虫! イクサーロボでやっつけろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bug, Bug, Giant Bug! Go Get `Em, Iczer Robo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mushi, Mushi, Kyomushi! Iczer Robo de Yattsukero!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16366" update="2010-05-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1990-12-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">げげ! あたしが二人!? 超ライバル・アトロスの出現!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yikes! There`s Two of Me?! Enter, Atros - The Ultimate Rival!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gege! Atashi ga Futari!? Chou Rival Atros no Shutsugen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16367" update="2010-01-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1991-02-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">すごい! 強い! かっこいい! イクサーズ最後の大決戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cool! Wild! Outta Sight! The Final Battle of the Iczers!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugoi! Tsuyoi! Kakkoii! Iczers Saigo no Dai Kessen!</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
