<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12851" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1932</startdate>
<enddate>1932</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kyoudai Koguma</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">兄弟こぐま</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Bear Brothers</title>
</titles>
<url>http://animation.filmarchives.jp/works/view/5226</url>
<creators>
<name id="7990" type="Direction">Yamamoto Sanae</name>
</creators>
<description>One spring day, little birds are singing and frogs are dancing. A mother bear in the cave tells her children to play outside, but also reminds the two brothers to be careful of the terrible humans. While they are sumo wrestling and eating honey, a hunter tries to shoot the bears. The two brothers see a human for the first time. They manage to find their way to the cave where the mother bear awaits them. They are amazed that the human walks upright. The mother bear teaches her two boys how to do it. Swallows and cranes fly away, summer goes by, and fall deepens. As a result of their efforts, the mother bear and her children master how to walk upright. When animals in the mountain see the bear brothers walking upright like hunters, they mistake them for humans and run away. The bear brothers stand triumphantly. Then, when a real hunter appears and other animals run for their lives, the bear brothers fight back, imitating the humans. However, when they realize there is no way they can win against the hunters, the two bears crawl under the trees and jump over valleys running on all fours to escape with their lives.
Source: Japanese Animated Film Classics</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="22">3.18</permanent>
<temporary count="22">4.22</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>198700.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34955</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://animation.filmarchives.jp/works/view/5226</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<episodes>
<episode id="184927" update="2017-02-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
