<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12879" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1929</startdate>
<enddate>1929</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Manga Futatsu no Sekai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Two Worlds</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">漫画 二つの世界</title>
</titles>
<description>On a summer day, father and son ants are carrying a large caterpillar. An old toad, already drunk in the daytime, teases the ants for their hard work. A young grasshopper and a butterfly are having a sumptuous meal while listening to music. Watching the ants dragging the caterpillar, the grasshopper and the butterfly mock the ants with grimaces. The ants take rest at home. While a daughter ant is busy washing a kimono, the grasshopper plays a banjo, with the butterfly dancing to the music on a table. The father ant admonishes his son, who envies the grasshopper and the butterfly, quoting a proverb, "Summer fun leads to a winter of misery." The summer gives way to autumn and then comes winter, when cold breezes blow. The ant family is spending time together in a warm home. The son ant beats the father in arm wrestling. The grasshopper, wearing ragged clothes and walking with a cane, begs for food through the window. The daughter ant says that the butterfly is bedridden. The old toad is also seriously ill. The father ant quotes the proverb once again: "Summer fun leads to a winter of misery."
Source: National Film Archive of Japan</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="16">5.58</permanent>
<temporary count="16">5.18</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>198733.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35408</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://animation.filmarchives.jp/en/works/view/86947</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<episodes>
<episode id="184956" update="2017-02-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
