<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12909" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-11-02</startdate>
<enddate>2017-11-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">To Love-Ru: Trouble - Multiplication - Mae kara Ushiro kara</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">To Loveru: Trouble - Multiplication - From the Front, from Behind</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">To LOVEる -とらぶる- Multiplication ~前から後ろから~</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">To LOVE루 -트러블- Multiplication ~앞에서 뒤에서~</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">出包王女Darkness OVA</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10992" type="Prequel">To Love-Ru: Trouble - Darkness 2nd</anime>
</relatedanime>
<description>Note: Bundled with a 10th anniversary book titled [i]Trouble Chronicle.[/i]</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="258">4.82</permanent>
<temporary count="261">6.43</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>199812.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35000</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="2354" type="main character in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="351">2.61</rating>
<name>Yuuki Rito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The male protagonist of To Love-Ru, Rito is a 16 year-old high-school student. Rito used to be on the soccer team in junior high and was quite good, but quit because he was constantly helping his father with his mangaka duties, thus did not want to leave his sister Mikan alone in the house. Mikan comments he is very good at the most "useless little things", like crane and festival games. Along with the numerous useless little things Rito is good at, he is also an accomplished florist/gardener/horticulturalist.</description>
<picture>61497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2355" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="542">8.21</rating>
<name>Lala Satalin Deviluke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The female protagonist of To Love-Ru, Lala is the princess of Deviluke. A rather childish girl, she is somewhat naïve of the culture and familiarities on Earth. Lala initially runs away from home, citing she does not wish to get married to any of her arranged suitors. She enjoys making all manners of inventions (usually designed as pranks) and uses them frequently, often prompting some disastrous effect or another. Upon arriving on Earth, Lala pretends to love Rito to keep herself from getting married, but does exactly what she did not intend, after she misinterprets what Rito shouts in self-defence. Throughout the series, she always tries to get Rito to love her more, and barely shows any form of negativity towards him; she even states it is impossible for her to hate him.</description>
<picture>61495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2356" type="appears in" update="2016-02-08">
<rating votes="85">5.82</rating>
<name>Peke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lala`s all costume robot, who acts as a module to form her clothing. Peke is exceptionally devoted to Lala and has the ability to shapeshift into any kind of clothing for her to wear, but this also drains her power supply. As her batteries run out, the clothing Lala wears will slowly dissolve, until it completely disappears. To recharge, Peke simply needs to sleep.</description>
<picture>17592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2357" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-16">
<rating votes="526">8.45</rating>
<name>Konjiki no Yami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A dispassionate, withdrawn assassin, Golden Darkness is hired by one of Lala`s arranged suitors, Lacospo to kill Rito, until she breaks the contract, noting the true nature behind her target. Golden Darkness is currently staying on Earth, roaming around the city streets and Sainan High, with a motivation to continue her duty to assassinate Rito, although she has yet to accomplish this (hinting she only said this as an excuse to stay on Earth). Commonly referred as "Yami-chan", she spends her time reading books and magazines, while eating taiyaki (it is the only thing she eats on Earth since it is the first food offered by Rito, prior to spending a night at the Yuuki residence for a sukiyaki dinner). By her planet`s calculations, she is 24 years-old, despite having an appearance of an 11 year-old and has a weakness towards anything slimy.
http://anidb.net/ch2387 [Eve] from http://anidb.net/a3321 [Black Cat], another of http://anidb.net/cr2985 [Yabuki Kentaro]`s works, and her are alternative reality versions of each other.</description>
<picture>61500.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2358" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="267">6.06</rating>
<name>Sairenji Haruna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Rito`s classmates and the girl of his affections, Haruna has similar feelings for him, having been attracted to his kind, gentle nature since junior high. Despite her growing love for Rito, which she believes to be unrequited, she usually suppresses her feelings and cannot confess to him because of her friendship with Lala, who also loves Rito. However, with some encouragement, she tells Lala of her ordeal, to which Lala accepts, claiming Haruna as her rival for Rito`s heart, while remaining friends. She lives with her older sister in an apartment and has a severe fear of ghosts and the supernatural, the exception being Shizu Murasame, to an extent. When frightened, she has a habit of grabbing the nearest thing around her -- typically Rito -- and swinging wildly, in an attempt to get rid of whatever frightens her. Some people know about her love for Rito like Oshizu, Ryouko, Nana, and Lala.</description>
<picture>61496.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2359" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="54">2.93</rating>
<name>Saruyama Ken`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The perverted best friend of Rito, Kenichi has known him since junior high and is more open and obvious of his obsession with girls and is one of the few male characters Rito can talk to about his situations involving Haruna or Lala.</description>
<picture>17595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2360" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="210">5.57</rating>
<name>Momioka Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Momioka Risa is one of the mischievous, cheerful best friends of Haruna, Risa and Mio spend as much time as they can with her and Lala. Whenever Lala inquires about Earth culture and habits, the two divulge as much information as they can for her (although it is often misleading and perverted). Risa and Mio are known for their playful habit of groping other girls.</description>
<picture>126812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2361" type="appears in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="116">5.36</rating>
<name>Sawada Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of the mischievous, cheerful best friends of Haruna, Risa and Mio spend as much time as they can with her and Lala. Whenever Lala inquires about Earth culture and habits, the two divulge as much information as they can for her (although it is often misleading and perverted). Risa and Mio are known for their playful habit of groping other girls.</description>
<picture>184983.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="540" picture="41046.jpg">Chiba Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2362" type="appears in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="149">6.87</rating>
<name>Run Elsie Jewelria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As Run is from planet Memorze, she can change gender in mind and body upon triggering a specific stimulus; in her case, a sneeze. As a girl, Run is in love with Rito, due to the kiss, and blames Lala for her misfortunes. However, her boy form, Ren, is still in competition, albeit one-sided, with Rito for Lala`s hand in marriage. Currently, Run is a famous idol, having released several albums.</description>
<picture>184984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2363" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="62">5.03</rating>
<name>Ren Elsie Jewelria</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A childhood friend of Lala, Ren is infamously known for wearing girls clothing during his play dates with Lala when he was a child. He arrives on Earth to win Lala by proving he is "man enough" for her, but becomes jealous of her relationship with Rito. Due to his pursuit of her, he accidentally gives Rito his first kiss. While Ren is furious, it has an unexpected consequence towards his "alter ego". As Ren is from planet Memorze, he can change gender in mind and body upon triggering a specific stimulus; in his case, a sneeze. As a girl, Run is in love with Rito, due to the kiss, and blames Lala for her misfortunes, while Ren is still in competition, albeit one-sided, with Rito for Lala`s hand in marriage.</description>
<picture>17600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2364" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="434">8.51</rating>
<name>Kotegawa Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An uptight, high-strung girl placed in Rito`s class during the second year, Yui has little to no tolerance for anything she does not consider to be "acceptable behavior". Her haughty opinions, quick temper, and habit of speaking her mind often results in her vocally reprimanding classmates. Yui quickly grows annoyed and disgusted by the eccentricities and bizarre actions, particularly with regards to Rito and Lala. Unfortunately, almost every encounter with Rito usually ends up with her embarrassed, and though her complicated nature prevents her from easing her behaviour, she does slowly warm up to his usual antics and develops feelings for Rito.</description>
<picture>61498.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2365" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="173">6.53</rating>
<name>Murasame Shizu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The ghost of a girl who died in the old abandoned school building 400 years ago, Oshizu is sincere, kind, and very curious about the modern world, but has a severe fear of dogs, likened to Haruna`s level of fear to the supernatural. When frightened, she can emit blasts of mental stress, blowing apart various objects and surroundings, but is also capable of manipulating others through sheer willpower. Since her meeting with Rito and the others, she begins exploring the world outside the old school building. Oshizu is aware of Haruna`s crush on Rito by her ability to sense feelings while possessing another person and becomes very supportive towards cheering Haruna into confessing her feelings to him.</description>
<picture>61499.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2366" type="appears in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="157">6.01</rating>
<name>Tenjouin Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The arrogant queen bee of the school, third-year student Saki consistently tries to one-up Lala, stating there can only be "queen" in Sainan High. She once tries to seduce Rito to make Lala jealous, but when that does not work, Saki takes up any excuse to physically assault Rito. She gains a crush on Zastin, only to be horrified when she discovers he is Lala`s servant. However, this makes her very determined to win his heart, at any cost.</description>
<picture>184979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2367" type="appears in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="137">6.63</rating>
<name>Kujou Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saki`s loyal and assisting friends, Rin is skilled in the kendo arts and has been a loyal bodyguard of Saki for years, as her family has always served the Tenjouin in this position.</description>
<picture>184981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="602" picture="79633.jpg">Hashimoto Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2368" type="appears in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="85">3.62</rating>
<name>Fujisaki Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saki`s loyal and assisting friends, The bespectacled Aya is weak-willed and became associated with Saki after she and Rin protected her from bullies when they were children.</description>
<picture>184982.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2369" type="appears in" update="2016-04-01">
<rating votes="142">7.26</rating>
<name>Mikado Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The provocative school doctor at Sainan High, Ryouko helps out other extraterrestrials on Earth in various manners, usually those dealing with medical care, though she does offer students a variety of her own concoctions. Formerly an operative for a shadowy, black market extraterrestrial organization, she fled from her superiors to Earth in hopes of hiding her identity. Proof of her non-human origins are the elf-like ears hidden by her short hair, though it has yet been specified what her species is.</description>
<picture>184980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2370" type="appears in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="80">3.56</rating>
<name>Kouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The unnamed principal of Sainan High is well-known throughout campus as a pervert. He will impulsively enrol girls into the school body, so as to ogle and grope them without hesitation, though this is not restricted in Sainan High, but in public, as well.</description>
<picture>17607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2371" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="428">8.43</rating>
<name>Yuuki Mikan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuuki Mikan is Rito`s independent and reliable 11 year-old sister, Mikan takes care of the housework while their parents are away on business. In contrast to her brother, she is very mature and does not hesitate to tease him, going as far as stating they aren`t blood related, just for a laugh. Mikan also seems to have a certain lack of respect for Rito because of this (she hardly ever addresses him by his honorific as an older brother), but does answer him "Onii-chan" as thanks for trying so hard to take care of her when she develops a fever and when he got her a Christmas present. Mikan may not show it, but she cares very deeply for Rito and misses his company, and states how they used to play together before Lala entered their lives.</description>
<picture>126813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13068" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="230">6.71</rating>
<name>Nana Astar Deviluke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Lala`s twin younger sisters, she is introduced when most of the characters are in a virtual game world created by Lala that she and Momo subsequently modify. Nana has long hair, a single visible sharp tooth and unlike her sisters, a flat chest. She understands and can talk to animals. Like her big sister, she too has cell phone capable of transporting objects, however instead of gadgets Nana summons animals.</description>
<picture>61501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13069" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="542">8.98</rating>
<name>Momo Belia Deviluke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Lala`s twin younger sisters, she is introduced when most of the characters are in a virtual game world created by Lala that she and Nana subsequently modify. Momo has short hair and is generally sweeter than her twin Nana, but develops a bad attitude whenever Nana takes credit for what she does; she shares a connection to plant life. Like her big sister, she too has cell phone capable of transporting objects, however instead of gadgets Momo summons plants.</description>
<picture>39003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16805" type="appears in" update="2013-12-24">
<rating votes="56">6.00</rating>
<name>Celine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Celine is Lala`s gift for Rito`s 17th birthday, she is a multi-story, carnivorous, sentient sunflower kept in the Yuuki`s residence backyard. Although seemingly monstrous, Rito cares for Celine deeply, referring to her as his family. The plant behaves akin to a human: perspiring when the climate is humid, wearing an oversized scarf during a chilly day and eating a bowl of ramen when hungry (though Celine still needs the basic nutrients of water and sunlight). When Celine contracts a deadly disease, Rito is fully dedicated to saving her from Kare Kare and finding the luckyberry. With his friends they journey to an S-level-danger class planet of Misletoe to retrieve an antidote, only to return and find the plant all dried up. In reality, it was germinating and from its single seed burst out Celine, taking the appearance of an infant girl, with a flower on her head. This event even shocks Momo, who is very knowledgeable with the galaxy`s flora, stating Celine`s biological makeup is still a complete mystery to her.
Referring to Rito as her "mama", the infant Celine develops a low tolerance for cola and can spray a pollen from the flower on her head that temporarily causes anyone who inhales it to fall in love with Rito - a side-effect that originates from Celine`s own affection for him from taking care of her everyday. A running gag as a child is Celine will playfully tackle any girl and attempt to breast feed on them. Comically mistaken for being Rito`s daughter, Celine as a plant and infant does make an appearance in the animated adaptation.</description>
<picture>126814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44759" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-05">
<rating votes="75">5.71</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Mea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49889" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-07-01">
<rating votes="80">7.37</rating>
<name>Nemesis</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>175001.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51799" type="appears in" update="2018-09-16">
<rating votes="54">7.50</rating>
<name>Tearju Lunatique</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="186149" update="2017-11-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OAD</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
