<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12986" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2018-01-05</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Devilman: Crybaby</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">DEVILMAN crybaby</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">DEVILMAN crybaby</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Devilman Crybaby</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">恶魔人 crybaby</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Devilman Crybaby</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="1236" type="Alternative Setting">Devilman</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10272" approval="12" total="25">Kiseijuu: Sei no Kakuritsu</anime>
<anime id="202" approval="9" total="17">Shinseiki Evangelion Gekijouban: Air / Magokoro o, Kimi ni</anime>
<anime id="749" approval="8" total="12">Devilman Lady</anime>
<anime id="98" approval="4" total="13">Kenpuu Denki Berserk</anime>
<anime id="10997" approval="3" total="12">Charlotte</anime>
<anime id="13283" approval="2" total="8">Devils` Line</anime>
<anime id="6032" approval="2" total="5">Casshern Sins</anime>
<anime id="4392" approval="2" total="3">Kemonozume</anime>
<anime id="1544" approval="1" total="9">Elfen Lied</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="212957">I watched this because it was marked as similar to Parasite. Although there are some similarities story-wise, it is unfortunately on another (much lower) level in any other aspect. Still, if you like dystopian animes filled with sex, violence, and like being depressed this might be for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="164713">Very nice. Show has refreshing music &amp; story. I liked it a lot. Especially those oldschoold beats in the first half. Story is nice, not super original, but haven`t seen something like this for quite some time. Pacing is good, but can be quite fast at times. For a moment I felt like they rushed 12 eps into 10. Good direction in my opinion, probably because there was some western influence of this show, it has a little bit different feeling than most of other shows this days. I liked charaters both in design and how they developed.
Animation can be cheap at times and they try to cover it by making screen super dark. 
Very hard to judge, but I will recommend it anyway for everyone 18+ :).

Please be aware that there are some sex scenes and there is a lot of violence.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="736643">Interesting things start happening after episode 5. In summary, it`s a typical story of friendship, love, betrayal, sex, violence and sadness. However, unlike most of the Japanese animes, where the demons, ghosts or spirits that have their origin in Japanese folklore, this anime draws references western scriptures.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://devilman-crybaby.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="48093" type="Animation Work">Science Saru</name>
<name id="868" type="Original Work">Nagai Gou</name>
<name id="49" type="Direction">Yuasa Masaaki</name>
<name id="39776" type="Music">Ushio Kensuke</name>
<name id="15765" type="Character Design">Oshiyama Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="3660" type="Character Design">Kurashima Ayumi</name>
</creators>
<description>With demons reawakened and humanity in turmoil, a sensitive demon-boy is led into a brutal, degenerate war against evil by his mysterious friend, Ryou.
Source: netflix</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1300">6.34</permanent>
<temporary count="1318">7.04</temporary>
<review count="1">3.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>209818.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19982</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35120</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://devilman-crybaby.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Devilman_Crybaby</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>デビルマン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360088</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>DevilmanCryBaby</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2753" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>track and field</name>
<description>A collection of sports events that involve running, throwing, and jumping.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2776" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>parasite</name>
<description>Parasites are life forms that feed off other beings in some way. In anime, they are often aliens and usually intelligent. For shock value, and to avoid having to draw aliens all the time, their prey is preferably human; they may see humans as food, as puppets for mind control, or simply as temporary body hosts. In every case, the human is the victim of a "merging", which is not to be confused with the more "amicable" symbiosis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3443" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-05">
<name>orgy</name>
<description>A wild gathering marked by promiscuous sexual activity.</description>
<picurl>190911.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4049" parentid="2721" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>outdoor sex</name>
<description>Popular place for sex in visual novels and manga.</description>
<picurl>175405.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4302" parentid="2876" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>Christianity</name>
<description>Christianity is a monotheistic religion based on the life and teachings of Jesus of Nazareth as presented in the New Testament. http://anidb.net/t524 [Christians] believe Jesus is the son of God, God having become man and the saviour of humanity. Christians, therefore, commonly refer to Jesus as Christ or Messiah.
Source: EN Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4387" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>good vs evil</name>
<description>A theme often used to relay lessons of morality. The fight between two entities, with one side representing all that is good and right and the other one all that is evil and wrong.
It’s one of the most conventional themes in literature, and sometimes considered to be a universal part of the human condition.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7131" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-05">
<name>Crunchyroll Anime Awards</name>
<description>Crunchyroll Anime Awards are annual awards given to recognize anime from the previous year. The awards were first held in January 2017. The judges create a short list in different categories and public votes for the winners are held online.</description>
<picurl>219996.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7692" type="main character in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="43">7.47</rating>
<name>Devilman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7693" type="main character in" update="2015-02-04">
<rating votes="93">6.75</rating>
<name>Fudou Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira Fudou lost his birth parents at a young age to an accident while exploring the Himalayas, killing his mother and father. He was then taken in to live in the care of close family friends. He has always been timid, shy, with very little courage and was often bullied before becoming into contact with the `Demon Lord of Battles`, Amon. It is Akira`s pure soul that keeps Amon trapped within Akira; allowing him to use Amon`s power and strength to transform freely into Devilman.</description>
<picture>26558.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7694" type="main character in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="41">3.74</rating>
<name>Asuka Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryo Asuka is the best friend of Akira Fudo, the main character of Nagai Go`s classical horror manga Devilman. As Akira is the strength, Ryo is the brain. His father discovered the existence of demons in our world and decided to fight them. He asked his friend Akira`s help. Ryo knew that to be able to beat a demon, one had to become a demon. He and Akira went through a ritual to fuse with demons, but in the end, only Akira was able to do so and became Devilman, leaving Ryo remain as a normal human.</description>
<picture>26559.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7695" type="appears in" update="2018-03-11">
<rating votes="2">9.63</rating>
<name>Satan</name>
<gender>intersexual</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Satan and Ryo are one and the same. Satan took the form of a human to observe humanity better. He will lead the devils back to their rightful place as rulers of the world. Humanity is headed towards doom and he knew it. In his devil form, Satan is androgynous, possessing the genitals of both man and woman. Satan used his powerful psychic abilities on himself to keep his devil persona asleep until he was needed to begin the Apocalypse.</description>
<picture>26560.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7709" type="appears in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="5">3.33</rating>
<name>Psycho Jenny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92384" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="2">2.70</rating>
<name>Kaimu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210899.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92385" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="2">1.79</rating>
<name>Gabi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25023" picture="70106.jpg">Kimura Subaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92386" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="2">2.70</rating>
<name>Kukun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52714" picture="209822.jpg">Young Dais</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92387" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="3">7.07</rating>
<name>Silene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92388" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="2">1.79</rating>
<name>Babo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52715" picture="209823.jpg">Hannya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92389" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="3">1.79</rating>
<name>Hie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52716" picture="209824.jpg">Afra</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92390" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="15">7.59</rating>
<name>Kuroda Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92391" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<name>Wamu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52713" picture="209821.jpg">Ken the 390</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92392" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="13">7.31</rating>
<name>Makimura Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92393" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="2">2.70</rating>
<name>Nagasaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93448" type="appears in" update="2018-01-28">
<name>Makimura Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31813" picture="223582.jpg">Inagawa Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194778" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">泣き虫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crybaby</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sulu Göz</title>
<summary>Confronted by Akira, Ryo reveals the truth about demonkind and himself. Humans, demons and devilmen gather for an ultimate battle for the world.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="194779" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地獄へ墜ちろ, 人間ども</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go to Hell, You Mortals</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Siz Ölümlüler, Cehenneme Gidin</title>
<summary>Betrayed and exposed, Akira becomes a target. After Miki takes to social media to defend his human soul, she and Miko find themselves under attack.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="194780" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレはオレを知らなくてはならない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Must Know Myself</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kendimi Tanımalıyım</title>
<summary>Ryo`s actions and motives remain a mystery to himself, so he revisits his past for answers. Miki`s father searches for his missing wife and son.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="194781" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間は弱く, 悪魔は賢い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Weak Humans, Wise Demons</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Güçsüz İnsanlar, Akıllı İblisler</title>
<summary>With the fear of demons gripping the world, humanity devolves into paranoia and violence. Akira tries to save other demon-human hybrids like himself.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="194782" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔でも人間でもない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Neither Demon nor Human</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ne İblis, Ne İnsan</title>
<summary>At a widely broadcast track meet, Ryo plans to expose high school athlete Koda as a demon, thereby spreading fear and distrust throughout society.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="194783" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シレーヌ, 君は美しい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beautiful Silene</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Güzel Silene</title>
<summary>Silene tracks down Amon, hoping to reawaken his demonic side. But in the ensuing battle, the human soul of Akira remains powerful.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="194784" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">明, 来て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Come, Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Akira, Gel</title>
<summary>Akira`s mother calls and says she`ll be home soon. Everyone is looking forward to seeing her, but Ryo warns Akira not to trust any human.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="194785" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オレは撮ったんだ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Believe Me!</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İnan Bana!</title>
<summary>After getting shut down by his editor, paparazzo Nagasaki gets desperate. Silene and Kaim learn what happened to their missing fellow demon, Amon.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="194786" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">片手で十分だ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Hand Is Enough</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Tek El Yeter</title>
<summary>Akira has become a completely different man -- he`s stronger and hungrier than ever before. He seeks out Ryo for answers.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="194787" update="2018-01-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おまえが必要なんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Need You</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sana İhtiyacım Var</title>
<summary>Ryo, a young professor returning from research abroad, takes his pure-hearted, crybaby friend Akira to a decadent party, where things turn demonic.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="200980" update="2018-06-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204624" recap="true" update="2018-08-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「DEVILMAN crybaby」ダイジェスト映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Devilman: Crybaby Recap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Devilman: Crybaby - Digest Eizou</title>
<summary>A short web recap of the Devilman: Crybaby series, posted on Aniplex`s official YouTube channel.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
