<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1298" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>1998-07-02</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sentimental Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Sentimental Graffiti</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">青涩宝贝</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">センチメンタルジャーニー</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">מסע מרגש</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=97</url>
<creators>
<name id="8569" type="Character Design">Hirayama Madoka</name>
<name id="8050" type="Original Plan">Kubota Masayoshi</name>
<name id="9603" type="Music">Hamada Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="1760" type="Series Composition">Katayama Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="1760" type="Direction">Katayama Kazuyoshi</name>
<name id="34699" type="Original Work">Marcus</name>
<name id="8569" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hirayama Madoka</name>
</creators>
<description>What makes "Sentimental Journey" unusual is that each episode is completed unrelated to any of the others; instead, each episode focuses solely on one girl and tells a short romantic story. The only common element tying the stories together is the presence of a boy (and not even the same boy) in each girl`s past, a boy who used to be puppy love, or an old crush, or a best friend, or just a short acquaintance. And this boy would have an influence over some part of that girl`s present life. The stories ranged widely from straightforward girl-gets-boy romance to supernatural drama, and the actual storytelling and animation quality also tended to fluctuate noticeably, but on the whole "Sentimental Journey" is an anime that is unlike anything else out there.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="169">5.51</permanent>
<temporary count="172">6.69</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>246367.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>851</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>677</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>445</identifier>
<identifier>tamidp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/work/detail.php?cid=97</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sentimental_Graffiti</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>センチメンタルジャーニー_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88872</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1649</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/267</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>219</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1998/sentimental_journey</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4722" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>omiai</name>
<description>One character promised to marry another one, either by free will (read: love), or due to external interference e.g. by parental "guidance".
This can be a comedy element, especially if both parties are less than thrilled by the prospect of marriage. There is also potential for embarrassment-related humour concerning the emotional interaction between the newly weds.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="21570" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Endou Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21259" picture="187131.jpg">Suzuki Urarako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21571" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Matsuoka Chie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17081" picture="46372.jpg">Yonemoto Chizu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21572" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<rating votes="2">4.64</rating>
<name>Nanase Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21258" picture="131789.jpg">Nishiguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21573" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<rating votes="3">5.77</rating>
<name>Serizawa Kotone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21574" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<name>Sugihara Manami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3834" picture="25805.jpg">Toyoshima Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21575" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<rating votes="1">8.81</rating>
<name>Morii Kaho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3127" picture="24743.jpg">Mannaka Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21576" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<name>Ayasaki Wakana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21260">Oda Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21577" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<name>Monk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2981" picture="23711.jpg">Noda Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21578" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Yamamoto Rurika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1429" picture="18686.jpg">Konno Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21579" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<name>Yamamoto Masahiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21580" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Imanaka Kasumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21581" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Hoshino Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1607" picture="19577.jpg">Okamoto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21582" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<name>Oki Mitsuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21583" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<name>Tazaki Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21584" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Hosaka Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2375" picture="23197.jpg">Makishima Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21585" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<name>Tayama Kazuyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21586" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<name>Takahashi Kaoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3002" picture="17154.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21587" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Nagakura Emiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1660" picture="53927.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21588" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Adachi Taeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="639" picture="130599.jpg">Okada Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21589" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<name>Sasaki Tetsuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2799" picture="23198.jpg">Matsuno Taiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21590" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Kudou Chigusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="396" picture="151685.jpg">Nakagawa Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21591" type="main character in" update="2016-02-19">
<name>Sawatari Honoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3128" picture="24744.jpg">Suzuki Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21592" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-12">
<name>Sawatari Soichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3317" picture="24700.jpg">Kishino Yukimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74880" type="appears in" update="2015-05-01">
<name>Taxi no Untenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20305" picture="223542.jpg">Okada Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74881" type="appears in" update="2015-05-01">
<name>Pianist</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="614" picture="18136.jpg">Hashi Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74884" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-02">
<name>Matsuoka Shingo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="74885" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-05-02">
<name>Inoue Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>172868.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4932" picture="16806.jpg">Horikawa Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="13714" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1998-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠藤 晶 ~少女のためのヴァイオリン・ソナタ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endou Akira: A Violin Sonata for Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo no Tame no Violin Sonata (Endou Akira)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13715" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1998-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">松岡千恵 ~書けないラブソング~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Matsuoka Chie: The Love Song Which Cannot be Written</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakenai Love Song (Matsuoka Chie)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13716" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">七瀬 優 ~星降る夜の天使~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nanase Yuu: The Angel of the Falling Star Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshifuru Yoru no Tenshi (Nanase Yuu)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13717" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">杉原真奈美 ~微熱少女~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sugihara Manami: The Enthusiastic Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Binetsu Shoujo (Sugihara Manami)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13718" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">森井夏穂 ~友情の通天閣スペシャル~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Morii Kaho: Skyscraper of Friendship Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuujou no Tsuutenkaku Special (Morii Kaho)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13719" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">綾崎若菜 ~莫煩悩~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ayasaki Wakana: Do not Fret</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ayasaki Wakana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13720" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">山本るりか ~中部戦線異状あり!~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yamamoto Rurika: Abnormalities at the Frontline!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuubu Sensen Ijou Ari! (Yamamoto Rurika)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13721" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">星野明日香 ~Dreams will never die.~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hoshino Asuka: Dreams Will Never Die</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dreams Will Never Die (Hoshino Asuka)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13722" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">保坂美由紀 ~私らしく明日へ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hosaka Miyuki: To My Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hosaka Miyuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13723" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永倉えみる ~はてしない物語~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nagakura Emiru: A Story that is not Told</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagakura Emiru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13724" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">安達妙子 ~ほろにがトライアングル~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adachi Taeko: The Bitter Triangle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Horoniga Triangle (Adachi Taeko)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13725" update="2006-02-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">沢渡ほのか ~ほのかな恋の物語~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sawatari Honoka: Honoka`s Love Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sawatari Honoka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138289" update="2012-03-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1998-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
