<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13035" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Urahara</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">URAHARA</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Urahara</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">우라하라</title>
</titles>
<url>http://urahara.party/</url>
<creators>
<name id="22100" type="Animation Work">Shirogumi</name>
<name id="43522" type="Animation Work">EMT Squared</name>
<name id="6028" type="Character Design">Fujita Mariko</name>
<name id="1465" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Natsuko</name>
<name id="50933" type="Chief Direction">Kubo Amika</name>
<name id="50933" type="Direction">Kubo Amika</name>
<name id="1551" type="Music">Iwasaki Yasunori</name>
<name id="49368" type="Original Plan">Patrick Macias</name>
<name id="50933" type="Original Animation Character Design">Kubo Amika</name>
<name id="3438" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ono Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="6028" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujita Mariko</name>
<name id="6004" type="Chief Direction">Arakawa Masatsugu</name>
</creators>
<description>Several years from now, the great cities of the world will be destroyed by creatures from another planet. Their next target is... Tokyo`s famed Harajuku district! Only a trio of treasure-seeking shop girls can hope to save the day. But first, do they have what it takes to become members of the PARK Harajuku: Crisis Team?
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="218">2.39</permanent>
<temporary count="219">4.59</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>205059.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19876</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35250</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://urahara.party/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>URAHARA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4719</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360197</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20533</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>urhr_pt</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07KTBKSFQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3667" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Tower</name>
<description>Tokyo Tower is a communications and observation tower in the Shiba-koen district of Minato, Tokyo, Japan. At 332.9 metres, it is the second-tallest structure in Japan. The structure is an Eiffel Tower-inspired lattice tower that is painted white and international orange to comply with air safety regulations.
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much younger http://anidb.net/t3037 [Tokyo Skytree].</description>
<picurl>161123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4424" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>American derived</name>
<description>A work which was created as a continuation/remake of an American based franchise or cartoon series. These works are completely Japan original, but which lack roots within Japanese media.
See also: http://anidb.net/t3714 [cartoon remake]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6006" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>Tokyo is the centre of the universe</name>
<description>Whether it`s the big bad evil aiming for world domination, demons bringing the hell over to this site or aliens attacking the Earth, their centre of attention is always Tokyo, as if the rest of the world did not even exist!
But worry not if you happen to live there, because your neighbour could just be the leader of a senshi team or the pilot of a giant mecha and they are surely going to save the day again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="90397" type="main character in" update="2017-07-13">
<rating votes="4">7.60</rating>
<name>Shirako Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90398" type="main character in" update="2017-07-13">
<rating votes="4">7.80</rating>
<name>Watatsumugi Kotoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49536" picture="228921.jpg">Iwami Manaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90399" type="main character in" update="2017-07-13">
<rating votes="4">7.60</rating>
<name>Sudou Rito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31064" picture="83225.jpg">Haruna Luna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91083" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-04">
<rating votes="4">7.39</rating>
<name>Sayumin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207884.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22171" picture="173757.jpg">Iida Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91084" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-04">
<rating votes="2">1.17</rating>
<name>Ebifurya</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207883.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91085" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-04">
<rating votes="3">5.33</rating>
<name>Maruno Misa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207882.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51392" picture="206521.jpg">Amano Kokoa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92342" type="appears in" update="2017-11-18">
<name>DJ Aoyama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="52671" picture="209740.jpg">Reina Scully</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="191067" update="2017-10-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドーナツクライシス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Donut Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">도넛 크라이시스</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Donut Crisis</title>
<summary>Harajuku, a place where culture, fashion, and cuteness gather.High school girls Rito, Mari, and Kotoko run a pop-up shop called "PARK" in the neighborhood. One day aliens come to Earth and begin stealing humanity`s culture. Then a mysterious girl calling herself Misa appears. In order to defend their beloved Harajuku, the three girls take action.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749259</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191427" update="2017-10-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2017-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まもなく世界同時配信! アニメ「URAHARA」生放送SP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamonaku Sekai Douji Haishin! Anime "Urahara" Namahousou SP</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191428" update="2017-10-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイスクリームフィーバー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ice Cream Fever</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아이스크림 피버</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ice Cream Fever</title>
<summary>Kotoko`s acting strange. Actually, she always acts strange... But she didn`t pull out people`s hair or lurk about with syringes before. Rito and Mari find her behavior suspicious, but Kotoko refuses to explain herself because she`s afraid of being alone again and accidentally tears Rito`s drawing. Then a Scooper appears...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749265</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191429" update="2017-10-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クレープクレービング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crepe Craving</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">크레이프 크레이빙</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Crepe Craving</title>
<summary>Rito and friends learn there are other survivors inside the bubble besides themselves. One of the survivors, Sayumi, is handing out hand made crepes to the people of Harajuku in order to make them smile. Inspired by Sayumi, the trio begins preparing to re-open PARK. However, when Rito finds herself unable to draw, she goes to look at a drawing she previously made on a city wall...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749263</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191430" update="2017-10-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ポップコーンパニック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Popcorn Panic</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">팝콘 패닉</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Popcorn Panic</title>
<summary>Using the Amatsumara, the device they received from Misa that turns anything you imagine into physical objects, the girls fight off the aliens known as Scoopers. By enveloping the entire neighborhood of Harajuku in a bubble, Rito, Mari, and Kotoko are able to defend the city. Misa and her pet Ebifurya offer their help, and together they begin searching the bubble. However, that`s when the Scoopers return...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749261</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191445" update="2017-10-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191446" update="2017-10-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191946" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファビュラスクレープ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fabulous Crepe</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">페뷸러스 크레이프</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fabulous Crepe</title>
<summary>Rito is shocked when she finds Mari and Kotoko stuffing their faces full of sweets. Their friend and ally Sayumi appears bringing a new crepe she wants the three of them to eat. Claiming it can grant any wish, she urges them to eat it. Realizing something has happened to her, Rito turns to face her alone, blade in hand.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749273</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191947" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">サクラモチブルー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sakuramochi Blues</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">사쿠라모치 블루</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakuramochi Blue</title>
<summary>Their powers run out of control, and strange forms begin appearing on their bodies. When the girls are told they`re no longer human, they`re unable to accept reality, and Rito, Mari, and Kotoko clash fiercely. Rito is overwhelmed by the shock, and Sayumi kindly cheers her up. Rito begins running through the downpour in Harajuku in order to make up with her friends without realizing what`s become of them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749271</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191948" update="2017-11-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コットンハート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cotton Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">코튼 하트</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cotton Heart</title>
<summary>Two drawings are on the wall. The new drawing next to the girl is of the home Rito once lived in with her parents. Rito is overjoyed when everyone tells her they like it. However, the drawing of the girl is taken by a powerful Scooper. Upon seeing the depressed trio, Misa suggests they cheer up by creating something together and takes her first stab at creating beaded accessories.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749269</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191949" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グミグミダミー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gummy Gummy Dummy</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">젤리젤리 모형</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gummy Gummy Dummy</title>
<summary>Harajuku`s been turned into a safari park?! Giraffe, alligator, and zebra shaped Scoopers have begun wandering around town. When a single bird comes flying into PARK, Misa attempts to chase it away, but right before her eyes the color is stolen right out of some beads. Rito and friends hurry after the bird, but the color has been stolen from all over town.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749267</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192950" update="2017-12-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">グッバイパフェ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye Parfait</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">굳바이 파르페</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goodbye Parfait</title>
<summary>"I`ll protect you!" The Amatsumara responds to Misa`s powerful resolve and creativity, creating colorful beads that fall from the sky like rain. Rito, Mari, and Kotoko join Misa in their final showdown against Ebifurya, and they use their creativity to devise a method to fight back. In their fantasy world they`re able to mature just a little and act decisively.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749281</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192951" update="2017-12-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エビフライランナウェイ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fried Shrimp Runaway</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">새우 튀김 런어웨이</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ebi Fry Runaway</title>
<summary>This Harajuku was a fantasy. Rito and her friends are deeply shocked to hear the truth. The people who complimented Rito`s drawings, their customers, and even Sayumi? Unable to understand why the girls are frozen in place with all the blood drained from their faces, Misa is at a loss. If it`s not the real world, then it`s meaningless. But the four of them realize there were real things even within the fake world. Meanwhile, the agitated Ebifurya becomes even more openly hostile...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749279</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192952" update="2017-12-26">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">マルノミクィーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Swallowing Queen</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">마루노미사 퀸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marunomi Queen</title>
<summary>Rito, Mari, and Kotoko decide to destroy the Amatsumara. The relief of their bodies returning to normal doesn`t last long--the furious Ebifurya attempts to capture the girls himself. However, Misa stands in his way in an attempt to stop him. When Misa describes her admiration and feelings towards creativity, the girls are deeply sympathetic. And then she reveals a shocking truth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749277</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192953" update="2017-11-29">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビターキャンディー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bitter Candy</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">비터 캔디</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bitter Candy</title>
<summary>Rito`s body transforms rapidly into a Scooper. Mari and Rito are relieved to see her obsessively eat candy, but she suddenly groans in pain. Rito begins running out of control. In a desperate attempt to stop her, Mari and Kotoko turn their weapons against her. Seeing the tears in her eyes, they think back on the days leading up to the opening of PARK.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749275</identifier>
<identifier>urahara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
