<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13036" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sengoku Night Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">戦刻ナイトブラッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sengoku Night Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Sengoku Night Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">전각 나이트 블러드</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">战刻夜想曲</title>
</titles>
<url>http://anime.senbura.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="43676" type="Animation Work">Typhoon Graphics</name>
<name id="10654" type="Character Design">Komatsubara Sei</name>
<name id="16985" type="Character Design">Nakata Chisato</name>
<name id="18042" type="Character Design">Okuyama Suzuna</name>
<name id="5071" type="Series Composition">Kakihara Yuuko</name>
<name id="42660" type="Original Work">Marvelous</name>
<name id="38970" type="Original Work">Kadokawa</name>
<name id="24131" type="Original Work">Otomate</name>
<name id="46166" type="Direction">Kikuchi Katsuya</name>
<name id="27469" type="Music">Horikou Naoyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>One day, http://anidb.net/ch91625 [Yuzuki] is enveloped by a mysterious light suddenly emanating from her cell phone and finds herself in an unfamiliar place.
The scenery spread out before her almost resembles Sengoku period Japan--
But this is another world known as "Shinga" where non-human creatures such as vampires and werewolves reside.
Long ago, the various tribes of Shinga lived together peacefully under the protection of the Himemiko who possessed special blood.
However, one day the Himemiko suddenly vanished.
With the protection of the Himemiko gone, the world has fallen into a period of strife as the warlords of the Gegga Tribes started fighting one another vying for control. And, as if summoned by all the unrest, strange monsters called "Yakuma" run rampant throughout the land attacking the inhabitants.
http://anidb.net/ch88504 [Toyotomi Hideyoshi], who leads the Toyotomi Army, takes in Yuzuki after rescuing her on the battlefield and accidentally discover that her blood awakens the latent powers of the Gegga Tribes.
Upon learning of the power of Yuzuki`s blood, the other warlords--http://anidb.net/ch88503 [Oda], http://anidb.net/ch88499 [Uesugi], http://anidb.net/ch88501 [Takeda], http://anidb.net/ch88502 [Sanada] and http://anidb.net/ch88500 [Date]--begin pursuing Yuzuki, each for their own purposes.
"Find the girl from another world," were the parting words from the vanished Himemiko left to http://anidb.net/ch91626 [Imari], a white tanuki bearing a teakettle. Yakuma continue to appear in increasing numbers and touched by Yuzuki`s powers the warlords struggle with what to protect and what to fight. A new story comes together in the midst of war set in another world...
Source: crunchyroll
Note: The first episode received an early screening at a special event held at Toho Cinemas Shinjuku in Tokyo on 29.09.2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="157">2.08</permanent>
<temporary count="161">4.14</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>206693.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20057</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35251</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>36834</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anime.senbura.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>戦刻ナイトブラッド</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4684</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360184</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20549</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>senbura_info</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1664" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-20">
<name>horse riding</name>
<description>Equestrianism (from Latin equester, equestr-, horseman, horse) more often known as riding, horseback riding (American English) or horse riding (British English) refers to the skill of riding, driving, or vaulting with horses. This broad description includes the use of horses for practical working purposes, transportation, recreational activities, artistic or cultural exercises, and competitive sport.</description>
<picurl>47385.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2792" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>reverse harem</name>
<description>Reverse harem, or sometimes also male harem, is the common name for the gender-reversed version of the usual http://anidb.net/t2859 [harem genre]. In a reverse harem, instead of the usual situation with several female characters focused on one male character, the viewer sees several male characters surrounding a single female character. Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. The most notable exception is that, due to the most relevant characteristics of the trope`s fan base, reverse harem authors tend to go for http://anidb.net/t1760 [bishounen] looks. Though they are also exceptions to the common harem genre, harems with homosexual relationships are not covered by reverse harem.</description>
<picurl>126787.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2804" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>visual novel</name>
<description>The two terms are similar yet different, however, the fact that they look and `feel` the same outweighs the technical differences. For clarification, visual novels are considered a sub-genre of adventure games and the term does not cover simulations. While the two genres often share a common visual presentation, dating sims are sometimes considered to be more statistically based than the "choose your own adventure" style of visual novels; basically, the choices you make might change something else than just the story arc (or your next porn pic). Dating sims can involve several technical elements such as a time limit, several statistics such as looks and charm which can be boosted through exercise, or an "attraction meter" which can increase or decrease depending on one`s decisions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2968" parentid="4831" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-05">
<name>faceless alien invasion</name>
<description>Uncommunicative, faceless aliens suddenly invade Earth from outer space or a parallel world thus causing a war with humans.
If the humans are lucky, the invasion may go off without a war that would cause untold destruction and death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3504" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>sake</name>
<description>Sake, generally referred to as a Japanese rice wine, is an alcoholic beverage made by fermenting rice.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>215208.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3671" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>footage reuse</name>
<description>Footage reuse is the employment of a sequence of frames many times, generally as a side effect of a constrained anime production budget. This can happen by using the same footage once at a time, but many times over the course of the show, or by directly looping it. Types of scenes that tend to get reused include: transformations, such as those typical of superheroes or magical girls, characters that change into powered-up versions of themselves, or robots changing shape; attacks, especially when involving a series of steps that must be followed before the attack can be launched; and any kind of action that involves repeating the same movement.
This tag does not apply if the footage changes significantly between iterations. An example of that is the infamous Endless Eight arc of http://anidb.net/a6367 [the 2009 iteration of Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu]; even as the plot repeated itself, each episode of the arc showed it in different ways.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3772" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>library</name>
<description>In a traditional sense, a library is a large collection of books, and can refer to the place in which the collection is housed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3941" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>flood</name>
<description>A flood is an overflow of water that submerges land which is usually dry. The European Union (EU) Floods Directive defines a flood as a covering by water of land not normally covered by water. In the sense of "flowing water", the word may also be applied to the inflow of the tide. Flooding may occur as an overflow of water from water bodies, such as a river or lake, in which the water overtops or breaks levees, resulting in some of that water escaping its usual boundaries, or it may occur due to an accumulation of rainwater on saturated ground in an areal flood. While the size of a lake or other body of water will vary with seasonal changes in precipitation and snow melt, these changes in size are unlikely to be considered significant unless they flood property or drown domestic animals.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4244" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>healthcare and medicine</name>
<description>The anime contains themes related to healthcare, medicine, or the human body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4274" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>hidden agenda</name>
<description>Someone or some organization/government/etc. is misrepresenting themselves by doing/saying one thing while hoping/striving for something else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4431" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-06">
<name>love at first sight</name>
<description>Plot device: When two characters meet for the first time, at least one party, supposedly, immediately falls in love with the other party, and from then on tries to get to know that party better.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="88499" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Uesugi Kenshin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17" picture="71152.jpg">Toriumi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88500" type="main character in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Date Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88501" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Takeda Shingen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88502" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Sanada Yukimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88503" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Oda Nobunaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88504" type="main character in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="1">7.95</rating>
<name>Toyotomi Hideyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91154" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Maeda Toshiie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51989" picture="207816.jpg">Yamamoto Ikkei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91155" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-16">
<name>Ishida Mitsunari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51988" picture="207815.jpg">Sasaki Yoshihide</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91156" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Takenaka Hanbee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91157" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Kuroda Kanbee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42164" picture="176249.jpg">Takeuchi Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91158" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Niwa Nagahide</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91159" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Akechi Mitsuhide</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91160" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Shibata Katsuie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91161" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Mori Ranmaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91162" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Uesugi Kagekatsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51987" picture="207814.jpg">Aramaki Yoshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91163" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Kakizaki Kageie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91164" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Amakasu Kagemochi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207787.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91165" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Naoe Kanetsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91166" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Naitou Masatoyo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32912" picture="183255.jpg">Nishiyama Koutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91167" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Yamagata Masakage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33069" picture="225127.jpg">Nakajima Yoshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91168" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Baba Nobuharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91169" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Kousaka Masanobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91170" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Sarutobi Sasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91171" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Yuri Kamanosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38431" picture="224824.jpg">Yashiro Taku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91172" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Sanada Nobuyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="143" picture="23260.jpg">Morikubo Shoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91173" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Kirigakure Saizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51985" picture="207813.jpg">Kitamura Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91174" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<name>Date Shigezane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91175" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Katakura Kojuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2328" picture="171565.jpg">Satou Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91625" type="main character in" update="2017-10-01">
<rating votes="2">8.71</rating>
<name>Yuzuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91626" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-01">
<name>Imari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45121" picture="225365.jpg">Fujiwara Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="190966" update="2017-10-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真田ファミリア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sanada Famiglia</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La famille Sanada</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">사나다 패밀리아</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanada Familia</title>
<summary>Having found a lead on the Himemiko, Yuzuki heads to Sanada territory with Kanbee and Hanbee at the behest of Imari. Along the way the trio is pelted by a rainstorm and Yuzuki collapses with a fever. Hanbee and Kanbee carry the ailing Yuzuki to the Sanada mansion where she is tended to by Saizou Kirigakure and Sasuke Sarutobi. While Yuzuki is recovering, Kanbee and Hanbee follow up on the lead and are given access to what information the Sanada have on the missing Himemiko, but they find little beyond that she had once visited the region. Once Yuzuki is feeling better she is shown around Sanada lands by Yukimura Sanada himself when suddenly the village is attacked by yakuma...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>748991</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190967" update="2017-10-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">武田バンケット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Takeda Banquet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le banquet des Takeda</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">타케다 뱅큇</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takeda Banquet</title>
<summary>Masanobu Kousaka, a vassal of Shingen Takeda, comes to Hideyoshi bearing a large number of gifts. He tells them that another portion of the gifts are in a nearby temple. Mitsunari and Hideyoshi`s other vassals are suspicious that this is a trap, but Hideyoshi heads to the temple without a care. At the temple, Shingen`s other vassals--Masakage Yamagata, Masatoyo Naitou, Nobuharu Baba--along with the warlord Shingen himself, are waiting. Shingen offers to form an alliance and fight against the Oda Army, but Hideyoshi refuses. There seems to be a mysterious connection between Hideyoshi and Nobunaga.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>748989</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190968" update="2017-10-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">豊臣アタック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toyotomi Attack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`attaque du clan Toyotomi</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">토요토미 어택</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toyotomi Attack</title>
<summary>Vampires. That is the true form of Hideyoshi. Shinga is a world where non-human tribes of vampires and werewolves live. By chance it is discovered that Yuzuki blood has the ability to awaken the latent powers of Gegga Tribe members, much like the mysterious Himemiko who has vanished. While the ability of her blood makes Yuzuki valuable in a battle, it also has the potential to become a reason why she might become a target. Hideyoshi tells Yuzuki that he will protect her, but she has to marry him first.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>748987</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190969" update="2017-10-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神牙スプレマシー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shinga Supremacy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La suprématie de Shinga</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">신아 수프리머시</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinga Supremacy</title>
<summary>One day, Yuzuki is enveloped by a mysterious light and taken to an unfamiliar world. It is a world like that of the Sengoku Period, where warlords are fighting for domination. In the midst of the chaos, Yuzuki encounters a warlord named Hideyoshi Toyotomi. Hideyoshi commands the Toyotomi Army, and, along with his retainers, Hanbee Takenaka, Kanbee Kuroda, Toshiie Maeda, and Mitsunari Ishida, fights for the unification of this world at war. This world is known as Shinga, where non-human Gegga Tribes fight against one another.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>748985</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191449" update="2017-10-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191723" update="2017-10-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191922" update="2017-12-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">織田プランダー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oda Plunder</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le butin des Oda</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">오다 플런더</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oda Plunder</title>
<summary>Yuzuki has fallen into the hands of the Oda Army. Rather than blazing ahead and recklessly going into Oda territory to rescue her, Hideyoshi decides to focus on rebuilding the town and his forces, all the while planning his next move. Many of the warlords are left feeling powerless as they worry about Yuzuki`s fate at the hands of Nobunaga Oda. Meanwhile, Yuzuki finds herself confused by Nobunaga`s motives and his actions. Both Hideyoshi and Nobunaga continue to investigate the increasing appearances of the yakuma and find that they seem to have something to do with Yuzuki.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>748999</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191923" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">伊達リバース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Date Double Face</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La renaissance des Date</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">다테 더블페이스</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Date Reverse</title>
<summary>With Yuzuki`s wound finally healed she wonders if it is about time for her to leave Uesugi`s castle. However, before she is able to speak with Kenshin, a mysterious warrior appears saying that he is a member of Toyotomi`s army and has come to take her back to Hideyoshi. Going with the mysterious man, Yuzuki is surprised to find herself in the company of Masamune Date and his subordinates, Shigezane Date and Kojuro Katakura. As they escape into the night with Yuzuki the men are forced to stay in an abandoned temple to regroup when they are attacked by yakuma. Locked up inside a warehouse Yuzuki can`t help but wonder what Masamune wants with her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>748997</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191924" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">上杉ディスコード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uesugi Discord</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Discorde chez les Uesugi</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">우에스기 디스코드</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uesugi Discord</title>
<summary>With the sudden appearance of the yakuma, the recent great battle ended without a clear victor. While escaping into the woods, Yuzuki is injured and loses consciousness but is found by Kenshin Uesugi and taken back to his castle to receive treatment. Kenshin entrusts Yuzuki`s care to his son, Kagekatsu but when her injury worsens Kagekatsu feels extremely responsible. It is during this time that information comes to light that the neighboring country is making suspicious movements so Kenshin decides to send a commander with reinforcements. He tries to task Kagekatsu with this mission, but having lost confidence in himself, Kagekatsu refuses and Yuzuki tries to get father and son to see eye-to-eye.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>748995</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191925" update="2017-11-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走フィーリング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wild Feeling</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sentiments tempétueux</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">폭주 필링</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou Feeling</title>
<summary>The time has finally come for the showdown between Hideyoshi and Nobunaga. Fighting alongside Hideyoshi are the Takeda and Sanada Armies while the Uesugi and Date Armies join Nobunaga`s side. At one end of the battle, Shingen faces off with his mortal enemy, Kenshin Uesugi, and, at the other, Hideyoshi rushes headlong into the burning forest by himself seeking his one chance to try and take Nobunaga`s head. Just as a victor in the battle seems about to be determined a large number of yakuma appear and the battlefield descends into utter chaos.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>748993</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192934" update="2017-12-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦刻ナイトブラッド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sengoku Night Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sengoku Night Blood</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">전각 나이트 블러드</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sengoku Night Blood</title>
<summary>The giant yakuma has disappeared into the ground after swallowing up Yuzuki. The Toyotomi Army manages to find most of the Oda Army and manages to convince them to help find the giant yakuma and Yuzuki, though Nobunaga himself remains missing. At the same time, the Sanada, Uesugi, Takeda, and Date armies all struggle with large numbers of yakuma, having also followed after Nobunaga and Hideyoshi in the quest to go after the yakuma`s nest. When Hideyoshi spots a wounded Nobunaga at the bottom of a cliff, he asks for his help as well. Suddenly, the cries of the smaller yakuma echo all over the mountain and the giant yakuma reappears from the ground. Will the combined forces of the six supreme commanders be enough to vanquish this enemy once and for all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749007</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192935" update="2017-12-28">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">動乱マーチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Turbulent March</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La marche vers la guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">동란 마치</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Douran March</title>
<summary>Having turned down Nobunaga`s request for his help with vanquishing the yakuma, Hideyoshi returns safely to his castle with Yuzuki at his side. Yuzuki`s return after so long away brings much chear to the rest of the Toyotomi Army. However, yakuma begin to attack the castle again, threatening the newly rebuilt town and army that Hideyoshi and his people worked so hard for. Hideyoshi realizes he will need to come up with a way to protect both his people and Yuzuki, and it is then that Nobunaga`s words about how to vanquish the yakuma come back to him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749005</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192936" update="2017-12-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">確執ターミナス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Discord Terminus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Terminus discorde</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">불화 터미너스</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakushitsu Terminus</title>
<summary>With the reparations to the village and his army finally reaching completion, Hideyoshi sets off on his own to Nobunaga`s castle to get Yuzuki back. Hideyoshi was once a vassal for Nobunaga in his question for unification, but somewhere along the way an event occured that changed everything. Will these two former allies be able to reach an agreement over Yuzuki`s fate?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749003</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192937" update="2017-12-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">厄魔コリドー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yakuma Corridor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le corridor des Yakuma</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">액마 코리더</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakuma Corridor</title>
<summary>Just what are the yakuma? Where on earth do they come from? In order to put an end to the yakuma once and for all, Nobunaga has been investigating the location of the yakuma`s nest on his own. Now he heads out with his retainers and Yuzuki in tow to search for the yakuma`s nest. Yuzuki`s long held suspicions are finally realized when she learns that it really is her blood that attracts them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749001</identifier>
<identifier>sengoku-night-blood</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193324" update="2017-11-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特番「戦刻ナイトブラッド」音楽大特集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuban "Sengoku Night Blood" Ongaku Dai Tokushuu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
