<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13037" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-09</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hatena Illusion</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">はてな☆イリュージョン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hatena Illusion</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4917" approval="2" total="7">Hayate no Gotoku!</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://hatenaillusion-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="59520" type="Character Design">Nakano Ruizu</name>
<name id="3065" type="Original Work">Matsu Tomohiro</name>
<name id="44690" type="Music">Kuroda Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="5497" type="Direction">Matsuo Shin</name>
<name id="18152" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Tatsuya</name>
<name id="49340" type="Animation Work">Children`s Playground Entertainment</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr3065 [Matsu Tomohiro] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr2985 [Yabuki Kentarou].
Fresh in his first year of high school, Shiranui Makoto came to Tokyo to seek an apprenticeship under his parent`s acquaintance, world famous Illusionist Mamoru Hoshisato. Ever since watching a performance by Mamoru Hoshisato and his wife, Makoto had always wanted to be a Illusionist. The couple`s daughter Kana (nicknamed Hatena), incidentally, was also his childhood friend. Though Tokyo is a constant source of many strange and chilling incidents, still, since Hatena would be by his side, Shiranui Makoto isn`t too concerned.
Inside the Hoshisato residence known as a haunted house, Makoto receives a warm welcome from the butler Jeeves and the maid Emma, and meets Hatena once again. However, as much as Hatena welcomes Makoto`s arrival, she and he don`t really get along, and in the end...!?
Source: Animesuki</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="120">2.41</permanent>
<temporary count="122">5.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>242033.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22390</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35252</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hatenaillusion-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hatena_Illusion</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>はてな☆イリュージョン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5544</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360192</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22438</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hatena_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0845Z5LVN</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4246" parentid="3395" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-01">
<name>childhood promise</name>
<description>Sweet childhood promises... who remembers them other than the Japanese anime characters?
It keeps the main characters obsessed with promises that they made when they were children, mostly related to love, with lines like "I will always protect you" or "I will marry you when we grow up".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="107534" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-18">
<name>Jeeves Wodehouse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="293" picture="185431.jpg">Matsuyama Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107535" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-18">
<rating votes="1">8.28</rating>
<name>Mariah Grene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107536" type="main character in" update="2020-01-18">
<rating votes="1">3.72</rating>
<name>Shiranui Makoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107537" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-18">
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<name>Hoshisato Maeve</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107538" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-18">
<rating votes="3">5.91</rating>
<name>Hoshisato Yumemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243841.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43492" picture="232251.jpg">Tomita Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107539" type="main character in" update="2020-01-18">
<rating votes="6">1.42</rating>
<name>Hoshisato Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243839.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41296" picture="177392.jpg">Suzuki Aina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107540" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-18">
<rating votes="1">1.63</rating>
<name>Hoshisato Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107541" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-18">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Kikyouin Kokomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107542" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-18">
<rating votes="4">5.62</rating>
<name>Sakurai Ema</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="225623" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225624" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225625" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225626" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226305" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226306" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226307" update="2020-02-14">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226308" update="2020-02-14">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226891" recap="true" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋と魔術のイリュージョンで, 夢中にさせちゃいます! スペシャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi to Majutsu no Illusion de, Muchuu ni Sasechaimasu! Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227157" update="2020-02-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227158" update="2020-02-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227159" update="2020-02-28">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
