<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13053" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-04</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ramen Daisuki Koizumi-san</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ラーメン大好き小泉さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ms. Koizumi Loves Ramen Noodles</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">라면 너무 좋아 코이즈미씨</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">爱吃拉面的小泉同学</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11601" approval="8" total="11">Dagashi Kashi</anime>
<anime id="12385" approval="7" total="11">Isekai Shokudou</anime>
<anime id="10684" approval="5" total="11">Koufuku Graffiti</anime>
<anime id="11157" approval="4" total="5">Wakako-zake</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://ramen-koizumi.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="43116" type="Animation Work">Axsiz</name>
<name id="22585" type="Animation Work">Studio Gokumi</name>
<name id="12882" type="Character Design">Tani Takuya</name>
<name id="18152" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Tatsuya</name>
<name id="9553" type="Original Work">Narumi Naru</name>
<name id="16733" type="Direction">Setou Kenji</name>
<name id="12882" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tani Takuya</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="45007" type="Music">Tanaka Takashi</name>
<name id="51902" type="Music">Hosono Shin`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr9553 [Narumi Naru]`s gourmet comedy manga.
A cool girl who rarely speaks... The mysterious transfer student http://anidb.net/ch91572 [Koizumi-san] doesn`t get along with others very well, but she`s actually a professional when it comes to ramen, who seeks out delicious ramen every day.
Source: crunchyroll
Note: The first episode received an early screening at a special event held at TOHO Cinemas Shinjuku on 21.12.2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="413">3.62</permanent>
<temporary count="415">5.86</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>207605.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19675</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35298</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ramen-koizumi.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ms._Koizumi_Loves_Ramen_Noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ラーメン大好き小泉さん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4777</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360258</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20757</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ramen_koizumi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2677" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Osaka</name>
<description>Osaka Prefecture is a prefecture located in the Kansai region on Honshu, the main island of Japan. The capital is the city of Osaka. It is the center of Osaka-Kobe-Kyoto area.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214384.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2683" parentid="2812" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Hawaii</name>
<description>Hawaii is the 50th and most recent state to have joined the United States of America, having received statehood on August 21, 1959. Located in Oceania, Hawaii is the only U.S. state outside North America and the only one composed entirely of islands. It is the northernmost island group in Polynesia, occupying most of an archipelago in the central Pacific Ocean.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214273.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2812" parentid="2832" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>United States</name>
<description>The United States of America (commonly referred to as the United States, the U.S., the USA, or America) is a federal constitutional republic comprising fifty states and a federal district. The country is situated mostly in central North America, where its forty-eight contiguous states and Washington, D.C., the capital district, lie between the Pacific and Atlantic Oceans, bordered by Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. The state of Alaska is in the north-west of the continent, with Canada to the east and Russia to the west across the Bering Strait. The state of Hawaii is an archipelago in the mid-Pacific. The country also possesses several territories in the Caribbean and Pacific.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>45504.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2832" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Americas</name>
<description>The Americas, also collectively called America, encompass the totality of the continents of North America and South America. Together they make up most of Earth`s western hemisphere and comprise the New World.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192247.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2927" parentid="2676" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Akihabara</name>
<description>Akihabara is a common name for the area around Akihabara Station in the Chiyoda ward of Tokyo, Japan. It gained the nickname Akihabara Electric Town shortly after World War II for being a major shopping center for household electronic goods and the post-war black market. Nowadays, Akihabara is considered by many to be an otaku cultural center and a shopping district for video games, anime, manga, and computer goods.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214314.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6184" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>autumn</name>
<description>Autumn, interchangeably known as fall in the US and Canada, is one of the four temperate seasons. Autumn marks the transition from summer into winter, in September (Northern Hemisphere) or March (Southern Hemisphere), when the arrival of night becomes noticeably earlier and the temperature cools considerably. One of its main features is the shedding of leaves from deciduous trees.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161967.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="91570" type="main character in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="5">5.59</rating>
<name>Nakamura Misa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41766" picture="242448.jpg">Kitou Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91571" type="main character in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="7">5.62</rating>
<name>Oosawa Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210873.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91572" type="main character in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="9">3.48</rating>
<name>Koizumi-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91573" type="main character in" update="2017-12-17">
<rating votes="8">5.04</rating>
<name>Takahashi Jun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93244" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-12">
<name>Oosawa Shuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93281" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-07">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Yamada-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95442" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-12">
<rating votes="2">9.21</rating>
<name>Oosawa Ayane</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194117" update="2018-01-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようしょくてん / 赤or白 / コンビニ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Western Restaurant / Red or White / Convenience Store</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Style occidental / Rouge ou blanc / Supérette</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">양식집 / 빨강 or 흰색 / 편의점</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youshoku Ten / Aka or Shiro / Konbini</title>
<summary>One day, Koizumi-san leaves school saying that she has something to do.
Yuu is doesn`t think anything of it, sure that she is talking about ramen again.
But of course, Yuu tails her again, and she sees Koizumi-san waiting for someone in front of a fancy western restaurant. When a dashing man appears she yells "Koizumi-san, don`t!"
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758821</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194118" update="2018-01-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイミン / 味集中カウンター / 即席麺</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Saimin / Flavor Concentration Counter / Instant Noodles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nouilles Saimin / Le comptoir concentré sur les saveurs / Ramen instantanés</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">사이민 / 맛 집중 카운터 / 즉석면</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saimin / Aji Shuuchuu Counter / Sokuseki Men</title>
<summary>Once again, Koizumi-san cooly declines Yuu`s invitation to go eat together, but giving up is not Yuu`s style. The two of them actually meet at a ramen shop, but it`s jam-packed and there are single seat cubicles and Koizumi-san could not be further away!
However, Yuu`s going to have her moment in the sun where she gets to flex her cooking chops...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758819</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194119" update="2018-01-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北極 / コココココイズミサン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hokkyoku / K-K-K-K-Koizumi-san</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pôle Nord / Kokoko... Koizumi !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">홋쿄쿠 / 코코코코코이즈미 씨</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokkyoku / Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Koizumi-san</title>
<summary>Nakamura Misa was supposed to go on a date, but instead her boyfriend dumps her without giving her any recourse. Misa spots Koizumi-san walking by and shadows her, thinking that she might have seen the embarrassing scene. Her destination seems to be a red ramen shop specializing in extremely spicy ramens...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758817</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194120" update="2018-04-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤサイマシニンニクカラメ / まーゆ / こってり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Garlic with Extra Vegetables / Maayu / Rich</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un ramen avec de l`ail et une grosse portion de légumes / Huile d`ail noir / Soupe très riche</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">채소 듬뿍 마늘 매운 맛 / 마유 / 진듯한 맛</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasai Mashi Ninniku Karame / Maayu / Kotteri</title>
<summary>Koizumi-san is a reserved and mysterious high school girl.
Her classmate Ohsawa Yuu is very interested in this new transfer student. 
One day on her way home, she happens to see Koizumi-san in a long line in front of a ramen shop, which leads to them eating ramen together, and yet...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758815</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194712" update="2018-01-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194713" update="2018-01-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195231" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ご当地袋麺 / 家系</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Local Instant Noodles / Iekei</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sachets de nouilles locales / Familial</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">본고장 봉지라멘 / 이에케이</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotouchi Fukuromen / Iekei</title>
<summary>Yuu and Misa are fully enjoying the gifts of summer at the ocean.
On the other hand, Jun is in the library working on her summer homework because she`s too embarrassed to wear her bathing suit. 
Jun`s agonizing about the report she`s supposed to write about her future career when she happens to meet Koizumi-san and asks her about her aspirations.
What could Koizumi-san`s dream be?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758829</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195232" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nationwide</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans tout le pays</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">전국</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenkoku</title>
<summary>Now that summer break is upon them, the trio try to come up with a plan.
Koizumi-san already has an answer for that, which is to travel all over the nation.
Koizumi-san is finally going nationwide?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758827</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195233" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">朝ラーメン / 冷やし / 博物館</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Morning Ramen / Hiyashi / Museum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ramen du matin / Ramen froid / Musée</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아침 라멘 / 냉 / 박물관</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asa Ramen / Hiyashi / Hakubutsukan</title>
<summary>The summer heat is on!
Koizumi-san looks at the trio loudly suffering from the heat with disdain while she continues on her ramen pilgrimage. 
Yuu wills herself to follow her, and Koizumi-san declares that she will be having "hiyashi" ramen.
What exactly is this "hiyashi" ramen?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758825</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195234" update="2018-02-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トマトラーメン / ミドリムシ / 行列</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tomato Ramen / Euglena / Huge Line</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ramen à la tomate / Euglène / Longue attente</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">토마토 라멘 / 연두벌레 / 행렬</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomato Ramen / Midorimushi / Gyouretsu</title>
<summary>In today`s science class, the four girls learn about the `green bug` which is known as euglena. Brimming with scientific curiousity, Jun can`t stop wondering about what that might taste like, and agrees to go have euglena ramen with Koizumi-san. What is that absolutely foreign flavor going to be like???
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758823</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196172" update="2018-04-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">名古屋 / 再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nagoya / Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nagoya / Retrouvailles</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">나고야 / 재회</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagoya / Saikai</title>
<summary>Yuu was on the train from Osaka to Tokyo, but when she senses Koizumi-san`s presence, she leaps off the train in Nagoya...
She then loses sight of Koizumi-san and only has a 500 Yen coin to her name.
Slightly faint, she enters a ramen shop where she can eat something that one coin...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758837</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196173" update="2018-04-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おいしいラーメン / 大阪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tasty Ramen / Osaka</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un ramen délicieux / Osaka</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">맛있는 라면 / 오사카</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oishii Ramen / Osaka</title>
<summary>Yuu tries to recreate the ramen of her childhood.
She can`t even remember the name of the place, and with only the fact that it`s "Delicious Ramen", she is a complete loss.
However, after Koizumi-san samples her ramen, they figure out the original source.
What exactly is the mysterious "Delicious Ramen"?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758835</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196174" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未知味の拉麺 / まわるラーメン / 挑戦受付中!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ramen with Unknown Flavor / Conveyor Belt Ramen / Accepting Challenges!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ramen aux étranges saveurs / Ramen su tapis roulant / Relever le défi !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">미지의 맛 라멘 / 회전 라멘 / 라멘 도전 접수 중!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michi Aji no Ramen / Mawaru Ramen / Chousen Uketsukechuu!!</title>
<summary>Yellow... Blue...?
Soy milk...? Milk coffee...!?
Alkali!?
"Today, Koizumi was eating some kind of water-colored ramen."
Ramen is... the universe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758833</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196175" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">山 / 豚野郎 / 背脂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mountain / Pork Guy / Back Fat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Montagne / Ramen butayarô / Ramen à la graisse de porc</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">산 / 부타야로 / 돼지고기 비계</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yama / Buta Yarou / Seabura</title>
<summary>Mountains. They proudly stand tall in the land and thwart man`s efforts.
Mountains. Mysterious places that continue to produce solemn silence.
Mountains. They challenge man to reach for the stars.
"Reaching the summit was not my goal"  -Why does man, why does Koizumi-san climb mountains-
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758831</identifier>
<identifier>ms-koizumi-loves-ramen-noodles</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
