<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1305" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>52</episodecount>
<startdate>1994-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>1995-03-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ginga Sengoku Gun Yuuden Rai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rai: Galactic Civil War Chronicle</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="synonym">ไร ซามูไรอวกาศ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">銀河戦国群雄伝ライ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Thunder Jet</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">هزيم الرعد</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="227701">One of the greatest tragedy I ever saw. If you like tragedy this anime is perfect for you. I personally dislike and i feel that I`m cheated, because can`t see such category.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="117027">Ih you like samurais or space operas or just a great war drama this is what you`re looking, a great and epic story with deep plot and characters, a very underrated and unknown jewel in anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="367941">this best anime i ever saw :)&lt;br /&gt;relly cool . see it and then tell me :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="277905">One of the best anime ever !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="366242">War in space with Japan Age Of Strife setting !
Warning ! Very Addicted !</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.enokifilmsusa.com/library/thunderjet.htm</url>
<creators>
<name id="858" type="Original Work">Manabe Jouji</name>
<name id="1089" type="Animation Work">E&amp;G Films</name>
<name id="4156" type="Series Composition">Toriumi Jinzou</name>
<name id="561" type="Direction">Okuda Seiji</name>
<name id="2703" type="Music">Wada Kaoru</name>
<name id="6648" type="Work">Enoki Yoshinori</name>
<name id="9725" type="Character Design">Takahoko Makoto</name>
</creators>
<description>After the collapse of the Sacred Galaxy Empire, a battle for control of the Milky Way Constellation breaks out among the War Lords. From the chaos of outerspace emerges a young courageous warrior, "THUNDER JET". THUNDER JET is a fearless warrior to his foes but to others, he is a gentle soul, dependable and loyal.
Two powerful forces aspire to reign over the entire Empire, Dan-Joe ruler of the North Region of the Milky Way and Queen Mussamney, ruler of the Southern Region.
THUNDER JET sees the ensuing battle and ponders the ultimate goal. Is it power and glory these rulers seek or a peaceful Milky Way under one rule? THUNDER JET realizes the importance of this battle and the purpose of his destiny.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="124">7.22</permanent>
<temporary count="137">7.41</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>53522.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2225</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3907</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2224</identifier>
<identifier>gjgsfv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.enokifilmsusa.com/library/thunderjet.htm</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ginga_Sengoku_Gun'yūden_Rai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89018</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1589" parentid="2622" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-08">
<name>samurai</name>
<picurl>244341.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="13917" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出撃! 4077部隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thunder Jet Sallies Forth to the South Region!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugeki! 4077 Butai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13918" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北天に嵐吹く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Feud Among Three Dominant Forces</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitaten ni Arashi Fuku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13919" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美貌の独眼竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Warlord Called One-Eyed Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bibou no Dokuganryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13920" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">討て! 偽皇帝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hate and Compromise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ute! Nise Koutei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13921" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝利への突入!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Ordeal of Galaxy Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouri e no Totsunyuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13922" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">太助のスパイ大作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Taskee`s Mission Impossible</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tasuke no Spy Daisakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13923" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライ! 危機一髪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hairbreadth Escape from the Killers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rai! Kikiippatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13924" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決死の脱出作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desperate Exodus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kesshi no Dasshutsu Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13925" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼刃を救え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rescue of Rogina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rouha o Sukue!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13926" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! ライ対正宗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thunder Jet vs. One-Eyed Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Rai tai Masamune</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13927" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">無敵の海賊艦隊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invincible Space Pirate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muteki no Kaizoku Kantai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13928" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">銀河の風雲児</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Flaming Star of Galaxy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ginga no Fuuunji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13929" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の大要塞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Fortress on Fire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Daiyousai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13930" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天才軍師! シシン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shin the Genius Strategist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensai Gunshi! Shishin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13931" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天下への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Road to the Throne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenka e no Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13932" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切り者を追え!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Destroy the Traitors!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragirimono o Oe!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13933" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">たった一人の戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One-Man War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatta Hitotsu no Sensou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13934" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">正宗の逆襲!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Counter-attack of Queen Massina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masamune no Gyskushuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13935" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼刃出陣!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rogina Challenges Thunder Jet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rouha Shutsujin!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13936" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">骸羅反乱!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revolt of Garer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukurora Hanran!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13937" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">五丈脱出作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape from Planet Go-Jo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gojou Dasshutsu Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13938" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金剛爆破作戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Man to Kill Thunder Jet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimu Tsuyoshi Bakuha Sakusen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13939" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弾正暗殺!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assassination of Dan-Joe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Danjou Ansatsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13940" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">捨て身の救出作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desperate Rescue Operation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sutemi no Kyuushutsu Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13941" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なぐりこみ戦艦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Headlong Charge to Enemy`s Flag Ship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagurikomi Senkan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13942" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">守れ! 南京楼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Defend Nankyo at All Risk!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamore! Nankinrou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13949" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">野望の若武者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Ambitious Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yabou no Wakamusha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13950" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">炎の中の決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle in Burning Inferno</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honoo no Naka no Kessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13951" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦いの果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Merciless Bombard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakai no Hate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13952" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帝王への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Road to the Emperor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teiou e no Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13953" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖魔のたくらみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gen-Yee`s Plot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youma no Takurami</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13954" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">虎丸の誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Oath of Tramaroon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toramaru no Chikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13955" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">南京楼脱出</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape from Nankyo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nankyin Rou Dasshutsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13956" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! ライ対ラコウ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Crash! Thunder Jet vs. King Racko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Rai tai Rakou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13957" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の果てに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beyond the Endless Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Hate ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13958" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">出現! 妖魔戦艦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Expected Warship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsugen! Youma Senkan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13959" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">紫紋の想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Simone`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Murasaki Mon no Omoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13960" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">金剛大爆発</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thunder Jet`s Warship Explodes!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimu Tsuyoshi Daibakuhatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13961" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガイラ死す!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fall of Garer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Garer Shisu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13962" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">玄偉の正体</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Identity of Gen-Yee</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Genera no Shoutai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13963" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば狼刃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Rogina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Rouha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13964" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魂の声に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Love and Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamashii no Koe ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13965" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦いの序曲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prologue of All-Out War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakai no Jokyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13966" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">対決! ライ対狼刃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel. Thunder Jet vs. Rogina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taiketsu! Rai tai Rouha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13967" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">討て! 羅候軍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take Back Nankyo!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ute! Rakougun</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13968" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">正宗の決断</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return of Massina, One-Eyed Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masamune no Ketsudan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13969" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠い平和</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calm Before a Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooi Heiwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13970" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">豪傑のさいご</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Battle of Pirate-Admiral</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouketsu no Saigo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13971" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1994-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖剣の罠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trap of Spelled Dagger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youken no Wana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13972" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">二重惑星の決戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle at Twin Planets</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nijuu Wakusei no Kessen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13973" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">和平会談</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Peace Talk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wahei Kaidan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13974" update="2004-01-13">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1995-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シシン敗れる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sishin Lose a Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shishi ni Yabureru</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
