<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13072" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1961</startdate>
<enddate>1961</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaguya-hime (1961)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">かぐや姫 (1961)</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.gakken.co.jp/campaign/70th/archives/</url>
<ratings>
<permanent count="23">3.88</permanent>
<temporary count="23">4.39</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>242257.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>29927</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gakken.co.jp/campaign/70th/archives/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=oF-beKY-yWs</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2685" parentid="2641" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>Heian period</name>
<description>Last division of classical Japanese history, covering the time period from 794 to 1185.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>puppetmation</name>
<description>A puppet is an inanimate object or representational figure animated or manipulated by a puppeteer. It is usually (but by no means always) a depiction of a human character, and is used in puppetry, a play or a presentation that is a very ancient form of theatre. The puppet undergoes a process of transformation through being animated, and is normally manipulated by at least one puppeteer.
There are many different varieties of puppets, and they are made of a wide range of materials, depending on their form and intended use. They can be extremely complex or very simple in their construction. They may even be found objects. As Oscar Wilde wrote, "There are many advantages in puppets. They never argue. They have no crude views about art. They have no private lives".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6352" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>Kaguya-hime</name>
<description>The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter (Taketori Monogatari, 竹取物語), also known as Princess Kaguya (かぐや姫 Kaguya-hime, 赫映姫 or 輝夜姫), is a 10th-century Japanese folktale. It primarily details the life of a mysterious girl called Kaguya-hime, who was discovered as a baby inside the stalk of a glowing bamboo plant by a bamboo cutter, alongside riches in gold. The thumb-sized girl grew into a beautiful woman, and this was known all over the lands. Eventually 5 princes made their way to her to ask her foster father for her hand. Each of them got tasked with something seemingly impossible to fullfil to marry her. After all of them failed, the emporer came to see her, and fell for her beauty. His proposal was denied as well, telling him that she wasn`t of this country and thus couldn`t marry him. In the summer Kaguya-hime started to cry upon seeing the full moon. Her foster parents inquired on the matter and after a while she gave in, telling them that she was actually coming from the moon, and that she needs to return there. When the day came to return, the emperor sent many guards to her home to protect her from the moon people. They came and took her with them anyway, leaving the parents in sadness and tears. The heartbroken emperor wanted to send her a message, and went on to ask where he could find the closest place to heaven. This being the Great Mountain of Suruga Provice. The tale goes on saying that the name of the mountain, which we know today as Mount Fuji, came from the word immortality (fushi, or fuji), and the Kanji from the emperor`s army ascending its slopes, meaning literally "Mountain Abounding with Warriours" (富士山).
The anime or episode either takes on the whole tale of Kaguya-hime or just parts of it.</description>
<picurl>169473.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="186844" update="2018-01-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
