<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13098" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-04-23</startdate>
<enddate>2020-04-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Koukaku Kidoutai: SAC_2045</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ghost in the Shell: SAC_2045</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">攻殻機動隊 SAC_2045</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Призрак в доспехах: Синдром одиночки 2045</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15512" type="Sequel">Koukaku Kidoutai: SAC_2045 S2</anime>
<anime id="4414" type="Prequel">Koukaku Kidoutai Stand Alone Complex: Solid State Society</anime>
<anime id="247" type="Other">Koukaku Kidoutai Stand Alone Complex</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="757481">Transfering into non-human made full CGI had heavy consequences for series.

Disadvantages of computer graphics mostly not hided: 
undinamic damage models geometry, gunfire sprites, wind-hair-grass movements, liquids as blood "suryp", intentional background overblurring, low-poly censored nakedness as wax figure, weird body language, faces with "doll effect".
3D is not awful or bad - just "too game-cutscene-ish", goes too far from hand made artistic drawning

1 / 10 for me, Netflix killed this series.
Yet fans can read subs / listen VA for story development purposes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="83187">Good continuation of the SAC series. And a recruitment of the old cast!

This version is a full 3D CG animated. Quality of the CG animation varies between good to bad sometimes. The good part is that the character design is good so is the action in it. It still has the nostalgic feeling from the previous anime. 
You can still start watching this as a standalone anime without seeing the previous seasons.
 
But sometimes the 3D CG can feel quite poorly done. E.g. light casting the shadows on some scene makes it feel like a poorly made 3D game from 20 years ago. As a CG animation of 2020 it could be better. But it doesn`t affect the enjoyment of the story.

Summary:
The current full 3D art style is quite good, but it might not be the for everyone, going from 2D to 3D art style. The story is as good as it have ever been and it has complexity in it. Cool action scenes and The Major Motoko is the quite cute in the current design.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://www.ghostintheshell-sac2045.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="150" type="Direction">Aramaki Shinji</name>
<name id="205" type="Direction">Kamiyama Kenji</name>
<name id="871" type="Original Work">Shirou Masamune</name>
<name id="721" type="Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="43739" type="Work">Sola Digital Arts</name>
<name id="57196" type="Character Design">Ilya Kuvshinov</name>
<name id="205" type="Series Composition">Kamiyama Kenji</name>
<name id="39809" type="Music">Toda Irone</name>
<name id="50876" type="Music">Jinnouchi Kazuma</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr871 [Shirou Masamune]`s original 1989 cyberpunk action manga Ghost in the Shell.
In the year 2045, after an economic disaster known as the Synchronized Global Default, rapid developments in AI propelled the world to enter a state of "Sustainable War". However, the public is not aware of the threat that AI has towards the human race.
Full-body cyborg http://anidb.net/ch109674 [Major Kusanagi Motoko] and her second-in-command http://anidb.net/ch109669 [Batou] are former members of Public Security Section 9, who are now hired mercenaries traveling hot devastated American west coast. This land is full of opportunity for the major and her team, they utilize their enhanced cyberbrains and combat skills from their time working in Section 9. However, things get complicated with the emergence of "post humans," who have extreme intelligence and physical powers. The members of Section 9 comeback together again in order to face this new threat.
Source: Official website</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="17">3.95</permanent>
<temporary count="19">5.71</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>245155.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21672</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38799</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.ghostintheshell-sac2045.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ghost_in_the_Shell:_SAC_2045</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>攻殻機動隊_SAC_2045</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360357</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22662</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gitssac2045</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3755" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-19">
<name>unintentional comedy</name>
<description>This anime contains certain elements intended to be serious, dramatic, or sad. However, these elements wind up provoking laughter instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4350" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>imperial stormtrooper marksmanship academy</name>
<description>When only the Bad Guys suffer from A-Team Firing. Also called The Principle of Evil Marksmanship. The good guys (the non-Red Shirt ones, at least - and sometimes even them, too) can stand in the middle of the firefight and never get hit, and can pick off any bad guy with even the most casually-aimed shot while the bad guys seem unable to hit the broad side of a barn.
This is a degree of Truth in Television, as by far most shots fired in firefights or combat are misses. Some sources report that in WWII, the average soldier needed to fire two hundred rounds for every hit scored on an enemy; numerous other examples are mentioned in the Real Life section of this page. So the fictional bad guys don`t actually suffer from unrealistic inaccuracy; rather, the heroes`s fictional performance would count as Improbable Aiming Skills in real life. Or they were instead ordered not to shoot the person. 
Source: TVTropes</description>
<picurl>162915.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9577" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-05-08">
<rating votes="358">9.06</rating>
<name>Tachikoma</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Tachikoma is an AI walker/roller tank. They are best described as a "spider type multi leg/multi ped combat vehicle equipped with artificial intelligence", possessing the ability to act as both personnel transport units and mobile weapons platforms.
Tachikoma are as large as an average sedan, are painted blue and have four "eyes" fitted on the surface of their bodies. Three are on the "head" and one is beneath the abdomen. Each eye has three pinholes, loosely resembling a bowling ball. These eyes sometimes become expressive in the typical anime style. Tachikoma are controlled by individual AIs, are capable of speech and generally exhibit a childish, curious, joyful and active personality, although they are consummate professionals in the field. They normally operate as independent units and receive orders from human agents, but they can also be directly piloted from a cockpit in their abdomen.</description>
<picture>2312.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="471" picture="242052.jpg">Tamagawa Sakiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109663" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Ishikawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="415" picture="241624.jpg">Nakano Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109664" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Saito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109665" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Shimamura Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109666" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>John Smith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30171" picture="246657.jpg">Soze Kaiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109667" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Standard</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109668" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Togusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109669" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Batou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109670" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Paz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="414" picture="211148.jpg">Onozuka Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109671" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Borma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2893" picture="240353.jpg">Yamaguchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109672" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Kurisu Otomo Teito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3162" picture="151662.jpg">Kiyama Shigeo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109673" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Esaki Purin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109674" type="main character in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Kusanagi Motoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="222" picture="19786.jpg">Tanaka Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109675" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-23">
<name>Aramaki Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="416" picture="23206.jpg">Saka Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="228565" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">NO NOISE NO LIFE 持続可能戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Noise No Life: Sustainable War</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">No Noise No Life: Jizokukanou Sensou</title>
<summary>The United States, 2045. Working as mercenaries, the Major and her team, including newbie Stan, defend a gated town from outlaws. Togusa takes a call.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228566" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">AT YOUR OWN RISK 壁が隔てるもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At Your Own Risk: Divided by a Wall</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">At Your Own Risk: Kabe ga Hedateru Mono</title>
<summary>Armed by a generous patron, the Nomads attack Section 9 with AI drones. Togusa accepts a new mission from Japan`s peace-seeking Prime Minister.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228567" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">MAVERICK 作戦行動中行方不明</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maverick: MIA</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maverick: Sakusen Koudou Naka Yukue Fumei</title>
<summary>As Togusa dives into cyberspace to track his former team members, the group is detained by a mysterious American organization seeking to employ them.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228568" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">SACRIFICIAL PAWN 分界よりの使者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sacrificial Pawn: Emissary from the Divide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sacrificial Pawn: Bunkai yori no Shisha</title>
<summary>While researching the team`s disappearance and John Smith, Togusa takes a calculated risk. The GHOST members question the true nature of their mission.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228569" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PATRICK HUGE 神からの贈り物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Patrick Huge: Gift from God</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Patrick Huge: Kami kara no Okurimono</title>
<summary>Aramaki sets off after Kusanagi in a race against time. GHOST begin their assignment, but Huge`s cybernetic security forces them to alter their plans.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228570" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">DISCLOSURE 量子化された福音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disclosure: Quantized Gospel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Disclosure: Ryoushika Sareta Fukuin</title>
<summary>Following the Section 9 reunion, Kusanagi and her colleagues learn about the "post-humans," a previously unknown threat to humanity.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228571" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PIE IN THE SKY はじめての銀行強盗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pie in the Sky: First Bank Robbery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pie in the Sky: Hajimete no Ginkou Goutou</title>
<summary>Back in Japan after six years, Batou decides to take a break while waiting for his delayed team. Then some amateur bank robbers interrupt his fun.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228572" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ASSEMBLE トグサの死によってもたらされる事象</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assemble: What Came About as a Result of Togusa`s Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Assemble: Togusa no Shi ni Yotte Motarasareru Jishou</title>
<summary>The Major and Smith clash over Section 9`s new mission hunting post-humans. She orders Togusa to investigate a suspected spy near the Prime Minister.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228573" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">IDENTITY THEFT 一人きりの闘争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Identity Theft: The Lonely Struggle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Identity Theft: Hitorikiri no Tousou</title>
<summary>Problems arise for Section 9 after one of the three post-humans in Japan murders several politicians, then targets the Prime Minister`s father-in-law.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228574" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">NET PEOPLE 炎上に至る理由</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Net People: Reasons Leading to Flameout</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Net People: Enjou ni Itaru Riyuu</title>
<summary>Section 9 investigates a possible post-human hacker who uses the web to incite physical attacks on people. The trail leads to a high school student.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228575" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">EDGELORD 14歳革命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Edgelord: The Revolution of the 14-year-olds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Edgelord: 14-sai Kakumei</title>
<summary>Pudding helps analyze the Thinkpol program while the Major and Togusa search for clues about the post-human middle school student Takashi Shimamura.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228576" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">NOSTALGIA すべてがNになる.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nostalgia: All Will Become N</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nostalgia: Subete ga N ni Naru.</title>
<summary>Togusa has a strange episode while analyzing the data confiscated from Shimamura. When he wakes up, he and Batou head out to investigate.
Source: netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228581" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228582" update="2020-04-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-04-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
