<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1312" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-04-17</startdate>
<enddate>2004-04-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Appleseed (2004)</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="synonym">Appleseed</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Obuolio sėkla</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Ябълкови семена</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">苹果核战记</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アップルシード</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Appleseed (2004)</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Appleseed</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Appleseed (2004)</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Appleseed - The Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Appleseed - The Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Яблочное зёрнышко</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">애플씨드</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Appleseed</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Appleseed - The Beginning - O Filme</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Appleseed</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Omenansiemen</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Appleseed - A jövő harcosai</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">แอปเปิ้ลซีด เดอะมูวี่ สงครามล้างเผ่าพันธุ์มนุษย์จักรกล</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Appleseed</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5080" type="Sequel">Appleseed Saga Ex Machina</anime>
<anime id="10636" type="Alternative Setting">Appleseed Alpha</anime>
<anime id="166" type="Alternative Setting">Appleseed</anime>
<anime id="8055" type="Other">Appleseed XIII</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="247" approval="37" total="49">Koukaku Kidoutai Stand Alone Complex</anime>
<anime id="5106" approval="18" total="18">Vexille: 2077 Nihon Sakoku</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="97536">Really great fighting scences but not much else. And the sway of 3D made me a little seasick. All in all, I`ve seen worse.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="447033">Need an action movie? 
Take this one! What else can I say?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="468231">If you have a surround system with sub, i recommend this with all my heart! The animation i stunning, the sound quality is "out of this world". I still remember (after 10 years) the sound of the 30-50 mm gatling gun firing in the beginning of the movie. Do not remember if the characters and manuscript was good, but i don`t think i cared;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="348382">Action-packed movie full of incredible CGI animation</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="271087">This is a Great anime with a Good Story Line with an even better Sequel</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="871" type="Original Work">Shirou Masamune</name>
<name id="1922" type="Character Design">Yamada Masaki</name>
<name id="150" type="Direction">Aramaki Shinji</name>
<name id="4827" type="Music">Boom Boom Satellites</name>
<name id="1388" type="Work">Digital Frontier</name>
</creators>
<description>In 2131 AD http://anidb.net/ch9605 [Deunan Knute] has been a soldier on countless battlefields for most of her life. When the World War ends, she is transported to the city of Olympus to live peacefully and finds out that, in an effort to protect the human race from future wars, humans have created the Bioroids, a genetically enhanced race of people that have restrained feelings and therefore cannot hurt each other.
She also discovers, however, that not everyone is happy with this Human-Bioroid symbiosis: many humans treat Bioroids as a lower species and as a threat to their future. The human-controlled military is seeking to annihilate all Bioroids, and the Bioroid-controlled government is afraid of a coup d`état.
The task falls on Deunan to control the situation, and to avert the inter-species war. In this she is aided by her former lover, http://anidb.net/ch9606 [Briareos], who has lost his body in war, to become a cyborg — a brain in an artificial body.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5325">5.40</permanent>
<temporary count="5354">7.25</temporary>
<review count="10">6.63</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224520.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2532</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>54</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1386</identifier>
<identifier>hzvwca</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Appleseed_(film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アップルシード#APPLESEED</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>336</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>319227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8855</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2180" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-24">
<name>cyborg</name>
<description>A cyborg is a cybernetic organism (i.e. an organism that has both artificial and natural systems). The term was coined in 1960 when Manfred Clynes and Nathan Kline used it in an article about the advantages of self-regulating human-machine systems in outer space. D. S. Halacy`s Cyborg: Evolution of the Superman in 1965 featured an introduction which spoke of a "new frontier" that was "not merely space, but more profoundly the relationship between `inner space` to `outer space` -a bridge...between mind and matter." The cyborg is often seen today merely as an organism that has enhanced abilities due to technology, but this perhaps oversimplifies the category of feedback.
Fictional cyborgs are portrayed as a synthesis of organic and synthetic parts, and frequently pose the question of difference between human and machine as one concerned with morality, free will, and empathy. Fictional cyborgs may be represented as visibly mechanical (e.g. the Cybermen in the Doctor Who franchise or The Borg from Star Trek); or as almost indistinguishable from humans (e.g. the "Human" Cylons from the re-imagining of Battlestar Galactica). The 1970s television series The Six Million Dollar Man featured one of the most famous fictional cyborgs. Cyborgs in fiction often play up a human contempt for over-dependence on technology, particularly when used for war, and when used in ways that seem to threaten free will. Cyborgs are also often portrayed with physical or mental abilities far exceeding a human counterpart (military forms may have inbuilt weapons, among other things).
Real (as opposed to fictional) cyborgs are more frequently people who use cybernetic technology to repair or overcome the physical and mental constraints of their bodies. While cyborgs are commonly thought of as mammals, they can be any kind of organism.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42022.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2643" parentid="2638" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>power suit</name>
<description>Power Suits are similar to Piloted Robots which are controlled from inside the robot except that Power Suits tend to be more directly tied to how the character moves and they are usually not as big as Piloted Robots can be. They are still mechanical and shouldn`t be confused with plug suits.</description>
<picurl>222235.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3322" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-04">
<name>remake</name>
<description>This anime is a remake of a previously released story, anime, or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5571" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-08-27">
<name>Greek mythology</name>
<description>The anime is derived or draws elements from the Greek mythology, and as such features some mythological characteristics of Ancient Greece. Those may be creatures, such as the Centaur or Hydra, tales, such as that of the Trojan War, or even the Gods themselves, like Zeus or Poseidon. More subtle references also count, such as the careful usage of names of places or people that hold significance in the myths.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5788" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-03">
<name>experiments</name>
<description>Involves (para-)scientific experiments.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5963" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-12">
<name>utopia</name>
<description>"Paradise". Portrays a peaceful, united civilization striving for perfection. This may include the world living as one in peace or just an isolated society, at peace with all their surroundings and anything that exists on the outside is irrelevant. In these conditions, humans may have obtained balance with technology which now exists merely to enhance human living standards. Advanced science and technology allow the absence of death and suffering and/or changes in human nature and condition. Technology has affected the way humans live to such an extent that normal functions such as sleep, eating or reproduction are replaced by artificial means (which may include a society comprised of a single gender). A healthier, more intelligent race has been bred. Many or all people exist with traits and special talents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5998" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-08">
<name>spider tank</name>
<description>A spider tank is a tank that uses four or more legs for movement instead of the tracks seen in most real-life tanks.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9605" type="main character in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="104">6.97</rating>
<name>Deunan Knute</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Deunan Knute along with her partner Briareos Hecatonchires, she is one of ESWAT`s most important members. Known for her tendency to anger and lack of patience, Deunan is still widely appreciated by her partners for her professionalism and acumen.
As an ESWAT member, Deunan is a specialist in weapons handling, explosive devices manipulations, hand-to-hand combat, and an excellent Landmate pilot. According to the Appleseed Databook, she is trained to be ambidextrous.</description>
<picture>29289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3092" picture="23997.jpg">Kobayashi Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9606" type="main character in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="61">6.51</rating>
<name>Briareos Hecatonchires</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Briareos is a trained ESWAT officer, his point man is Deunan. They met in her father`s SWAT unit before World War III broke out. Briareos and Deunan are lovers and have been involved since before the war. Since moving to Olympus with Deunan, they have joined the ESWAT unit (Extra Special Weapons And Tactics). He is named after Briareus the Vigorous, one of the Hecatonchires (hundred-armed giants) of Greek mythology.</description>
<picture>29290.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14432" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="14">5.20</rating>
<name>Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A second-generation Bioroid, Hitomi is charged with recruiting new members of ES.W.A.T. She had led the rescue mission of Deunan Knute in the Badlands, as well as aiding her getting settled in Olympus. Although her emotions are regulated, she has interest in the emotion of love, and is disturbed by hate, as expressed by the human soldiers of the O.R.A, especially towards the Bioroids.</description>
<picture>42018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14433" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-27">
<rating votes="3">2.45</rating>
<name>Hades</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Colonel Hades is Gen. Uranus`s subordinate. Like Uranus, he has a great distrust of the Bioroids. However, his distrust has evolved into an irrational, all-consuming hatred, and wishes to see the Bioroids destroyed.</description>
<picture>42019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14434" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-31">
<rating votes="5">6.04</rating>
<name>Athena Areios</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Friend of Gilliam Knute that helped to destroy and hide the original Appleseed data from the hands of humans.</description>
<picture>42020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14539" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-29">
<rating votes="3">3.75</rating>
<name>General Edward Uranus III</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>General Edward Uranus III is the supreme commander of Olympus` regular army. He greatly distrusts the Bioroids, so much so that he is willing to start a coup de `etat in order to wipe them out!</description>
<picture>42136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3135" picture="24120.jpg">Fujimoto Yuzuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36267" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-02-23">
<rating votes="9">4.75</rating>
<name>Nike</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>81359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="65413.png">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="14992" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="6">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="16927" update="2008-08-28">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="5">6.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26320" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2004-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26321" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2004-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26612" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="1">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Backstage Features</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26701" update="2005-06-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>105</length>
<airdate>2004-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31206" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2004-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31207" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2004-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31208" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>35</length>
<airdate>2004-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35992" update="2011-05-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2005-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Extra - Dive For You</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92179" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Design Archives</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92180" update="2010-04-14">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>35</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Birth of 3D Live Anime</title>
</episode>
<episode id="92723" update="2008-08-28">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">US Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
