<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13157" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>2</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-08-25</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Honoo no Haramase Oppai: Ero Appli Gakuen The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">불꽃의 능욕 가슴: 에로어플리 학원</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">炎の孕ませおっぱい★エロアプリ学園 THE ANIMATION</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4737" type="Same Setting">Honoo no Haramase Tenkousei</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=1829&amp;cid=1</url>
<creators>
<name id="1332" type="Original Work">Squeez</name>
<name id="27343" type="Animation Work">Seven</name>
<name id="55613" type="Direction">Pyou Ryuu</name>
<name id="55613" type="Character Design">Pyou Ryuu</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="109">5.40</permanent>
<temporary count="112">6.18</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>203110.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35512</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=1829&amp;cid=1</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.pinkpineapple.co.jp/detail.php?did=1914&amp;cid=4</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19345</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="301" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-10">
<name>lactation</name>
<description>Capable of secreting breast milk, sometimes referred to as Mother`s milk.</description>
<picurl>176139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2693" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-10">
<name>handjob</name>
<description>A handjob is the manual stimulation of the penis by another person`s hand. The female equivalent is http://anidb.net/t7229 [fingering].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2695" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>yuri</name>
<description>Yuri refers to anime that portray lesbian (female/female) sex. Do not confuse this with the http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai] category under Romance, which only portrays girl/girl relationships, but generally not anything pornographic. This is real female/female porn.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>150944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2699" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>sixty-nine</name>
<description>At least one sex position from a group generically called sixty-nine or 69 is featured, characterised by a mutually inverted alignment of two people of any sex in which both perform oral sex simultaneously. Putting it another way, the top of the head of one person points more or less towards the feet of the other, and the head of each is at the height of the other`s genitals, and both perform cunnilingus or fellatio, whichever is appropriate in each case. The name stems from this mutual inversion, which resembles the numbers 6 and 9.</description>
<picurl>162104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2702" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-16">
<name>mammary intercourse</name>
<description>Mammary intercourse is a sex act, performed as foreplay or as non-penetrative sex, that involves the stimulation of the male penis by the female breasts. Commonly, this sex act involves the man placing his penis in the woman`s cleavage and thrusting between her breasts, while the breasts are squeezed around the penis for additional stimulation, and fellatio may also be performed in combination. Mammary intercourse is also commonly known as titty-fucking or titfuck in the United States, as well as tit wank or French fuck in the United Kingdom. The Japanese term, paizuri (from oppai, breasts, and the verb suru, used in this context to describe the sexual act), is commonly used in the anime fandom. A variant term is "naizuri" (a pun on nai, the negative of the verb aru, indicating existence/presence), which describes an attempt to do a paizuri, but with insufficient cleavage.</description>
<picurl>174692.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2705" parentid="2848" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>creampie</name>
<description>The act of a man ejaculating inside a girl`s vagina, leaving the semen oozing out of her.</description>
<picurl>160720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2722" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>doggy style</name>
<description>Bang her from behind and use her boobies as a steering wheel!</description>
<picurl>161394.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2725" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-20">
<name>ahegao</name>
<description>A term for the weird face occasionally seen in adult games/anime/manga. Canonically, ahegao has eyes rolled up, mouth open and tongue sticking out. Sometimes also referred to as "fucked silly".</description>
<picurl>175637.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2734" parentid="2695" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-18">
<name>scissoring</name>
<description>Scissoring is a lesbian sex act where the partners interlock their spread legs (like two pairs of scissors) and grind their vulva together to stimulate each other.</description>
<picurl>166100.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2739" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>brother-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two siblings of opposite sex.</description>
<picurl>210881.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2899" parentid="2712" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-04-21">
<name>strapon</name>
<description>Employs the use of an artificial phallus so that the female can engage in the penetrating role during intercourse. Not to be confused with a http://anidb.net/t6455 [double-sided dildo].</description>
<picurl>185955.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2900" parentid="2712" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-20">
<name>dildos - vibrators</name>
<description>These are toys that are used for sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3976" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-18">
<name>impregnation</name>
<description>At least one of the character is impregnated during the anime. This is confirmed by the characters, or the character is later shown as pregnant. Merely shouting "I`ll become pregnant!" or something similar during sex is not impregnation.
A porn anime can be tagged with impregnation only when all of the following conditions are met:
* She must be shown having sex in such a way that she can become pregnant
* She must be known as http://anidb.net/t775 [pregnant] after the fact, be it the pregnant stomach, pregnancy test, verbal confirmation, doctor`s report, etc
* Having an abortion after the event, does not change the fact that an impregnation still occurred
* http://anidb.net/t2705 [Creampies] are not a necessary criteria to have an impregnation, and impregnations do not automatically result from a creampie.
If she is impregnated by a non-human, the http://anidb.net/t7148 [impregnation with larvae] tag may also apply.</description>
<picurl>221652.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4049" parentid="2721" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>outdoor sex</name>
<description>Popular place for sex in visual novels and manga.</description>
<picurl>175405.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6268" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>fellatio</name>
<description>Fellatio is oral sex performed upon the penis. It may be performed to induce male orgasm and ejaculation of semen, or it may be used as foreplay prior to sexual intercourse.</description>
<picurl>165408.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6455" parentid="2900" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>double-sided dildo</name>
<description>A regular dildo is inserted by hand. A double-sided dildo is inserted into the penetrating girl`s vagina and held in place there, so that she can penetrate the receiving girl the same way a male would. Not to be confused with a http://anidb.net/t2899 [strapon].</description>
<picurl>175704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89131" type="main character in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="2">9.25</rating>
<name>Shamy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42805" picture="171542.jpg">Yatsuhashi Kinako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89132" type="main character in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="4">8.99</rating>
<name>Velka Valentina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42805" picture="171542.jpg">Yatsuhashi Kinako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89133" type="main character in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="3">9.20</rating>
<name>Uesaka Ayane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50052" picture="197256.jpg">Yuuki Honoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89134" type="main character in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="5">7.92</rating>
<name>Hatsunegaoka Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202793.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89135" type="main character in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="3">9.20</rating>
<name>Shiramine Sumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48607" picture="197436.jpg">Kazahana Mashiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89136" type="main character in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="4">9.46</rating>
<name>Majime Risa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50051" picture="201925.jpg">Hano Natsuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91229" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-02">
<rating votes="1">4.70</rating>
<name>Shamy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206750.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42805" picture="171542.jpg">Yatsuhashi Kinako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91390" type="main character in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="1">9.73</rating>
<name>Majime Masato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207061.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43178">Yuuhi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95058" type="main character in" update="2018-04-17">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Nikozaki Riko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48664" picture="197511.jpg">Fujimura Suzuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95059" type="main character in" update="2018-04-17">
<rating votes="2">9.50</rating>
<name>Kimizuka Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12423" picture="30758.jpg">Kannazuki Honoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95060" type="main character in" update="2018-04-17">
<rating votes="2">9.50</rating>
<name>Kisaragi Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216320.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52501" picture="209350.jpg">Arikawa Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95061" type="main character in" update="2018-04-17">
<rating votes="2">9.50</rating>
<name>Shimano Matsuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43976" picture="178145.jpg">Ayane Mako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95062" type="main character in" update="2018-04-17">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Sayama Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216319.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46911" picture="191216.jpg">Yahiro Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="187489" update="2017-06-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2017-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194393" update="2017-12-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2018-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
