<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13165" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Houseki no Kuni (2017)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Страна самоцветов</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">보석의 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Bảo Thạch Chi Quốc</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">寶石之國</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">宝石の国 (2017)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Land of the Lustrous</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">L`Ère des Cristaux</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">宝石之国</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9983" type="Other">Houseki no Kuni</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="26332">Not bad, but there is no proper ending. The 12 episodes feels like only the beginning of the story. It ends with a cliffhanger.........</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="625307">slice-of-life, action and mystery. this show is centred around Phos creating relationships, exploring the world and coping with truth.

characters are lively and likeable. comedic relief is woven into the story in a natural way. the mystery of the world is the driving force behind the plot.

if you can stomach the badly executed information dumps at the beginning, you get a nice joyride around Phos world.

PS: be warned. this ends in a huge cliffhanger.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://land-of-the-lustrous.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="4246" type="Character Design">Nishida Asako</name>
<name id="23623" type="Series Composition">Oono Toshiya</name>
<name id="16800" type="Work">Orange</name>
<name id="21152" type="Direction">Kyougoku Takahiko</name>
<name id="31562" type="Music">Fujisawa Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="38265" type="Original Work">Ichikawa Haruko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a slice of life fantasy seinen manga series written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr38265 [Ichikawa Haruko].
In the distant future, microscopic organisms have left the planet desolate and given way to a new life form: Houseki. However, all is not peaceful. The 28 Houseki must fight against the Moon Dwellers, beings who attack them without discrimination and use their shattered bodies as decorations. For this reason, each Houseki is assigned a role, whether it be a fighter or a medic. http://anidb.net/ch91046 [Phosphophyllite], or Phos, is the youngest of their kin, and has not been given an assignment due to a lack of skill. Everything changes when http://anidb.net/ch91112 [Kongou], the leader of the Houseki, assigns Phos the task of creating an encyclopedia of natural history.
Source: sentai filmworks
Note: The first three episodes received an early screening at a special event held at Toho Cinemas Roppongi Hills in Tokyo on 24.09.2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1315">8.01</permanent>
<temporary count="1322">7.82</temporary>
<review count="1">4.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221763.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19614</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35557</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://land-of-the-lustrous.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Land_of_the_Lustrous</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>宝石の国</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4696</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360705</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20569</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>houseki_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0767P3MV6</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="807" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>prosthesis</name>
<description>A prosthesis (prosthetic) (from Ancient Greek πρόσθεσις, "addition, application, attachment") is a device that replaces a missing body part.</description>
<picurl>223944.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1396" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-01">
<name>immortality</name>
<description>Immortality is the ability to live in a physical or spiritual form for an infinite or inconceivably vast length of time. Humans, whose life span is limited and who die of age, disease and external trauma, have long sought ways to extend their lives; the Epic of Gilgamesh, considered one of the first great literary works created by mankind, is primarily the quest of a hero seeking to become immortal. The advances of science, in particular medicine and engineering, and especially in the last few centuries, have helped people extend their life span and may yet continue finding ways to do so.
In fiction, immortals are not quite as uncommon as in real life, and the possible implications of endless or very long lives are often explored. Such implications include, but are not limited to: repeatedly accompanying the deaths of those dear to them; having to hide their condition from the mortals surrounding them; becoming disillusioned with their lives and being unable to kill themselves; and even staying forever trapped in the body of a specific physical age, that body most often being that of a child. As such, while many may wish for immortality, it may be little more than a curse for the few who have it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2481" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-08">
<name>teleportation</name>
<description>Teleportation is the transfer of matter from one point to another, possibly a distant one, without application of force, and generally instantly. This contradicts scientific law as we know it, and is therefore nowadays impossible. Sometimes it appears as a paranormal or supernatural ability, and sometimes it is shown in science fiction through technological devices backed up by scientific laws yet to be discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3097" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-29">
<name>underwater</name>
<description>Underwater is a term describing the realm below the surface of water where the water exists in a natural feature such as an ocean, sea, lake, pond, or river.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3265" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>death is cheap</name>
<description>Important characters will have a terrible tendency to die dramatically, but will not, under any circumstances, stay dead. This tends to cheapen the dramatic death of a character to the point of being little more than a flesh wound if overused. If you ever hear passing mention of any form of afterlife in a series, be warned that the value of "dead" has become a whole lot less all of a sudden. Similarly, if the entire supporting cast is being killed off left and right, expect a resurrection by the end of the current arc. This trope became so common in some series that most people are more likely to be shocked if a character does not come back from the dead than when it does.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4196" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-23">
<name>fate worse than death</name>
<description>If you think death is the worst that can ever happen to someone, you had better think again: at least one character in this show is sure to end up in such a terrible way that many people would likely have preferred death if they had the choice. The fate of such characters is normally not for the faint of heart, and the audience is expected to at least sympathise with the poor character`s fate, and at times even be horrified at the shocking turn of events that led to their demise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4388" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-16">
<name>deconstruction</name>
<description>In the context of fiction, a deconstruction is the act of taking storytelling devices and exploring their real-life consequences, commonly in dark and cynical ways. Deconstructions often reveal the dark and terrifying aspects of some of the themes and elements that appear recurrently in fictional works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4558" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-12">
<name>long time span</name>
<description>The anime spans a much longer than usual (for that genre) period of time, typically several years (possibly decades or even centuries).
Example: In a school setting this could mean the character development is followed from school through college right into working life and the founding of a family with children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5284" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-22">
<name>ocean world</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7086" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>soft science fiction</name>
<description>Soft science fiction is a type of science fiction in which the science presented is scientifically inaccurate or unimportant to the story, in contrast to http://anidb.net/t4667 [hard science fiction]. Its elements generally present themselves via artistic licence.
This is not to be confused with social science fiction, confusingly also called "soft science fiction", which is science fiction concerned with the "soft sciences" (social sciences), as opposed to the "hard sciences" (natural sciences).</description>
<picurl>222752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7131" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-05">
<name>Crunchyroll Anime Awards</name>
<description>Crunchyroll Anime Awards are annual awards given to recognize anime from the previous year. The awards were first held in January 2017. The judges create a short list in different categories and public votes for the winners are held online.</description>
<picurl>219996.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="91046" type="main character in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="26">7.16</rating>
<name>Phosphophyllite</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Phosphophyllite, Phos for short, is one of the weaker jewel people, with a hardness of 3.5. Declared as too weak for battle, Phos is tasked with creating an encyclopedia logging new information. As Phos keeps experiencing hardships in battle, their limbs, along with their memories, are gradually lost and replaced with other elements, including agate legs and arms made from gold and platinum alloy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91047" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="10">7.24</rating>
<name>Shinsha</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Cinnabar is an aloof jewel person who is even weaker than http://anidb.net/ch91046 [Phos], with a hardness of 2, but carries a powerful poison in their body. Because this poison taints the environment and erases memories stored inside affected jewel shards, Cinnabar is kept on night watch, but yearns to escape the night.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91048" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="16">7.54</rating>
<name>Diamond</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diamond is kindhearted jewel person who has the maximum hardness of 10, but is still fragile against enemy attacks.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91049" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="14">6.77</rating>
<name>Bort</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bort is a diamond-class jewel person who is powerful in combat and protective of http://anidb.net/ch91048 [Diamond].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91050" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="4">7.43</rating>
<name>Morganite</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91051" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="3">7.23</rating>
<name>Goshenite</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91052" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="7">7.71</rating>
<name>Rutile</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rutile is the medic jewel person in charge of fixing the others jewels when they`re broken, although they have a habit of wanting to dissect what catches their attention.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91053" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="6">6.43</rating>
<name>Alexandrite</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Alexandrite is a jewel person with an obsession with understanding the Lunarians, although they have a tendency to turn berserk when they see one. As such, http://anidb.net/ch91112 [Master Kongo] has forbidden them from fighting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91054" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="3">7.23</rating>
<name>Euclase</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206456.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91055" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="6">7.16</rating>
<name>Jade</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jade is a jewel person who works as secretary for http://anidb.net/ch91112 [Master Kongo]. http://anidb.net/ch91054 [Euclase]`s partner.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91056" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="3">7.23</rating>
<name>Zircon</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zircon is the second youngest jewel person after http://anidb.net/ch91046 [Phos], and http://anidb.net/ch91057 [Yellow Diamond]`s partner.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38966" picture="147731.jpg">Akaneya Himika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91057" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="5">7.71</rating>
<name>Yellow Diamond</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="570" picture="151691.jpg">Minagawa Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91107" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-21">
<rating votes="4">6.26</rating>
<name>Amethyst 33</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91108" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="4">5.76</rating>
<name>Obsidian</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Obsidian is a jewel person in charge of manufacturing the tools, weapons and daily items for the other jewels.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>208344.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="346" picture="17184.jpg">Hirohashi Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91109" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-14">
<rating votes="3">5.92</rating>
<name>Neptunite</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208343.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91110" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-14">
<rating votes="3">6.58</rating>
<name>Benitoite</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208342.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39007" picture="148258.jpg">Ozawa Ari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91111" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="4">6.96</rating>
<name>Red Beryl</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Red Beryl is a jewel person in charge of designing and fixing the outfits of the other jewels, changing their hairstyle frequently.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>208345.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91112" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="5">7.11</rating>
<name>Kongou-sensei</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Master Kongo is a powerful monk who oversees the jewel people. He is much sturdier than the jewels and when meditating or sleeping, he scarcely wakes up.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>208346.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91755" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-21">
<rating votes="4">6.26</rating>
<name>Amethyst 84</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212163.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92472" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-25">
<rating votes="8">8.86</rating>
<name>Antarcticite</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209906.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92473" type="appears in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="2">7.55</rating>
<name>Aculeatus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92474" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="10">7.30</rating>
<name>Ventricosus</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93001" type="appears in" update="2018-01-20">
<rating votes="4">6.45</rating>
<name>Padparadscha</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Padparadscha is http://anidb.net/ch91052 [Rutile]`s partner. A jewel person nearly as old and strong as the diamonds, who was born incomplete, hence spending most of their time asleep.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93169" type="appears in" update="2018-01-04">
<rating votes="1">3.81</rating>
<name>Shiro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211614.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="190944" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魂・肉・骨</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soul - Flesh - Bone</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Âme, chair et os</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">혼・살・뼈</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamashii Niku Hone</title>
<summary>Phos is attacked, but manages to make a new friend out of the attacker. Together, both travel to the ocean where Phos learns more about the past.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190945" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メタモルフォス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Metamorphose</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Métamorphos</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">메타모르포제</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Metamorphose</title>
<summary>Unable to find Phos the group is concerned of what happened to them. However, Diamond is determined to bring Phos back.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190946" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイヤモンド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Diamond</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Diamant</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">다이아몬드(금강석)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Diamond</title>
<summary>Phos is looking for ideas for the encyclopedia but is struggling to come up with anything. They go to Diamond for help as they have been working on a new technique.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190947" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フォスフォフィライト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phosphophyllite</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Phosphophylllite</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">포스포필라이트(인협석)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Phosphophyllite</title>
<summary>Master Kongo finally decides to give the young Phos an assignment. Much to Phos dismay the assignment is to write an encyclopedia about the world.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191225" update="2018-03-19">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">「鏡面の波」MV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kyoumen no Nami Music Video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">`Kyoumen no Nami` MV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191730" update="2017-10-15">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191731" update="2017-10-15">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192067" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アンタークチサイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Antarcticite</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Antarcticite</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">안타르크티사이트(남극석)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Antarcticite</title>
<summary>Pho has lost their arms, but Master Kongo believes them to be at the Chord Shore. Antarcticite makes it their mission to piece Phos back together.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="192068" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬眠</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hibernation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hibernation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">동면</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toumin</title>
<summary>It`s winter time and everyone is discussing the best way to make it through the cold. Meanwhile, Phos gets roped into Antarcticite`s yearly duties.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="192069" update="2017-11-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初陣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Première campagne</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">첫 출전</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uijin</title>
<summary>Phos has recovered from the disaster at sea and has gained a new ability! What will happen to Phos as they put their skill to use as a lookout?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="192070" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">귀환</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan</title>
<summary>Phos is captured by the Lunarians. King reveals the truth behind the deception but is interrupted by their slumbering brother.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193120" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい仕事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Work</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nouveau travail</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">새로운 일</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Shigoto</title>
<summary>Phos must now decide to follow their instinct or back down. What will happen if they try to investigate further?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193121" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secrets</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">비밀</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu</title>
<summary>A recent incident has ignited some internal questions in Phos` mind. Who`s Shiro and why is Sensei so kind to this Lunarian?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193122" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しろ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shiro</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shiro</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">시로</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiro</title>
<summary>To help them get a better grasp of their new-found abilities, Bot and Phos team up. Dia on the other hand feels a bit left out.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193123" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">春</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spring</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Printemps</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">봄</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru</title>
<summary>Spring comes with a bitter taste for Phos as they try to cope with the kidnapping of Antarcticite. In the meantime, the gems are trying to come to terms with the new Phos.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197187" update="2018-03-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">松本憲生氏作画によるスペシャルプリビズ映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Previsualization of Episode 8b by Matsumoto Norio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matsumoto Norio-shi Sakuga ni Yoru Special Pre-Viz Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198488" update="2018-04-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オープニング・ビデオコンテ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Storyboard</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Opening Video Konte</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
