<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13198" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-01</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Enmusubi no Youko-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">狐妖小红娘 (2017)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="synonym">Huyao Xiao Hongniang</title>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="synonym">Hu Yao Xiao Hongniang (Japanese Version)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">縁結びの妖狐ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Fox Spirit Matchmaker</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">인연을 맺어주는 여우 요괴</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">狐妖小红娘</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12119" type="Alternative Setting">Hu Yao Xiao Hongniang</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="540059">has many nice elements, feel like it doesnt add up though. Especially dont like the main underlying premise which is this kinda tragic comedy feel.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="89628">I liked the description, comedy+fantasy with romance is my thing. BUT it`s more like a parody than comedy. It feels as if this show is mocking my taste. Baka-bakashi and not in a good way. For fans only.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="724939">Comedy 7 / Romanic 5
Can`t wait for Season 2 or if it possible to have those. Story wasn`t end yet, if you thinking follow the story while watching it and try to link the clue together their is something nagging you to discover the truth secret of "Black Fox Spirit", "Tosan Koko", "Haku Gessho" aka "Touhou Gessho", "Tosan Yaya (Why she want Tosan Suusu to marry? or She just want her sister back, isn`t she?)" even those "Unification League" are also want "Void of Tears" to be complete. WHY?!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://enmusuyouko.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="29115" type="Character Design">Sin Gi-Cheol</name>
<name id="46246" type="Direction">Wang Xin</name>
<name id="44379" type="Work">Haoliners Huimeng Animation</name>
</creators>
<description>In a world where Spirits and Humans coexist and can fall in love with each other, many Spirits see their human loved ones die before them due to the Spirits` much longer life expectancy.
Even when that human is reborn, the previous memories of their past life is erased from their memory. However, it is said among Spirits that a certain "service" is spreading. This "service" is provided by the "Fox Spirit Matchmakers" who can revive the lost memories of their former lover.
This story follows a young Fox Spirit Matchmaker who tries her best to restore lost memories and spread love.
Source: crunchyroll
This is the 24 episode Japanese broadcast version that aired from 01.07.2017 till 16.12.2017. The original serialized Chinese broadcast version, http://anidb.net/a12119 [Hu Yao Xiao Hongniang], started airing from 26.06.2015.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="146">3.70</permanent>
<temporary count="149">5.59</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>204129.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19818</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31499</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://enmusuyouko.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>縁結びの妖狐ちゃん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4647</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360781</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20364</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>狐妖小红娘</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>enmusuyouko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3823" parentid="6348" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-03">
<name>recap in opening</name>
<description>A short recap of the previous episode(s) is included in the opening sequence. This can result in an opening longer than the traditional 1m30s.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4558" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-12">
<name>long time span</name>
<description>The anime spans a much longer than usual (for that genre) period of time, typically several years (possibly decades or even centuries).
Example: In a school setting this could mean the character development is followed from school through college right into working life and the founding of a family with children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6348" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2015-02-19">
<name>old animetags - OP ED</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6493" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manhua</name>
<description>The Chinese equivalent of the Japanese manga, produced in Mainland China, Hong Kong, and Taiwan.
See also http://anidb.net/t2798 [manga] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="90223" type="main character in" update="2017-12-04">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Haku Gesshou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90224" type="main character in" update="2017-07-04">
<rating votes="2">8.65</rating>
<name>Tosan Suusu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90225" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-04">
<rating votes="3">9.72</rating>
<name>Tosan Yaya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204611.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1961" picture="222838.jpg">Yonezawa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90226" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-04">
<rating votes="3">8.89</rating>
<name>Tosan Roro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90227" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-04">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Ou Fuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90228" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-04">
<rating votes="2">8.55</rating>
<name>Reki Setsuyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204614.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90229" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-04">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Han Unhi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91868" type="main character in" update="2017-10-20">
<rating votes="3">8.88</rating>
<name>Tosan Koko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92624" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-03">
<rating votes="3">9.33</rating>
<name>Seitou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210221.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92625" type="appears in" update="2017-12-03">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Ouken Fuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210222.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="262" picture="62656.jpg">Kirii Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92626" type="appears in" update="2017-12-03">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Touhou Gesshou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188442" update="2017-07-25">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの思い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les sentiments de chacun</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">저마다의 생각</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Omoi</title>
<summary>With his half of the frozen jewel in hand, Han Unhi has regained his human form and youkai powers. Now, he along with Gessho and Suusu are off to catch up with Setsuyo again to see if they can get the other half, since they stand greater chance of returning Setsuyo`s memories with it. However, according to Rei-chan, Unhi`s servant, the closer the two halves of the jewels get to each other disaster is sure to occur. Undeterred, Unhi heads to the hospital where Setsuyo is recovering only to encounter Fuuki and his nefarious plans.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741043</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188443" update="2017-07-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誓いの宝物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sworn Treasure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Serment sur l’objet précieux</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">맹세의 보물</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikai no Takaramono</title>
<summary>Gessho and Unhi follow Setsuyo and Fuuki on their date, using the memory mallets to continue to return the memories of Setsuyo`s former life to her. Unfortunately, nothing goes quite as smoothly as planned and Gessho begins to suspect there`s more here at play. Unhi needs to marry Setsuyo in order to regain his place in the line of succession but the universe and even Unhi`s own servant seem to be against him being reunited with his love.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741041</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188444" update="2017-07-25">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蘇る記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resurrected Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs exhumés</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">되살아 나는 기억</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Kioku</title>
<summary>In order to evade the clutches of Oh Fuuki and Unification League, Suusu and Haku Gessho have teamed up with Han Unhi, prince of the fox sand clan the Nishisaiiki. Unhi has been pursuing his lover, Reki Setsuyo, through her various reincarnations and seeks to revive their love but Setsuyo`s current incarnation is reluctant to cooperate. Thanks to Gessho`s intervention she has begun to remember her past life and her interactions with Unhi but it might not be enough. Meanwhile, Fuuki plots to find and capture Gessho by any means necessary.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741039</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188445" update="2017-07-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖狐スース</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fox Spirit Suusu</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sûsu l’esprit-renard</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">요우코 스스</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youko Suusu</title>
<summary>Tosan Suusu wishes to become a fully fledged fox spirit. However, to balance out the face that Suusu is not incredibly beautiful or intelligent like the rest of her clan, she is urged by her older sister, Tosan Yaya, to agree to an arranged marriage. Not willing to go along with her sister`s plans, Suusu runs away and winds up stumbling onto the set of a matchmaking television show. There she encounters a young man, Haku Gessho, who agrees to help her with her matchmaking assignment for a price. Suusu`s future rests on the outcome on this successful completion of this assignment.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741037</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189097" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚空の涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">False Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les larmes du vide</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">허공의 눈물</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuu no Namida</title>
<summary>In their search for the book of reincarnation, Gessho and Suusu find themselves under attack from various youkai, but one in particular, a spider youkai known as Seitou, has her own plans for the book. After she is powered up by a mysterious man, Seitou once again attacks the pair seeking the book. Suusu is left defenseless when Seitou appears to have done away with Gessho, but just as things look desperate, Suusu`s older sister, Yaya appears and things take a strange turn. The mysterious link between Suusu and Gessho only deepens, while Seitou seems to have some kind of tie to Oh Fuuki.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741051</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189098" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">転生の書</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Book of Reincarnation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le livre des réincarnations</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">전생의 서</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshou no Sho</title>
<summary>Just as it seems Haku Gessho`s life will go back to normal, he finds out his reward from Unhi has been confiscated by the Tosan Clan. Down on his luck, Gessho then finds himself being handed over to the Unification League by his own father, but surprisingly, Oh Fuuki tells him that he is now free and the League will no longer interfere with is life. Celebrating his new found freedom, Gessho attempts to begin life anew, but is quickly interupted by Suusu seeking his help in finding a special book called the Book of Reincarnation. However, when youkai attack Gessho`s new school, Gessho and Suusu learn they are not the only ones seeking the book.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741049</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189099" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誤解の真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Truth of the Misunderstanding</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vérité sur le malentendu</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">오해의 진실</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokai no Shinjitsu</title>
<summary>Attempting to deal with the unidentified youkai that is attacking them, Gessho uses his pure flame technique but in doing so he seems to awaken something in Suusu, though it only lasts for an instant. His flames, however, consume the hospital with Unhi and Setsuyo still inside. As the end draws near, Setsuyo reflects on her past life as she descends into the flames trying to put together the missing pieces of her memories. As the last puzzle piece falls into place it lookd as though it might be too late for the lovers. Will Unhi and Setsuyo`s love endure into another life time or will they perish in the flames?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741047</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189100" update="2017-09-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傷ついた心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wounded Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cœurs blessés</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">상처받은 마음</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizutsuita Kokoro</title>
<summary>As the situation at the hospital worsens, the memories that Setsuyo has awakened of her previous life awaken old wounds and misunderstandings. Setsuyo`s broken heart and rage fuels the much larger youkai that seems to be the root cause of all the trouble. Suusu and Haku Gessho are pulled into the fray as the confrontation between Setsuyo and Unhi only grows more desperate. Gessho attempts to sever the youkai tentacles that are feeding off of and manipulating everyone, but they will not be disconntected from Setsuyo and Unhi. Now it is up to Unhi to save his former lover before they are all destroyed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741045</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189956" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">南国の姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Southern Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La princesse venue du Sud</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">남국의 공주</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nankoku no Hime</title>
<summary>In order to try and recreate the only time SHE appeared, Tosan Yaya and the others have captured Haku Gessho and Tosan Suusu to put them through their elaborate recreation with the exact same situation as before. However, a mysterious figure known as the Southern Princess plots against them. Using Haku Gessho as her puppet, this shadowy young woman has possessed Haku Gessho with an evil demon and he begins to attack Suusu and their companions. Thanks to Tosan Yaya`s advanced techniques she is able to pull the demon from Haku Gessho but all is not well...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741059</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189957" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東方月初[げっしょう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Touhou Gessho</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gesshô Tôhô</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">토호 겟쇼</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touhou Gesshou</title>
<summary>With Ohken Fuuki`s life hanging in the balance, Touhou Gessho arrives just in time to save him from certain death. Will they be able to safely leave the Ohken mansion? Meanwhile, in the future, Tosan Roro employs a particular method to try and help Haku Gessho and Tosan Suusu regain the memories of their past lives.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741057</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189958" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">王権の剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ohken`s Sword</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’épée des Ouken</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">오켄의 검</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ouken no Ken</title>
<summary>Just as things are getting desperate and it looks like Seitou is going to be killed by Fuuki, she is saved by Haku Gessho. Seitou and Suusu are whisked away by the mysterious fox spirit woman to watch the fight unravel from a safe distance, but Seitou is unable to sit still and goes after Fuuki again. All attempts to make Fuuki remember his past life and the time he and Seitou spent together seem to not matter as he continues to attack Seitou. In desperation Seitou puts her own life on the line to remind her former lover of how much they once meant to each other.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741055</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189959" update="2017-10-08">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">王権富貴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ohken Fuuki</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fûki Ouken</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">오켄 후키</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ouken Fuuki</title>
<summary>Haku Gessho and Oh Fuuki are brought to the fox spirit village by Tosan Yaya. Following after them, the spider youkai, Seitou, is determined to help Fuuki remember their romance from his past life. While Fuuki is off charming women at a local tavern, Gessho accompanies Suusu to get her book of reincarnation repaired. Seitou, on the advice of a mysterious fox spirit woman, tries to sprinkle a memory powder on Fuuki while he is in the tavern, but he discovers her and Seitou is confronted with his passionate hatred of youkai.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741053</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190703" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対零域</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Absolute Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le zéro absolu</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">절대영역</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Reiiki</title>
<summary>Due to his possession by an even worse demon, Haku Gessho has lost consciousness and unleashed his void tears upon Tosan Yaya. Desparate to save her sister, Tosan Suusu jumps in front of the attack. In that moment, Tosan Koko appears before Yaya. However, she is consumed by Gessho`s void tears and vanishes right before their eyes and Yaya is heartbroken. Consumed by grief and regret, Yaya begins attacking the out of control Gessho. Can they successfully retrieve Suusu from the void?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741061</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191130" update="2017-10-24">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東方月初の選択</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Touhou Gessho`s Decision</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le premier vrai choix de Gesshô Tôhô</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">토호 겟쇼의 선택</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touhou Gesshou no Sentaku</title>
<summary>Having deceived the monks of the Unification League into finally leaving by faking Touhou Gessho`s death, Tosan Koko takes the boy in as repayment for his having saved her life. Thus, time passes and Gessho lives his life with the Tosan. However, 10 years later, Gessho suddenly decides to leave Tosan for reasons unknown. Yaya has always been mystified by this but Gessho insists that it is all part of his and Koko`s dream.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749849</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191131" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">東方霊族の血</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blood of the Touhou Spirit Clan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le sang du clan Tôhô</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">토호 영족의 피</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Touhou Reizoku no Chi</title>
<summary>Having taken the flaming red pill, Kinmen Kashin is not only brought back from the brink of death, but now possesses power beyond imagination. Tosan Koko struggles desperately to protect her sisters from his powerful attacks but even she is no match for his immense powers. Just as all hope is seemingly lost, young Gessho steps forward and offers the power of his blood and his own life to save them. Does this mean the end of the irreplaceable Touhou spirit clan blood line?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749847</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191132" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金面火神</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Golden Fire God</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kinmen, le sage du feu</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">금면화신</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanezura Kagami</title>
<summary>Fleeing both the bad guys responsible for his parents` murder and a suspiciuos monk afer his family`s powerful lineage, a young Touhou Gessho retreats across the border into Tosan territory. Tosan Koko appears to keep the men out of her domain, and Gessho manages to secure sanctuary with the fox spirits for a few months. Just as Gessho is pleaing with Koko to allow him to remain in Tosan, another enemy suddenly appears to rain fire and destruction upon Koko and her clan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749845</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191718" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">七夕の計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tanabata Plans</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le plan de la fête du Tanabata</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">칠석의 계획</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanabata no Keikaku</title>
<summary>Haku Gessho manages to barely save Koko by diving into her dreams and preventing Sashi from stealing her youkai powers. In order to release Koko from the memories of her past that bind her, Haku Gessho hits her and himself with the memory mallets, but there is no change in her. However, Koko reacts to a random outburst from Gessho. 500 years ago, Touhou Gessho is readying to make things perfect to surprise Koko and confess his feelings for her on Tanabata. Will his feelings that he wasn`t able to confess that day finally free Koko from her trance?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749857</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191719" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心の傷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wounds of the Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La blessure du cœur</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">마음의 상처</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro no Kizu</title>
<summary>Koko and Roro were kidnapped by monks when they were children. In order to save them from being sold into slavery Koko did something that she will ultimately regret for the rest of her life. Using this incident against her Sashi controls Koko with his illusions. Wanting to return Suusu back to herself Haku Gessho returns to the fight and with Roro`s help dives into Koko`s dreams to try and break her from Sashi`s control before it`s too late.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749855</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191720" update="2017-11-07">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ココの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Koko`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret de Kôko</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">코코의 비밀</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koko no Himitsu</title>
<summary>Sashi, the adopted younger brother of Tosan Yaya and her sisters, who was enticed by the boss of the black fox spirits, has returned to destroy Tosan. He comes aided by a giant man with incredible powers packed into his fists and the fearsome Nightmare Fox to attack the fox spirits. Obsessed with his adoptive sister, Yaya, he has come to finally make her acknowledge him by destroying the ones she loves the most, Koko and Gessho. He reveals to Yaya that he knows about Koko`s secret, one that even she doesn`t know about that has scarred her older sister to her very core.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749853</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191721" update="2017-10-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">苦情樹への誓い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vow on the Grievance Tree</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le serment à l’Arbre des plaintes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">고정수에 맹세</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kujou Ki e no Chikai</title>
<summary>Haku Gessho and the others watch the performance in the Tosan Theater, watching the final scenes that unfold between Tosan Koko and an elderly Touhou Gessho. The effects of the little theater production become increasingly real much to the surprise of the observers, including Tosan Roro. As the performance reaches the climax a mysterious man appears who controls illusions and puts all but Roro to sleep. This man is revealed to be younger brother to the Tosan sisters. Just what is he after?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749851</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192789" update="2017-12-28">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スースの夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Suusu`s Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rêve de Sûsu</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">스스의 꿈</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suusu no Yume</title>
<summary>With the help of Haku Gessho and Suusu, all of the Northern Mountain Emperor`s memories of the time he lived in the Goyou kingdom have been returned. Angered by this, Sashi tries to use the Nightmare Fox to bring the Northern Mountain Emperor back under his control, but is thwarted by the mysterious appearance of the Goyou kingdom`s princess from so long ago. Will the Northern Mountain Emperor be able to fulfill the reincarnation matchmaking vow he made as a young boy? Meanwhile, Yaya convinces Haku Gessho to marry Suusu by agreeing to his enormous debt, but Suusu is not thrilled by this turn of events. What does this mean for their future?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749865</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192790" update="2017-12-28">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">破壊の王 北山妖帝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King of Destruction: The Northern Mountain Emperor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yôtei Hokusan, le Roi de la destruction</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">파괴의 왕 북산요제</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakai no Ou: Hokusan Youtei</title>
<summary>Long ago, there once was a kingdom called Goyou where youkai were forced into servitude using the mother and child talisman. One day, a youkai rebellion occured in that kingdom. Youkai who had spent hundreds of years being oppressed rose up seeking their freedom. That was also the day of the Goyou kingdom`s princess`s wedding. As the youkai lay siege to the castle a single man faces them in an effort to repel their attack and save the woman he loves. This is the story of the Northern Mountain Emperor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749863</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192791" update="2017-12-26">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚空の涙vs虚空の涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Void Tears vs Void Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Larmes du vide contre larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">허공의 눈물 VS 허공의 눈물</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuu no Namida vs Kokuu no Namida</title>
<summary>Trying to escape from the Northern Mountain Emperor and his violent rampage, Haku Gessho is stopped by Suusu noticing that the book of reincarnation is glowing signaling a new mission. Bolstered by the thought of his past debts being wiped clean Gessho agrees to help Suusu bring back the Northern Mountain Emperor`s memories of his former love. Gessho decides to use the void tears against his fearsome opponent but finds himself unprepared for the shrewdness of the youkai and it seems his quest to erase his past life debts won`t be going as easy as he thought.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749861</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="192792" update="2017-12-05">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北山妖帝の狙い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Aim of the Northern Mountain Emperor</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le but de Yôtei Tokusan</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">북산요제의 노림수</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokusan Youtei no Nerai</title>
<summary>As Oh Fuuki and the others are escaping the Tosan theater they encounter the Four Heavenly Kings and dispose of all but one easily. The remaining member, known as the Hundred Youkai King, proves to be especially challenging and without a single magical tool at his disposal, Oh Fuuki runs away leaving Seito and the others to handle things on their own. Meanwhile, with Koko`s consciousness under Touhou Gessho`s control, Suusu has returned to normal. Having subdued the Northern Mountain Emperor, Yaya has gone off to deal with the leader of the black fox spirits, but some surprising words from Sashi encourage him to break his icey prison.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749859</identifier>
<identifier>fox-spirit-matchmaker</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194389" update="2019-07-13">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194390" update="2019-07-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194391" update="2019-07-13">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194392" update="2019-07-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
