<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13192" restricted="true">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Skirt no Naka wa Kedamono Deshita.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">A Wolf in Women`s Clothing</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スカートの中はケダモノでした.</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">스커트의 안은 짐승이었습니다</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">裙子里面是野兽</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13402" approval="10" total="10">Omiai Aite wa Oshiego, Tsuyoki na, Mondaiji.</anime>
<anime id="13597" approval="9" total="10">25-sai no Joshikousei</anime>
<anime id="12760" approval="6" total="6">Souryo to Majiwaru Shikiyoku no Yoru ni...</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://skirt.w-anime.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="893" type="Animation Work">Magic Bus</name>
<name id="10926" type="Direction">Noshitani Mitsutaka</name>
<name id="50309" type="Original Work">Hanamaluo</name>
<name id="47183" type="Music">Kisaragi Natsuki</name>
<name id="52701" type="Work">Picante Circus</name>
<name id="53735" type="Series Composition">Toda Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="53736" type="Character Design">Nanashi</name>
<name id="53736" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nanashi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr50309 [Hanamaluo]`s adult romance manga.
http://anidb.net/ch89466 [Kominami Shizuka] is a mild-mannered college student who is having trouble adjusting to city life. One day, she meets http://anidb.net/ch89468 [Kirishima Ryou], another student who projects the image of a cool older sister. The two hit it off, but Shizuka is shocked when Ryou attempts to seduce her. Shizuka initially assumes that Ryou is a lesbian, but Ryou is in fact a man who dresses like a lady.
Source: crunchyroll
[i]Note: The first episode received an advance screening at a special event held at Shinjuku Loft/Plus One in Tokyo on 01.07.2017.
The anime has 3 versions - general version for regular TV audiences, an R15 version that was broadcast on AT-X, and an R18 version distributed via Anime Zone.[/i]</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="329">2.24</permanent>
<temporary count="335">4.75</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>202809.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19667</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35629</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://skirt.w-anime.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>スカートの中はケダモノでした。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4634</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360773</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20304</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sukakeda_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="618" parentid="2565" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>trap</name>
<description>A trap is a plot device where a male character is mistaken for a female, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the male (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the male, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the male character as a female; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through his behaviour, and/or language. A male character misinterpreted by others as female, without action from the male (explicitly feminine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t1637 [reverse trap].
Note: the tag image is from http://anidb.net/a10475 [Himegoto].</description>
<picurl>161537.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2667" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>university</name>
<description>Since college/university students are typically at least eighteen years old, with stories covering mature everyday life topics, you will find the college setting quite often in seinen and josei anime.
Topics that can now be covered - as compared to High School settings - are higher education (i.e. coping with higher intellectual stress), the more adult party life (i.e. alcohol, smoking, sex), the issues of daily life vs. studying - especially when having to work to pay for bills, and finally the possible friction between those in and out of college.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2713" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>oral</name>
<description>Oral sex is sexual activity involving the stimulation of the genitalia of a sex partner by the use of the mouth, tongue, teeth or throat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2827" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>sudden naked guy appearance</name>
<description>A male specimen previously unknown to the viewer and not dressed in any clothes suddenly appears out of nowhere.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2896" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-23">
<name>deflowering</name>
<description>Deflowering is the act of breaking the hymen of a female who hadn`t yet had vaginal intercourse. This tag can be applied only to pornographic anime in which a female is seen being deflowered; most often, one knows she had been a virgin because blood is seen coming out of her vagina during sex or after it, but her word on the matter is also considered valid.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2918" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>cunnilingus</name>
<description>Cunnilingus is an oral sex act performed on a female. It involves the use by a sex partner of the mouth, lips and tongue to stimulate the female`s clitoris and vulva. A female may receive cunnilingus as part of foreplay before sexual intercourse, or the sex partner may proceed until the female reaches orgasm.
The term is derived from the Latin words for the vulva (cunnus) and tongue (lingua).</description>
<picurl>161636.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2920" parentid="2713" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>rimming</name>
<description>Rimming is the act of using one`s tongue on the anus or perineum of another person in order to gain and/or give sexual pleasure.</description>
<picurl>165410.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3202" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-04">
<name>adoring fan club</name>
<description>A character, group or characters, or an organisation is considered so awesome that a adoring fan club is formed to idolise them. Not only do they have notable admirers, but their fans become organised in such a fashion to have a following that could only be guaranteed in real life by precise and long increments of paparazzi-like stalking.
If the character is sufficiently cool, an instant fan club may happen practically overnight (i.e., within a few episodes of them being introduced), although the subject of admiration typically has mixed feelings about the entire affair.</description>
<picurl>48684.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7134" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-08">
<name>ComicFesta Anime Zone</name>
<description>ComicFesta Anime Zone, established March 2017, is the anime distribution website for ComicFesta. ComicFesta is an electronic comic distribution site operated by WWWave Corporation (株式会社ウェイブ), with many original works (including doujin) posted directly by their publishers.
ComicFesta Anime Zone contains several original work and doujin teen and adult love anime. The full, uncensored versions are distributed on Anime Zone. The R-15 versions are broadcast on terrestrial TV and mainstream internet distribution websites. The late-night TV slot has also been referred to as the "monk frame" (僧侶枠) named after http://anidb.net/a12760 [the work which was first broadcast and delivered in this timeslot].
The anime from ComicFesta can have various levels of censorship depending on the distribution level used. Standard file notes as follows are used to denote the censorship level:
1) "Non-hentai broadcast." --- the airing on terrestrial TV, without any adult scenes.
2) "Hentai broadcast (creative censorship)." --- most likely an online stream, with http://anidb.net/t4112 [creative censorship] applied.
3) "Hentai broadcast." --- typical mosaic censoring applied on the genitals.</description>
<picurl>220426.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7222" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-30">
<name>groping</name>
<description>Groping is the act of subjecting another person to unwanted sexual touching.</description>
<picurl>68310.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7229" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>fingering</name>
<description>Fingering is the manual stimulation of the vagina by another person`s hand and fingers. The male equivalent is a http://anidb.net/t2693 [handjob].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7238" parentid="7220" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>attempted rape</name>
<description>Attempted rape is an unsuccessful attempt at http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape]. For AniDB purposes, generally an "unsuccessful" attempt is where both fellatio and penetration did not occur. Discretion should be applied on a case-by-case basis.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89465" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-24">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Kuratani Sousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202812.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89466" type="main character in" update="2017-05-24">
<rating votes="5">3.22</rating>
<name>Kominami Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50898" picture="215000.jpg">Hanakage Hotaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89467" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-24">
<rating votes="3">5.59</rating>
<name>Sakurai Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44297">Hara Maika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89468" type="main character in" update="2017-05-24">
<rating votes="4">3.95</rating>
<name>Kirishima Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50896">Satsuki Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96816" type="appears in" update="2018-07-20">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Kirishima Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220616.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50896">Satsuki Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188477" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静歌ちゃん, 好きだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">시즈쿠, 좋아해</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shizuka-chan, Suki Da yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188478" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どう? 俺のホントの姿</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">어때? 내 진짜 모습</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dou? Ore no Honto no Sugata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188479" update="2017-06-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こないだの続き, 今度は最後までシようか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">저번에 못한것, 이번엔 끝까지 해볼까?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Konaida no Tsuzuki, Kondo wa Saigo made Shiyouka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188480" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ごめんね, 我慢できなくなっちゃった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">미안, 더 이상 못참겠어</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gomen ne, Gaman Dekinakunacchatta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189138" update="2017-07-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">またデートしてほしいな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">또 데이트 하고 싶어라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mata Date Shite Hoshii na</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189139" update="2017-07-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">煽ったのはキミだからね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">부추긴건 너니까</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aotta no wa Kimi Dakara ne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189140" update="2017-07-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺のこと, ちゃんと見てほしくて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">날, 똑바로 봐줘</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore no Koto, Chanto Mite Hoshikute</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189141" update="2017-07-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本気じゃなきゃ, こんなに執着しない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">진심이 아니라면 이렇게까지 집착하지 않아</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honki ja Nakya, Konna ni Shuuchaku Shinai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189994" update="2017-08-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">...かわいいな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">...귀여워</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">...Kawaii na</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189995" update="2017-08-14">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もったいないよ. ちゃんと綺麗にしないと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아까워, 제대로 예쁘게 하지 않으면</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mottainai yo. Chanto Kirei ni Shinai to</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190065" update="2017-08-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">好きだ... 本当に好きだ...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">좋아해... 정말로 좋아해...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suki Da... Hontou ni Suki Da...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190066" update="2017-08-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">1.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対に嫌だ. 諦めるなんてできない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">절대로 싫어, 포기할 수 없어</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai ni Iya Da. Akirameru Nante Dekinai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202925" update="2018-07-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
