<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1320" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-12-20</startdate>
<enddate>2003-12-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Inuyasha: Tenka Hadou no Ken</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Sword of the World Conquest</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Sword That Rules Over the Empires</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">InuYasha - The World Conquering Swords</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">InuYasha - Sword of World Conquest</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Инуяша - Мечът на истинския владетел</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">IY Movie 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">IY THnK</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">犬夜叉 天下覇道の剣</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">InuYasha the Movie 3: Swords of an Honorable Ruler</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">InuYasha: Der Film - Die Schwerter, die die Welt unterwerfen</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">InuYasha - La Spada del Dominatore del Mondo</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Inuyasha - A Film 3: A világhódítás kardjai</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">犬夜叉 天下霸道之劍</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">犬夜叉 天下霸道之剑</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Inuyasha - La Espada Que Domina El Mundo</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="144" type="Parent Story">Inuyasha</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.toho-a-park.com/video/new/inuyasha3/</url>
<creators>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="3119" type="Character Design">Motohashi Hideyuki</name>
<name id="3412" type="Character Design">Hishinuma Yoshihito</name>
<name id="818" type="Original Work">Takahashi Rumiko</name>
<name id="124" type="Direction">Shinohara Toshiya</name>
<name id="2703" type="Music">Wada Kaoru</name>
<name id="3119" type="Chief Animation Direction">Motohashi Hideyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Many years ago, Inuyasha`s father, the Great Dog Demon, wielded the Three Swords of the Fang. Upon his death he bequeathed a sword to each of his sons, Inuyasha and his rival brother, Sesshomaru. He locked the third sword, the wrath-filled Sounga, away forever. Now, 700 years later, the Sounga`s tremendous power has been awakened and the two brothers must set aside their differences and join forces in an unlikely and uneasy alliance to battle a force that spells doom for all mankind.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1881">6.69</permanent>
<temporary count="1900">7.61</temporary>
<review count="3">6.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>48208.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2981</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>451</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1473</identifier>
<identifier>fxyqej</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.toho-a-park.com/video/new/inuyasha3/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>InuYasha_the_Movie_3:_Swords_of_an_Honorable_Ruler</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>犬夜叉_天下覇道の剣#.E7.8A.AC.E5.A4.9C.E5.8F.89_.E5.A4.A9.E4.B8.8B.E8.A6.87.E9.81.93.E3.81.AE.E5.89.A3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>430</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>318913</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6415</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2020</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>inuyasha-the-movie-3-swords-of-an-honorable-ruler</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7245" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="411">7.31</rating>
<name>Inuyasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>InuYasha is a hanyou (half-demon), the product of an inu-youkai (犬妖怪, dog demon) and a human. He wields Tetsusaiga, a supernatural sword made from one of his deceased father`s fangs. When properly wielded, the sword can destroy one hundred demons with a single swing. InuYasha can quickly recover from injuries that would be fatal to a human, largely due to his demonic blood. During the first night of each lunar month (new moon), InuYasha changes into a normal human with black hair and black eyes and loses his demonic powers.
InuYasha was bound to Goshinboku by Kikyo`s arrow for fifty years until Kagome freed him. InuYasha wears a special bead necklace that forces him to respond to Kagome`s command "Osuwari!", which translates to "Sit!" in English. In the English-dubbed version, "InuYasha, sit!" or "Sit, boy!" are sometimes used instead. Following the command, InuYasha is thrown to the ground. Kaede had placed the necklace upon InuYasha because he had threatened to kill Kagome if she refused to give the Jewel of Four Souls to him. As the series goes on, he begins to like Kagome more and more, shown when he will leave a battle to save her from being hurt.</description>
<picture>36855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7246" type="main character in" update="2011-04-09">
<rating votes="314">5.43</rating>
<name>Higurashi Kagome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Higurashi Kagome is one of the main protagonists of the series. Born in modern Japan as the reincarnation of the priestess Kikyo, Kagome has the Shikon Jewel unknowingly hidden inside her body until 1997, when a demon pulls her into the Bone Eater`s Well and 500 years back through time. They emerge in the Feudal Era about 50 years after Kikyo`s death, where the demon extracts the jewel from Kagome. When another demon seizes the jewel, Kagome shoots it with a bow and arrow.
While trying to protect the jewel using a bow and arrow, she accidentally shatters it into numerous shards that disperse throughout the country. She agrees to help find them, as she can sense the presence of nearby shards. As the series progresses, she falls in love with InuYasha, and finds herself competing with the revived Kikyo for his affections. During the search for the jewel, Kagome`s own spiritual powers and archery skills continue to improve.
At the end of the series, Kagome returns to her own time for three years. She is then able to return to the Feudal era where she and InuYasha acknowledge their love for one another and she chooses to remain there with him.</description>
<picture>36854.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="271" picture="171555.jpg">Yukino Satsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10477" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-02-09">
<rating votes="591">8.49</rating>
<name>Sesshoumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sesshoumaru is InuYasha`s older half-brother. Like their father, he is the Lord of the Western Lands, although Sesshoumaru maintains no permanent home. As a full-blooded Inu-yokai, he is a very powerful demon and nearly unequalled in raw power, but is unable to defeat Naraku in volume twenty-three of the manga. He has no interest in possessing even one shard of the Shikon Jewel to enhance his powers, since he is already supremely confident of his own strength.</description>
<picture>36856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10909" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="171">6.97</rating>
<name>Kikyou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kikyou is a powerful shrine maiden, or miko, who is given the task of guarding the Shikon Jewel. She falls in love with InuYasha and considers using the jewel to turn him from a half-demon into a full human; this would cause the Shikon Jewel to vanish, allowing her to live as an ordinary woman by his side. However, Naraku disguises himself as InuYasha to attack her village, mortally wounding her. With her last strength, Kikyou shoots a charmed arrow into the real InuYasha to seal him to a sacred tree, then orders the Shikon Jewel to be burned with her on her funeral pyre. The jewel disappears and is apparently destroyed, but is reborn 500 years later in the body of Higurashi Kagome, her spiritual reincarnation.
After Kagome travels back through time and reappears fifty years after Kikyou`s death, an ogress tries to pull her reincarnated soul into a clay body made with Kikyou`s bones and ashes. Kagome appears to suffer no permanent harm, but a small part of her soul detaches and reanimates the new body with Kikyou`s memories, personality, and human appearance. Although Kikyou retains some of her old powers in this form, she remains technically "dead" and must absorb the souls of dead women in order to move. At first, she wants to vengefully drag InuYasha to hell and kill Kagome to recover the rest of her soul. However, Kikyou gradually returns to her former compassionate nature and learns the real circumstances of her death was caused by Naraku.
She is also the sister of Kaede.</description>
<picture>36877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12156" type="appears in" update="2012-02-27">
<rating votes="23">7.44</rating>
<name>Toutousai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A youkai (probably) swordsmith. He forged both Inuyasha`s Tessaiga and Sesshoumaru`s Tenseiga. Toutousai generally appears with his flying, three-eyed cow.</description>
<picture>36861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3241" picture="24745.jpg">Yanami Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12160" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="90">3.82</rating>
<name>Shippou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shippou is an orphaned young fox demon who attempts to steal the Shikon Jewel from Kagome and InuYasha, wanting to become stronger and avenge his father`s death. Though his plan fails, Kagome and InuYasha aid him after hearing his story, and he becomes their companion for the rest of the series.
Shippou normally appears to be a young boy with certain fox-like features: his legs, feet, ears, and tail. He can shape-shift, but his other forms (such as a large pink flying balloon) are temporary and often ineffective, usually given away by his lingering fox tail. He can also create illusory duplicates of himself, as well as weak fox-fire magic and toy-based tricks such as his giant spinning top attack. Naively observant, he often directs cheeky comments to InuYasha, earning a smack on the head. InuYasha and Kagome serve as older sibling figures to Shippou. Because of his small size, Shippou often rides on Kirara or the shoulders of others. His actual age is never stated in the series; according to the official InuYasha guide by Takahashi Rumiko, his appearance is equivalent to that of a seven year old boy.</description>
<picture>36876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12161" type="main character in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="135">6.04</rating>
<name>Miroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miroku is a Buddhist monk who travels the countryside performing services such as exorcisms and demon exterminations, although sometimes he deliberately falsifies these to earn comfortable rewards. Miroku can attack enemies with his holy staff and sutra scrolls, but his greatest weapon, the Wind Tunnel embedded in the palm of his hand, is also a hereditary curse originally inflicted by Naraku upon Miroku`s grandfather Miyatsu. The Wind Tunnel sucks in almost anything in its path and is a powerful weapon against demons; however, it grows larger with increasing use, so that Miroku`s grandfather and father were eventually consumed by their own Wind Tunnels. Miroku hopes to break the curse by killing Naraku.
Miroku first meets InuYasha by stealing the Shikon Jewel, causing them to fight one another until Kagome leaps between them. After Miroku explains his situation, InuYasha allows him to join their group as a valuable ally. Miroku`s lechery is a recurrent habit, usually manifesting as shameless flattery, semi-surreptitious groping, and asking random women to bear him a child; he learned these bad habits from the monk Mushin who raised him, but he also has the more serious motive of wanting an heir to follow him if he dies without defeating Naraku.</description>
<picture>36866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12162" type="main character in" update="2017-01-11">
<rating votes="186">7.10</rating>
<name>Sango</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sango is a demon slayer who hails from a village of professional demon slayers. Naraku wipes out her entire family and village, then causes Sango to blame InuYasha and try to kill him. When the plot fails, Naraku revives Sango`s little brother Kohaku, controlling him as a pawn to manipulate Sango`s emotions and attack the rest of InuYasha`s group. Sango seeks vengeance against Naraku, but her primary goal is to rescue Kohaku from Naraku`s influence and save his life.
Of her broad repertoire of tools and tricks for fighting demons, her most powerful weapon is the Hiraikotsu, a massive boomerang made of purified demon bones. She is accompanied by the demon cat Kirara. Sango is often the victim of Miroku`s lecherous tendencies and slaps him for it.
She has three kids with Miroku by the end of the series, twin girls and a boy.</description>
<picture>36867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12163" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-04-11">
<rating votes="92">3.99</rating>
<name>Jaken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jaken is a small green imp-like youkai who is extremely loyal to Sesshomaru, often praising his master`s greatness although Sesshomaru usually ignores him. Jaken himself is not especially powerful, despite bearing a weapon known as the Staff of Two Heads. He seldom engages in battle and is actually killed by Kaijinbo with Toukijin, but Sesshomaru resurrects him with Tenseiga.</description>
<picture>46124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2244" picture="52187.jpg">Nagashima Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12164" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-11-11">
<rating votes="97">7.25</rating>
<name>Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rin is an orphan girl who finds http://anidb.net/ch10477 [Sesshomaru] in the woods after he is badly injured by InuYasha. Although Sesshomaru snubs her, she visits him regularly and attempts to take care of him, even stealing fish from the village for him until she learns that he doesn`t eat human food. The villagers beat her for the theft, but when Sesshomaru idly inquires about her injuries, she seems strangely happy about his interest in her welfare. During this time, she never speaks, only communicating with hand gestures and smiles.
Later, the wolf-demon http://anidb.net/ch12169 [Kouga] chases a thief to her village, then lets his wolves kill and eat the villagers. Rin flees through the forest towards Sesshomaru, but the wolves catch up to her. Recovered from his wounds, Sesshomaru is leaving when he catches Rin`s scent and follows it to her mauled corpse. Remembering her smile, he retests Tenseiga by using it to resurrect her. After setting Rin on her feet again, Sesshomaru walks away, leaving the dumbfounded http://anidb.net/ch12163 [Jaken] and a wide-eyed Rin standing on the path. After a moment, they both follow. The next time Rin appears, she is clean, wearing a new, colourful kimono, and talking and acting more like a typical child. Throughout the series, she continues to follow "Lord Sesshomaru", as she calls him; when he is away on dangerous tasks, she waits for him with Jaken and a two-headed dragon which she names "Ah-Un".
Though Sesshomaru never states any feelings for her, he displays a strong protective instinct and Rin is obviously devoted to him.</description>
<picture>36875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12165" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-07">
<rating votes="31">5.77</rating>
<name>Myouga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Myouga is a flea demon who appears randomly and gives InuYasha information on current events, foes, and the shards of the Shikon Jewel. Assigned to protect Tetsusaiga`s hiding place in the grave of InuYasha`s father, he runs away when Sesshomaru comes there in search of the sword. Myoga often flees before or during a battle, which the others recognize as a sign of pending danger; his mere presence in any area is enough to determine its safety. Myoga enjoys drinking demon blood, and actually saves InuYasha`s life at one point by drinking a spider demon`s venom out of his blood. He can save the others in a similar manner, but often gets slapped for drinking their blood without permission. In the anime series, he is engaged to another flea demon named Shoga, but continually runs from her to avoid the marriage.</description>
<picture>36874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="14095" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19053" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2003-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Many years ago, the Great Dog Demon wielded the Three Swords of the Fang. Upon his death, he bequeathed a sword to each of his sons, Inuyasha and Sesshomaru, leaving the third sword, the wrath-filled Sounga, locked away forever. Now that the Sounga`s power has been awakened, these two battling brothers must put away their sibling rivalry and face off against the force that spells doom for all mankind.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791417</identifier>
<identifier>inuyasha-the-movie-3-swords-of-an-honorable-ruler</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="21398" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>55</length>
<airdate>2003-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21401" update="2013-04-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2003-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
