<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13241" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-07-23</startdate>
<enddate>2018-10-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shingeki no Kyojin Season 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Shingeki no Kyojin S3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">AoT S3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">AoT3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SnK3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">進撃の巨人 attack on titan Season 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Attack on Titan Season 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">진격의 거인 3</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">进击的巨人 第三季</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14444" type="Sequel">Shingeki no Kyojin Season 3 (2019)</anime>
<anime id="10944" type="Prequel">Shingeki no Kyojin Season 2</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2"/>
<url>http://shingeki.tv/season3/</url>
<creators>
<name id="34645" type="Animation Work">Wit Studio</name>
<name id="6331" type="Character Design">Asano Kyouji</name>
<name id="6722" type="Music">Sawano Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="2702" type="Series Composition">Kobayashi Yasuko</name>
<name id="34803" type="Original Work">Isayama Hajime</name>
<name id="6969" type="Direction">Koizuka Masashi</name>
<name id="522" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kadowaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="1523" type="Chief Direction">Araki Tetsurou</name>
<name id="6331" type="Chief Animation Direction">Asano Kyouji</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch51115 [Eren] and his companions in the 104th are assigned to the newly-formed Levi Squad, whose assignment is to keep Eren and http://anidb.net/ch95626 [Historia] safe given Eren`s newly-discovered power and Historia`s knowledge and pedigree. http://anidb.net/ch54440 [Levi] and Erwin have good reason to be concerned, because the priest of the Church that http://anidb.net/ch54442 [Hanji] had hidden away was found tortured to death, making it clear that the Military Police are involved with the cover-up. Things get more harrowing when the MPs make a move on Erwin and the Levi Squad narrowly avoids capture. Eren is also having problems with http://anidb.net/ch55904 [his Titan transformation], and a deadly killer has been hired to secure Eren and Historia, one Levi knows all too well from his youth.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1712">8.19</permanent>
<temporary count="1725">7.97</temporary>
<review count="1">7.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221456.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19819</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35760</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>39477</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://shingeki.tv/season3/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Attack_on_Titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4983</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360990</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07LFKNBR3</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2649" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>dark fantasy</name>
<description>Focus set on darker themes in a fantasy setting, sometimes leaning towards horror elements. Bleak and pessimistic tones often dominate. Dark supernatural beings like vampires may play a significant role.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3435" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>eating of humans</name>
<description>The eating of humans, also called man-eating, is the practice of some species to prey on human beings for nourishment. Examples of possible hunters may include Earth animals, alien species, zombies or other undead, and so forth. Eating of humans is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3815 [human cannibalism]; the former is about other species eating people, while the latter is about humans eating fellow humans.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3958" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>coup d`etat</name>
<description>A coup d`état (/ˌkuːdeɪˈtɑː/; French: blow of state; plural: coups d`état), also known as a coup, a putsch, or an overthrow, is the sudden and illegal seizure of a government, usually instigated by a small group of the existing state establishment to depose the established government and replace it with a new ruling body. A coup d`état is considered successful when the usurpers establish their dominance. If a coup fails, a civil war may ensue.</description>
<picurl>10266.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5150" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-11">
<name>asymmetric warfare</name>
<description>Asymmetric warfare is war between conflicting groups whose relative military power differs, or whose strategy or tactics differ significantly.
Asymmetric warfare can describe a conflict in which the resources of two groups differ in essence, and in the struggle, they interact and attempt to exploit each other`s weaknesses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5842" parentid="2925" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-23">
<name>guerilla warfare</name>
<description>Guerrilla warfare is a form of irregular warfare and refers to conflicts in which a small group of combatants including, but not limited to, armed civilians use military tactics, such as ambushes, sabotage, raids, the element of surprise, and extraordinary mobility to harass a larger and less-mobile traditional army, or strike a vulnerable target, and withdraw almost immediately.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6730" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>torture</name>
<description>Torture involves the deliberate act of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or apply coercion to compel action from the victim. Torture, by definition, is a knowing and intentional act; deeds which unknowingly or negligently inflict pain without a specific intent to do so are not typically considered torture.
This is distinct from http://anidb.net/t2905 [erotic torture], which is generally for the purpose of using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="51114" type="main character in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="179">3.84</rating>
<name>Armin Arlert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eren`s best friend, he is physically and emotionally weak. His strategic abilities have saved Eren and Mikasa several times. He himself does not notice the things he does for Eren and Mikasa, and believes himself to be completely incompetent and hates himself for having to rely of Eren and Mikasa.</description>
<picture>134316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51115" type="main character in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="247">3.04</rating>
<name>Eren Yeager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eren Yeager is Shingeki`s protagonist. His adoptive sister, Mikasa, notes on numerous occasions that he acts on impulse without thinking things through, and she often pulls/carries/throws him when he starts fighting with others to protect him from himself. Along with Mikasa, he tends to spend his free time with their mutual friend, Armin.
When Eren was a child, he saved Mikasa from being killed when visiting her home with his father. Three men - killers of her parents - were in her house, and he killed two of them--one by slitting his throat and the other by charging at with a quickly assembled spear. Mikasa herself killed the third man when he attempted to strangle Eren. After this, he gave Mikasa his scarf and took her into his family.
Later, when the giants invaded his home, he could only watch on as his mother - trapped under the rubble of their house - was eaten by a giant. This event made him swear that he`d kill every giant and not live a life cowering in fear.
Sometime after this - before the timeskip that jumped a few years ahead, to when he became a soldier - his father injected him with something. It`s unknown what at this time but it turns out, because of the injection, Eren can regenerate lost limbs and transform into a somewhat out of control giant.</description>
<picture>134314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51116" type="main character in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="573">7.47</rating>
<name>Mikasa Ackerman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikasa Ackerman is the adoptive sister of Eren and mutual childhood friend of Armin, Mikasa hides her emotions but cares deeply for Eren--never hesitating to cry with tears of joy or despair depending on what happens to him. She shares an unbreakable bond with Eren following events in their past, and his mother requesting that she protect him made her even more overly protective of him than she was beforehand.
Subtle (and not-so-subtle) hints throughout the manga suggest she loves Eren as a man, rather than as a brother. However, in the first four volumes he hasn`t shown any such feelings in return; while he does show hints indicating he cares for her, it is still not known if it is as his sister or as a woman.
When Mikasa`s parents were murdered, and she was tied-up on the floor, Eren saved her life - when visiting by chance with his father - by killing two of the three men who killed her parents, in spite of him only being a child at the time. And then, when the third man was strangling a helpless Eren after catching him off-guard, she picked up a knife off the floor and stabbed the man in the back; killing him.
Afterward, Eren gave Mikasa his scarf - which, even many years later, she still wears - and made sure she understood that he, and his parents, were now her family. Because of his heroics and this gesture, she feels her life is Eren`s now, because - in her mind - she already died once.</description>
<picture>246175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="443" picture="145927.jpg">Ishikawa Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51167" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="94">6.14</rating>
<name>Jean Kirstein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked 6th of the trainee class. Extremely pessimistic about the War with the Titans. He ends up leading the people on the supply mission for gas. From the Trost District. He is highly competent at the three dimensional maneuver and highly skilled at efficiently using it. Good at asserting his situation at any given time, but is far too quick to unsheathe his sword. He is also prone to sparking conflict.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51169" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="182">7.12</rating>
<name>Sasha Blouse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked 9th of the trainee class. A thief from the mountain Daupa District, she joined in order to find tasty things to eat. Lightning fast, with an uncanny intuition, but her eccentricity makes her unfit for group operations.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51170" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-16">
<rating votes="108">5.12</rating>
<name>Krista Lenz</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Krista Lenz is a petite girl who is described as friendly, warm-hearted, and popular to the point where her peers regard her as a goddess or an angel. She was ranked 10th in the trainee class (due to http://anidb.net/ch53535 [Ymir] holding back during the assessment) and was later put into the 41st squad during the invasion of Trost in the year 850. She later develops a fear of facing the Titans and spends much of her time around Ymir.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4007" picture="25937.jpg">Mikami Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51171" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="52">2.80</rating>
<name>Connie Springer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked 8th of the trainee class, an upbeat and naive personality. Aims to apply to the scouting legion because he was motivated by Eren. From Ragako District. Good balance especially good at making tight turns but he is slow to the uptake, and his grasp of strategy is often less than perfect.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53532" type="appears in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="62">5.17</rating>
<name>Reiner Braun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked 2nd of the trainee class, is considered strong-willed with a solid constitution and most adept at gaining the trust of his comrades.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134326.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="53533" type="appears in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="33">2.74</rating>
<name>Bertolt Hoover</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked 3rd of the trainee class. Highly proficient in various hand to hand combat styles. He seems to have great potential but lacks in self-confidence and has a tendency to leave it to others whenever it comes to showing assertiveness.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134327.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5039" picture="33316.jpg">Hashizume Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53534" type="appears in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="23">2.86</rating>
<name>Hannes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53535" type="appears in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="59">3.71</rating>
<name>Ymir</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>134328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54440" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-26">
<rating votes="372">8.20</rating>
<name>Levi Ackerman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as humanity`s most powerful soldier. He is a clean-freak. While it is said that he is blunt and unapproachable, it is noted that he has a strong respect for structure and discipline. The rumors are that he was originally part of underground crime before he became a soldier.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54441" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="180">7.86</rating>
<name>Erwin Smith</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54442" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="274">7.17</rating>
<name>Hanji Zoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A scientist studying the Titans, showing no real fear in them and intense interest in Eren`s new physiology as a Titan. Considered weird by the rest of her comrades, only a few tolerate her obsession with Titans. In the past, she used to have a strong hatred against Titans until the death of her comrade Ilse convinced her to see the Titans in a different light. Hanji is not only responsible for the research the Survey Corps have on the Titans but also the special weapons they use, such as a barrel that fires multiple grappling hooks to capture Titans alive.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54899" type="appears in" update="2013-04-10">
<rating votes="20">6.18</rating>
<name>Karla Yeager</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3890" picture="186170.jpg">Takamori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54900" type="appears in" update="2013-04-10">
<rating votes="4">4.19</rating>
<name>Nick Shisai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54901" type="appears in" update="2013-04-10">
<rating votes="12">1.98</rating>
<name>Grisha Yeager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2585" picture="22579.jpg">Tsuchida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54902" type="appears in" update="2013-04-17">
<rating votes="12">7.54</rating>
<name>Keith Shardis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54913" type="appears in" update="2013-05-02">
<rating votes="32">8.92</rating>
<name>Chousa Heidan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>136163.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54914" type="appears in" update="2014-02-15">
<rating votes="10">9.22</rating>
<name>Chousa Heidan Tokubetsu Sakusen Han</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>150272.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54915" type="appears in" update="2013-05-02">
<rating votes="8">5.60</rating>
<name>Chuuton Heidan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>136162.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55561" type="appears in" update="2013-05-03">
<rating votes="13">3.29</rating>
<name>Kenpei Dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>136165.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55580" type="appears in" update="2013-05-05">
<rating votes="8">3.45</rating>
<name>Anka Rheinberger</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9124" picture="186845.jpg">Hayama Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55584" type="appears in" update="2013-05-05">
<rating votes="25">8.22</rating>
<name>Dott Pixis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136256.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="284" picture="225436.jpg">Tanaka Masahiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55904" type="appears in" update="2013-05-19">
<rating votes="24">8.06</rating>
<name>Shingeki no Kyojin</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55905" type="appears in" update="2013-08-04">
<rating votes="12">6.71</rating>
<name>Yoroi no Kyojin</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136780.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="57871" type="appears in" update="2013-07-13">
<rating votes="6">5.01</rating>
<name>Daris Zakkre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11025" picture="43745.jpg">Tezuka Hideaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57872" type="appears in" update="2013-07-13">
<rating votes="5">1.72</rating>
<name>Nile Dawk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2002" picture="21307.jpg">Katsu Anri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58033" type="appears in" update="2013-07-20">
<rating votes="5">2.70</rating>
<name>Mobrit</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59884" type="appears in" update="2013-09-16">
<rating votes="12">4.70</rating>
<name>Hitch</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59886" type="appears in" update="2013-09-16">
<rating votes="7">3.42</rating>
<name>Marlo Freudenberg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88690" type="appears in" update="2017-06-26">
<rating votes="4">7.65</rating>
<name>Kemono no Kyojin</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89481" type="appears in" update="2017-05-25">
<name>Keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40346" picture="223801.jpg">Matsuda Shuuhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89483" type="appears in" update="2017-05-25">
<rating votes="3">1.64</rating>
<name>Nifa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90141" type="appears in" update="2017-06-26">
<rating votes="6">4.69</rating>
<name>Zeke Yeager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95626" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-21">
<rating votes="17">8.17</rating>
<name>Historia Reiss</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4007" picture="25937.jpg">Mikami Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97662" type="appears in" update="2018-08-27">
<rating votes="4">7.76</rating>
<name>Kenny Ackerman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4494" picture="245665.jpg">Yamaji Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102689" type="appears in" update="2019-05-10">
<rating votes="1">2.20</rating>
<name>Dirk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102730" type="appears in" update="2019-06-04">
<name>Klaus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102731" type="appears in" update="2019-05-10">
<rating votes="4">1.14</rating>
<name>Flock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102853" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<name>Auril</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5887" picture="203017.jpg">Nagano Yoshikazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102854" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="1">1.36</rating>
<name>Abel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2501" picture="191381.jpg">Yoshikai Kiyohito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102855" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="1">6.31</rating>
<name>Caven</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47855" picture="194958.jpg">Terai Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102856" type="appears in" update="2019-06-04">
<name>Gerald</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42036" picture="186168.jpg">Takashina Toshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102857" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="1">8.59</rating>
<name>Sanes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102858" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="1">6.31</rating>
<name>Flegel Reeves</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26645" picture="171630.jpg">Hatanaka Tasuku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102859" type="appears in" update="2019-06-04">
<name>Ralph</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4706" picture="171561.jpg">Takaguchi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102860" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="1">3.92</rating>
<name>Dimo Reeves</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2672" picture="188511.jpg">Endou Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102861" type="appears in" update="2019-05-19">
<rating votes="1">8.59</rating>
<name>Rod Reiss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102862" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<name>Deletov</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44893" picture="223787.jpg">Ihara Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102863" type="appears in" update="2019-08-15">
<name>Nile no Sokkin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237334.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40910" picture="223781.jpg">Komatsu Shouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102864" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<name>Roderich</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56039" picture="222895.jpg">Sumi Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102865" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="1">2.20</rating>
<name>Alma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="158" picture="38198.jpg">Neya Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102866" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="1">2.20</rating>
<name>Dimo no Tsuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45852" picture="186681.jpg">Maruyama Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102867" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<name>Roger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1913" picture="186187.jpg">Chiba Isshin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102868" type="appears in" update="2019-05-19">
<rating votes="1">3.92</rating>
<name>Historia Reiss</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233714.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4007" picture="25937.jpg">Mikami Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102869" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="2">1.78</rating>
<name>Pierre</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="169" picture="16976.jpg">Takahashi Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102870" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="1">2.20</rating>
<name>Roy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="414" picture="211148.jpg">Onozuka Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102871" type="appears in" update="2019-05-31">
<rating votes="1">2.20</rating>
<name>Fritz Ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="587" picture="228627.jpg">Sonoe Osamu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102872" type="appears in" update="2019-06-04">
<rating votes="1">2.20</rating>
<name>Kenny no Sobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102873" type="appears in" update="2019-05-27">
<rating votes="1">3.92</rating>
<name>Frieda Reiss</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233905.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102874" type="appears in" update="2019-05-19">
<rating votes="1">1.36</rating>
<name>Shiso no Kyojin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233716.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102875" type="appears in" update="2019-05-19">
<rating votes="1">6.31</rating>
<name>Rod Reiss</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233717.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="102951" type="appears in" update="2019-05-27">
<name>Karsten</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7049" picture="32044.jpg">Sakai Keikou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102952" type="appears in" update="2019-05-27">
<rating votes="1">6.31</rating>
<name>Uri Reiss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233904.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102953" type="appears in" update="2019-05-27">
<name>Harold</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38264" picture="140212.jpg">Sano Yasuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102954" type="appears in" update="2019-05-27">
<name>Marlene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233902.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55794" picture="220730.jpg">Endou Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104408" type="appears in" update="2019-07-13">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Shingeki no Kyojin</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236254.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="104409" type="appears in" update="2019-07-13">
<rating votes="1">8.17</rating>
<name>Eren Yeager</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>236255.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="202660" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信頼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trust</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Confiance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinrai</title>
<summary>On the run and running out of time, the Scouts must entrust their lives to others if they plan on surviving.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776026</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202661" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">昔話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Old Story</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mukashibanashi</title>
<summary>Historia and Erwin look back on their past, revealing a shady government with a hidden agenda and inspiration for an uprising.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776025</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202662" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">痛み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Douleur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itami</title>
<summary>The Scouts take a stand against a new enemy, but it`s not just Titans they`ll be fighting anymore.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776024</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202663" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狼煙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Smoke Signal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Colonne de fumée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Noroshi</title>
<summary>After barely surviving Eren`s recovery, a rising threat from the shadows puts everyone`s lives in danger again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>775810</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202853" update="2018-07-16">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>75</length>
<airdate>2018-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">進撃の声優 大集合!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shingeki no Seiyuu: Dai Shuugou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203286" update="2018-07-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203625" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">回答</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reply</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Réponse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitou</title>
<summary>Erwin pleads his case for the Scouts to be spared, but an unforeseen announcement puts the fate of humanity at risk.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776027</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203788" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オルブド区外壁</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Outside the Walls of Orvud District</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le rempart d’Orvud</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orvud-ku Sotokabe</title>
<summary>When everything falls apart, Eren must believe in himself to save his friends. But Eren alone may not be enough to stop the impending doom.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776030</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203789" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">願い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souhait</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Negai</title>
<summary>As battle breaks out to prevent the ritual, Historia makes a shocking decision which leads to catastrophe.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776029</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203790" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Crime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumi</title>
<summary>While sins of the past reveal new truths, both sides prepare for the upcoming showdown before they run out of time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776028</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204327" update="2018-09-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="205963" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">壁の王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ruler of the Walls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La reine de ces murs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kabe no Ou</title>
<summary>The survey corps and the wall garrison must protect the Orvud District from the impending attack of Rod Reiss`s titan.
Source: IMDb</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776031</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="205964" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’amitié</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuujin</title>
<summary>Kenny recalls the life which has brought him to death`s door, but he gets to decide whether to live on or not.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776032</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="205965" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-08</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">傍観者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bystander</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un simple spectateur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boukansha</title>
<summary>Having seen a glimpse of his father`s memories, Eren attempts to track down a man hoping they might shed some light on his father`s secrets.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776033</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="205966" update="2019-06-29">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-15</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奪還作戦の夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Night of the Battle to Retake the Wall</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">A la veille de la reconquête</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakkan Sakusen no Yoru</title>
<summary>The Scouts gather for a feisty feast before leaving to retake Wall Maria to uncover what`s hidden in the basement once and for all.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>776034</identifier>
<identifier>attack-on-titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209619" update="2018-10-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちみキャラ劇場 "とんでけ! 新生リヴァイ班"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chimi Chara Theater 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chimi Chara Gekijou: Tondeke! Shinsei Levi Han</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209620" update="2019-03-03">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2018-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちみキャラ劇場 "とんでけ! 新生リヴァイ班"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chimi Chara Theater 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chimi Chara Gekijou: Tondeke! Shinsei Levi Han</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209621" update="2019-03-03">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2019-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちみキャラ劇場 "とんでけ! 新生リヴァイ班"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chimi Chara Theater 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chimi Chara Gekijou: Tondeke! Shinsei Levi Han</title>
</episode>
<episode id="213149" update="2019-03-03">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2019-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちみキャラ劇場 "とんでけ! 新生リヴァイ班"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chimi Chara Theater 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chimi Chara Gekijou: Tondeke! Shinsei Levi Han</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228703" update="2020-04-25">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228704" update="2020-04-25">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
