<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="133" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>38</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-07-04</startdate>
<enddate>2003-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dragon Drive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">DD</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ドラゴンドライブ</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/2002-2001/works_tv_dragondrive.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="780" type="Unknown Relation">Shueisha</name>
<name id="3719" type="Series Composition">Inoue Toshiki</name>
<name id="3580" type="Direction">Kawase Toshifumi</name>
<name id="3569" type="Music">Mitsumune Shinkichi</name>
<name id="6655" type="Character Design">Umehara Takahiro</name>
<name id="20205" type="Original Work">Sakura Ken`ichi</name>
</creators>
<description>Oozora Reiji was one of the most laid back people in all of Japan. Considered to be the king of lateness at his school, he`s never finished a single thing that he`s started, simply because it doesn`t look cool if he can`t do it.
But it all changes when, one day, his childhood friend Yukino Maiko invites him to the only thing he`ll ever finish... deep beneath Tokyo, there is a secret building run by Rion. It is here that the most powerful Virtual Reality technology resides... in the hands of the powerful corporation, Rion. With it, they have created an addictive game where you control a dragon. It is called Dragon Drive.
Its no surprise when Reiji gets his dragon... a small white dragon -- thats sleeping! But his first time playing, Chibisuke reveals his true power, when he easily defeats one of the current champions!
But Dragon Drive is more than it seems... unbeknowest to its players, there are two worlds... there is Earth, and then there is Reverse-Earth, or Ri-kyuu. In this alternate dimension, dragons are real -- and so is death. Theres a power growing inside Chibisuki and Reiji, and only their bond of trust, and the friendship of all their allies, will they be able to save the two worlds from Rion, and return back to Earth!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="877">4.08</permanent>
<temporary count="897">6.75</temporary>
<review count="2">6.08</review>
</ratings>
<picture>2751.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1167</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>296</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>938</identifier>
<identifier>iitoyv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/2002-2001/works_tv_dragondrive.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dragon_Drive</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ドラゴンドライブ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>239227</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5496</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="155" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-16">
<name>bodyguard</name>
<description>A bodyguard is a type of security guard or government law enforcement officer or soldier who protects a person or people, usually high-ranking public officials or officers, wealthy people, and celebrities, from danger: generally theft, assault, kidnapping, assassination, harassment, loss of confidential information, threats, or other criminal offences.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>213116.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3481" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-04-19">
<name>recruiting teammates</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4712" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>childhood ties</name>
<description>At least two of the characters share a childhood experience together that plays a part in the plot of the anime. The experience can be anything that ties them together, be it a memory, friendship, promise, tragedy, etc. Something happened to them in their childhood which binds them in a way that is unique.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5355" parentid="3863" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-13">
<name>tournament</name>
<description>A competition involving a large number of participants. Such competitions may range from friendly, moderated sporting events to anything-goes, all-out fights to the death.
All participants take part in the tournament in want or need of the final goal and possible prizes; which depending on genre, may range from a boastful record at school to great riches and/or the granting of a wish. 
Depending on the type of tournament, contestants will either act alone, be permitted a team, or construct a team of chance throughout the ongoing competition.</description>
<picurl>227699.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="44964" type="main character in" update="2012-05-19">
<name>Oozora Reiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>88091.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108288" type="appears in" update="2020-02-05">
<name>Sayaka Towa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244306.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15" picture="44976.jpg">Yukana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108289" type="appears in" update="2020-02-05">
<name>Agent L</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244307.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108290" type="appears in" update="2020-02-05">
<name>Sally</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244308.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="319" picture="228606.jpg">Okamura Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108291" type="appears in" update="2020-02-05">
<name>Mukai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244309.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="984" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">眠れる龍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The sleeping dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemureru Ryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="987" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃の覚醒[めざめ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An awakening from the impact</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki no Mezame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="988" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リベンジ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Revenge</title>
</episode>
<episode id="989" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束のダイブ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dive of promise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku no Dive!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2169" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラゴニックヘヴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dragonic Heaven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dragonic Heaven</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3005" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自分らしく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like Yourself</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jibun Rashiku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3661" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信頼の証</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Proof of trust</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinrai no Akashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3662" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">集結</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gathering</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3818" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏球[りきゅう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inside out Sphere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rikyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3819" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">継承者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The successor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keishousha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3820" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦いの始まり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The beginning of a battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakai no Hajimari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3821" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怒りの行方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The place of anger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikari no Yukue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3822" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">使命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mission</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shimei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3917" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝者と敗者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Winner and a Loser</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shousha to Haisha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4257" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">前夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Last Night</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zen`ya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="4766" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">強奪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Robbery</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goudatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5010" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">復讐の果て</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Extremity of Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu no Hate</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5488" recap="true" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">道のり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michi Nori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5572" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">再生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebirth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saisei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5648" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">試練の旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Travel of Ordeals</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiren no Tabidachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5781" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">伝説の山へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To The Legendary Mountain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densetsu no Yama e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6022" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">暴走</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Berserk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bousou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6145" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">シンセイバー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shinseiber</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinseiber</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6278" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">力の代償</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In return for the power</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chikara no Daishou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6329" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の戦士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mysterious Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Senshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6393" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">親友[とも]の影</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Friends Shadow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomo no Kage</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6472" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternal Life</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Inochi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6564" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6667" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Young Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6811" update="2012-09-02">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Betrayal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6941" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">四神龍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shishinryuu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shishinryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7050" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rival</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7206" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇の迷宮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dark Labyrinth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Meikyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7261" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真実</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Truth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinjitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7406" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dゾーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">D Zone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">D Zone</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7407" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7512" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">真龍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shinryuu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7527" update="2007-06-17">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dブレイク!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">D-Break</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">D-Break!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11185" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121142" update="2010-08-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121143" update="2010-08-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
