<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13312" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2018-12-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sora to Umi no Aida</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ソラとウミのアイダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Space Fish: Between the Sky and Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">하늘과 바다 사이</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">天空与海洋之间</title>
</titles>
<url>http://soraumi-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="917" type="Animation Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="3774" type="Original Work">Hiroi Ouji</name>
<name id="3774" type="Chief Direction">Hiroi Ouji</name>
<name id="15915" type="Animation Character Design">Yamamoto Shuuhei</name>
<name id="2939" type="Series Composition">Yamada Takashi</name>
<name id="19341" type="Direction">Nigorikawa Atsushi</name>
<name id="54318" type="Original Work">Forward Works</name>
<name id="34207" type="Music">Tachibana Asami</name>
</creators>
<description>In the future in Onomichi, Hiroshima fish disappear from the sea around the world and only whales live in the ocean. The Ministry of Fishery decides to set up giant experimental Universe Fish Tanks in space. The Onomichi Universe Fishery Union is established and begins to train space fishermen. Female fishermen are in demand due to the strengthening of an equal employment law for men and women. Six new female space fishermen are selected, and the story centers on supporting their growth.
Source: ANN
Note: The first episode received a preliminary screening held at Bunka Housou on 29.09.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="167">2.21</permanent>
<temporary count="167">4.48</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221249.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20389</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36000</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://soraumi-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Between_the_Sky_and_Sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ソラとウミのアイダ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5056</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361354</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21446</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>soraumi_app</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1032" parentid="2881" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-10">
<name>fishing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1241" parentid="2881" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-18">
<name>swimming</name>
<description>Swimming is an individual or team sport that involves using arms and legs to move the body through water. Typically, the sport takes place in pools or in open water. Competitive swimming is one of the most popular Olympic sports, with events in butterfly, backstroke, breaststroke, freestyle, and individual medley. In addition to these individual events, swimmers take part in relays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>208479.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2671" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>school dormitory</name>
<description>A school dormitory or residence hall is the student living quarters at an elite academy, boarding school, or military school. The main characters may live or work at the dormitory, and it often becomes the backdrop for a reoccurring part of the story.</description>
<picurl>223167.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2978" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-28">
<name>aim for the top</name>
<description>This can be a positive or negative plot device. A character may strive to become the best in an altruistic way (e.g. best healer, most widely learned master), or it can be quite banal and primitive (e.g. challenged delinquents wanting to be the strongest fighters).
Alas in fighting anime the latter usually prevails.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3149" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-15">
<name>journalism</name>
<description>Journalism is the work and distribution of reports on the interaction of events, facts, ideas, and people that are the "news of the day" and that informs society to at least some degree. The word applies to the occupation (professional or not), the methods of gathering information, and the organizing literary styles. Journalistic media include: print, television, radio, Internet and, in the past, newsreels.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3395" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-18">
<name>promise</name>
<description>A dramatically-made promise that serves as foreshadowing. The promise will eventually be called in and action will be required.
Whether they succeed, fail or refuse to keep their promise depends almost entirely on the idealism-level of the story. Other factors, such as whether they were told what they had to do, or if it was a Leonine Contract, may come into play. Even Releasing from the Promise is usually a scene of high drama.
Source: TVTropes</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3581" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>tactics</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4267" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-31">
<name>underwater diving</name>
<description>Underwater diving is the practice of descending below the water`s surface to interact with the environment. It is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6903 [acrobatic diving]. Please note that this tag is only about underwater diving as a sport; diving for e.g. salvaging shipwreck should be tagged with other, more specific tags.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4347" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space exploration</name>
<description>To cross the last frontier and have a look, what lies beyond it.</description>
<picurl>242378.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5695" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>preschool</name>
<description>Preschool education (or infant education) is the provision of learning to children before the commencement of statutory and obligatory education, usually between the ages of zero and three or five, depending on the jurisdiction.
In Japan, development of social skills and a sense of group belonging are major goals for preschools. Class sizes tend to be large, up to 40 students per class, to decrease the role of the teacher`s personality and increase the likelihood of peer interactions. Because exclusion from the group is extremely undesirable, a wide range of behaviors is tolerated.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7117" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-12">
<name>sexism</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="97033" type="main character in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Ruby Azumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46819" picture="224887.jpg">Inoue Honoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97034" type="main character in" update="2018-09-27">
<rating votes="1">8.31</rating>
<name>Murakami Namino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42286" picture="167754.jpg">Tachibana Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97035" type="main character in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Sakura Maiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55852" picture="221251.jpg">Suzuki Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97036" type="main character in" update="2018-09-27">
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<name>Soramachi Haru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224538.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36509" picture="134698.jpg">Takahashi Karin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97037" type="main character in" update="2018-09-27">
<rating votes="1">6.53</rating>
<name>Mitsurugi Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57094" picture="217164.jpg">Kousaka Mio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97038" type="main character in" update="2018-09-27">
<rating votes="1">2.80</rating>
<name>Maki Makiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55851" picture="224888.jpg">Komeno Maori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98209" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Mannen Reiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98210" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Mamiana Koujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98211" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Kagitani Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="84" picture="16692.jpg">Tai Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98212" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Kazamatsuri Jouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98213" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<rating votes="1">8.26</rating>
<name>Narumi Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98214" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Mishima Mitsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224549.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8830" picture="224890.jpg">Takeuchi Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98215" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Matsushima Meiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98216" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<rating votes="1">4.68</rating>
<name>Sakakibara Mariko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224551.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33515" picture="224889.jpg">Momono Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98217" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Midorikawa Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32612" picture="223330.jpg">Toujou Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98218" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Udagawa Genta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224553.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="261" picture="151648.jpg">Ikeda Masaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98219" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Udagawa Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48523" picture="197285.jpg">Nishikawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98220" type="appears in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Strike Pod (Soramachi Haru Ki)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>224556.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98221" type="appears in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Strike Pod (Murakami Namino Ki)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>224558.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98222" type="appears in" update="2018-09-27">
<name>Shimanami</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>224559.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="208336" update="2018-10-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙でサカナをとっちゃうぞ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gonna Fish in Space!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je vais attraper des poissons dans l`espace !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu de Sakana o Tocchauzo!</title>
<summary>Soramachi Haru has dreamed of becoming one of the first-ever space fisherwomen, so that she can feed her beloved grandma her favorite sushi dishes. But she never expected it to go like this!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777584</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208337" update="2018-10-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女子部シューゴウ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girls` Squad Gathers!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La section féminine au complet !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joshibu Shuugou!</title>
<summary>Following the disastrous debut expedition for their squad, the girls get together and begin training in earnest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777585</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208338" update="2018-10-31">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルビー, スパイだからな!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ruby`s a Spy, Okay?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ruby est une espionne !</title>
<summary>Haru and Namino must work together for the girls` squad to have any chance in the upcoming test. However, Namino refuses to even fish with Haru, and so the gang comes up with an idea.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777586</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208339" update="2018-10-31">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなでウミにいきませんか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shall We All Hit the Beach?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et si on allait à la plage ensemble ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna de Umi ni Ikimasenka?</title>
<summary>Ruby may have played a key role in securing the girls` squad`s use of the Union pool, but the team has a hard time accepting her childish and sometimes eccentric nature.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777587</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208910" update="2018-10-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208911" update="2018-10-03">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209339" update="2018-11-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ボクにチカラを!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Give Me Strength!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Donnez-moi la force !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku ni Chikara o!</title>
<summary>Makoto has been keeping something a secret from the rest of the girls` squad, but it unexpectedly ends up coming to light.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777588</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209340" update="2018-11-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラムネと秘密とお兄ちゃん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ramune, Secrets, and Brothers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De la limonade, un secret et un frère aîné</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ramune to Himitsu to Onii-chan</title>
<summary>Maiko`s reason for joining the girls` squad and aiming to be a space fisher is different from the rest, and she`s unable to keep up with training and starts thinking about quitting.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777589</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209341" update="2018-11-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リーダーは, わたし!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m the Leader!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C’est moi la chef !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Leader wa, Watashi!</title>
<summary>The girls` squad finally receives their official permit to go space fishing. But Makiko has a problem with the lineups Narumi chooses.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777590</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209342" update="2018-12-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">春と波乃のアイダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Between Haru and Namino</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Entre Namino et Haru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haru to Namino no Aida</title>
<summary>City Hall accepts a request from a TV station which wants to film the girls` squad for a documentary. Namino and Haru end up being chosen to represent the squad, but can they really work together?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777591</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210137" update="2018-12-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">浴衣でラクしい夏休み!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fuper Sun Summer Break in Yukatas!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des vacances d’été funny en yukata !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukata de Rakushii Natsuyasumi!</title>
<summary>With a short summer break coming up, the girls decide to stay behind and take in Namino`s place and the local summer festivities. But during the festival, Ruby loses something very important to her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777592</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210138" update="2018-12-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キオクとキロク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Records and Remembrance</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs et archives</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kioku to Kiroku</title>
<summary>Maiko feels responsible for Ruby`s getting hurt trying to save her, and she ends up making a drastic choice.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777593</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210139" update="2018-12-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">笑顔でソラへ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take to the Skies with a Smile!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Direction l`espace, le sourire aux lèvres !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Egao de Sora e!</title>
<summary>Makiko heads to Tokyo to confront her father. Meanwhile, Kazamatsuri`s squad is stranded in Tank 99 and requires immediate rescue...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777594</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210140" update="2019-01-14">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソラとウミのアイダ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Between the Sky and Sea</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Entre le ciel et la mer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora to Umi no Aida</title>
<summary>The girls` squad reaches the tank in their rescue op for Kazamatsuri and Kagitani, but things aren`t going to be easy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777595</identifier>
<identifier>between-the-sky-and-sea</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211224" update="2019-02-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ソラとウミのアイダ~おのぎょ大忘年会SP~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora to Umi no Aida: Onogyo Dai Kinenkai SP</title>
<summary>Voice actors talking about the series and eating breakfast.</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
