<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13331" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2018-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Persona 5 the Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ペルソナ5</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Persona 5 tv</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">P5A</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">PERSONA5 the Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Persona 5 the Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">페르소나 5 the Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">女神异闻录5</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14421" type="Sequel">Persona 5 the Animation (2018)</anime>
<anime id="9299" type="Same Setting">Persona 3 the Movie</anime>
<anime id="11607" type="Side Story">Persona 5 the Animation: The Day Breakers</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://p5a.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9257" type="Character Design">Ishikawa Tomomi</name>
<name id="7880" type="Series Composition">Inotsume Shin`ichi</name>
<name id="1039" type="Original Work">Atlus</name>
<name id="3754" type="Direction">Ishihama Masashi</name>
<name id="24686" type="Music">Meguro Shouji</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="11871" type="Chief Animation Direction">Haneda Kouji</name>
<name id="12902" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hasegawa Michio</name>
<name id="10654" type="Chief Animation Direction">Komatsubara Sei</name>
<name id="10929" type="Chief Animation Direction">Inadome Kazumi</name>
<name id="9257" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishikawa Tomomi</name>
<name id="15243" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ootsuka Yae</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch83172 [Amamiya Ren] is about to enter his second year after transferring to Shujin Academy in Tokyo. Following a particular incident, his Persona awakens,
and together with his friends they form the "Phantom Thieves of Hearts" to reform hearts of corrupt adults by stealing the source of their distorted desires.
Meanwhile, bizarre and inexplicable crimes have been popping up one after another... Living an ordinary high school life in Tokyo during the day, the group maneuvers the metropolitan city as Phantom Thieves after hours.
Let the curtain rise for this grand, picaresque story!
Source: Official page</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="356">4.44</permanent>
<temporary count="358">6.12</temporary>
<review count="1">3.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221806.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20469</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36023</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://p5a.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://p5ausa.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Persona_5:_The_Animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ペルソナ5#テレビアニメ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4873</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361376</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21050</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>P5_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="37509" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-23">
<rating votes="15">6.14</rating>
<name>Igor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious, long-nosed gentleman who resides in the Velvet Room. Igor`s purpose is to provide insight to the protagonists regarding their powers, emotional bonds, and possible dangers that await them in their journey. It is revealed by http://anidb.net/ch37510 [Margaret] that Igor creates the Velvet Room himself and bases its appearance on who the protagonist is at the time, as well as their situation.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>175780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2080" picture="43095.jpg">Tsukayama Masane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83171" type="main character in" update="2018-10-07">
<name>Morgana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Morgana is a mysterious cat-like creature whom Ren and Ryuuji first encounter in the dungeons of Kamoshida`s Palace, when they inadvertently stumble into it on what should have been Ren`s first day at Shuujin Academy. He teaches them the ins and outs of the Metaverse, Palaces, and Personas. He later appears to them in the real world as an ordinary domestic cat. Only people like them who have been able to enter the Metaverse can hear him speak in the real world, everyone else just hears him meowing. His true origins are a mystery even to him and he works as one of the Phantom Thieves in mostly in an attempt to seek answers, though he is convinced that he must have once been human. In the Metaverse he can also transform into a van which the Phantom Thieves can ride.</description>
<picture>65883.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83172" type="main character in" update="2018-10-08">
<rating votes="5">7.93</rating>
<name>Amamiya Ren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Amamiya Ren is the protagonist of the story. Originally coming from an unspecified small town, after intervening in a street altercation between a drunk man (who turns out to be the powerful politician Shidou Masayoshi) and a woman, he is convicted of assault, expelled from his former school, and sentenced to one year of probation. He is ordered by the court to transfer schools, with Shuujin Academy in Tokyo being the only one that would accept him with his criminal record. He is made to stay with Sakura Soujirou, who begrudgingly gives him a place to stay as a favour for Ren`s parents, who are acquaintances. As he serves out his sentence of probation, he begins to awaken to strange powers that might enable him to avert the coming ruin that is about to fall upon the world.</description>
<picture>216367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83173" type="main character in" update="2019-10-21">
<name>Kitagawa Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83174" type="main character in" update="2018-12-30">
<name>Sakamoto Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83175" type="main character in" update="2018-11-24">
<rating votes="40">7.17</rating>
<name>Takamaki An</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takamaki Ann is a second year student at Shuujin Academy, and is Amamiya Ren`s classmate, and works part-time as a fashion model. Despite being beautiful and kind, before meeting Ren and Ryuuji she has few friends at school, the only one being the volleyball player Suzui Shiho. She later becomes one of the Phantom Thieves with Ren, Ryuuji, and Morgana when she resolves to punish Kamoshida for what he had done to Shiho.</description>
<picture>216365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85171" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<name>Akechi Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="381" picture="186189.jpg">Hoshi Souichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90687" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-12">
<rating votes="8">8.65</rating>
<name>Sakura Futaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90688" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-21">
<rating votes="3">8.34</rating>
<name>Okumura Haru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90689" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-07">
<rating votes="31">7.01</rating>
<name>Niijima Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Niijima Makoto is a third-year honour student and the student council president of Shuujin Academy. Despite this status, she is actually rather unpopular, being perceived as cold and unapproachable by most of the student body, and after Kamoshida`s fall, as another authority figure who turned a blind eye to his abuses for her own selfish ends. Makoto is the younger sister of the prosecutor Niijima Sae. Their father, a police officer, was murdered in the line of duty three years ago, and after his death, Sae has had to work extra hard in order to support Makoto as well, which she resents, so Makoto has tried her best to excel in school so she could get into a good college and work to support herself as soon as possible.
After the Kamoshida incident, the Principal orders her to investigate the possibility that these so-called Phantom Thieves that claimed responsibility for his fall are students at the school, which leads her on the trail of Ren, Ryuuji, and Ann.</description>
<picture>216362.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94977" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-21">
<name>Sakura Soujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura Soujirou is manager of Café LeBlanc. He begrudgingly takes Amamiya Ren as his ward as a favour to a friend, but is initially wary of him as a juvenile delinquent.</description>
<picture>222615.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94978" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="3">8.53</rating>
<name>Kawakami Sadayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawakami Sadayo teaches Japanese language at Shuujin Academy, and is homeroom teacher for Ren and Ann`s class. In the evenings she moonlights at a dubious maid service, using the alias `Becky`.</description>
<picture>222609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10333" picture="170916.jpg">Fuchigami Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94979" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-21">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Niijima Sae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Niijima Sae is a public prosecutor at the Tokyo District Special Investigation Department. She has been investigating the strange mental shutdown incidents that have been occurring around the city, and later on, the Phantom Thieves, believing the two are somehow related. She is Niijima Makoto`s elder sister, has been her legal guardian since the murder of their father.</description>
<picture>222617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97022" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-31">
<rating votes="2">5.06</rating>
<name>Takemi Tae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takemi has dark blue hair in a messy bob-cut with blunt bangs and brown eyes. She has red nail polish on her fingernails and toenails.
Her outfit consists of a typical white lab-coat that is worn over a short black dress. She accessorizes with a red grommet belt, a black studded necklace choker which connects to multiple necklaces, and strappy black platform high heels.
In her casual outfit, she still wears her choker and necklace. She now has a bracelet, short black jacket, a blue dress with a white spiderweb design, and black ripped leggings.
Tae Takemi is the owner of Takemi Medical Clinic in Yongen-Jaya. She believes in her own theory of pharmaceutics and sells barely legal prescriptions to her patients secretly. She originally worked for a university but was fired after she was scapegoated for a disastrous medical trial she advised against, and it is eventually revealed her clinical trial is actually an attempt to perfect the drug and regain her credibility. Later, it is revealed the patient who died actually survived, but lost her confidence in Takemi`s old hospital and transferred out-to prevent bad PR, the director Ooyamada Shouichi (who was jealous of Takemi to begin with, feeling he only received his position due to nepotism) covered up her survival and perjured Takemi for the patient`s "death;" after stealing his heart, he admits the truth and Takemi`s good name is restored.
After the completion of Futaba`s Palace, the protagonist calls Takemi. After a brief examination, Takemi states that Futaba Sakura has unnaturally low stamina and strength, most likely due to her shut-in nature.
Source: Wikia</description>
<picture>221166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4006" picture="25936.jpg">Saitou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97612" type="appears in" update="2018-08-21">
<name>Kokoro no Kaitoudan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Phantom Thieves of Hearts are a group of Persona Users led by Amamiya Ren. Sick of the hypocrisy, deception, and corruption around them, they are devoted to stealing the corrupt hearts of those they consider evil people, and in so doing change society for the better. The ethics and morality of what they do has polarised people and society, with some feeling them to be heroes who bring criminals who might be otherwise untouchable to justice, and others feeling that they are criminals themselves who have no right to forcibly change people`s hearts.</description>
<picture>66521.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="98409" type="appears in" update="2018-10-09">
<name>Kamoshida Suguru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamoshida Suguru was the PE teacher and volleyball coach at Shuujin Academy. A former Olympic medallist, he brought the school`s volleyball team to the national level, which permitted him to get away with sexually harassing the female team members and subjecting the male team members to brutal physical abuse which he justified as "training". With no one able to stop his abusive behaviour, he began to see himself as a king with the Academy as his castle. After Ren and Ryuuji face expulsion at his hand and Ann`s best friend Shiho tries to kill herself after being sexually molested by him, he becomes the first target for a change of heart by what will become known as the Phantom Thieves.</description>
<picture>224997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3270" picture="30153.jpg">Mitsuya Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98410" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-05">
<name>Mishima Yuuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mishima Yuuki is a student at Shuujin Academy. He was originally a member of the volleyball team, and was a frequent target of Kamoshida`s abuse. After Kamoshida`s fall, he becomes fascinated by the mysterious Phantom Thieves that brought it about, starting a web forum called the Phan-Site where he holds discussions and polls about the Phantom Thieves. He befriends Amamiya Ren, believing him rightly to be the leader of the Phantom Thieves.</description>
<picture>225003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98411" type="appears in" update="2018-10-05">
<name>Suzui Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzui Shiho was a student at Shuujin Academy, and Takamaki Ann`s best friend. A member of the school volleyball team, she was sexually abused by Kamoshida after Takamaki refused his advances, and tried to commit suicide.</description>
<picture>225004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3710" picture="25089.jpg">Satou Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98412" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Justine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Justine is one of the twin wardens who assist Igor in the Velvet Room.</description>
<picture>225005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98413" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-05">
<name>Caroline</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Caroline is one of the twin wardens who assist Igor in the Velvet Room.</description>
<picture>225006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98415" type="appears in" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Okumura Kunikazu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Okumura Kunikazu is the CEO of Okumura Foods, and the father of Okumura Haru. A ruthless and ambitious businessman, he oppresses his employees, imposing punishing working conditions on them, treating them like disposable robots, and cuts corners where he can get away with it for the sake of profit. There is a mysterious swell of support for him to be targeted by the Phantom Thieves on the Phan-Site. He is also forcing Haru into a marriage with a horrible man solely to advance his political ambitions, adding further pressure for him to be targeted.

This turns out to be a well-orchestrated trap. The Phantom Thieves change his heart, but shortly after, the black-masked man assassinates his Shadow form in the Metaverse, causing him to die just as he is in the middle of a press conference where he confesses his misdeeds. The Phantom Thieves are blamed for his death and public support for them crumbles.
</description>
<picture>225008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3099" picture="24698.jpg">Kakegawa Hirohiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98422" type="appears in" update="2018-10-06">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Tougou Hifumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tougou Hifumi is a beautiful shogi player who attends Kosei High School, with Kitagawa Yusuke. During their school trip in Hawaii, she is rescued by Amamiya Ren from harassment by a group of rowdy Americans. Ren befriends her, learning of her domineering mother who is trying to use her beauty and skill in shogi as a cash cow, while learning to play shogi from her.</description>
<picture>225015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10361" picture="38073.jpg">Isomura Tomomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98425" type="appears in" update="2018-10-05">
<name>Madarame Ichiryuusai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Madarame Ichiryuusai was a famous artist and mentor to Kitagawa Yuusuke. Coming off initially as a kindly and soft-spoken old man and a great painter, in reality he has been suffering from artist`s block for many years and has been secretly abusing his students and plagiarising their works. This makes him a target for a change of heart for the Phantom Thieves.</description>
<picture>225025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4686" picture="171399.jpg">Hori Yukitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98444" type="appears in" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Kaneshiro Junya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaneshiro Junya is a callous and ruthless organised crime boss operating in Shibuya. He especially targets high school students, tricking them into becoming unwitting drug mules and then blackmailing them with photographic evidence of this illegal activity. He has kept himself carefully hidden and not even the police were able to figure out that he was the true mastermind pulling the strings of crime in Shibuya. Some students of Shuujin Academy were victims of his scams. He thus became a target for the Phantom Thieves.</description>
<picture>225065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3998" picture="33313.jpg">Fujimoto Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98445" type="appears in" update="2018-10-06">
<name>Shidou Masayoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shidou Masayoshi is a rising politician who might become Japan`s next Prime Minister. Unknown to the public at large he seems to be involved in shady dealings that orchestrated his rise to power. He was also responsible for Amamiya Ren`s arrest and probation, although he had somehow kept his name out of the public record of the incident.</description>
<picture>225066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="413" picture="151647.jpg">Ikeda Shuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98502" type="appears in" update="2018-10-07">
<name>Ooya Ichiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ooya Ichiko is a journalist and paparazza, with a tendency to write articles of a sensationalistic bent. After being relegated to the entertainment section of her newspaper after what should have been an article about a political scandal, she became depressed and cynical. She meets with Amamiya and the Phantom Thieves at several points, at first providing them with the tip that leads them to crime lord Kaneshiro.</description>
<picture>225172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="197443" update="2018-04-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Steal it, if you can</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Steal It, If You Can</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Steal It, If You Can</title>
<summary>The first heist of the Phantom Thieves of Hearts is underway, as the group sends Kamoshida a calling card, threatening to steal away is twisted desires. Ren and the gang begin prepping for their dangerous delve into the cognitive world, and encounter a couple potential allies in the process. Will they be successful in taking the terrible King Kamoshida’s precious Treasure?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768991</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197444" update="2018-04-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">A beautiful rose has thorns!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Beautiful Rose Has Thorns!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Beautiful Rose Has Thorns!</title>
<summary>The members of the volleyball team are terrified of the tyrannical Kamoshida`s irrational violence. Meanwhile, Ren`s classmate, Ann Takamaki, has been protecting her best friend from being cut as a regular player on the volleyball team, but she`s at a loss as to what to do about the persistent approaches of Kamoshida, who lusts for her with his twisted desires.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768989</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197445" update="2018-04-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Let`s take back what`s dear to you.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Take Back What`s Dear to You.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Let`s Take Back What`s Dear to You.</title>
<summary>Ren begins his new school life, but it`s tough being a transfer student, especially when he comes with seemingly shady baggage. He meets Ryuji, a classmate who`s similarly isolated, and they use a mysterious app to enter a world in which their gym teacher, Kamoshida, is a sadistic king.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768987</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197446" update="2019-01-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">I am thou, thou art I</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am Thou, Thou Art I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">I Am Thou, Thou Art I</title>
<summary>After high school student Ren Amamiya gets in trouble with the police, he’s labeled as a juvenile delinquent. As part of his probation, he is forced to start living with Sojiro Sakura, a stranger who agreed to take him in. While walking to his new school Shujin Academy, Ren becomes lost in another world…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768985</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198181" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198182" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198301" update="2018-05-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Put an end to all this and use your own artwork for once.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Put an End to All This and Use Your Own Artwork for Once.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Put an End to All This and Use Your Own Artwork for Once.</title>
<summary>After Yusuke`s eyes are opened to Madarame`s true motives, he asks to join the Phantom Thieves. Ren and company leave a calling card and infiltrate the Palace to steal Madarame`s treasure, but they find Shadow Madarame waiting for them with a version of his most famous painting, "Sayuri," except now the subject is cradling a baby.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768999</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198302" update="2018-05-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">He is my other self</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He Is My Other Self</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">He Is My Other Self</title>
<summary>After confirming the existence of the Palace and learning Yusuke`s true feelings, Ren and his partners decide on Madarame as their next target. While Ren and Ryuji infiltrate the Palace, Ann plays the role of decoy, as the model for Yusuke`s painting. She finds something unexpected in Madarame`s storage room.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768997</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198303" update="2018-05-12">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Our next target is...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Next Target Is...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Our Next Target Is...</title>
<summary>Ren and his partners encounter Yusuke Kitagawa, a young disciple of a well-known painter, Ichiryusai Madarame. Yusuke begs Ann to model for his painting, bewildering the three teens. That weekend, they accept Yusuke`s invitation to visit Madarame`s exhibition. Madarame appears to be a man of integrity, but Ren senses that something is off.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768995</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198304" update="2018-07-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">The Phantoms</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Phantoms</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Phantoms</title>
<summary>After safely changing Kamoshida’s heart, Ren and friends decide to continue changing the hearts of selfish, clueless adults. And no sooner are the “Phantom Thieves of Hearts” established than a fan website springs up, soliciting requests from troubled teens who want the heart of an adult in their life changed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768993</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199575" update="2018-06-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">I found the place where I belong</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Found the Place Where I Belong</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">I Found the Place Where I Belong</title>
<summary>After emerging from her "fake self," Makoto is awakened to Persona and joins the Phantom Thieves in the role of advisor. Ren and company infiltrate a Palace again to change the heart of Kaneshiro, the boss of a criminal group that targets young people and rips them off.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769007</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199576" update="2018-06-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Let`s be friends, shall we?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Be Friends, Shall We?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Let`s Be Friends, Shall We?</title>
<summary>The Student Council president of Shujin Academy, Makoto Niijima, has learned that Ren and his friends are the Phantom Thieves. In order to carry out Makoto`s demand to prove that they`re actually on the side of justice, Ren and company attempt to infiltrate the Palace of a new target, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769005</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199577" update="2018-06-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">I want to see justice with my own eye</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to See Justice with My Own Eye</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">I Want to See Justice with My Own Eye</title>
<summary>When Ren, Ryuji, and Ann visit a TV station on a school field trip, they encounter famous high school detective Goro Akechi, who was on a TV show as a guest. The three become anxious when Akechi talks about the Phantom Thieves on live TV. Meanwhile, someone at Shujin Academy is also interested in probing the motives of Ren and friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769003</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199578" update="2018-06-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Operation maid watch</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Maid Watch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Operation Maid Watch</title>
<summary>After reforming Madarame, Ren and company realize that the Phantom Thieves of Hearts are slowly starting to become famous. However, Morgana urges Ren and Ryuji in particular to lead normal, serious lives as high school students, and for a time, they do go back to their normal lives.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769001</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201665" update="2018-07-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">This place is my grave</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Place Is My Grave</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">This Place Is My Grave</title>
<summary>The enigmatic "Alibaba" proposes a deal to the Phantom Thieves: In exchange for Alibaba`s help with getting rid of the Medjed threat, they have to change the heart of a particular person. Their target is a girl, Futaba Sakura, whose foster father happens to be Sojiro, a former acquaintance of her mother.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774633</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201666" update="2018-07-15">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">I am Alibaba</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am Alibaba</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">I Am Alibaba</title>
<summary>After their finals are over, Ren and the gang head out to see the much-anticipated fireworks. While they start contemplating their next target, the Phantom Thieves suddenly find themselves targeted by Medjed, an international group of hackers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774632</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201667" update="2018-07-17">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">What life do you choose?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Life Do You Choose?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">What Life Do You Choose?</title>
<summary>Makoto struggles to figure out what she wants to do with her life. While doing so, she makes friends with a fellow third-year, who is dealing with a shady character from Shinjuku.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774631</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201668" update="2018-07-07">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dreams and Desires</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreams and Desires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dreams and Desires</title>
<summary>With Kaneshiro reformed, the Phantom Thieves take some time to relax after their hard work, except for Yusuke who is dealing with a dilemma. He asks for the assistance of Ren, who is also called out by Goro Akechi for another situation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769009</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202727" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202728" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202783" update="2018-08-19">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">My name is Beauty Thief!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Name Is Beauty Thief!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">My Name Is Beauty Thief!</title>
<summary>It`s been days since Morgana ran out on Ren and the others, and he still hasn`t returned. Worried about their feline-like friend, the Phantom Thieves minus one sneak into the Palace of their next target, Okumura. But standing in their way is the missing Morgana and a girl who calls herself Beauty Thief.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774637</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202784" update="2018-08-12">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Aloha</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aloha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aloha</title>
<summary>Ren and the others enjoy their school trip to Hawaii, but as soon as they get back, they hear the news that the principal of Shujin Academy has died suspiciously, an event that leads to turmoil among the Phantom Thieves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774636</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202785" update="2018-08-04">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">I`ll guide you to victory</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Guide You to Victory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">I`ll Guide You to Victory</title>
<summary>Futaba has conquered the warped memories of her mother and has awakened to Persona. Now she hopes to join the Phantom Thieves for her own personal goal. Meanwhile, Ren and the others want to help improve Futaba`s social skills, so they suggest an outing to the beach.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774635</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202786" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">X Day</title>
<title xml:lang="en">X Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">X Day</title>
<summary>Ren and the others convince Futaba to open the door to her room of her own free will. Then the Phantom Thieves sneak back into the Palace to steal Futaba`s Treasure, but she follows them, becoming the first case of someone entering their own Palace. Inside, Futaba encounters a giant monster in her mother`s form with a deep grudge against Futaba.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774634</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203644" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204136" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">A challenge that must be won</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Challenge That Must Be Won</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Challenge That Must Be Won</title>
<summary>The Phantom Thieves agree to help Akechi by changing the heart of Makoto`s sister, public prosecutor Sae Niijima, so they infiltrate her Palace. Meanwhile, a man who claims to be a relative of Futaba`s pays Sojiro a visit…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774641</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204137" update="2018-09-09">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">How about a deal with me?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How About a Deal with Me?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">How About a Deal with Me?</title>
<summary>Ren and friends are on guard when Akechi is invited to be a special guest at Shujin Academy`s culture festival. On the day of the fest, when Akechi shows up, he surprises them with a proposal regarding the Phantom Thieves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774640</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204138" update="2018-09-02">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Is it our fault...?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is It Our Fault...?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Is It Our Fault...?</title>
<summary>The Phantom Thieves succeed in stealing the Treasure from the Palace of Okumura, Haru`s father, and they have a party to celebrate their victory. However, when something happens during Okumura`s subsequent press conference, Ren and the others begin to have doubts about their actions as Phantom Thieves.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774639</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="204139" update="2018-09-01">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">You can call me "Noir"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Can Call Me "Noir"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">You Can Call Me "Noir"</title>
<summary>After sharing their feelings, Ren and the rest patch things up with Morgana. Then, in order to save Haru Okumura, who`s stressed out about her upcoming arranged marriage to a creep, the Phantom Thieves sneak back into her devious father`s Palace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774638</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="206495" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Jealous Sinner</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jealous Sinner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jealous Sinner</title>
<summary>The Phantom Thieves infiltrate Niijima Palace to steal Sae`s Treasure. When Shadow Sae reveals herself inside, Makoto realizes just how warped her thinking has become and is determined more than ever to stop her big sister.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774642</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="206496" update="2018-09-30">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">I won`t let it end here</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Won`t Let It End Here</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">I Won`t Let It End Here</title>
<summary>Ren and the rest of the Phantom Thieves attempt to escape from Niijima’s Palace. They split up to increase their chances, but Ren, acting as a decoy, is captured by the riot police. Ren undergoes a cruel interrogation while the friends he left behind prepare for a last-ditch battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774643</identifier>
<identifier>persona5-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208816" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="211613" recap="true" update="2018-12-30">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">総集編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Recap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soushuuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214532" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214533" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214534" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214535" update="2019-03-30">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226410" update="2020-01-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2018-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第1話冒頭6分公開</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 6min Preview</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 1 Wa Boutou Roppun Koukai</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
