<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1333" restricted="true">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-05-28</startdate>
<enddate>2004-05-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Green Green Thirteen Erolutions</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Green Green Erolutions</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">그린그린 에로루션즈</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Green Green 13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gg13</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">erolutions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gge</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">グリーングリーン THIRTEEN エロリューションズ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="834" type="Prequel">Green Green (2003)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="4360" type="Character Design">Nakahara Kiyotaka</name>
<name id="10280" type="Original Work">Groover</name>
<name id="3688" type="Series Composition">Tomioka Atsuhiro</name>
<name id="779" type="Animation Work">Studio Matrix</name>
<name id="4463" type="Direction">Mutou Yuuji</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the game by http://anidb.net/cr10280 [Groover].
The love between http://anidb.net/ch6512 [Futaba] and http://anidb.net/ch6506 [Yuusuke] is still at a quite vulnerable stage, so that http://anidb.net/ch6511 [Midori] appears in the dreams of both of them and tries to match them up.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2625">2.90</permanent>
<temporary count="2675">6.16</temporary>
<review count="3">7.10</review>
</ratings>
<picture>3850.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3520</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>651</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1440</identifier>
<identifier>chwsau</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Green_Green_(anime)#OVAs</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>グリーングリーン_(ゲーム)#18.E7.A6.81OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>178</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2803" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>erotic game</name>
<description>An erotic game (eroge) is a Japanese video or computer game that features erotic content, usually in the form of anime-style artwork. In English, eroge are often called hentai games in keeping with the English slang definition of hentai. This is sometimes shortened to H games. In Japan, eroge are also referred to as 18+ games. Most erotic games are visual novels or dating sims but are not limited to them.
Any anime adaptation of a game that contains (or had a version that contains) adult content (generally sex scenes), regardless of how some fanboys blabber on how "the story in that visual novel was too good to be labelled as porn!", should definitely get this category added under them. This should make it pretty clear as to what is an erotic game and what is not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6506" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="19">3.89</rating>
<name>Takasaki Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main male lead, Yuusuke is perhaps the most "normal" of the boys at Kanenone. He is friends with the Baka Trio, but does not share their more perverted interests. Despite this, the Baka Trio consider Yuusuke to be a member of their group, and he usually finds himself forced or dragged along into involvement with their less-than-wholesome activities.
Yuusuke is implied to be the reincarnation of the boy from the tale of ill-fated lovers mentioned at the start of every episode, with Midori as his partner. However, Yuusuke appears to have no recollection of his past, and initially responds to Midori`s affectionate advances by either pushing her away or treating her harshly. Only after recovering his past memories does he fall in love with her. Yuusuke also finds himself liking the tomboyish Futaba Kutsuki, creating a love triangle between the three main characters.</description>
<picture>24007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="589" picture="186167.jpg">Takeuchi Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6507" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="20">1.42</rating>
<name>Ijuuin Tadatomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The apparent leader of the Baka Trio, Bacchi-Guu is an overweight, bespectacled pervert who has no shame. The arrival of beautiful girls to Kanenone seems to send him out of control. He does things such as drinking the bath water the girls recently bathed in, to making a nipple print of his own nipples so he can imagine they belong to a girl.</description>
<picture>24008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2976" picture="234380.jpg">Tanaka Kazunari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6508" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="19">2.16</rating>
<name>Ichibanboshi Hikaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Literally translated in English as "number one shining star," Ichibanboshi believes himself to be a suave ladies man. He has a book of pick-up lines to use on his new female classmates, but he always fails and makes a fool of himself. He is perhaps the least perverted of the Baka Trio, but he is still a pervert nonetheless.</description>
<picture>24009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2047" picture="68288.jpg">Domon Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6509" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="16">1.68</rating>
<name>Tenjin Taizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tenjin has an odd fetish. He dreams of having Sanae consider him a big brother, and then she will sleep next to him... while he smells her and eats rice at the same time (a joke referring to the word okazu, which means both "meal" and "porn"). Sanae`s young appearance makes him instantly attracted to her, but Sanae wants nothing to do with Tenjin.</description>
<picture>24010.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6510" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="25">1.45</rating>
<name>Haruno Arisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A brash, bespectacled girl with braided hair who has rather vivid bishounen sexual fantasies. Her apparent role in the anime is to provide comic relief from the side of the girls. Although her physical attributes manage to attract the attentions of the Baka Trio every now and then, the sight of her face is enough to put an end to any perverted thoughts they may have.</description>
<picture>24011.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3129" picture="24103.jpg">Yoshitake Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6511" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="33">4.98</rating>
<name>Chitose Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main female lead, Midori is an outgoing and cheerful girl who seems to know Yuusuke and is in love with him. She seems willing to do anything for him, even filling out a form of perverted questions the Baka Trio gave her, hoping it will please Yuusuke. In the opening scene of the series, Midori narrates a tale about two people who were in love, but their love was forbidden at the time and they could not stay together. They promised each other to meet again in another life, hinting that Midori is the girl from the tale and somehow retained her memories, while Yuusuke is the boy from the tale, but he has not retained the memories of his past life. She seemingly has no grasp at the effects some of her antics have wrought, such as climbing on top of a bedridden Yuusuke in the nurses` office while in lingerie, and hanging on to his arm after class ended.</description>
<picture>24012.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="431" picture="23201.jpg">Nakayama Sara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6512" type="main character in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="59">6.89</rating>
<name>Kutsuki Futaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Futaba plays the role of the tough, boy-hating tsundere. She is less than enthusiastic about the co-ed trial run of the schools, and acts as the self-appointed protector of the girls against the boys of Kanenone. She is particularly disgusted by the antics of the Baka Trio, and does not hesitate to resort to physical violence against them as punishment for their indiscretions.</description>
<picture>24013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3126" picture="24742.jpg">Fujimaki Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6513" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="24">4.42</rating>
<name>Kutsuki Wakaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Futaba`s younger sister. She shows a deep amount of respect for Futaba, referring to her as onee-sama. Wakaba is almost always seen carrying around her potted cactus, whom she named Togemura (literally translated as "thorn village"). Like some devoted plant lovers, Wakaba talks to Togemura as if it was a person; what is unusual is that Togemura appears to be able to communicate with Wakaba as well. Wakaba also uses Togemura as a fortune-telling device and as a weapon to defend herself and her friends, magical girl-style.</description>
<picture>24014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3127" picture="24743.jpg">Mannaka Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6514" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="25">4.63</rating>
<name>Minami Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A friend of Wakaba, Sanae is a weak and shy girl who joins the trip to Kanenone because her doctors believe that the fresh country air will be beneficial to her health. Her need to take medication on a regular basis is highlighted in several episodes.
Sanae has a much younger appearance than the rest of the major female characters. This draws the attention of Tenjin, who has a fetish for "little sister" types. Unfortunately for Tenjin, his unusual and over-enthusiastic advances only manage to frighten Sanae away from him.</description>
<picture>24015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2222" picture="25843.jpg">Suzuki Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6515" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-28">
<rating votes="31">6.01</rating>
<name>Iino Chigusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The nurse at the all-girls boarding school. She came along on the trip as the girls` supervisor. The Baka Trio, especially Bacchi-Guu, are enamoured by Chigusa`s beauty and her E-cup breasts. Although she should be keeping the girls in order, Chigusa is very easy-going and actually encourages the girls to flirt with the boys.</description>
<picture>24016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3128" picture="24744.jpg">Suzuki Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="14219" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">1.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19779" update="2005-12-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">1.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130944" update="2011-06-17">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">"Who am I?" Game</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
