<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13401" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-09</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kaijuu Girls: Ultra Kaijuu Gijinka Keikaku (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kaijuu Girls S2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">怪獣娘[かいじゅうがーるず] ~ウルトラ怪獣擬人化計画~ (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kaiju Girls: Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">怪兽娘～奥特怪兽拟人化计划～ 第二季</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13975" type="Sequel">Kaijuu Girls (Kuro): Ultra Kaijuu Gijinka Keikaku</anime>
<anime id="12021" type="Prequel">Kaijuu Girls: Ultra Kaijuu Gijinka Keikaku</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://kaiju-gk.jp/anime/2nd/</url>
<creators>
<name id="23382" type="Animation Work">Studio Pu Yukai</name>
<name id="11038" type="Original Work">Tsuburaya Production</name>
<name id="39147" type="Original Plan">Kaihou Norimitsu</name>
<name id="21007" type="Direction">Ashina Minoru</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
</creators>
<description>The battles between mankind and Kaiju are in the distant past. Now, souls of those giant monsters are manifesting in the young women called "Kaiju Girls." Having become full-fledged members of GIRLS, http://anidb.net/ch83299 [Agira], http://anidb.net/ch83306 [Miclas], and http://anidb.net/ch83300 [Windom] are growing into productive members of the organization, with fulfilled lives. But one day, a new breed of Shadows is reported to be causing trouble.
Meanwhile, another member of GIRLS, http://anidb.net/ch92484 [Alien Guts], is experiencing a strange change...
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="77">2.77</permanent>
<temporary count="77">5.05</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>209921.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20504</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36196</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kaiju-gk.jp/anime/2nd/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kaiju_Girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ウルトラ怪獣擬人化計画</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4820</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361678</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19603</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ultrakaiju_gk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2503" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>magical girl</name>
<description>Magical girls (also known both in Japan and in the West as mahou shoujo, and in Japan as majokko) are young girls with superhuman abilities of magical nature. In the early years, magical girls usually used magic to solve everyday problems and often transformed into idols; nowadays, however, the term is most often used to refer to with girls who fight evil using magical powers, and, although transformations are still common, they tend to be more along the lines of a change of costume.</description>
<picurl>29577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2629" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-16">
<name>desert</name>
<description>Setting with vast amounts of sand, merciless high temperatures, and very little water.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="83299" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Agira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196423.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22171" picture="173757.jpg">Iida Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83300" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Windom</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36511" picture="134700.jpg">Endou Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83301" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Eleking</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83302" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Gomora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34407" picture="202909.jpg">Suwa Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83303" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Zandrias</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40415" picture="158225.jpg">Yuasa Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83304" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Zetton</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83305" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Pigmon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83306" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Miclas</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196424.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41296" picture="177392.jpg">Suzuki Aina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83307" type="main character in" update="2017-01-04">
<name>Red King</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92484" type="main character in" update="2018-11-08">
<name>Guts-seijin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66782.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="41504" picture="178543.jpg">Matsuda Risae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92485" type="main character in" update="2018-11-07">
<name>King Joe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66779.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92486" type="main character in" update="2018-11-08">
<name>Maga Jappa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43914" picture="225361.jpg">Kondou Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92487" type="main character in" update="2018-11-08">
<name>Maga Basser</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52981" picture="211828.jpg">Terada Haruna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99124" type="main character in" update="2018-11-08">
<name>Noiseler</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34545" picture="224469.jpg">Kiyoto Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194372" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特訓! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Training! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokkun! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>When Keika regains consciousness he finds himself in a hotel room with Shin Shiyou. She explains what happened and how Tanmoku Ki used her powers to save him. Upon returning home, Keika goes along with Tanmoku Ki to visit the grave of his old friend and former bodyguard, Shinryuu Shouken. There a mysterious man appears saying he wants to make Shouken`s wish come true and that he isn`t truly dead. Ki is shaken by this and he opens the grave to find out the truth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759259</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194373" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カフェ! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cafe! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cafe! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Agira and Guts commiserate over the threat of Shadow Mist, and decide to be there for each other when they need help. Which doesn`t take long, because the Shadows are attacking again!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759257</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194374" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝撃! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shock! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shougeki! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Agira helps Alien Guts and King Joe overcome the threat of Shadow Mist, a type of Shadow that possesses people! They can`t risk hurting the people who are being controlled, and when you can`t use brute force to defeat your enemy, what`s a kaiju to do?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759255</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194375" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">登場? 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arrival? Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toujou? Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>The girls from GIRLS are back! Agira, Miclas, and Windom have settled in as full fledged members of the International Kaiju Resue and Mentoring Organization, but it`s not long before the threat of the Shadows appears again...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759253</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195055" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195406" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">衝突! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Collision! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoutotsu! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Windom, Noiseler, and Zandrias run into Alien Guts and... Alien Guts!? The two mirror images engage in battle, but which one is the real deal?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759267</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195407" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">成長! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Growth! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seichou! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Miclas was attacked and the culprit is... Alien Guts!? But Agira has trouble accepting that her new friend could do such a thing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759265</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195408" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お母さん? 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mom? Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okaasan? Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Shouken encourages Ki to seek becoming the head of the Tanmoku family so he can fulfill his wishes; however, when Ki is promoted to the position there are many who oppose him. Ki, who doesn`t want to be hated by anyone, puts on a smiling face, but since his kind nature has already been taken advantage of before, Shouken advises Ki to refrain from smiling too much for his own sake. To cheer him up, Shouken asks Ki what he really wants to do and throws his full support behind making it happen, but when Ki`s desires land them in hot water Shouken`s future with Ki is placed in jeopardy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759263</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195409" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">街ぶら! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Around Town! Kaiju Girls!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Machi Bura! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Rocked by the truth of his dearest friend`s fate, Ki is overcome by nightmares that leave him unconscious and could prevent him from ever awakening again. Keika, the only one who can save him, dives into Ki`s memories to try and free him from the nightmares. Silently, Keika watches from the sidelines as he relives Ki`s memories from before he knew him to see just what in his past is preventing Ki from moving forward. As his bodyguard, Shinryuu Shouken spent a great deal of time with Ki, but what were his true motives?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759261</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196551" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">みんなで! 怪獣娘!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Together! Kaiju Girls!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Minna de! Kaijuu Girls!!</title>
<summary>Shadow General appears, and she`s the girls` toughest foe yet. All seems lost! Will Agira and Alien Guts be able to get the girls out of this alive?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759275</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196552" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着☆怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaiju Girls Settle the Score!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku: Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>The powerful Shadow Guts is toying with Alien Guts. Awakened by Agira`s words, Alien Guts rises again, to fight alongside her fellow Kaiju Girls!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759273</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196553" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">登場☆怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On Stage! Kaiju Girls?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toujou: Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>Alien Guts has a showdown with her double, Shadow Guts. The Kaiju Girls are nervous about their first big plan since they teamed up. But they`re joined by...?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759271</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196554" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">作戦! 怪獣娘!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Plan! Kaiju Girls?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakusen! Kaijuu Girls!?</title>
<summary>The news of Alien Guts` evil doppleganger shakes Agira up, but Pigmon and Eleking are already coming up with a plan to stop the savage lookalike from causing more havoc.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759269</identifier>
<identifier>kaiju-girls</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212813" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212814" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212815" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212816" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212817" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212818" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212819" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212820" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212821" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212822" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212823" update="2019-09-29">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おしエレ おしえてエレキング先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tell Ele: Tell Me, Eleking-senpai 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi Ele: Oshiete Eleking-senpai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221763" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221764" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221765" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221766" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221767" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221768" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221769" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221770" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221771" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-05-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221772" update="2019-09-28">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-05-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Unused Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
