<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13410" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-08-21</startdate>
<enddate>2017-08-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Starship Troopers: Red Planet</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">スターシップ・トゥルーパーズ レッドプラネット</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Starship Troopers: Traitor of Mars</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9083" type="Prequel">Starship Troopers: Invasion</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://sst-mars.jp/</url>
<description>Federation trooper Johnny Rico is ordered to work with a group of new recruits on a satellite station on Mars, where giant bugs have decided to target their next attack.
Source: IMDB
Note: US cinematic release Aug 21, 2017. Japanese cinematic release Feb 10, 2018</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="68">4.81</permanent>
<temporary count="68">5.99</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>206680.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21558</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36194</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20180717221209/http://sst-mars.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.starshiptroopers.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Starship_Troopers:_Traitor_of_Mars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361872</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2765" parentid="2660" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Mars</name>
<description>Mars is the fourth planet from the Sun and the second-smallest planet in the Solar System after Mercury. In English, Mars carries a name of the Roman god of war, and is often referred to as the "Red Planet" because the reddish iron oxide prevalent on its surface gives it a reddish appearance that is distinctive among the astronomical bodies visible to the naked eye. Mars is a terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere, having surface features reminiscent both of the impact craters of the Moon and the valleys, deserts, and polar ice caps of Earth.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214389.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4424" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>American derived</name>
<description>A work which was created as a continuation/remake of an American based franchise or cartoon series. These works are completely Japan original, but which lack roots within Japanese media.
See also: http://anidb.net/t3714 [cartoon remake]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="192528" update="2017-11-04">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2017-08-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
