<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13427" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>3</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-09-06</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fastening Days 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">FASTENING DAYS 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">ربط الأيام 3</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15303" type="Sequel">Fastening Days 4</anime>
<anime id="12309" type="Prequel">Fastening Days 2</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.ykkfastening.com/fd/</url>
<creators>
<name id="38997" type="Work">Studio Colorido</name>
<name id="41412" type="Original Plan">Tanaka Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="12846" type="Direction">Shibayama Tomotaka</name>
<name id="17355" type="Music">Sunahara Yoshinori</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch71392 [Youji], http://anidb.net/ch71393 [Kei], http://anidb.net/ch83942 [Kelly], and the little bear-shaped robot http://anidb.net/ch71395 [Oscar] are small heroes who must save the town. Today is Youji`s birthday, but this doesn`t seem to excite him. Whether or not they know this, Kei, Kelly, and the woman who raised him as her own, http://anidb.net/ch71394 [Anna], seem to be planning something. And that`s when it appears over the city – an out-of-control sightseeing airship!
Our little heroes must face their biggest challenge yet! The action-packed drama even includes an evolved Fastening Machine! Will our heroes be able to fasten the town`s future? What will become of Youji`s birthday? There`s only one way to find out!
Source: Official page</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="64">4.75</permanent>
<temporary count="64">5.87</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>206867.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>28205</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ykkfastening.com/fd/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ykkfastening.com/fd/en/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361807</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4610" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-22">
<name>commercial</name>
<description>This title is used to sell and/or promote a real-life product or service. Not to be confused with "product placement" or "subliminal advertising" — this features *direct* promotion for such element.
Depending on the setting, some could even be considered as "animated infomercials".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="71392" type="main character in" update="2014-11-16">
<name>Youji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young boy compelled to play the good Samaritan whenever the need arises, Youji is good-natured and twice as determined as the average person to see justice served.
Source: Official Website</description>
<picture>164235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47785" picture="225124.jpg">Ono Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71393" type="main character in" update="2014-11-16">
<name>Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A passionate machining enthusiast with dexterous hands, Kei is an outgoing yet somewhat naive girl.
Source: Official Website</description>
<picture>164236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="208" picture="20458.jpg">Shiraishi Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71394" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-16">
<name>Anna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anna, a widow, is a gentle woman living in her family`s house up on a hill. She took in and raised Youji and Kei, who are orphans.
Source: Official Website</description>
<picture>164237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="598" picture="45415.jpg">Sadaoka Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71395" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-11-16">
<name>Oscar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anna`s husband left behind this robot bear who understands human emotions. He always looks out for Youji, Kei and Anna.
Source: Official Website</description>
<picture>164238.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="83942" type="main character in" update="2016-08-21">
<rating votes="1">1.34</rating>
<name>Kelly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>190295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="349" picture="79057.jpg">Kanda Akemi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="190694" update="2017-09-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2017-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190695" update="2017-09-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190696" update="2017-09-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191072" update="2017-09-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-09-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
