<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13478" restricted="false">
<type>Other</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-08-06</startdate>
<enddate>2002-08-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Full Moon o Sagashite: Kawaii Kawaii Daibouken</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">fmos ova</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">fmws ova</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">満月[フルムーン]をさがして かわいい かわいい 大冒険</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="21" type="Parent Story">Full Moon o Sagashite</anime>
</relatedanime>
<creators>
<name id="730" type="Animation Work">Studio Deen</name>
<name id="6586" type="Character Design">Kudou Yuka</name>
<name id="4018" type="Original Work">Tanemura Arina</name>
<name id="8144" type="Direction">Bob Shirahata</name>
<name id="7970" type="Music">Fukushima Yuuko</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: Originally shown at the annual Ribon Otanoshimi Matsuri event on August 6, 2002. It was later bundled together with http://anidb.net/a503 [Tokimeki Fushigi Diary: Ultra Maniac] on a VHS that was included with the November 2002 issue of Ribon magazine, released on October 3, 2002.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="64">4.46</permanent>
<temporary count="64">5.75</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>207386.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3542</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1996</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Full_Moon_o_Sagashite#OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="7633" type="main character in" update="2011-03-31">
<rating votes="20">7.13</rating>
<name>Kouyama Mitsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouyama Mitsuki is a 12-year-old girl who dreams of becoming a pop singer but a tumor in her vocal cords restricts her ability to sing. She is an orphan who grew up in an orphanage, then later went to live with her strict grandmother, Fuzuki, who forbid her from singing. When Mitsuki learned that she would die if her vocal cords were not removed, she refused the surgery, saying that she would rather die than not be able to sing. With Takuto`s help, she can transform into Fullmoon, a 16-year-old pop idol, completely free of cancer and able to sing. As Fullmoon, she is discovered by Seed Records during an audition and releases several singles in both the manga and anime; the anime ending theme songs are all supposedly sung by her. Mitsuki chooses the stage name Fullmoon both because mitsuki means "full moon" in Japanese and because her childhood friend, Sakurai Eichi, wants to become an astronomer and the name reminds her of him.
Mitsuki wants to become a singer because she wants to tell Eichi that she loves him.
However, the shinigami eventually discover that Eichi is dead. In the manga, they realise that Mitsuki knew all along; in the anime, Mitsuki learns of his death during a trip to America. Both the manga and anime revolve around Mitsuki dealing with Eichi`s death, as well as her eventual feelings for Takuto.
Mitsuki`s corkscrew hairstyle is taken from Ai Kago from the group Morning Musume. Mitsuki herself is modeled on one of Arina Tanemura`s assistants, Airi Teito.
Her birthday in the manga is May 12 and in the anime April 4.</description>
<picture>29594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4258" picture="26502.jpg">Myco</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7634" type="appears in" update="2009-06-21">
<rating votes="10">8.58</rating>
<name>Full Moon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4258" picture="26502.jpg">Myco</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7637" type="main character in" update="2016-06-09">
<rating votes="8">9.11</rating>
<name>Takuto Kira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takuto is Meroko`s partner and trainee, and they are assigned to take Mitsuki`s soul. His shinigami costume is a cat outfit plus a backpack with wings without which, as a trainee shinigami, he cannot fly. Takuto is capable of transforming into an anthropomorphic cat plushie. Moved by Mitsuki`s plight, he transforms her into the 16-year-old Fullmoon to let her audition as a singer, and develops romantic feelings for her. He becomes depressed at times, especially when Mitsuki talks about Eichi, the boy she loves.</description>
<picture>2359.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4426" picture="26692.jpg">Saitou Yasuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7638" type="main character in" update="2009-06-21">
<rating votes="9">7.55</rating>
<name>Meroko Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meroko is a rabbit shinigami with long ears, capable of transforming into an anthropomorphic bunny stuffed toy. In the anime, she is fond of changing her appearance into other characters using the catchphrase "Mero Mero Change!" Meroko is Takuto`s partner and is infatuated with him, though her love is unrequited. She is jealous of Takuto`s affection for Mitsuki, and fears that being around Mitsuki will cause Takuto to remember his past, and thus become a ghost. Meroko was Izumi`s former partner and was infatuated with him; when Izumi grew tired of her frequent declarations of love, he tricked her into training newcomer Takuto in his place.</description>
<picture>2360.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="1742" picture="20193.jpg">Honda Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="6810" update="2017-11-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>9</length>
<rating votes="2">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かわいい かわいい 大冒険</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaii Kawaii Daibouken</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
