<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13482" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-11-18</startdate>
<enddate>2017-11-18</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mobile Suit Gundam: Twilight Axis - Akaki Zan`ei</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">機動戦士ガンダム Twilight AXIS 赤き残影</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">機動戦士ガンダム トワイライトアクシズ 赤き残影</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mobile Suit Gundam: Twilight Axis Red Blur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kidou Senshi Gundam: Twilight Axis - Akaki Zan`ei</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">MOBILE SUIT GUNDAM Twilight AXIS 赤き残影</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13019" type="Summary">Mobile Suit Gundam: Twilight Axis</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://g-twilight-axis.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="726" type="Animation Work">Sunrise</name>
<name id="1352" type="Original Work">Yatate Hajime</name>
<name id="147" type="Original Work">Tomino Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="18247" type="Character Design">Kim Se-Jun</name>
<name id="37307" type="Story Composition">Ark Performance</name>
<name id="18247" type="Direction">Kim Se-Jun</name>
<name id="43276" type="Music">Oomama Takashi</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: A theatrical short compilation film with added new scenes shown together with http://anidb.net/a13288 [Kidou Senshi Gundam: Thunderbolt - Bandit Flower].</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="27">4.05</permanent>
<temporary count="27">5.48</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>207570.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22477</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36436</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://g-twilight-axis.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>機動戦士ガンダム_Twilight_AXIS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361987</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3216" parentid="2626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>Universal Century</name>
<description>Refers to the Universal Century timeline in Gundam anime. Gundam anime with this tag all belong in the same universe.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3974" type="appears in" update="2012-04-10">
<rating votes="332">9.00</rating>
<name>Char Aznable</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as the "Red Comet" for his high-speed attack tactics, Char is the most famous of Zeon`s ace mobile suit pilots. He earned his nickname by destroying five Federation battleships during the Battle of Loum, and after the attack on Side 7, he becomes the dreaded nemesis of the White Base crew. However, defeating the Federation isn`t the only thing on Char`s mind, and his distinctive mask hides the face of a young man bent on his own personal quest for revenge. As the story continues, Char begins putting his own complicated schemes into motion, even as he becomes distracted by his growing rivalry with the Gundam`s pilot.
Source: Official Site</description>
<picture>85692.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="10951" type="appears in" update="2012-05-06">
<rating votes="37">7.98</rating>
<name>Lalah Sune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This young woman is a test subject of the Flanagan Institute, a Zeon research organization created to investigate the gifted humans known as "newtypes." While the exploits of pilots like Char and Amuro have led to speculation that they may be newtypes, Lalah`s powers are obvious and undeniable, and accompanied by a profound spiritual awareness. However, despite her gentle nature, Lalah is fiercely loyal to the man who saved her life - Char Aznable, the scheming "Red Comet."</description>
<picture>87316.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="88455" type="main character in" update="2017-05-16">
<rating votes="6">7.19</rating>
<name>Arlette Almage</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A talented woman who took part in weapons development for the Principality of Zeon during the One Year War. She escaped to Axis following the battle at A Baoa Qu. After that, she participated in a wide range of technological developments at Axis. Following the end of the Second Neo Zeon War, she lives with Danton on Side 6 where she accepts an invitation from the Federation Forces Special Forces to return to Axis.
Source: zeonic-republic.net</description>
<picture>202328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4659" picture="175153.jpg">Shimizu Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88456" type="main character in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Danton Hyleg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A young test pilot of the Principality of Zeon during the One Year War who was tasked with data acquisition on the battlefield. Following the war, he returns to the Earth Sphere on Axis with Arlette. Although he lived a reclusive life with Arlette following the Axis Shock, but he will once again face his past on Axis.
Source: zeonic-republic.net</description>
<picture>202329.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3156" picture="76983.jpg">Sakaguchi Shuuhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88458" type="appears in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>RX-160G Byarlant Isolde</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>A mobile suit of the mysterious group "Barnum" that attacked the "Mastima" special forces commanded by Mehmet. This suit is piloted by Quentin`s younger brother Walter Fermo. Though the suit is known to be a variant of Byarlant, the details in which how it was obtained or developed remain unknown.
Source: gundam.info</description>
<picture>202333.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89263" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Quentin Fermo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An enhanced human affiliated with the mysterious armed group "Barnum" that attacks the "Mastima" unit investigating Axis. It is believed that he was once a subject of various experiments at a New Type research institute established nearby the Earth Federations Augusta base. His current background and purpose in appearing on Axis is unknown.
Source: gundam.info</description>
<picture>202331.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23805" picture="66166.jpg">Masuda Toshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89264" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-16">
<name>Mehmet Merka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of "Cabinet Department 6," an intelligence bureau under the direct jurisdiction of the Earth Federations government, and a commanding officer of the Earth Federation special forces "Mastima." He is ranked a first lieutenant. He has been ordered to confirm the existence of research materials related to the Psycho Frame in a research facility located inside Axis and to recover those materials if present. He requests Arlette and Danton to accompany him as guides to Axis and acts as their guard.
Source: gundam.info</description>
<picture>202330.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89269" type="appears in" update="2017-05-11">
<name>RX-78AN-01 Gundam AN-01 "Tristan"</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>202332.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="191259" update="2018-04-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2017-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214822" update="2019-04-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
