<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13496" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-10-11</startdate>
<enddate>2017-10-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Road to You: Kimi e to Tsuzuku Michi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ROAD TO YOU ~君へと続く道~</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14425" type="Other">Road to You: Hoshi Furu Oka no Yakusoku</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20180126121646/http://tyre.dunlop.co.jp:80/roadtoyou/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1292" type="Work">The Answer Studio</name>
<name id="26069" type="Direction">Kawamata Hiroshi</name>
<name id="52075" type="Music">Suda Keina</name>
</creators>
<description>* Promotional anime for Dunlop`s Winter Maxx 02 studless tires.
The story is set in a certain snowy land and centers on the intermingling feelings of three pairs of men and women: a couple, a parent and child, and coworkers.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="81">4.37</permanent>
<temporary count="81">5.82</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224496.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36492</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20180126121646/http://tyre.dunlop.co.jp/roadtoyou/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ROAD_TO_YOU〜君へと続く道〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>362048</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=gLuZhjvAG8M</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4610" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-22">
<name>commercial</name>
<description>This title is used to sell and/or promote a real-life product or service. Not to be confused with "product placement" or "subliminal advertising" — this features *direct* promotion for such element.
Depending on the setting, some could even be considered as "animated infomercials".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="92111" type="main character in" update="2017-11-02">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Ryouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92112" type="main character in" update="2017-11-02">
<rating votes="1">9.22</rating>
<name>Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209156.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92113" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-22">
<rating votes="1">9.22</rating>
<name>Toshirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6854" picture="216700.jpg">Tani Atsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92114" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-22">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21823" picture="131326.jpg">Tsuda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92115" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-22">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="193" picture="233471.jpg">Asano Masumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92116" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-22">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Jin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="191385" update="2017-10-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2017-10-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Web</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
