<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13524" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2019-12-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Granblue Fantasy The Animation Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">グランブルーファンタジー The Animation Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">GRANBLUE FANTASY The Animation Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Granblue Fantasy: The Animation Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">碧蓝幻想 第二季</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11597" type="Prequel">Granblue Fantasy The Animation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="73747">This anime is an adaptation of a RPG video game which I still haven’t played.  Since I still have no prior knowledge to this material besides S1, the full impact of characters and situations presented in this anime wouldn`t be the same as someone that has played the video game.  Needless to say, this is for fans of this franchise.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="14899">Were the questions from first season answered? Not really? Are there new questions? Yes. Expect a season 3. Recommended for fans of the first season that have nothing else to watch.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://anime.granbluefantasy.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="8477" type="Series Composition">Yoshimura Kiyoko</name>
<name id="44418" type="Music">Narita Tsutomu</name>
<name id="48503" type="Music">Nishiki Yasunori</name>
<name id="19309" type="Direction">Umemoto Yui</name>
<name id="44461" type="Original Work">Cygames</name>
<name id="4212" type="Character Design">Sai Fumihide</name>
<name id="31375" type="Animation Work">MAPPA</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on an action role-playing video game developed by http://anidb.net/cr44461 [Cygames].
As the new captain of the Grandcypher airship, http://anidb.net/ch83929 [Gran] will stop at nothing as they soar through the Sky Realm to find the Island of the Astrals and his father. But Gran, http://anidb.net/ch83930 [Vyrn] (his reptilian friend), http://anidb.net/ch83931 [Lyria], and their new allies face countless obstacles and challenges along their journey. Bound together forever through a magical power, Gran and Lyria vow to protect each other from the evil Erste Empire.
Source: Funimation</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="172">3.94</permanent>
<temporary count="173">6.01</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238869.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22508</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36587</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anime.granbluefantasy.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://granbluefantasyanimeusa.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Granblue_Fantasy_The_Animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>グランブルーファンタジー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5431</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367130</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19969</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>碧藍幻想</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_gbf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2391" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>bishoujo</name>
<description>In Japanese, a bishoujo is any pretty female from toddlerhood to late adolescence. In the West, the word specifically refers to attractive girls generally from late childhood or early adolescence, especially those that appeal to males, and particularly to fictional characters designed in a way traditionally associated to shoujo manga. Fictional bishoujo tend to be cute, pastel-coloured teenagers; they lack the sophistication of older women, instead having detailed eye and hair design, fluttery costumes often including ribbons, and all sorts of generally sparkly fluff.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2837" parentid="2628" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>floating island</name>
<description>A floating island is an island either floating in the sky, or actually floating in the ocean (mobile). The island`s flotation can be powered either by magic or science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3896" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-23">
<name>bloodless wounds</name>
<description>No matter what weapon is used in what way to attack, hurt or kill somebody, there won`t be blood. You may see ripped clothes and smoke coming from the deadly wounds, but that`s it.
So if you have an aversion towards the red liquid but still love some action going on - this is the anime for you!</description>
<picurl>39189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="83928" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="18">8.01</rating>
<name>Katalina Aryze</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83929" type="main character in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="6">4.82</rating>
<name>Gran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83930" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="8">2.35</rating>
<name>Vyrn</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196855.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83931" type="main character in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="17">5.89</rating>
<name>Lyria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83932" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="10">4.99</rating>
<name>Io</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83933" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="5">7.03</rating>
<name>Eugen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83934" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="5">6.66</rating>
<name>Rackam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83935" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-02">
<rating votes="14">7.36</rating>
<name>Rosetta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86847" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-04-19">
<rating votes="9">2.25</rating>
<name>Sierokarte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86848" type="appears in" update="2017-04-19">
<rating votes="6">6.79</rating>
<name>Sturm</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86849" type="appears in" update="2017-04-19">
<rating votes="2">5.29</rating>
<name>Drang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88926" type="appears in" update="2017-04-19">
<name>Ponmern</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36576" picture="134934.jpg">Yokojima Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88927" type="appears in" update="2017-04-19">
<name>10-sai no Aaron</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49776" picture="201281.jpg">Fushida Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88928" type="appears in" update="2017-04-19">
<name>10-sai no Gran</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201276.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36498" picture="223591.jpg">Kaiden Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88929" type="appears in" update="2017-05-01">
<name>Furias</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89119" type="appears in" update="2017-05-01">
<name>Kuro Kishi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89253" type="appears in" update="2017-05-09">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Orchid</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202255.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90133" type="appears in" update="2017-06-25">
<name>Colossus</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204237.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="98862" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-23">
<rating votes="6">7.40</rating>
<name>Ferry</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1961" picture="222838.jpg">Yonezawa Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105845" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-08">
<name>Noa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105846" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-13">
<rating votes="7">6.41</rating>
<name>Vira Lilie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105961" type="appears in" update="2019-12-27">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Aliza</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239313.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106142" type="appears in" update="2019-10-12">
<name>Garcia</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239612.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107273" type="appears in" update="2019-11-30">
<name>Freesia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107343" type="appears in" update="2019-12-07">
<name>Osanai Rackam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107679" type="appears in" update="2019-12-27">
<name>Lecia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107680" type="appears in" update="2019-12-27">
<name>Adam</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242502.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107681" type="appears in" update="2019-12-27">
<name>Gandharva</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242503.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107682" type="appears in" update="2019-12-27">
<name>Monika Weisswind</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242504.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="221482" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">騎空士の空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Skyfarers in the Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikuushi no Sora</title>
<summary>Leaving behind his homeland, Zinkenstill, Gran continues his journey with the other skyfaring crew members, hoping to reach the Island of the Astrals.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789458</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221483" update="2019-10-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">城砦都市アルビオン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Albion Citadel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jousai Toshi Albion</title>
<summary>Gran and the others are on the run from the Erste Empire, when out of the blue, the Empire proposes peace talks, and the crew heads to the Albion Citadel for the negotiations.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789459</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221484" update="2019-10-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">偽りの自由</title>
<title xml:lang="en">False Freedom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuwari no Jiyuu</title>
<summary>Gran and his crew are acquitted, thanks to the Erste Empire`s pardon. But the morning after the banquet, they wake up to find Katalina gone, having left behind only a letter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789460</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221485" update="2019-10-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かぬ想い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unconveyable Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanu Omoi</title>
<summary>Due to a past incident, Katalina feels indebted to Vira and wants to provide her support after the many years of pressure and loneliness Vira has endured as Lord Commander.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789461</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222755" update="2019-11-02">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カタリナとヴィーラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Katalina and Vira</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katalina to Vira</title>
<summary>Releasing the primal beast Luminiera`s power, Vira attacks Gran and the others. When she sees Vira in berserk mode, Katalina is consumed with guilt. And so she makes up her mind to face up to Vira`s feelings, to make up for the past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789462</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222756" update="2019-11-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">霧に包まれた島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mist-Shrouded Island</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiri ni Kurumareta Shima</title>
<summary>After leaving Albion, the Grandcypher lands on an island shrouded in thick mist, notorious for being inescapable.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789464</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222757" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不死の星晶獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Immortal Primal Beast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushi no Seishoujuu</title>
<summary>Lyria, Io, and Orchis have been swallowed by Celeste. Left behind, Gran and the others search for a way to save them, along with a ghost girl, Ferry, whom they met in the village.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789465</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222758" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家族の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories of Family</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kazoku no Kioku</title>
<summary>Celeste is being manipulated by someone. Someone who has forced the primal to attack the village and devour its undead residents. Gran takes the chance to leap into Celeste to rescue Lyria, Io, and Orchis.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789466</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224566" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">約束の街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Town of Promises</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yakusoku no Machi</title>
<summary>Gran and the others head to Golonzo Island, known as the mecca of shipbuilding, in order to repair the damaged Grandcypher.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789467</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224567" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見果てぬ夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Impossible Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mihatenu Yume</title>
<summary>Under the command of Pommern, the imperial army takes Gran and Lyria away. Meanwhile, Noa is held captive in a research lab as he suffers from the effects of dark essence.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789468</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224568" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誓約</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Contract</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiyaku</title>
<summary>Gran and Lyria escape from the empire`s garrison and are reunited with Rackam and the others. Noa tries to resurrect the Grandcypher that had been damaged by the empire`s strike, but finds himself too weak to provide sufficient power. He suggests they ask Mithra, the primal beast of promises on Golonzo, to help them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789469</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224569" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">道標</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Signpost</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michishirube</title>
<summary>The Black Knight, trapped by her own past, is set on attaining Lyria`s power, but Gran vows adamantly to protect Lyria. Their unwavering beliefs clash, neither willing to bend.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789470</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225652" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225653" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225654" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227335" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もう一つの旅路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Another Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mouhitotsu no Tabiji</title>
<summary>Djeeta and the crew head to an ancient castle after hearing rumors about the Wish Egg, a fairy tale treasure said to grant any wish.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793625</identifier>
<identifier>granblue-fantasy-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227628" update="2020-03-29">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
