<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13540" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2018-06-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Souten no Ken: Regenesis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Souten no Ken Re-Genesis</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">蒼天の拳 REGENESIS</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Fist of the Blue Sky: Regenesis</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">창천의 권: Regenesis</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13843" type="Sequel">Souten no Ken: Regenesis (2018)</anime>
<anime id="4750" type="Prequel">Souten no Ken</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="779518">Very good! And I like how the characters look and I also like the storyline. I am looking forward to the next season.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.souten-regenesis.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="30744" type="Animation Work">Polygon Pictures</name>
<name id="26153" type="Direction">Kazumi Yoshio</name>
<name id="53157" type="Series Composition">Ozaki Satoshi</name>
<name id="4120" type="Original Work">Hara Tetsuo</name>
<name id="6841" type="Music">Nishimura Masatoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>The year is 193X in Shanghai, the city where lives are valued least. The rivalry between the two factions controlling the underworld, the Green Gang and Red Flower Gang, reaches its peak and is nearing its end with a Green Gang victory. The individuals responsible for the revival of the Green Gang, http://anidb.net/ch93008 [Kasumi Kenshirou] and Yu-Ling, are enjoying a brief rest from the conflict. Meanwhile, in Harbin, Liu Fei-yan and http://anidb.net/ch93362 [Erika Arendt] are carefully transporting something. With their course set for Shanghai, they are headed to meet French intelligence officer http://anidb.net/ch94264 [Charles de Guise].
Source: crunchyroll
Note: The first three episodes received an early screening at a special event held at UDX Theater on 25.02.2018. It was delivered on Amazon Prime Video Japan and Crunchyroll and other streaming services one week ahead of its TV broadcast.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="108">2.27</permanent>
<temporary count="111">4.28</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221719.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20470</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36655</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.souten-regenesis.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fist_of_the_Blue_Sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>蒼天の拳</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4905</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>362301</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21060</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>soutenregenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4364" parentid="2674" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Shanghai</name>
<description>Shanghai is one of the four direct-controlled municipalities of China and the most populous city in the world. It is a global financial centre and transport hub, with the world`s busiest container port. Located in the Yangtze River Delta, it sits on the south edge of the estuary of the Yangtze in the middle portion of the East China coast.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="93008" type="main character in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="2">8.36</rating>
<name>Kasumi Kenshirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="380" picture="158572.jpg">Yamadera Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93362" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="2">2.41</rating>
<name>Erika Arendt</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93363" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="2">5.03</rating>
<name>Yasaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2786" picture="211228.jpg">Satou Setsuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93364" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="2">8.18</rating>
<name>Ryuu Hien</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93365" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="2">5.03</rating>
<name>Han Gyokurei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1446" picture="19314.jpg">Touma Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94264" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Charles de Guise</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94265" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="1">3.33</rating>
<name>Han Kourin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6854" picture="216700.jpg">Tani Atsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94266" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>You</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94267" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-04">
<rating votes="2">5.03</rating>
<name>You Shiei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="192" picture="41287.jpg">Watanabe Akeno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94880" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="2">9.63</rating>
<name>Simeon Naggit</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94881" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-12">
<rating votes="2">6.73</rating>
<name>Himuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97340" type="appears in" update="2018-10-14">
<rating votes="2">3.33</rating>
<name>Ryuu Hikaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="197501" update="2018-05-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北斗神拳の源流</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Origin of the Divine Fist of the North Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokuto Shinken no Genryuu</title>
<summary>Fei-Yan becomes a priest at the church on the top of the hill where he lives with Erika. The army hastily moves through the settlement of Shanghai, and the sinister threat of war hangs thick in the air. Kenshiro and Ye Zi-Ying head out to the streets of Shanghai to search for the man who killed Guise. When they eventually arrive in an alleyway, Kenshiro smells the scent of the Silk Road.
Kenshiro learns the government hired a martial artist who practices the West Dipper Lunar Fist. He recalls the white wolf he once saw while traveling the Silk Road and takes his time explaining the bloody destiny of the West Dipper and North Star.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768653</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197502" update="2018-05-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血を纏う死鳥鬼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bloodstained Death Bird Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chi o Matou Shichouki</title>
<summary>When a Japanese military officer is murdered, the situation in Shanghai grows tense, and the threat of a world war looms near. Sensing his death is near, Fei-Yan asks Yu-Ling to look after Erika and tells her the hidden truth behind the List of Hope. He is deeply concerned for Erika.
Fei-Yan starts a brawl with the Green Gang members at the Great New World, and Kenshiro appears before him. What is the tragic fate of the two martial artists who cross fists once again...? Meanwhile, a lone figure watches their heroic battle from the shadows.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768651</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197503" update="2018-05-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">届かぬ願い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unattainable Desires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Todokanu Negai</title>
<summary>The French and German armies as well as those with other purposes seek "The List of Hope" in Erika`s possession. Guise, who sought the List of Hope in order to make his dream a reality, dies when he is attacked by the mysterious martial artist who appears before him.
Meanwhile, Fei-Yan recalls the tragedy that occured at Erika`s mansion. After personally witnessing the powerful feelings the mother and child had for the List of Hope, he swore to protect Erika, who brought tears once again to his eyes.
"You can protect lives with strength, but not hearts."
Spurred to action by Yu-Ling`s words, Fei-Yan chooses to become a demon and resolves to battle Kenshiro to the death as the Death Bird Demon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768649</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197504" update="2018-05-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">北斗神拳伝承者 霞拳志郎</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Successor to the Divine Fist of the North Star: Kasumi Kenshiro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokuto Shinken Denshou: Kasumi Kenshirou</title>
<summary>The year is 193X in Shanghai, the city where lives are valued least. The rivalry between the two factions controlling the underworld, the Green Gang and Red Flower Gang, reaches its peak and is nearing its end with a Green Gang victory. The individuals responsible for the revival of the Green Gang, Kasumi Kenshiro and Yu-Ling, are enjoying a brief rest from the conflict.
Meanwhile, in Harbin, Liu Fei-yan and Erika Arendt are carefully transporting something. With their course set for Shanghai, they are headed to meet French intelligence officer Charles de Guise. However, a sinister figure appears before Guise...
I am the 62nd successor to the Divine Fist of the North Star! With a peal of thunder, Kenshiro announces his title. The destiny of the North Star brings new conflict. And at the end of that conflict, will there be light or darkness--?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768255</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197694" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197695" update="2018-04-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197699" update="2018-10-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">放送直前特番~北斗の文句はオレに言え!~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Housou Chokuzen Tokuban: Hokuto no Monku wa Ore ni Ie!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198092" update="2018-06-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命の死合い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of Destiny</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei no Shiai</title>
<summary>"Now, then... Shall we fight?"
As Kenshiro prepares for battle, Yasaka learns the North Star blood he`s hated for so long flows in his veins and despairs. Enraged by the way he`s been led by the nose by his twisted rage, Yasaka springs into action. While fighting Yasaka, Kenshiro senses his hidden resolve.
Meanwhile, Yu-Ling and Erika flee from German soldiers seeking the List of Hope. Just as they`re cornered, someone leaps from the debris. And a behemoth watches the entire thing from the shadows...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768661</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198093" update="2018-05-15">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二千年の愛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Thousand Year Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nisennen no Ai</title>
<summary>Kenshiro and Yasaka`s battle is interrupted by the Chinese army`s attack. Kenshiro follows Yasaka across the ocean to Ningpo, and they meet again at the North Star family temple. With the force of a two thousand year grudge, Yasaka destroys the Divine Fist of the North Star successors` Tower of Souls, prompting a brightly glowing jewel to appear. Enveloped in the blinding glow of the jewel, Yasaka and Kenshiro learn the sad and violent truth of the North Star and West Dipper.
"Why..."
What was the West Dipper that the stunned Yasaka saw in the light...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768659</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198094" update="2018-05-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立つ燕</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Departing Swallow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidatsu Tsubame</title>
<summary>Just as Yasaka and Fei-Yan`s battle is about to end, a single tank rolls up. From inside the tank, Kenshiro emerges! In order to save his pengyou Fei-Yan, he charged through a Shanghai burning with the flames of war.
"You got a problem with the North Star?"
The battle between West Dipper Lunar Fist user Yasaka driven by the will of the Yuezhi god and Kenshiro begins now!!
Meanwhile, Erika waits at the church where the swallow`s chicks are crying for Fei-Yan to return. As Erika gazes up at the nest, the chicks fly off into the great blue sky one by one.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768657</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198095" update="2018-05-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">餓狼の怨念</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Grudge of the Hungry Wolf</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Garou no Onnen</title>
<summary>War finally breaks out when the Chinese army drops bombs over Shanghai. The Pan family mansion becomes a target of the bombing. In the church that escaped the damage, Kenshiro learns from Erika that Fei-Yan hasn`t been back since last night.
"The god of the Yuezhi will never forgive those who follow the way of the North Star!"
Yasaka, the West Dipper Lunar Fist user who appeared before Fei-Yan, releases the captured Fei-Yan from his bonds so they can battle and settle the West Dipper`s two thousand year old grudge.
At the end of their battle, Fei-Yan witnesses Yasaka use the ultimate technique of the West Dipper Lunar Fist...
"You bastard!" Fei-Yan`s voice echoes through the ashes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768655</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199166" update="2018-07-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">朋友を想う拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fists for Pengyou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Houyuu o Omou Ken</title>
<summary>Kenshiro`s North Star and Simeon Nagid`s Heaven Dipper, the styles of two men that have followed the same ancient history, finally stand face to face.
During their intense battle, Kenshiro detects a certain smell he`s smelled before on Simeon. The circumstances of Guise`s death are finally revealed!
"If you want to complain about my pengyou... complain to me!"
Kenshiro is enveloped by a fierce Fighting Spirit, and Simeon`s arms glow with spirals of blinding light! How will this battle of styles end?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768669</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199167" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天斗聖陰拳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heaven Dipper Sacred Yin Fist</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tentosei Inken</title>
<summary>The German army demands Yasaka`s jewel and Erika herself, a lead to finding the List of Hope, in exchange for Ramon. Kenshiro heads to the ruined temple alone in order to save Ramon. There he finds Simeon`s follower Shamura dressed as a German soldier. While fighting against Kenshiro, Shamura mentions the Heaven Dipper Sacred Yin Fist.
Meanwhile, at Kenshiro`s mansion, a concerned Erika takes Yasaka`s jewel and suddenly disappears.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768667</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199168" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">若き伝承者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Successor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakaki Deshousha</title>
<summary>Ramon and Erika escape the Chinese army`s attack on the church graveyard and flee into the complex network of alleyways of Shangai. In order to keep the promise he made to his older brother Kenshiro, Ramon becomes Erika`s "Little Guardian," protecting her from their attackers one after another. However, the giant and beast-like Shamura comes charging towards them. On the main streets, Zi-Ying and Yu-Ling escape the army`s machine gun fire, but they eventually find themselves cornered... Meanwhile, while trying to flee from Kenshiro, Tian Xue-Yun runs into a mysterious figure whose face is hidden beneath the hood of their cloak...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768665</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199169" update="2018-06-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赦す者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forgiver</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yurusu Mono</title>
<summary>"Glowing fists...?"
Based on the burn marks left on Guise`s body, Kenshiro, Ye, Zi-Ying, and Yasaka arrive at one answer when discussing who killed him. On a hill near the church, Erika is praying over Fei-Yan`s grave. Yasaka approaches to ask for her forgiveness. When she sees the glowing jewels dangling around his neck, she reveals their surprising past. Meanwhile, Kenshiro`s surroundings suddenly grow dark with the color of the Nahash people...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768663</identifier>
<identifier>fist-of-the-blue-sky-regenesis</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
