<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13597" restricted="true">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">25-sai no Joshikousei</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The 25 Year Old High School Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">25歳の女子高生</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">25세의 여고생</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">25岁的女高中生</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12760" approval="9" total="10">Souryo to Majiwaru Shikiyoku no Yoru ni...</anime>
<anime id="13192" approval="9" total="10">Skirt no Naka wa Kedamono Deshita.</anime>
<anime id="13402" approval="7" total="13">Omiai Aite wa Oshiego, Tsuyoki na, Mondaiji.</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://nigojo.cf-anime.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="7211" type="Series Composition">Sawayama Shin`ichirou</name>
<name id="40530" type="Music">Kanayama Noboru</name>
<name id="32365" type="Animation Work">Lyrics</name>
<name id="5516" type="Character Design">Yamamoto Sawako</name>
<name id="35820" type="Direction">Oota Hideta</name>
<name id="5516" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamoto Sawako</name>
<name id="52701" type="Work">Picante Circus</name>
<name id="52703" type="Original Work">Makana</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shoujo romance smut manga by http://anidb.net/cr52703 [Makana].
http://anidb.net/ch92378 [Natori Hana] is an earnest, good-natured 25-year-old woman whose cousin refuses to go to high school. Hana takes her cousin`s place and attends the high school. On her first day, though, Hana`s ruse is discovered by her former high school classmate http://anidb.net/ch92380 [Kanie Akito] - who happens to be the high school`s world history teacher.
Source: ANN
Note: The complete edition with explicit scenes was distributed web via Comic Festa Anime Zone. One hour later the normal version was broadcasted on Tokyo MX.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="134">2.07</permanent>
<temporary count="139">4.47</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>209800.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20391</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36840</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://nigojo.cf-anime.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>25歳の女子高生</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4819</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>362948</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>playlist?list=PLjv-26OPfXENyASqmq7iNIQ2eAcj4Xxi0</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2615" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-25">
<name>18 restricted</name>
<description>This isn`t really an "audience".
While some anime might feature sexual content they still might not be considered pornography. This category is meant only for when the content is clearly *not* intended for minors. The distinction is made by whether the content is sold only to adults.</description>
<picurl>67867.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7134" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-08">
<name>ComicFesta Anime Zone</name>
<description>ComicFesta Anime Zone, established March 2017, is the anime distribution website for ComicFesta. ComicFesta is an electronic comic distribution site operated by WWWave Corporation (株式会社ウェイブ), with many original works (including doujin) posted directly by their publishers.
ComicFesta Anime Zone contains several original work and doujin teen and adult love anime. The full, uncensored versions are distributed on Anime Zone. The R-15 versions are broadcast on terrestrial TV and mainstream internet distribution websites. The late-night TV slot has also been referred to as the "monk frame" (僧侶枠) named after http://anidb.net/a12760 [the work which was first broadcast and delivered in this timeslot].
The anime from ComicFesta can have various levels of censorship depending on the distribution level used. Standard file notes as follows are used to denote the censorship level:
1) "Non-hentai broadcast." --- the airing on terrestrial TV, without any adult scenes.
2) "Hentai broadcast (creative censorship)." --- most likely an online stream, with http://anidb.net/t4112 [creative censorship] applied.
3) "Hentai broadcast." --- typical mosaic censoring applied on the genitals.</description>
<picurl>220426.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="92378" type="main character in" update="2018-01-14">
<rating votes="2">5.68</rating>
<name>Natori Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5878" picture="45926.jpg">Harada Hitomi</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="52746">Waou Kirika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92379" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-14">
<rating votes="2">1.60</rating>
<name>Aida Naoyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46709" picture="208260.jpg">Takatsuka Tomohito</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="38657" picture="223514.jpg">Furukawa Tetsuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92380" type="main character in" update="2018-01-14">
<rating votes="2">2.17</rating>
<name>Kanie Akito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38360" picture="239389.jpg">Sawashiro Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194595" update="2018-01-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">同窓会の夜に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On the Night of the Class Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">동창회의 밤</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dousoukai no Yoru ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194596" update="2018-01-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密の放課後レッスン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret After-School Lesson</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">비밀의 방과후 수업</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu no Houkago Lesson</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194597" update="2018-01-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">保健室のベッドで...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Nurse`s Office Bed</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">양호실 침대에서...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokenshitsu no Bed de...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194598" update="2018-01-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それは突然の再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Unexpected Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">그것은 갑작스런 재회</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Totsuzen no Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195339" update="2018-01-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの日あの時あの場所で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On That Day, at That Time, in That Place</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">그날 그때 그 곳에서</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Hi Ano Toki Ano Basho de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195340" update="2018-01-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人だけの勉強会♥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Private Study Session</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">둘만의 스터디 그룹 ❤</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari dake no Benkyoukai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195341" update="2018-01-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秘密がバレちゃう!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Going to Be Found Out!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">비밀이 들켜 버려!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Himitsu ga Barechau!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195342" update="2018-01-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とんでもない忘れ物!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Could I Have Lost Those?!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">터무니없는 분실물!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tondemonai Wasuremono!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196343" update="2018-02-19">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大好き!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love You!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">좋아해!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisuki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196344" update="2018-02-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最低最悪の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Worst Day</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">처저최악의 날</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saitei Saiaku no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196345" update="2018-02-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それってヤキモチ?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is That Jealousy?</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">혹시 질투?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorette Yakimochi?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196346" update="2018-02-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その朝, 二人は...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Morning, Just the Two of Them</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">그 아침, 두사람은...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Asa, Futari wa...</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
