<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13636" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-04-20</startdate>
<enddate>2018-04-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aggressive Retsuko (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アグレッシブ烈子 (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Aggretsuko</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14199" type="Sequel">Aggressive Retsuko (2019)</anime>
<anime id="12002" type="Alternative Setting">Aggressive Retsuko</anime>
<anime id="14531" type="Other">Aggressive Retsuko: We Wish You a Metal Christmas</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13573" approval="2" total="3">Hataraku Onii-san!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="758779">This one took a while to get into but I`m glad I stuck with it. While at first I was bored by how flat the characters appeared at first glance I was very pleased by the end to see how well developed they were by the end. As an added bonus, there is basically no fluff in this series and while it may seem repetitive at times there is always a point to what is going on.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="271983">First few episodes are a bit flat, but then it really picks up. Recommended for anyone working in the office, even if they don`t have a shitty boss.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<creators>
<name id="31380" type="Direction">Rareko</name>
<name id="23366" type="Animation Work">Fanworks</name>
<name id="1288" type="Original Work">Sanrio</name>
<name id="42509" type="Music">Houno Satoshi</name>
<name id="48386" type="Music">Tabuchi Natsumi</name>
<name id="48387" type="Music">Nakamura Hanae</name>
<name id="56514" type="Music">Sakurai Miki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr1288 [Sanrio]`s character.
http://anidb.net/ch81939 [Retsuko] is a 25-year old red panda who works in her dream company`s accounting department. But it turns out that she is forced to keep doing more and more impossible tasks by her superiors and co-workers. She doesn`t talk back to them, but she still has to let off steam, so she ends up going to karaoke by herself and singing death metal.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="448">7.26</permanent>
<temporary count="450">7.48</temporary>
<review count="1">7.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221210.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20607</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36904</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Aggretsuko</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アグレッシブ烈子</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>362722</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.netflix.com/title/80198505</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3750" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-08">
<name>thick line animation</name>
<description>The characters are drawn with a thicker outline than is usually seen in anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4259" parentid="2857" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>animal world</name>
<description>All characters of the show are walking-talking animals. Their behaviour and clothing can resemble that of humans. They also may try to mirror human society.
There are no humans present in this world.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3968 [animal protagonist].</description>
<picurl>10254.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5084" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>heavy metal music</name>
<description>Heavy metal (or simply metal) is a genre of rock music that developed in the late 1960s and early 1970s, largely in the United Kingdom and the United States. With roots in blues rock and psychedelic rock, the bands that created heavy metal developed a thick, massive sound, characterized by highly amplified distortion, extended guitar solos, emphatic beats, and overall loudness. Heavy metal lyrics and performance styles are often associated with masculinity, aggression, and machismo.
Heavy metal is traditionally characterized by loud distorted guitars, emphatic rhythms, dense bass-and-drum sound, and vigorous vocals. Metal subgenres variously emphasize, alter, or omit one or more of these attributes.
The anime features a theme revolving around metal music or generally features metal music.</description>
<picurl>10251.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="81939" type="main character in" update="2016-05-14">
<rating votes="15">7.90</rating>
<name>Retsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Retsuko-chan is a 25-year-old OL, much put upon by her colleagues, who vents her frustrations by singing death metal karaoke.</description>
<picture>186373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31380" picture="84418.jpg">Rareko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81940" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="4">7.89</rating>
<name>Washimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>186371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54699" picture="216514.jpg">Koiwasaki Komegumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81941" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="3">7.09</rating>
<name>Gori Buchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>186372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54697" picture="216507.jpg">Tsuruta Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81942" type="appears in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="2">1.14</rating>
<name>Yagyuu Kachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>186369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56949" picture="228001.jpg">Katou Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81943" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="3">2.47</rating>
<name>Komiya Kakarichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>186370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28672" picture="84423.jpg">Arai Souta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81944" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="4">2.50</rating>
<name>Ton Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63763.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="28672" picture="84423.jpg">Arai Souta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81945" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="3">2.99</rating>
<name>Kaba Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63764.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="81946" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="4">8.37</rating>
<name>Haida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63765.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="56949" picture="228001.jpg">Katou Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81947" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-01">
<rating votes="2">1.27</rating>
<name>Tsubone-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>63766.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="54697" picture="216507.jpg">Tsuruta Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82058" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-05-14">
<name>Yoga Instructor no Sensei</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoga instructor to Retsuko and friends. Catchphrase is "Protein".</description>
<picture>186742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28672" picture="84423.jpg">Arai Souta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95121" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="5">8.04</rating>
<name>Fenneko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54698" picture="216508.jpg">Inoue Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95122" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="5">3.76</rating>
<name>Tsunoda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54698" picture="216508.jpg">Inoue Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95123" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-21">
<rating votes="3">4.12</rating>
<name>Puko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54698" picture="216508.jpg">Inoue Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100009" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-28">
<name>Ookami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28672" picture="84423.jpg">Arai Souta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100016" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-29">
<name>Resasuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66971.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="56949" picture="228001.jpg">Katou Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100038" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-12-29">
<name>Yokosawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66976.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100039" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-12-30">
<name>Masashiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66977.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100114" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-12-31">
<name>Bibanuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67002.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="100117" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-31">
<name>CEO</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67004.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="56949" picture="228001.jpg">Katou Shingo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100820" type="appears in" update="2019-02-13">
<name>Manumaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28672" picture="84423.jpg">Arai Souta</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="198257" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウェディングロード</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Walking Down the Aisle</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Evlilik Hayali</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wedding Road</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198258" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">腰かける女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Short-timer</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Gelip Geçici</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koshikakure Onna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198259" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真面目ないい子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Good, Hard-working Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İyi ve Çalışkan Bir Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majime na Ii Ko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198260" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">烈子の日常</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day in the Life of Retsuko</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Retsuko`nun Bir Günü</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Retsuko no Nichijou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198274" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢のおわり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dream Ends</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Hayal Kırıklığı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Owari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198275" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ばら色の世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Rosy World</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Toz Pembe Bir Dünya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Barairo no Sekai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198276" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自腹のプリンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Out of Pocket Prince</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Cep Prensi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jibara no Prince</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198277" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガチバトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Düello</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gachi Battle</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198278" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">反逆の狼煙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stoking Rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Başkaldırı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hangyaku no Noroshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198279" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デスバレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exposed</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Açığa Çıkan Sır</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Desubare</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
