<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13713" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>0</episodecount>
<startdate>2022</startdate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tiger &amp; Bunny 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">TIGER &amp; BUNNY 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8101" type="Prequel">Tiger &amp; Bunny</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.tigerandbunny.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1542" type="Direction">Kase Mitsuko</name>
<name id="42824" type="Original Work">BN Pictures</name>
<name id="42824" type="Work">BN Pictures</name>
<name id="866" type="Hero Design">Katsura Masakazu</name>
<name id="24539" type="Series Composition">Nishida Masafumi</name>
<name id="866" type="Character Design">Katsura Masakazu</name>
</creators>
<picture>245578.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tigerandbunny.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tiger_&amp;_Bunny</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>TIGER_&amp;_BUNNY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>TIGERandBUNNY</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="26673" type="main character in" update="2012-03-29">
<rating votes="17">6.89</rating>
<name>Wild Tiger</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Wild Tiger as seen when sponsored by Apollon Media, wearing his new ultra resistant high tech suit. This Hero has the NEXT power "Hundred Power", which boosts his physical abilities by 100 times for five minutes (requiring an hour to recharge afterwards). He is best known for his strong punching. He is the partner of the Hero Barnaby and his catchphrase is "It`s time to let out a wild roar!".</description>
<picture>63022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26674" type="main character in" update="2012-04-03">
<rating votes="56">8.42</rating>
<name>Kaburagi T. Kotetsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaburagi T. Kotetsu is one of the protagonist of the series "Tiger &amp; Bunny" and the one behind the guise of the Hero Wild Tiger. As a NEXT he possesses Hundred Power, a power that, once activated, increases his physical abilities by 100 times for five minutes. Kotetsu is driven by a strong sense of justice and he has a firm belief in his self-image as a Hero; thus, he keeps his real identity a secret. He does not care about racking up points to increase his rank at Hero TV, and instead he attempts his best to save civilians and bring criminals to justice. Kotetsu is incredibly reckless, which often leads him to cause propriety damage, a habit that awarded his Hero persona the nickname "The Crusher of Justice". In spite of being depicted as silly and clumsy, Kotetsu can be passionate and serious, especially if to preserve the well-being of those around him.</description>
<picture>63023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26675" type="main character in" update="2012-04-03">
<rating votes="26">6.28</rating>
<name>Barnaby Brooks Jr.</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Barnaby Brooks Jr. is one of the protagonists of the series "Tiger &amp; Bunny". He is also a rookie Hero, and, unlike the others, he does not keep his identity a secret. As a NEXT he possesses Hundred Power, a power that, once activated, increases his physical abilities by 100 times for five minutes. Barnaby faces his job as a Hero as just work and is intent in accumulating points. He is a good looking "cool smart" person who thinks before he acts. Despite coming across as cold-hearted and stoic, Barnaby does care about others; he is simply tormented by his tragic past and pushed forward by a need for revenge. Kotetsu often calls Barnaby "Bunny" due to the resemblance his Hero suit`s helmet adornments have to the ears of a rabbit.</description>
<picture>63021.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="26676" type="main character in" update="2012-03-30">
<rating votes="11">4.41</rating>
<name>Barnaby Brooks Jr.</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Barnaby as seen wearing his regular ultra resistant high tech suit. This Hero has the NEXT power "Hundred Power", which boosts his physical abilities by 100 times for five minutes (requiring an hour to recharge afterwards). He is best known for his strong kicking. He is the partner of the Hero Wild Tiger.</description>
<picture>63020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="138" picture="23200.jpg">Morita Masakazu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
</anime>
