<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13745" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-01-11</startdate>
<enddate>2019-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Grimms Notes the Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">グリムノーツ The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Grimms Notes the Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">그림노츠 The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">格林筆記 The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">格林笔记</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13839" approval="3" total="4">Pastel Memories</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/grimmsnotes/</url>
<creators>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="14016" type="Character Design">Matsumoto Kentarou</name>
<name id="1519" type="Series Composition">Yamaguchi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="1130" type="Original Work">Square Enix</name>
<name id="19293" type="Direction">Sugawara Seiki</name>
<name id="56629" type="Music">Mirai Kodai Gakudan</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a role-playing game developed by http://anidb.net/cr1130 [Square Enix].
In this mysterious world, everyone is granted a Book of Fate. These powerful books chronicle everything that is and will be about a person`s life. But the sinister Chaos Tellers are rewriting people`s destinies to include catastrophic events. The only ones who can stand against them are a select few who possess blank books of fate.
Source: sentai filmworks</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="187">2.46</permanent>
<temporary count="188">5.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>227229.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21266</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37154</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/grimmsnotes/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Grimms_Notes</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>グリムノーツ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5146</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>365145</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21699</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>grimmsnotes_ta</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="97146" type="main character in" update="2018-12-27">
<name>Ex</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97147" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-27">
<rating votes="1">9.67</rating>
<name>Shane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36583" picture="134947.jpg">Kubota Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97148" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-27">
<name>Tao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97149" type="main character in" update="2018-12-27">
<rating votes="1">5.76</rating>
<name>Reina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34984" picture="222849.jpg">Ueda Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99081" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<name>Alice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="36583" picture="134947.jpg">Kubota Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99082" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-27">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Curly</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99083" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<name>Cinderella</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="34984" picture="222849.jpg">Ueda Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99084" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-12-27">
<name>Loki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99085" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<name>Robin Hood</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99086" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Shirayuki Hime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99087" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-10">
<name>Akazukin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="211110" update="2019-01-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤ずきんの森</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Red Riding Hood`s Forest</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La forêt du chaperon rouge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akazukin no Mori</title>
<summary>Ex, Reina, Tao, and Shane are travelers who journey between Story Zones, places where a single story is repeated over and over again. In the newest zone they`ve arrived at, they save a girl being attacked by a monster. The villagers tell her the girl`s name is "Little Red Riding Hood", but she disappears into the forest...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781447</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211111" update="2019-01-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドン・キホーテの信念</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don Quixote`s Faith</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Don Quichotte, homme de convictions</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Don Quixote no Shinnen</title>
<summary>The heroes find themselves in Don Quixote`s story zone. But instead of the story proceeding like it should, the people are being attacked by hordes of devils. The sky has turned an eerie red, and the whole zone is about to collapse. The heroes act to try and stop it, but they meet a surprising person...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781448</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211112" update="2019-01-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">追憶のシンデレラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinderella of Recollection</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs de Cendrillon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuioku no Cinderella</title>
<summary>The story moves to the past. Ex is still living in the town where he was born, spending his days with a girl named Cinderella. Ex lost both his parents when he was little, and Cinderella has lost her mother. The two of them grow up supporting each other.
Finally, the day comes when Cinderella`s fate will change forever. That`s when Ex meets a girl named Reina in the forest.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781449</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211113" update="2019-02-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エクスの旅立ち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ex`s Journey Begins</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hiks part à l’aventure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ex no Tabidachi</title>
<summary>Ex now knows that he`s been given a special destiny: a Blank Book. But before he can leave on his fantastic journey, he must first defeat the enemies that threaten his childhood friend Cinderella.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781450</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211826" update="2019-01-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212026" update="2019-01-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212241" update="2019-02-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢とロマンの宝島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Treasure Island, a Place of Dreams and Adventure</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’île de l’aventure et des rêves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume to Roman no Takarajima</title>
<summary>The crew travels to the world of Treasure Island, and fantastic booty awaits!  They test out their new swimsuits while searching for buried treasure and making their way past deadly traps.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781451</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212242" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エクスと白雪姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ex and Snow White</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hiks et Blanche-Neige</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ex to Shirayukihime</title>
<summary>Ex and his friends find themselves in Snow White`s Story Zone. But thanks to a zany misunderstanding, Snow White mistakes Ex for her prince!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781452</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212243" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲルダと雪の女王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gerda and the Snow Queen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gerda et la reine des neiges</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gerda to Yuki no Joou</title>
<summary>In a snowy story zone, Ex saves a girl who`s collapsed. Her name is Gelda and she`s trying to rescue her brother. But something seems off about her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781453</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212244" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鬼ヶ島の兄妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Brother and Sister of Onigashima</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le frère et la sœur de l`île aux démons</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onigashima no Kyoudai</title>
<summary>Ex goes to the story zone of Momotaro. There he learns of the past of Tao and Shayne, and the sad events that brought them together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781454</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212902" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">熱砂のアラジン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aladdin of the Burning Sand</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aladin dans le sable brûlant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nessa no Aladdin</title>
<summary>In the sunny desert, the gang encounters Aladdin. He first introduces himself by hitting on Reina, and then making off with her book of fate!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781455</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212903" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オルレアンの聖女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Maid of Orleans</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Sainte d`Orléans</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Orleans no Seijo</title>
<summary>In medieval France, the gang encounters Joan of Arc. She`s the saint of Orleans, and fighting a battle that the enemy doesn`t want her to win. But if she wins, she`ll face a terrible fate...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781456</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212904" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不思議の国のレイナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reina in Wonderland</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Reina au pays des merveilles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushigi no Kuni no Reina</title>
<summary>In Wonderland, the Tao Family encounters Loki and the force behind the Chaostellers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781457</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="212905" update="2019-05-06">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誰も知らない童話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fairy Tale Nobody Knows</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Conte inconnu de tous</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daremo Shiranai Douwa</title>
<summary>The enemy summons a terrible Jabberwock to defeat the Tao Family. Can they overpower this awesome enemy?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>781458</identifier>
<identifier>grimms-notes-the-animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
