<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1374" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>4</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-11-25</startdate>
<enddate>2006-02-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tales of Phantasia The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Tales of Phantasia</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Сказания Фантазии</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Приказки от Фантазия - Анимацията</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tales of Phantasia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ToP</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">テイルズ オブ ファンタジア THE ANIMATION</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Tales of Phantasia - The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Tales of Phantasia - The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">테일즈 오브 판타지아 The Animation</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4548" type="Same Setting">Tales of Symphonia The Animation</anime>
<anime id="389" type="Other">Tales of Eternia The Animation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="238016">A must for fans and non fans alike.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ova-top.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1038" type="Animation Work">Actas</name>
<name id="6896" type="Character Design">Matsutake Tokuyuki</name>
<name id="8976" type="Original Work">Namco</name>
<name id="6896" type="Chief Animation Direction">Matsutake Tokuyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the 1995 Super Famicom game Tales of Phantasia by http://anidb.net/cr8976 [Namco].
http://anidb.net/ch7758 [Cless Alvein], a young swordsman from the town of Totus, along with his friend http://anidb.net/ch7755 [Mint Adnade], a healer with the talent of Mana, are sent back in time to defeat http://anidb.net/ch7763 [Dhaos], a sorcerer imprisoned by their parents decades ago. Along with the help of the archer http://anidb.net/ch7759 [Chester Barklight], the summoner http://anidb.net/ch7761 [Klarth F. Lester] and the half-elf http://anidb.net/ch7760 [Arche Klaine], they seek to right the wrongs of Dhaos and return peace to the land.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1416">5.12</permanent>
<temporary count="1437">7.08</temporary>
<review count="3">6.77</review>
</ratings>
<picture>154901.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3341</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>391</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1570</identifier>
<identifier>xrzwfx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ova-top.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://funimation.com/talesofphantasia/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Tales_of_Phantasia:_The_Animation</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>テイルズ_オブ_ファンタジア#OVA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>970</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>321291</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7160</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1256</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1244" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-01">
<name>summoning</name>
<description>Ability to call/materialize some kind of creature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2487" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>charismatic</name>
<description>Charisma is a compelling attractiveness or charm that can inspire devotion in others.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2801" parentid="2800" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>RPG</name>
<description>Any anime that is based on a role-playing game aka RPG. A role-playing video game is a video game which includes elements of non-electronic role-playing games. The player assumes control of one or several fictional characters (a party) who have joined forces in order to perform quests and overcome a great number of challenges and enemies, usually monsters inspired by fantasy, and, to a lesser extent, science fiction and classic mythology. During the course of the game the characters, or avatars, which are generally defined by quantized characteristics, evolve and improve in that their various attributes increase, as well as by gaining more powerful artefacts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3175" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-12-22">
<name>hand signs</name>
<description>Characters form attacks through a succession of special hand signs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7755" type="main character in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="5">5.16</rating>
<name>Mint Adnade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This healer was kidnapped by knights from the Order of Black Armor and imprisoned in a dungeon underneath their stronghold. Mint always supports her friends with divine healing powers obtained by offering up prayers to the gods. Although Mint is modest and reserved, she possesses an unbending will and a stout heart.</description>
<picture>2152.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7758" type="main character in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="8">3.94</rating>
<name>Cless Alvein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A swordsman living in the village of Toltus. This son of the local sword fighting school`s master has practiced sword fighting since he was a small child. Although Cress`s kind and gentle nature make him quite popular with the girls, once he confronts and enemy, he fights fearlessly and with valor. Cress is a truly dependable friend.</description>
<picture>26709.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7759" type="main character in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="4">5.33</rating>
<name>Chester Barklight</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chester and Cress grew up together and are best friends. Orphaned at a young age, Chester lives with his little sister. A master of the bow, he is a tireless worker with a somewhat sarcastic attitude.</description>
<picture>2151.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="493" picture="65381.jpg">Itou Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7760" type="main character in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="12">7.42</rating>
<name>Arche Klaine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This half-elven magic user from the town of Hamel flies through the air on a broom. Although Arche can sometimes say harsh things, she actually possess a kind heart. She is a cheerful member of the party who is impossible to hate.</description>
<picture>26710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7761" type="main character in" update="2009-05-31">
<rating votes="6">7.42</rating>
<name>Klarth F. Lester</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Claus studies the art of summoning in the village of Euclid. Deeply envious of the elves` natural ability to use magic, he suffers from an inferiority complex with respect to elves.</description>
<picture>26712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7763" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-29">
<rating votes="3">4.72</rating>
<name>Dhaos</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7764" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-09-20">
<rating votes="3">5.04</rating>
<name>Martel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7765" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-28">
<rating votes="4">4.73</rating>
<name>Fujibayashi Suzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suzu is an 11 year old ninja and is granddaughter of the chief of the Ninja Village, Japoni. Suzu seeks her parents, who have been missing for months now ever since Dhaos began to brainwash and recruit other ninjas of her clan. This eventually leads to their tragic deaths during Cless` fights in the coliseum in Euclid, which Suzu witnesses herself. Upon revisiting Japoni, she and her grandfather Ranzo both will ask the party to let her join and help them in their quest, for as promised, they helped her find her missing parents despite the sad turn of events.</description>
<picture>2153.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2792" picture="26717.jpg">Kawata Taeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57520" type="appears in" update="2013-06-27">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Trinicus D. Morrison</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139172.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57521" type="appears in" update="2013-06-27">
<name>Mars Uldole</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139171.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57522" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-06-27">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Lyzen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139170.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="199" picture="23218.jpg">Shimada Bin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57523" type="appears in" update="2013-06-27">
<name>Kishi-chou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139169.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19591" picture="50874.jpg">Katou Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57525" type="appears in" update="2013-06-27">
<name>Merrill Adnade</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57526" type="appears in" update="2013-06-27">
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57544" type="appears in" update="2013-06-28">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Sylph</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>139203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3143" picture="170720.jpg">Nakajima Yumiko</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="37973" picture="139346.jpg">Hotta Asuka</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="37972">Kida Ikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57545" type="appears in" update="2013-06-28">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Brambard Meleney</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139204.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57546" type="appears in" update="2013-06-28">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Runeglom</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="99" picture="139554.jpg">Hirakawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57565" type="appears in" update="2013-06-29">
<name>Alvanista Ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3094" picture="50367.jpg">Kanao Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57566" type="appears in" update="2013-09-20">
<rating votes="1">4.52</rating>
<name>Origin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4433" picture="194705.jpg">Sekine Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57567" type="appears in" update="2013-06-29">
<name>Dozo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19591" picture="50874.jpg">Katou Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="24686" update="2008-03-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2004-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24687" update="2008-03-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24688" update="2008-03-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2006-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="24689" update="2008-03-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2005-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Volume 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="26487" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82828" update="2007-09-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Fandisc Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82968" recap="true" update="2010-04-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Fandisc Bonus - Avant-titles 1-4 Kaigaiban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120791" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136821" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136822" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (Episode 4)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136823" update="2012-06-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2006-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening (Episode 4)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154282" update="2013-09-19">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Original Picture Gallery</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154283" update="2013-09-19">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Original Picture Gallery - Sketch version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154284" recap="true" update="2013-09-19">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>2007-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アセリア ~悠久の旅~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aselia: The Eternal Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aselia: Yuukyuu no Tabi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
