<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13767" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>21</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2019-02-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Radiant</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ラディアン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Radiant</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">虚空魔境</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14701" type="Sequel">Radiant (2019)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="157231">If the first season was mostly goofy. And started to get serious at the end. The second one has darker motifs. Characters are better written. And with every new answer, you get more questions.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.nhk.or.jp/anime/radiant/</url>
<creators>
<name id="27220" type="Animation Work">Lerche</name>
<name id="26894" type="Direction">Fukuoka Daiki</name>
<name id="1540" type="Series Composition">Uezu Makoto</name>
<name id="46783" type="Character Design">Kawano Nozomi</name>
<name id="1050" type="Work">NHK</name>
<name id="1234" type="Work">NHK Enterprises</name>
<name id="53544" type="Original Work">Tony Valente</name>
<name id="4489" type="Direction">Kishi Seiji</name>
<name id="37306" type="Music">Kouda Masato</name>
<name id="46783" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawano Nozomi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a French comic book series by http://anidb.net/cr53544 [Tony Valente].
Seth is an aspiring sorcerer from the Pompo Hills area. Like all wizards, he is an "infected": one of the few living beings who survived the contact of the Nemesis, these creatures fallen from the sky that contaminate and decimate all those they touch. His apparent immunity made him choose a path which seemed to him to be all the more appropriate: to become a Hunter and to fight the Nemesis. But more than that, Seth wants to engage in a quest that goes beyond the simple hunt for monsters... He wants to find the Radiant, their presumed cradle. Surrounded by a faction of sorcerers, he traveled the world in search of the Radiant, under the terrible eye of the Inquisition...
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="379">3.71</permanent>
<temporary count="382">6.04</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>222983.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20793</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37202</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://anime-radiant.com/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.nhk.or.jp/anime/radiant/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Radiant_(TV_series)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ラディアン</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5079</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363310</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21520</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>nep_radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07K5CGL4V</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2647" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-03">
<name>high fantasy</name>
<description>Generally a serious and epic story set in an invented world. The world may be more or less based on real world environments or history. Typical fantastical elements are usually dominating, such as elves, dwarves, magicians, invented languages, quests; just to name a few.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3020" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-01">
<name>chibi ED</name>
<description>Some or all of the endings feature chibi versions of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3423" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>religious persecution</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3430" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-04">
<name>Western comics</name>
<description>This anime is based on a western comic book.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3671" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-09">
<name>footage reuse</name>
<description>Footage reuse is the employment of a sequence of frames many times, generally as a side effect of a constrained anime production budget. This can happen by using the same footage once at a time, but many times over the course of the show, or by directly looping it. Types of scenes that tend to get reused include: transformations, such as those typical of superheroes or magical girls, characters that change into powered-up versions of themselves, or robots changing shape; attacks, especially when involving a series of steps that must be followed before the attack can be launched; and any kind of action that involves repeating the same movement.
This tag does not apply if the footage changes significantly between iterations. An example of that is the infamous Endless Eight arc of http://anidb.net/a6367 [the 2009 iteration of Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu]; even as the plot repeated itself, each episode of the arc showed it in different ways.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3703" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-01-26">
<name>fist fight</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3797" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-13">
<name>trapped in the body of a child</name>
<description>For some reason, a character in this anime who is a late-teenager or an adult, has their mind trapped in the body of a child. E.g. a former late teenager or an adult is transformed into a child. This can be the result of magic, science, or otherwise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3823" parentid="6348" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-03">
<name>recap in opening</name>
<description>A short recap of the previous episode(s) is included in the opening sequence. This can result in an opening longer than the traditional 1m30s.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5285" parentid="3411" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>street fighting</name>
<picurl>211275.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5293" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>crash landing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5585" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-29">
<name>curse</name>
<description>A "curse" in this manner depicts an adversity placed upon a person or object by a supernatural power often represented by unique designs and symbols found on the inflicted. While not all curses have negative effects, the majority are meant to remain forever hexing to the receiving victim`s soul.
A common portrayal is that which is conjured by an individual that has been caused great suffering and thereby extracts revenge against the accuser in the form of a curse. This abuser will then have their soul spirited away to hell to suffer endlessly for the rest of eternity. In some instances (such as in `Jigoku Shoujo`) the character who extracts revenge also condemns their own soul to Hell upon death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6348" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2015-02-19">
<name>old animetags - OP ED</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="94706" type="main character in" update="2018-09-22">
<rating votes="4">5.41</rating>
<name>Alma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224224.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94708" type="main character in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<name>Doc</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240069.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2071" picture="74324.jpg">Oohata Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94709" type="main character in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="24">8.23</rating>
<name>Melie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240068.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98080" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Ullmina Bagliore</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240076.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98081" type="main character in" update="2018-09-22">
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<name>Grimm</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224227.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98082" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Santori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98083" type="main character in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Seth</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98084" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Torque</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98085" type="main character in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<name>Dragunov</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98086" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Piodon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98087" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Von Teppes</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240075.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="202" picture="25743.jpg">Terashima Takuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98088" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">1.38</rating>
<name>Don Bossman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98089" type="main character in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Master Lord Majesty</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240071.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98090" type="main character in" update="2018-09-22">
<rating votes="2">3.18</rating>
<name>Mister Boobrie</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>224225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44112" picture="225552.jpg">Koichi Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98091" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Miss Melba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240073.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98092" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Yaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240072.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98093" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Liselotte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101009" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Konrad de Marbourg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="331" picture="17167.jpg">Murase Katsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101010" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<name>Taji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101011" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-20">
<rating votes="4">6.83</rating>
<name>Hameline</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="207953" update="2018-10-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法使いの少年 -Seth-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Young Sorcerer: Seth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jeune sorcier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Tsukai no Shounen: Seth</title>
<summary>Seth is a boy who lives in the remote village of Pompo Hills. He spends his days training to be a great sorcerer, but he`s always messing up. After angering the villagers yet again by letting valuable livestock escape from a ranch, his guardian, Alma, gives him a harsh scolding. Then, one day, a Nemesis egg falls from the sky. Only sorcerers can defeat the Nemesis, so Seth makes up his mind to fight the beast in Alma`s absence, but his foe is much stronger than he expected...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777751</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="207954" update="2018-10-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当の勇気 -Bravery-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Courage: Bravery</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le vrai courage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hontou no Yuuki: Bravery</title>
<summary>A group of four sorcerers, the Bravery Quartet, appears in the village and seals the Nemesis`s movements. Seth has never met any other sorcerers besides Alma and is immediately taken with them. Hoping to prove that he can be of use too, Seth asks their leader, Don Bossman (Boss), if he can work with them. Impressed, Boss asks Seth to keep the Nemesis occupied while the quartet evacuates the villagers. And so, Seth faces the powerful Nemesis once again!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777752</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="207955" update="2018-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立ちの日 -Alma-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day of Departure: Alma</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jour du départ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi no Hi: Alma</title>
<summary>No matter how often Alma explains that sorcerers and ordinary humans don`t understand each other, Seth just can`t accept it. So, to stop people from seeing sorcerers as the bad guys, Seth swears to destroy all the Nemesis. To do this, he decides to go to Radiant, a land of legend where the Nemesis` nest is said to be. Exasperated by his recklessness, Alma warns him against it, but the two can`t see eye to eye. That night, Alma recalls the time she and Seth first met...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777753</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="207956" update="2018-11-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大空の出会い -Encounter-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Meeting in the Sky: Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rencontre dans le ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oozora no Deai: Encounter</title>
<summary>Seth heads for Artemis Academy in search of clues as to where he can find Radiant. On the way, he runs into Captain Dragunov of the Inquisition, an organization that cracks down on sorcerers. Even though Seth did nothing wrong, he`s thrown in a cage just for being a sorcerer. When all his attempts to escape fail, he meets a red-haired girl named Melie, who`s also in a cage. Meanwhile Alma, who`s still worried about Seth, is visited by a man called Doc who calls himself a researcher...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>777754</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208741" update="2018-09-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">空前絶後の冒険アニメ「ラディアン」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuuzenzetsugo no Bouken Anime "Radiant"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208985" update="2018-10-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208986" update="2018-10-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209368" update="2018-11-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">英知と希望の楽園 -Artemis-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Paradise of Wisdom and Hope: Artemis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le paradis du savoir et de l`espoir</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eichi to Kibou no Rakuen: Artemis</title>
<summary>Immediately after arriving in Artemis Academy, Seth decides to take part in the ceremony welcoming new residents to the city. However, the founder of the academy, Master Lord Majesty, ends up saddling him with a certain immense penalty. Seth then proceeds to search for Yaga, the powerful sorcerer Alma told him to meet, but he unwittingly lands in more and more trouble!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>778423</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209369" update="2019-01-31">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">友情の雫 -Mélie-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drops of Friendship: Melie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les gouttes de l`amitié</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuujou no Shizuku: Melie</title>
<summary>To be accepted as Yaga`s pupil, Seth must prove his strength as a sorcerer. He asks Melie for help, but attack magic isn`t her strong suit, so she tells him she can`t help... but her worry for Seth causes her personality to take a drastic turn into "Crazy Melie." She teaches Seth the harsh and dangerous lesson that strength can`t be gained unless you`re prepared to die for it, but then things go horribly wrong...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779183</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209370" update="2018-11-29">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地下水道に潜む者 -Monster-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beast of the Underground Water System: Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce qui se cache dans les égouts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chika Suidou ni Hisomu Mono: Monster</title>
<summary>As Doc is enjoying another peaceful afternoon drinking coffee at Miss Melba`s café, he`s suddenly pulled underground through a manhole by a tentacled beast. This monster of the underground water system is know as the Devil Fish Kraken, and it just happens to love coffee, so it was attracted to Doc`s coffee-saturated scent. Seth and Melie head underground to save him, but Seth`s attacks have no effect on the beast`s soft body.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779184</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209371" update="2018-11-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強さの証明 -Progress-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Proof of Strength: Progress</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Démonstration de force</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyosa no Shoumei: Progress</title>
<summary>Seth has rapidly gained more magical power, but he`s gotten so used to it that his handling of magic is has grown sloppy. To teach him a lesson, Yaga forces Seth to wear gloves that prevent magic use and says that if he removes them, he`ll be expelled. Meanwhile, the Bravery Quartet that Seth met in Pompo Hills is now up to no good in Artemis Academy. Seth tries to stop them, but without the use of his magic, it`s a tough battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779185</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210026" update="2018-12-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異端を狩る者たち -Inquisition-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Hunt Heretics: Inquisition</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ceux qui chassent les anomalies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itan o Karusha-tachi: Inquisition</title>
<summary>A new recruit in the Inquisition notices that Captain Dragunov`s attitude seems quite careless, and he can`t understand why his men have such faith in him. He joined the Inquisition hoping to fight dangerous sorcerers, not handle odd jobs. Dragunov then receives an urgent request for aid from Captain Edmund, whose ship was attacked by a Nemesis, and they rush to help. The rookie is instantly impressed by the great number of sorcerers Edmund has captured, but Dragunov then notices something...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779186</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210027" update="2018-12-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出の箒 -Memory-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Broom of Memories: Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le balai des souvenirs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide no Houki: Memory</title>
<summary>It`s been a month since Seth parted ways with Alma. A festival is about to be held in Artemis Academy, and Seth is excited by the joyous atmosphere. The festival appears to be one of Majesty`s whims, but it`s actually held to raise funds for the city`s defense. Its highlight event is the broom race. When Nick, the favorite to win, makes fun of Alma, Seth decides to enter the race using the broom Alma gave him.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779187</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210169" update="2018-12-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">轟音と喧騒の街 -Rumble Town-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The City That Roars Like Thunder: Rumble Town</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La ville au vacarme incessant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouon to Kensou no Machi: Rumble Town</title>
<summary>Doc has received a request to handle a job involving a Nemesis. He rejects it at first, but Seth is determined to go after the Nemesis and accepts the job for him. Thus Seth, Melie, and Doc depart for Rumble Town, the city that roars like thunder. Sorcerers are treated very coldly in this town due to the harsh policies of Captain Konrad of the Inquisition. When Seth encounters the Nemesis, he tries to capture it, but a mysterious sorcerer wrapped in bandages stands in his way...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779188</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210170" update="2019-01-14">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">街に巣食う闇 -Darkness-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shadow Lurking in the City: Darkness</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les ténèbres nichées dans la ville</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Machi ni Sukuu Yami: Darkness</title>
<summary>Seth, Melie, and Doc visit the house in the slums where the one who sent the job request lives. The family requested an investigation because their eldest son, Taj, has been infected, but because they are immigrants, their pleas for help are ignored by the Inquisition. But just as Seth and company get to work, the bell in the clock tower rings out an order to evacuate. Due to its poorly planned construction, Rumble Town`s foundation is unstable, so its residents have to move around on a regular basis to keep it balanced. And as soon as the part of the town they`re in is deserted, a Nemesis appears!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779189</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210822" update="2019-01-14">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">動乱序曲 -Storm-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Overture of Turbulence: Storm</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le prélude à la révolte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Douran Jokyoku: Storm</title>
<summary>Captain Konrad of the Inquisition convinces the people of Rumble Town that all the accidents there have been the fault of immigrants and sorcerers. Fueled by anger and fear, the town`s residents lead an uprising, demanding the elimination of all infected people... all according to Konrad`s plan. When the people begin to riot, they capture Taj and are about to execute him when Seth and Melie sweep in to his rescue. Seth then sets out to stop Konrad, the one inciting all the outrage...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>779190</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210874" update="2019-01-14">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">崩壊の鐘の音 -Catastrophe-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bell Tolls the Sound of Destruction: Catastrophe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La cloche de l’effondrement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Houkai no Kanenone: Catastrophe</title>
<summary>Seth tries to rescue Doc, who`s been taken hostage, and ends up captured himself. Konrad denounces him to the people as a criminal who colluded with the immigrants to do evil, and then kicks off a bombardment of cannon fire on the part of the town where the immigrants had settled. Seth is rescued with Grimm`s help, but at the same time, the Nemesis appears and creates further chaos. They learn that the Nemesis is being controlled by a female sorcerer named Hameline, who despises Rumble Town. Just what is Hameline`s objective?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780882</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210881" update="2019-01-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">その拳は流星のように -Burst-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With Fists Like Shooting Stars: Burst</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce poing est comme une météorite</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Kobushi wa Ryuusei no You ni: Burst</title>
<summary>Fifteen years ago, a young Hameline, having been infected, was imprisoned in Rumble Town along with three other infected children. When Major Oxumare of the Inquisition stands up for the children, a young Konrad kills him and frames the children for his mutiny. Frightened, the people had the entire district where the prison was removed from the island to plunge into the abyss. This is the truth of what happened fifteen years ago. The sole survivor of that incident, Hameline, has been awaiting this moment to take revenge.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780883</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210882" update="2019-01-31">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">嵐穿ち舞い上がれ -Rising-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fly High and Pierce Through the Storm: Rising</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Envole-toi et transperce la tempête</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Arashi Ugachi Maiagare: Rising</title>
<summary>Konrad makes a formidable foe with his giant lance. After a grueling fight, Seth finally defeats Konrad, but the collapse of the town has already begun by Hameline`s hand. When she attacks Seth, he is sent flying and loses consciousness. He awakes to find himself face-to-face with a man whose face closely resembles his own. The man calls himself Piodon and asks Seth what he`s fighting for, what side he`s truly on. Seth then rushes back to the battle to stop Hameline.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780884</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211726" update="2019-01-31">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-01-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">いま風の音を止めて -Serenade-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Stop the Sound of the Wind: Serenade</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Arrête la mélodie du vent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima Kaze no Oto o Tomete: Serenade</title>
<summary>At last, Seth faces Hameline. She asserts that the people of this town aren`t worth saving as she unleashes fierce attacks on him. Seth has always used his magic to protect people, but after reflecting on his own past, he sympathizes with Hameline as he realizes that her circumstances and his are not so different. Sorcerers do indeed face persecution and segregation... but Seth promised Alma that he would never become a monster and use his powers violently. Just as Seth proposes an idea to Hameline, an Inquisition battleship suddenly attacks!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780885</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211893" update="2019-02-09">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">闇のあとの光 -Awakening-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Light That Follows the Darkness: Awakening</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Après les ténèbres vient la lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yami no Ato no Hikari: Awakening</title>
<summary>Hameline is defeated by General Torque, "the Beast." The enraged Seth continues to fight, but Von Teppes of the Inquisition turns the tables on him. Seth finally loses consciousness, but then an immense hidden power he didn`t know he had sends him on a rampage. He defeats Teppes and, still unconscious, goes after Torque. The battle grows even more intense as Colonel Santori jumps in to assist Torque. Then, as Melie and Grimm attempt to flee the town, a ride appears for them from Artemis courtesy of Majesty himself...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780886</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211894" update="2019-02-19">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君が変えた世界 -Relief-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World That You Changed: Relief</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde que tu as changé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi ga Kaeta Sekai: Relief</title>
<summary>When Seth and company return to Artemis Academy, they are enthusiastically welcomed as the heroes who exposed the misdeeds of an Inquisitor. But when Seth thinks about Hameline, and about his own blind rampage during the battle, he can`t find it in him to be pleased by the town`s accolades. Even when Majesty says he`s throwing a party for Seth, he can`t shake his sadness. Then, while Seth is alone and lost in his thoughts, Alma appears and shows him a letter from Taj in Rumble Town...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780887</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211895" update="2019-03-04">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">予兆 -Sign-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Omen: Sign</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Présage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yochou: Sign</title>
<summary>With public trust in the Inquisition waning after their misdeeds were exposed in Rumble Town, there are no towns willing to provide Dragunov and his men with much-needed supplies. A rookie soldier laments how unfair it is that they`re being treated as harshly as Konrad himself, when they actualyl fought against him to protect the people. Dragunov cautions him that just because one thinks they are doing the right thing doesn`t mean they will be rewarded. Meanwhile, after what happened in Rumble Town, distribution of goods into Artemis Academy has all but stopped.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780888</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="211896" update="2019-03-04">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-02-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">未来を求めて -Utopia-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In Search of the Future: Utopia</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la recherche du futur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mirai o Motomete: Utopia</title>
<summary>Just when Seth decides to set out on a new journey after hearing what Yaga wrote in a letter to Alma, a massive number of Nemesis eggs rains down on Artemis Academy. The sorcerers of the city intercept them, but an egg they miss falls on an isolated island where Melie happens to be gathering mushrooms. Seth rushes to save her and fights the Nemesis that hatches from the egg, but its immense strength forces Seth into a corner, and his power once again goes berserk. Frightened by this inner power that he can`t control, Seth makes a decision...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>780889</identifier>
<identifier>radiant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
