<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13789" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-20</startdate>
<enddate>2018-07-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="main">Douluo Dalu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Soul Land</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Combat Continent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="official">斗罗大陆</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14675" type="Sequel">Douluo Dalu Di Er Ji</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="354308">The Novel ist Geat, the Manhua is scrap, and this Animation is a Masterpiece.

The story go`s after the Novel, not the Manhua, and the Fighting Scene are really good in scene placed. 

The Animation it`s like you play a Video Game so not all will like it.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<description>Tang San spent his life in the Tang Outer Sect, dedicated to the creation and mastery of hidden weapons. Once he stole the secret lore of the Inner Sect to reach the pinnacle of his art, his only way out was death. But after throwing himself off the deadly Hell`s Peak he was reborn in a different world, the world of Douluo Dalu, a world where every person has a spirit of their own, and those with powerful spirits can practice their spirit power to rise and become Spirit Masters.
The spirit that awakens within Tang San is Blue Silver Grass, a useless spirit. Can he overcome the difficulties to reach the high ranks of Spirit Masters and bring the glory of the Tang Sect into this new world?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="61">6.62</permanent>
<temporary count="62">7.08</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>212726.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37150</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://v.qq.com/detail/m/m441e3rjq9kwpsc.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4611" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>nearly almighty protagonist</name>
<description>Man 1: "Hey man, did you see me take down that guy over there, there`s no way he could have survived that!"
Man 2: "Yeah I know what you mean, it would take the strength of 1 million men to be able to ..... HE`S GETTING BACK UP!!?!?"
*synonymous jaws dropping*
This anime`s main character is comparable to the gods themselves in terms of resistibility, strength and/or downright bad-assery. Whenever they seem as if the fire inside has burnt out, they rise from the ashes with enough tenacity and ferocity to vanquish any foe that dare stand against them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5463" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-25">
<name>boarding school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6707" parentid="2282" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-11">
<name>wuxia</name>
<description>Wuxia, which literally means "martial hero", is a genre of Chinese fiction concerning the adventures of martial artists in ancient China or pre-modern China. A typical wuxia story features a young male protagonist who experiences a tragedy, such as the loss of his loved ones, and goes on to undertake several trials and tribulations to learn several forms of martial arts from various fighters. At the end of the story, he emerges as a powerful fighter whom few can equal.
The heroes in wuxia fiction typically do not serve a lord, wield military power or belong to the aristocratic class. They often originate from the lower social classes of ancient Chinese society. A code of chivalry usually requires wuxia heroes to right and redress wrongs, fight for righteousness, remove oppressors, and bring retribution for past misdeeds. Chinese xia traditions can be compared to martial codes from other cultures such as the Japanese bushidou tradition.
Source: English Wikipedia
Note: Pre-modern China is generally accepted as the period from the 1890s dying days of the Qing dynasty to the early 1930s before the Sino-Japanese Wars.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7438" parentid="2282" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>cultivation</name>
<description>Cultivation is a Taoist concept that describes extending one`s lifespan through the practice of martial and mystical arts with the goal of cultivating qi/chi, spiritual life force. Cultivation is a common theme in both Wuxia and Xianxia stories</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="93906" type="main character in" update="2018-03-30">
<name>Tang San</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tang San is a former young master of the renowned Tang Sect. Following his death he was reborn while maintaining his past memories as the son of the Title Douluo, Tang Hao of the Clear Sky Clan and Ah Yin.
Originally Tang San had a pair of blue eyes and medium-length hair, and was presented in a messy way. His appearance was considered normal with intimidating yet appealing facial features.
Following his secondary awakening, his whole body underwent a metamorphosis, and thus his skin became fairer, and he attained dark blue eyes, long deep blue hair and a handsome face with an imposing manner.</description>
<picture>213342.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93908" type="main character in" update="2018-02-21">
<name>Xiao Wu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213344.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93911" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-21">
<name>Tang Hao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213346.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93912" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-21">
<name>Yu Xiaogang</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213348.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="94864" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-30">
<name>Dai Mubai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Dai Mubai is the second prince of the royal household in the Star Luo Empire. The heir to the throne is by tradition the strongest in the royal famil, so he and his older brother are rivals. Dai Mubai since the birth of Zhu Zhuqing was promised in marriage to her as per agreement of their families. Dai Mubai left home in order to become stronger and never lose to anyone.</description>
<picture>215627.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95232" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-27">
<name>Zhu Zhuqing</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216779.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95233" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-27">
<name>Ning Rongrong</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216780.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95234" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-27">
<name>Oscar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216781.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95292" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-29">
<name>Ma Hongjun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216951.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95293" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-29">
<name>Flender</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216952.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="195912" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195913" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195914" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195915" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195916" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195917" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195918" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195919" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195920" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195921" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195922" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195923" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195924" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195925" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195926" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195927" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195928" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195929" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195930" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195931" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195932" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195933" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195934" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195935" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195936" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195937" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
