<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13800" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-03-30</startdate>
<enddate>2016-09-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="main">Shuang Yue Zhi Cheng</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Twin Moons</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">双月之城</title>
</titles>
<description>In the second calendar year of the Western calendar, in 2200, the two forces in the Earth Circle, "Xuanyue" and "Shangyue", ended the Cold War for more than 50 years. The "Bimonthly Peace Agreement" will soon be signed. However, in the mysterious colonial city Crescent City, Xuan Yue suddenly had a governor`s alternation event, heralding the hidden secret behind what seemed to be hidden from all this. In the past few months, because of this series of changes, there have been new actions. Hyundai Branch of the Earth Renaissance Society, a paramilitary organization that has long-term cooperation with the Sumitomo Government, has received a special mission to steal confidential information from the "Hive" company. The city of Crescent Moon was caught in the center of the "storm" at night, and the fragile human civilization once again faced a huge crisis.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2">6.35</permanent>
<temporary count="2">3.00</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>212879.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33757</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="195991" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5 Extended Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195992" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-08-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4 Extended Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195993" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3 Extended Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195994" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 Extended Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195995" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2016-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 Extended Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195996" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195997" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-08-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195998" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-08-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195999" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196000" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196001" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196002" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196003" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196004" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196005" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196006" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196007" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196008" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2016-03-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
