<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1382" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>67</episodecount>
<startdate>1999-09-04</startdate>
<enddate>2000-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Zoids</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">ZOIDS: Guardian Forces</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Zoids Classic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">zds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Zoids: CC</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゾイド</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">ZOIDS: Chaotic Century</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">זוידס</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13845" type="Same Setting">Zoids Wild</anime>
<anime id="1774" type="Same Setting">Zoids Shin Seiki/Zero</anime>
<anime id="1775" type="Same Setting">Zoids Fuzors</anime>
<anime id="3070" type="Same Setting">Zoids Genesis</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20050114083810/http://mbs.jp/zoids/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7716" type="Character Design">Sakazaki Tadashi</name>
<name id="10217" type="Original Work">Ueyama Michirou</name>
<name id="682" type="Direction">Kato Takao</name>
<name id="719" type="Animation Work">Xebec</name>
<name id="52434" type="Music">Robert Etoll</name>
<name id="52435" type="Music">Sugiuchi Shinsuke</name>
<name id="3748" type="Series Composition">Sumisawa Katsuyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Zoids are beast-like fighting machines used in both everyday use such as transportation, and special use such as war. Some types of Zoids, know as Organoids, are miniature Zoids that are living organisms. These Organoids have the capability to fuse with a non-living Zoid and make it much more powerful.
Van (Ban) Freiheit discovers a Zoid Organoid in an abandoned laboratory while running from two strangers piloting Zoids. Also in the laboratory, in a suspended animation tube is a strange girl. He breaks the tube open and takes her and the Organoid with him. Spotting a ruined Shield Liger Zoid outside nearby, the Organoid fuses with it and repairs the damages. Making his escape, Van names the Organoid Zeke, and decides to keep him as a friend. The girl, who says her name is Fiona, wants to find something called Zoids Eve, and so Van, Zeke, and Fiona begin their adventure.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="484">5.40</permanent>
<temporary count="494">7.05</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>159009.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1031</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>763</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>813</identifier>
<identifier>lyxgjl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20050114083810/http://mbs.jp/zoids/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zoids:_Chaotic_Century</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゾイド_-ZOIDS-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3948</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>162330</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3146</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="14748" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">極秘指令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Secret Orders</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gokuhi Shirei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14749" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">助けた男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saviour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tasuketa Otoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14750" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14751" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">48</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い稲妻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Lightning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Inazuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14752" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">共和国への道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Road To The Republic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouwa Koku e no Michi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14753" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スナイパー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sniper</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sniper</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14754" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">62</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">重力砲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gravity Cannon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juuryoku Hou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14755" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">55</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">音速の決闘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sonic Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onsoku no Kettou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14756" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">42</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レイヴン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raven</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14757" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">65</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゾイドイヴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zoids Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zoid Eve</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14758" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">66</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">滅びの刻</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endgame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Horobi no Koku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14759" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">67</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">明日への帰還</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Return to Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ashita e no Kikan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14760" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">破滅の魔獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deathsaurer Revived!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hametsu no Majuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14761" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">53</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ファントム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phantom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Phantom</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14762" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鋼鉄の野牛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Steel Bison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutetsu no Yagyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14763" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">52</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">バンの力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Van`s Power</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Van no Chikara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14764" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の美少女フィーネ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mysterious Fiona</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Bishoujo Fiona</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14765" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">相棒の死!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell To A Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aibou no Shi!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14766" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふたりの用心棒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Protectors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Youjinbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14767" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新(ニュー)ライガー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Liger</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">New Liger</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14768" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">蘇る魔獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Resurrection Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yomigaeru Majuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14769" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">41</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪魔の迷宮</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Devil`s Maze</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akuma no Meikyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14770" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">58</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">翼竜迎撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intercept Pterosaur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsubasa Ryuugeigeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14771" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">49</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠い星空</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Distant Starry Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooi Hoshizora</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14772" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大空の勇者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heroes of the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oozora no Yuusha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14773" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">50</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">G包囲網</title>
<title xml:lang="en">G Encircling Net</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">G Houi Mou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14774" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">スリーパー・トラップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sleeper Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sleeper Trap</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14775" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れウルフ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run, Wolf!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashire Wolf</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14776" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宿命の対決</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Predestined Confrontation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shukumei no Taiketsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14777" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">40</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゾイド狩り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zoid Hunting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zoid Kari</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14778" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">45</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">漆黒の翼</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jet-black Wings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shikkoku no Tsubasa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14779" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">54</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Gファイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">G File</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">G File</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14780" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">帝都炎上</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Destruction of the Capital</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teito Enjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14781" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">44</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">機獣大激突</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Duel of the Organoids</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kijuu Dai Gekitotsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14782" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">レッドリバーの戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of Red River</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Red River no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14783" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">首都攻防</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Defense of the City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuto Koubou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14784" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プロイツェンの陰謀</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Prozen`s Conspiracy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Prozen no Inbou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14785" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">47</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔獣新生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Monster Reborn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majuu Shinsei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14786" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-09-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">惑星Ziの少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy from Planet Zi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakusei Zi no Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14787" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">皇帝の指輪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Imperial Ring</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutei no Yubiwa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14788" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">激戦! クロノス砦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle of Cronos</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekisen! Cronos Toride</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14789" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">荷電粒子砲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Charged Particle Gun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaden Ryuushi Hou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14790" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">見えざる敵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Invisible Enemy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miezaru Teki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14791" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">63</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">大決戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Decisive Battle / The Final Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai Kessen!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14792" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔物のすむ谷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Valley of the Monster</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamono no Sumu Tani</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14793" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">遠い呼び声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Voice from Afar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tooi Yobigoe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14794" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ニューヘリックシティ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chaotic Century</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">New Heric City</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14795" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">56</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケルベロス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cerberus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cerberus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14796" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">君(ムンベイ)のワルツ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moonbay`s Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moonbay no Waltz</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14797" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">43</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">皇帝の休日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emperor`s Holiday</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koutei no Kyuujitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14798" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Ziの記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories of Zi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zi no Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14799" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">めざめろジーク!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wake Up! Zeke!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mezamero Zeke!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14800" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ZG発動!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deploy The ZG</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ZG Hatsudou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14801" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">三人の騎士</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Three Guards</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sannin no Kishi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14802" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">61</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">巨竜大海戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Naval Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyoryou Dai Kaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14803" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒のオーガノイド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Organoid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuro no Organoid</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14804" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">57</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nightmare</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14805" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">46</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">海底の悪魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Demon from the Depths</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaitei no Akuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14806" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">59</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">首都崩壊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Capital Falls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuto Houkai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14807" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">イセリナの霧の中で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fog at Iselina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iselina no Kiri no Naka de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14808" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-11-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢の降る山</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mountain of Dreams</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yume no Furu Yama</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14809" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">60</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">超巨大要塞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Great Fortress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Kyodai Yousai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14810" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">64</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">古代の記憶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ancient Memories</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodai no Kioku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14811" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-10-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とべ! ジーク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jump Zeke!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jump! Zeke</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14812" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">青い悪魔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blue Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Akuma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14813" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">51</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">遺跡の少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Remains of a Little Boy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iseki no Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14814" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">共和国の一番長い夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Longest Night of the Republic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyouwa Koku no Ichiban Nagai Yoru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="90374" update="2008-04-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="91020" update="2008-05-23">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
